<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Libya - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIQgKIhtDQkFTRGdvSUwyMHZNRFJuY1hJU0FtVnVLQUFQAQ?hl=en-NG&amp;gl=NG&amp;ceid=NG:en</link><language>en-NG</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 14:34:43 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>VIDEO: 174 Nigerians arrive from Libya - The Punch</title><link>https://punchng.com/video-174-nigerians-arrive-from-libya/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiOmh0dHBzOi8vcHVuY2huZy5jb20vdmlkZW8tMTc0LW5pZ2VyaWFucy1hcnJpdmUtZnJvbS1saWJ5YS_SAYIBaHR0cHM6Ly9wdW5jaG5nLWNvbS5jZG4uYW1wcHJvamVjdC5vcmcvdi9zL3B1bmNobmcuY29tL3ZpZGVvLTE3NC1uaWdlcmlhbnMtYXJyaXZlLWZyb20tbGlieWEvYW1wLz9hbXBfanNfdj0wLjEjd2Vidmlldz0xJmNhcD1zd2lwZQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://punchng.com/video-174-nigerians-arrive-from-libya/" target="_blank"&gt;VIDEO: 174 Nigerians arrive from Libya&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Punch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The National Emergency Management Agency has received another batch of 174 stranded Nigerians from Libya. The News Agency of Nigeria reports that the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://punchng.com">The Punch</source></item><item><title>NEMA Receives 193 Nigerians From Libya - Leadership Newspaper</title><link>https://leadership.ng/2018/12/07/nema-receives-193-nigerians-from-libya/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiSGh0dHBzOi8vbGVhZGVyc2hpcC5uZy8yMDE4LzEyLzA3L25lbWEtcmVjZWl2ZXMtMTkzLW5pZ2VyaWFucy1mcm9tLWxpYnlhL9IBkgFodHRwczovL2xlYWRlcnNoaXAtbmcuY2RuLmFtcHByb2plY3Qub3JnL3Yvcy9sZWFkZXJzaGlwLm5nLzIwMTgvMTIvMDcvbmVtYS1yZWNlaXZlcy0xOTMtbmlnZXJpYW5zLWZyb20tbGlieWEvYW1wLz9hbXBfanNfdj0wLjEjd2Vidmlldz0xJmNhcD1zd2lwZQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 10:41:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://leadership.ng/2018/12/07/nema-receives-193-nigerians-from-libya/" target="_blank"&gt;NEMA Receives 193 Nigerians From Libya&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Leadership Newspaper&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NEMA Receives 193 Nigerians From Libya The National Emergency Management Agency (NEMA) has received another batch of 193 stranded Nigerians from ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://leadership.ng">Leadership Newspaper</source></item><item><title>AFCON 2019: Rohr advises South Africa on how to beat Libya after 1-1 draw with Nigeria - Daily Post Nigeria</title><link>http://dailypost.ng/2018/11/17/afcon-2019-rohr-advises-south-africa-beat-libya-1-1-draw-nigeria/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiYGh0dHA6Ly9kYWlseXBvc3QubmcvMjAxOC8xMS8xNy9hZmNvbi0yMDE5LXJvaHItYWR2aXNlcy1zb3V0aC1hZnJpY2EtYmVhdC1saWJ5YS0xLTEtZHJhdy1uaWdlcmlhL9IBqAFodHRwczovL2RhaWx5cG9zdC1uZy5jZG4uYW1wcHJvamVjdC5vcmcvdi9kYWlseXBvc3QubmcvMjAxOC8xMS8xNy9hZmNvbi0yMDE5LXJvaHItYWR2aXNlcy1zb3V0aC1hZnJpY2EtYmVhdC1saWJ5YS0xLTEtZHJhdy1uaWdlcmlhL2FtcC8_YW1wX2pzX3Y9MC4xI3dlYnZpZXc9MSZjYXA9c3dpcGU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://dailypost.ng/2018/11/17/afcon-2019-rohr-advises-south-africa-beat-libya-1-1-draw-nigeria/" target="_blank"&gt;AFCON 2019: Rohr advises South Africa on how to beat Libya after 1-1 draw with Nigeria&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Daily Post Nigeria&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Super Eagles head coach, Gernot Rohr has advised South Africa on how to defeat Libya following his side's 1-1 draw with the Bafana Bafana in Saturday's 2019 ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://dailypost.ng">Daily Post Nigeria</source></item><item><title>94 migrants refuse to leave Libyan ship– Coastguard - Vanguard</title><link>https://www.vanguardngr.com/2018/11/94-migrants-refuse-to-leave-libyan-ship-coastguard/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiV2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LnZhbmd1YXJkbmdyLmNvbS8yMDE4LzExLzk0LW1pZ3JhbnRzLXJlZnVzZS10by1sZWF2ZS1saWJ5YW4tc2hpcC1jb2FzdGd1YXJkL9IBpwFodHRwczovL3d3dy12YW5ndWFyZG5nci1jb20uY2RuLmFtcHByb2plY3Qub3JnL3Yvcy93d3cudmFuZ3VhcmRuZ3IuY29tLzIwMTgvMTEvOTQtbWlncmFudHMtcmVmdXNlLXRvLWxlYXZlLWxpYnlhbi1zaGlwLWNvYXN0Z3VhcmQvYW1wLz9hbXBfanNfdj0wLjEjd2Vidmlldz0xJmNhcD1zd2lwZQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.vanguardngr.com/2018/11/94-migrants-refuse-to-leave-libyan-ship-coastguard/" target="_blank"&gt;94 migrants refuse to leave Libyan ship– Coastguard&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Vanguard&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ninety-four migrants, desperate to go to Italy, are refusing to leave a container ship in Libya, a week after they were rescued from drowning at sea, a Libyan ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.vanguardngr.com">Vanguard</source></item><item><title>NEMA receives 121 more Nigerians from Libya - Guardian Nigeria</title><link>https://guardian.ng/news/nema-receives-121-more-nigerians-from-libya/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM6NIikErrCuPlZcRBKAsPMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow5tb5CjCzyuYCMOHttwU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://guardian.ng/news/nema-receives-121-more-nigerians-from-libya/" target="_blank"&gt;NEMA receives 121 more Nigerians from Libya&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Guardian Nigeria&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The National Emergency Management Agency (NEMA) has received another batch of 121 stranded Nigerians from Libya.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://guardian.ng">Guardian Nigeria</source></item><item><title>OPEC and Russia pledge to cut oil production - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/business/2018/12/07/opec-saudi-arabia-russia-oil-production-cut.cnn-business</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENJ2xheotEDcQtOTLWd7Q3MqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 18:46:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/business/2018/12/07/opec-saudi-arabia-russia-oil-production-cut.cnn-business" target="_blank"&gt;OPEC and Russia pledge to cut oil production&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;OPEC and its allies reached a deal to slash oil production despite pressure from President Donald Trump to keep pumping. Iran, Venezuela and Libya have been granted exemptions from the cuts. ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A WarnerMedia Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Libyan election commission says needs budget for February constitution vote - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-libya-security-election/libyan-election-commission-says-needs-budget-for-february-constitution-vote-idUSKBN1O51U6</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJRiahsqii5nyEtXAbJ-uVAqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 20:32:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-libya-security-election/libyan-election-commission-says-needs-budget-for-february-constitution-vote-idUSKBN1O51U6" target="_blank"&gt;Libyan election commission says needs budget for February constitution vote&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Libya's electoral commission has asked the government for $28.7 million, saying the funding is needed to boost its "zero" budget to organize a vote on a new constitution as early as February. Western powers and the United Nations hope Libya will hold a national election by June after a referendum on a constitutional framework to chart a way out of a conflict stemming from the overthrow of Muammar Gaddafi in 2011. A French plan, backed by the United Nations, had initially called for a presidential and parliamentary vote on Dec. 10. But weeks of fighting in the capital Tripoli between competi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Libya to Vote on New Constitution Before February - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/libya-to-vote-on-new-constitution-before-february-/4689905.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGPvFI1bUi4dgyqjROuZxroqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw6pwi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 20:57:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/libya-to-vote-on-new-constitution-before-february-/4689905.html" target="_blank"&gt;Libya to Vote on New Constitution Before February&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The chairman of Libya’s elections commission said Thursday that the beleaguered North African nation will hold a referendum on a new constitution before the end of February. The announcement by Emad Al-Sayeh signals a small step toward restoring unity and political stability after years of chaos that followed the 2011 uprising. But authorities have yet to agree on a date or mechanism for presidential or parliamentary elections, and the security situation remains volatile. Moammar Gadhafi ruled Libya with an iron fist from 1969 until he was overthrown and killed in the uprising. The energy-r...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>OPEC deal could push oil to $80 per barrel – analyst tells RT - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/news/445938-opec-oil-price-increase/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBJSE2arQ7cAtqxmAOAsNL4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww_oMo</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 10:21:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/news/445938-opec-oil-price-increase/" target="_blank"&gt;OPEC deal could push oil to $80 per barrel – analyst tells RT&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Organization of Petroleum Exporting Countries (OPEC) has reached a new deal to restrict global output. Oil prices jumped in response, and they will continue to soar, analyst told RT. The deal between OPEC’s 15 member states and allied states led by Russia was reached at a meeting between OPEC and global oil producers in Vienna, Austria on Friday. Under the agreement, global crude oil output will be slashed by 1.2 million barrels per day (bpd) for the first six months of 2019. The deal comes as oil prices have been declining steadily for six months, crashing 30 percent in the last two mo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Libya: Conte meets Haftar in Rome - Agenzia ANSA</title><link>http://www.ansamed.info/ansamed/en/news/sections/politics/2018/12/06/libya-conte-meets-haftar-in-rome_7d74978d-0234-4fce-83c9-e3f02a7ea192.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEChbFC6rX3t_43JjypPMxfUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowsP-hCTCXv5cCMIWA0QU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 15:39:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.ansamed.info/ansamed/en/news/sections/politics/2018/12/06/libya-conte-meets-haftar-in-rome_7d74978d-0234-4fce-83c9-e3f02a7ea192.html" target="_blank"&gt;Libya: Conte meets Haftar in Rome&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Agenzia ANSA&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(ANSAmed) - Rome, December 6 - Italian Premier Giuseppe Conte met Khalifa Haftar, the Libyan general whose forces control much of the east of the North African country, in Rome on Thursday morning. Talks between Conte and Haftar at the premier's office lasted over one hour. According to an official statement, the talks focused mostly on "follow ups to the Palermo conference on Libya, and on the necessity of continuing support for UN's special envoy for Libya Ghassan Salameh, and his effort for the stabilization of the country". (ANSAmed). Read the full article on Ansamed&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.ansamed.info">Agenzia ANSA</source></item><item><title>Benghazi airport closed as heavy rain triggers flooding - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/benghazi-airport-closed-heavy-rain-flooding-181206085052199.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM-EoUHlv3rWR7eV2oSm3DYqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 12:03:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/benghazi-airport-closed-heavy-rain-flooding-181206085052199.html" target="_blank"&gt;Benghazi airport closed as heavy rain triggers flooding&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Torrential rain has brought much of Libya’s second city of Benghazi to a standstill, closing major roads and shutting its airport. Water flooded the passenger terminal and parts of the car park at Benina airport on Wednesday. Osama Alfargany, Benina Aiport’s Vice President, told Reuters news agency that "the water came all the way into the passenger halls, which was approximately one to one and a half metres high." The airport ''took the necessary procedures and halted all flights temporarily as well as taking all safety and security measures including disconnecting the airport's power supp...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Migrant rescue ship that saved thousands 'forced' to end operations - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-07/migrant-search-and-rescue-ship-aquarius-ends-operations/10595438</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN2AsRHr_jxDATx58TpoXy4qFwgEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDD7kIkG</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 06:33:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-07/migrant-search-and-rescue-ship-aquarius-ends-operations/10595438" target="_blank"&gt;Migrant rescue ship that saved thousands 'forced' to end operations&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A search-and-rescue ship that saved tens of thousands of migrants from drowning in the Mediterranean has ended its operations, the charity that runs the ship has said. Key points: - Up to 5,000 migrants died in 2016 while trying to cross the route the Aquarius monitored - The ship had already lost its registration in France and faced calls to be impounded in Italy - Doctors Without Borders denies wrongdoing Doctors Without Borders (MSF) and its partner SOS Mediterranee said they were forced to terminate the Aquarius' operations due to a "smear campaign" by European governments. The ship has...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Refugee ship Aquarius to stop rescue mission in the Mediterranean - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/refugee-ship-aquarius-stop-rescue-mission-mediterranean-181207062845983.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKud7Uw8DzlQO-Rxrilh3tgqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 16:24:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/refugee-ship-aquarius-stop-rescue-mission-mediterranean-181207062845983.html" target="_blank"&gt;Refugee ship Aquarius to stop rescue mission in the Mediterranean&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rescue and relief organisations SOS Mediterranee and Doctors Without Borders (MSF) have announced they are ending the Aquarius refugee rescue mission in the Mediterranean Sea after what they call "a relentless ongoing political, judicial and administrative campaign backed by several European states". Thursday's decision came after the Aquarius, which has been operating since February 2016, was forced to wait in a port in Marseille for two months, following the revocation of its registration. "Repeated and targeted attacks against life-saving aid organisations, coupled with the EU states' cr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Medecins Sans Frontieres forced to pull rescue boat from Mediterranean after being stuck in port for months - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/europe/msf-rescue-boat-aquarius-mediterranean-sea-migrants-refugees-italy-salvini-libya-a8671571.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPfcoCHUJt9GX1cQt3AZIRoqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 23:05:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/europe/msf-rescue-boat-aquarius-mediterranean-sea-migrants-refugees-italy-salvini-libya-a8671571.html" target="_blank"&gt;Medecins Sans Frontieres forced to pull rescue boat from Mediterranean after being stuck in port for months&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;An aid organisation has been forced to end its rescue missions of migrants in the Mediterranean Sea. Medecins Sans Frontieres (MSF) and its partner SOS Mediterranee said the rescue ship Aquarius would no longer be used to save migrants travelling by boat from North Africa to Italy - one of the deadliest migration routes in the world. The vessel had remained in port for the past two months, MSF said, due to a “sustained smear campaign” headed by the Italian government. Last month, regional prosecutors in Italy baselessly claimed the Aquarius could bring infectious diseases such as HIV, menin...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Airport flooded in Libya's Benghazi after heavy rain - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-libya-floods/airport-flooded-in-libyas-benghazi-after-heavy-rain-idUSKBN1O4256</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMSWh4g_7sbUtPU4u3xzZRcqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 17:20:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-libya-floods/airport-flooded-in-libyas-benghazi-after-heavy-rain-idUSKBN1O4256" target="_blank"&gt;Airport flooded in Libya's Benghazi after heavy rain&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Heavy rain brought much of Libya's second city Benghazi to a standstill on Wednesday, closing major roads and shutting its airport, officials said. Water flooded the passenger terminal, rising up to 1.5 meters (5 feet), the airport's deputy manager, Usama Ferjani, said. Parts of the parking lot were also under water. Benghazi's Benina airport had only been renovated and reopened in 2017 following a three-year closure during which military forces were fighting Islamists. Authorities in eastern Libya announced a two-day holiday as most public workers were unable to reach their offices. The ba...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Fifteen migrants die in boat off Libya, Egyptian survivor says - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-europe-migrants-libya-idUSKBN1O310Y</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEbi_AEwQ93XWup0rcSoT8QqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 16:15:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-europe-migrants-libya-idUSKBN1O310Y" target="_blank"&gt;Fifteen migrants die in boat off Libya, Egyptian survivor says&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fifteen migrants have died in a boat off the Libyan coast after spending 12 days at sea without food or water, an Egyptian survivor said on Tuesday. Only 10 migrants from the capsized boat survived, all of whom were suffering from severe dehydration, Othman Belbeisi, head of the U.N. migration agency IOM in Libya, said on Twitter. The owner of a beach chalet found the migrants washing up on the shore near the city of Misrata and called authorities, who brought them to the Red Crescent relief service and hospitals, residents said. "We were 25 migrants on a boat ... We set off from (the weste...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Libyans protest against U.S. air strike in southern Libya - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-libya-security-protests/libyans-protest-against-us-air-strike-in-southern-libya-idUSKBN1O4028</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPOjFg2szVVlA_Ahdbd4C3QqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 00:45:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-libya-security-protests/libyans-protest-against-us-air-strike-in-southern-libya-idUSKBN1O4028" target="_blank"&gt;Libyans protest against U.S. air strike in southern Libya&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dozens of Libyans protested on Tuesday against a U.S. air strike on suspected al Qaeda militants in the country's southwestern desert, saying civilians had been targeted, witnesses said. The U.S. Africa Command (Africom) on Thursday said it had killed 11 al Qaeda militants near the town of al Uwaynat in its third strike since March on the militant group’s North African branch - al Qaeda in the Islamic Maghreb (AQIM). The strike close to the Algerian border, destroyed three vehicles, Africom had said in its statement last week, adding that at the time, they had assessed "no civilians were in...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Opec in Vienna: five things to watch as cartel eyes output cut - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/637db3e4-f6e6-11e8-8b7c-6fa24bd5409c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL4K2g3VKvtf8XQ4EO3uSswqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw4tp6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 10:05:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/637db3e4-f6e6-11e8-8b7c-6fa24bd5409c" target="_blank"&gt;Opec in Vienna: five things to watch as cartel eyes output cut&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oil prices fell on Thursday as the truce in the US-China trade war frayed after the arrest of a high-profile Chinese executive, deepening fears about the world economy. The drop came as expectations remained that Opec and its allies would agree to cut production at their meetings in Vienna that begin today. International benchmark Brent crude fell below the $60 a barrel mark, down 3.2 per cent at $59.61 by the London morning. US benchmark West Texas Intermediate was down 2.9 per cent at $51.33. The latest slide follows a tumble of almost 30 per cent since early October. The looming prospect...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Economic Reforms Offer Scant Relief in Tripoli - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/economic-reforms-offer-scant-relief-in-tripoli/4687266.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFRUi2e-a7LiiH92t0h0xmEqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw6pwi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 00:09:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/economic-reforms-offer-scant-relief-in-tripoli/4687266.html" target="_blank"&gt;Economic Reforms Offer Scant Relief in Tripoli&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;After a month strolling the gold market in Libya's capital, retired public servant Milud Farhat was unable to find any jewelry he could afford for his daughter's wedding. The 60-year-old is typical of Libya's once well-to-do middle class, impoverished by high inflation and devaluation during years of conflict in what used to be one of the Arab world's wealthiest countries. In contrast, armed groups whose commanders cruise Tripoli's potholed streets in luxury cars have become rich by forcing authorities to hire them and grant them cheap dollars they can change on the black market for a premi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Separated at sea: a Sierra Leonean father's desperate fear for his boy - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/dec/04/separated-at-sea-fathers-desperate-fear-for-boy-held-in-libyan-camp</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELsw50nEsxhJTFWd1Ura06kqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 05:00:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/dec/04/separated-at-sea-fathers-desperate-fear-for-boy-held-in-libyan-camp" target="_blank"&gt;Separated at sea: a Sierra Leonean father's desperate fear for his boy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;One night in March, a packed dinghy was afloat in the Mediterranean. Thirty metres ahead was a rescue ship but giving chase was a Libyan coastguard vessel. If it reached the boat it would send its passengers back to Libya and into militia-run detention centres. So they paddled harder, using their hands and feet. Among them were a father and his 10-year-old son, Chica and Alfonsine Camara. The dinghy crashed into the rescue ship and dozens were thrown into the sea, Chica among them. He looked around frantically for Alfonsine, who had been at his side since leaving Sierra Leone. He screamed a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>At least 14 dead on refugee boat off Libya: Official - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/14-dead-refugee-boat-libya-official-181204141649478.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBXIB9Vpa5nv4_qKTrmENswqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 15:40:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/14-dead-refugee-boat-libya-official-181204141649478.html" target="_blank"&gt;At least 14 dead on refugee boat off Libya: Official&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Libyan official said at least 14 refugees died off the North African nation's coast while attempting to cross the Mediterranean to reach Europe. Colonel Hisham Aldwaini, a spokesman for Misrata's security forces, said on Tuesday a wooden boat was found off the Libyan port city with two bodies on board. He added 12 others were thrown into the sea and died. Aldwaini said 10 refugees were rescued from the boat, which was adrift at sea for days without food or water. 160804091028172 An Egyptian survivor told Reuters news agency the refugees died after spending nearly two weeks without provisi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Inside the chaos and corruption of Tripoli, where militias rule the streets - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/dec/01/inside-tripoli-chaos-corruption-militas-rule-streets</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJdJ9LFoGXsCDTJ_5BVccBwqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 15:24:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/dec/01/inside-tripoli-chaos-corruption-militas-rule-streets" target="_blank"&gt;Inside the chaos and corruption of Tripoli, where militias rule the streets&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The drive through the southern outskirts of Tripoli takes frightened travellers past the devastation caused by the latest battle between the militias over the wreckage of Libya’s civil war. There are smashed homes and rubble-strewn streets left by the blasts of tank and rocket fire during fighting in September. Some compare militia-dominated Tripoli with Al Capone’s Chicago but the comparison is false: Al Capone never had access to heavy artillery. Meeting opponents of Libya’s government these days is no easy matter. Doing so means slipping past the official minder assigned to me in a Tripo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>U.S. strike kills 11 suspected Qaeda militants in Libya: Africom - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-libya-security/us-strike-kills-11-suspected-qaeda-militants-in-libya-africom-idUSKCN1NZ238</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE0_SNnW35FRRlvakrOeoCgqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 16:23:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-libya-security/us-strike-kills-11-suspected-qaeda-militants-in-libya-africom-idUSKCN1NZ238" target="_blank"&gt;U.S. strike kills 11 suspected Qaeda militants in Libya: Africom&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The U.S. military said on Friday it killed 11 suspected al Qaeda militants in an air strike in Libya's southwestern desert. U.S. Africa Command (Africom) said Thursday's attack was its third since March on the militant group's North African branch - al Qaeda in the Islamic Maghreb (AQIM). The strike near the town of Al Uwaynat, close to the Algerian border, destroyed three vehicles and "at this time, we assess no civilians were injured or killed," Africom added. Jihadists linked to al Qaeda and Islamic State have found a haven in Libya's vast southern desert as the country struggles to rest...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>After Trump calls, Gulf OPEC members cover most of Iran oil loss: Reuters survey - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-oil-opec-survey/after-trump-calls-gulf-opec-members-cover-most-of-iran-oil-loss-reuters-survey-idUSKCN1NZ21S</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELe56K60K46heereUlj29uAqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 16:41:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-oil-opec-survey/after-trump-calls-gulf-opec-members-cover-most-of-iran-oil-loss-reuters-survey-idUSKCN1NZ21S" target="_blank"&gt;After Trump calls, Gulf OPEC members cover most of Iran oil loss: Reuters survey&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;OPEC oil supply has fallen in November from a two-year high due to U.S. sanctions on Iran, a Reuters survey found, although most of the output gap left by Iran was plugged by Saudi Arabia and the UAE in response to calls from U.S. President Donald Trump. The 15-member Organization of the Petroleum Exporting Countries has pumped 33.11 million barrels per day this month, the survey on Friday found, down 160,000 bpd from October, which was the highest by OPEC as a group since December 2016. The survey adds to indications that OPEC output remains ample despite U.S. sanctions imposed on Iran thi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>The Latest: Spain holds talks over fate of rescued migrants - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/bd00814e25ec4329bf0e4bdfda3ccf9f</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI3L5w2cRW6gkG727UOHZZoqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 16:51:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/bd00814e25ec4329bf0e4bdfda3ccf9f" target="_blank"&gt;The Latest: Spain holds talks over fate of rescued migrants&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BERLIN (AP) — The Latest on Europe's migrant crisis (all times local): 5:45 p.m. The Spanish government says is holding "intense diplomatic talks" to resolve the stranding of a Spanish fishing vessel for nearly one week after it took on board 12 migrants, including two children, north of the Libyan coast. The rescue by the crew aboard the Nuestra Senora de Loreto took place on Nov. 22 in waters under Libyan jurisdiction after a Libyan coast guard boat took another group of migrants from the same vessel. According to Spain, Libya has not responded to requests to take in the migrants and bad ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Chad's Idriss Deby in first-ever visit to Israel - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/chad-idriss-deby-visit-israel-181125135735540.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBvG6qtuNilE03SFJIRc2rgqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2018 15:43:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/chad-idriss-deby-visit-israel-181125135735540.html" target="_blank"&gt;Chad's Idriss Deby in first-ever visit to Israel&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chadian President Idriss Deby is in Israel for talks with Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu, the first such visit by a leader of the northcentral African nation which severed bilateral ties in 1972. Deby landed on Sunday in Tel Aviv, where he was received by Tzachi Hanegbi, minister for regional cooperation. "It was my honor to welcome the President of Chad, Idriss Deby, to Israel. This historic visit is yet another diplomatic breakthrough between Israel and Africa," Hanegbi posted on Twitter. Ofir Gendelman, a spokesperson for Netanyahu, quoted the Israeli prime minister as saying he will ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>The Latest: Slovak minister quits over UN migration pact - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/441ef96af2264ad286798d7597e02d7d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFSRpypuFHSP-qBUoUb2VWcqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 18:24:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/441ef96af2264ad286798d7597e02d7d" target="_blank"&gt;The Latest: Slovak minister quits over UN migration pact&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;LONDON (AP) — The Latest on migration in Europe (all times local): 6:15 p.m. Slovakia's foreign minister has resigned from his post over his disagreement with his country's negative stance on a United Nations pact seeking to promote an international approach to safe and orderly migration. Miroslav Lajcak announced his decision after the country's lawmakers rejected the U.N. pact Thursday in a 90-15 vote, saying it's not in line with the country's policies on migration and security. Prime Minister Peter Pellegrini welcomed Parliament's move. His coalition government is expected next week to ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Migrant flows slow to trickle in Libyan former smuggling hub - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-europe-migrants-libya/migrant-flows-slow-to-trickle-in-libyan-former-smuggling-hub-idUSKCN1NW0IF</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFvr96khhDVML7K6ZGisjyAqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 14:23:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-europe-migrants-libya/migrant-flows-slow-to-trickle-in-libyan-former-smuggling-hub-idUSKCN1NW0IF" target="_blank"&gt;Migrant flows slow to trickle in Libyan former smuggling hub&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Departures of migrant-laden boats to Italy from Sabratha, formerly Libya's biggest people-smuggling hub, have slowed to a trickle thanks to a security crackdown triggered by European pressure that ejected the city’s top smuggler. But the local branch of Libya's coastguard feels neglected. It says it is still starved for resources, unable to run its own patrols with only one broken-down boat, one car and no uniforms. Sabratha, 75 km (47 miles) west of the capital Tripoli where people smugglers exploited gang lawlessness for years, was the main launchpad on Libya's Mediterranean coast for Ita...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Lavrov says Russia supports Italian initiative on Libya - Agenzia ANSA</title><link>http://www.ansamed.info/ansamed/en/news/sections/politics/2018/11/23/lavrov-says-russia-supports-italian-initiative-on-libya_7a69f6be-2b67-43a0-af69-adc965e03d0e.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG3kWizK7xnp25TfpwgkeuwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowsP-hCTCXv5cCMIWA0QU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 17:26:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.ansamed.info/ansamed/en/news/sections/politics/2018/11/23/lavrov-says-russia-supports-italian-initiative-on-libya_7a69f6be-2b67-43a0-af69-adc965e03d0e.html" target="_blank"&gt;Lavrov says Russia supports Italian initiative on Libya&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Agenzia ANSA&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ROME - Russian Foreign Minister Sergey Lavrov on Friday said Russia supports Italy's initiative on Libya. Speaking at a press conference at Villa Madama with Italian Foreign Minister Enzo Moavero Milanesi, Lavrov said Russian Prime Minister Dmitry Medvedev spoke with his Italian counterpart Giuseppe Conte on the matter at the Palermo summit. "All of Libya's problems are linked to the behavior of NATO," Lavrov said. "We need to find solutions to the crisis, but without forgetting the causes that have thrown this region into the abyss and stimulated the intensity of terrorist activity and the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.ansamed.info">Agenzia ANSA</source></item><item><title>British student who took photo from plane faces Egypt spying trial - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/30/british-student-who-took-photo-from-plane-faces-egypt-spying-trial</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI50Nu-QJIwb7uf34W8o4uAqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 15:16:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/30/british-student-who-took-photo-from-plane-faces-egypt-spying-trial" target="_blank"&gt;British student who took photo from plane faces Egypt spying trial&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A 19-year-old British student is facing trial in Egypt for spying, after being accused of taking a photograph of a military helicopter, his family says. Muhammed Fathi Abulkasem was detained on arrival at Alexandria airport, on Egypt’s north coast, after he took a photograph out of the window of the plane that included a military helicopter. Abulkasem, an A-level student from Cheetham Hill in Manchester, is due in court accused of collecting information on the Egyptian army. His family says he has been accused of “collecting information of a military facility” and is being held in an Egypti...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>How security agencies, police and Home Office missed chances to stop Manchester bombing - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/crime/manchester-bombing-ariana-grande-concert-bomber-police-mi5-salman-abedi-a8647286.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKg6F136slxEME3QVklxm6sqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 19:39:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/crime/manchester-bombing-ariana-grande-concert-bomber-police-mi5-salman-abedi-a8647286.html" target="_blank"&gt;How security agencies, police and Home Office missed chances to stop Manchester bombing&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The atrocity in the Manchester Arena was particularly shocking even at a time when jihad had come to Britain and Europe with increasingly savage attacks. It was a suicide bombing targeting young fans at a concert by Ariana Grande, the intent to murder and maim in a packed and confined space with little chance of escape. Now, in a report by the Intelligence and Security Committee (ISC), comes the details of systemic failures by the security agencies, police and the Home Office that helped enable Salman Abedi to carry out his personal act of jihad with a homemade explosive device. The documen...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Libya: child refugees abused in UK-funded detention centres - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/20/child-refugees-facing-abuse-in-libyan-detention-centres</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENPdIbF47m0NUc_RzuNnoagqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 12:37:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/20/child-refugees-facing-abuse-in-libyan-detention-centres" target="_blank"&gt;Libya: child refugees abused in UK-funded detention centres&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Child refugees are facing abuse and malnutrition in a network of 26 Libyan detention centres the British government is helping to fund, the Guardian has learned. In the first accounts to the media from minors being held in the camps, the children described being starved, beaten and abused by Libyan police and camp guards. One said the conditions were like “hell on earth”. According to documents seen by the Guardian, there are 26 active camps which are part-funded by the UK across Libya. While the existence of the camps had previously been reported, the scale of the network was not public. T...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Chad president to make first Israel visit on Sunday, focus on security - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-israel-chad-idUSKCN1NU0D3</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENzuWTmqcnchCB_gLLtnskwqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2018 11:33:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-israel-chad-idUSKCN1NU0D3" target="_blank"&gt;Chad president to make first Israel visit on Sunday, focus on security&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chadian President Idriss Deby will meet Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu in Jerusalem on Sunday, the first such visit by a leader of the central African nation which severed bilateral ties in 1972, Netanyahu's office said. Two N'Djamena government sources confirmed Deby's trip. "The visit is focused on security," one source told Reuters, adding that Israel has supplied the Chadian army with weaponry and other equipment this year to help in its fight against northern rebels. "This is the first visit of a Chad president in Israel since the establishment of the state (of Israel). It f...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Israel: Visit by Chad's leader Is 'Diplomatic Breakthrough' - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/israel-visit-by-chad-s-leader-is-diplomatic-breakthrough-/4672916.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEbvbIbu1Vn_FIz-y22fcgoqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw6pwi</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2018 12:51:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/israel-visit-by-chad-s-leader-is-diplomatic-breakthrough-/4672916.html" target="_blank"&gt;Israel: Visit by Chad's leader Is 'Diplomatic Breakthrough'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Israel's prime minister says the leader of the African nation of Chad is arriving for a historic visit. Benjamin Netanyahu says he will host President Idriss Deby on Sunday in Jerusalem. He says they'll meet privately and then give a joint press statement before dining together. It's the first ever visit of a president of Chad, which broke off relations with Israel in 1972. Netanyahu calls the visit “another diplomatic breakthrough.” Netanyahu has made great efforts to extend Israeli diplomacy to Africa and has visited the continent several times in recent years. It's part of an overall pol...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>The Latest: NGOs urge Europe to take in 12 stranded migrants - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/bed1fb3d1e2749bf914ec88d82030443</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE1RxDZqBAiRf_AWsAgGW7YqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 16:58:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/bed1fb3d1e2749bf914ec88d82030443" target="_blank"&gt;The Latest: NGOs urge Europe to take in 12 stranded migrants&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PARIS (AP) — The Latest on migrants in Europe (all times local): 5:55 p.m. __ Three European non-governmental organizations are criticizing ongoing negotiations by the European Union to return to Libya 12 migrants rescued last week by a Spanish fishing vessel in the Central Mediterranean. The Nuestra Madre de Loreto trawler has been stranded in waters north of Libya since last Thursday, awaiting permission to disembark the 12 migrants. The NGOs — Open Arms, Sea Watch and Mediterranea — said Tuesday in a joint statement that Libya can't be considered a safe port and that migrants could be to...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>9 Dead in Suspected IS Attack in Libya - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/dead-in-suspected-is-attack-in-libya-/4672051.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGZNx_wu_rFTCm6sY6oqcb4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw6pwi</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2018 02:19:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/dead-in-suspected-is-attack-in-libya-/4672051.html" target="_blank"&gt;9 Dead in Suspected IS Attack in Libya&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;At least nine security service members were killed in a suspected Islamic State group attack in the southeastern Libyan town of Tazerbo on Friday, a senior security official said. Eleven other people including civilians and a security chief were also “kidnapped” by members of the extremist group, which attacked a police station in the oasis town, added the official. The Tazerbo desert region is controlled by the forces of strongman Khalifa Haftar, who heads the self-styled National Libyan Army (ANL). The capital Tripoli is the seat of a rival administration — the internationally-backed gove...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Hypocrisy overload? Hillary Clinton tells Europe to stem refugee flow to avoid 'populist politics' - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/news/444677-hillary-clinton-europe-immigration/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFm-1Si4qzbmPzShBFLuU3IqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww_oMo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 20:12:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/news/444677-hillary-clinton-europe-immigration/" target="_blank"&gt;Hypocrisy overload? Hillary Clinton tells Europe to stem refugee flow to avoid 'populist politics'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;It wasn’t too long ago that Hillary Clinton famously celebrated the intervention that turned Libya into a failed state and hotbed for terrorism. Now she’s telling Europe to ‘curb’ immigration from North Africa and Middle East. Speaking to the Guardian as part of a series of interviews with “senior centrist political figures” about the rise of right-wing populism, Clinton mused that Europe “needs to get a handle on migration” because the influx of refugees from the Middle East and Africa in recent years is “what lit the flame” of support for anti-immigration political figures. Harrowing scen...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Migrants fleeing Libya refuse to leave ship and be sent back to camps - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/17/migrants-fleeing-libya-refuse-to-leave-ship-and-be-sent-back-to-country</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJXSKpZ3S2QqtHZ_Ww6jKjoqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 18:03:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/17/migrants-fleeing-libya-refuse-to-leave-ship-and-be-sent-back-to-country" target="_blank"&gt;Migrants fleeing Libya refuse to leave ship and be sent back to camps&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eighty-one migrants have refused to disembark from a merchant ship off the coast of Misrata in Libya, according to reports. The migrants were rescued by the ship’s crew a week ago on 10 November, 115 miles east of Tripoli, after leaving Libya on a raft. Fourteen people decided to leave the cargo ship and were transferred to Libya, while the remaining 81 have refused to disembark in Misrata for fear of being sent back to Libyan detention camps. “I prefer to die on this ship,” one of the migrants told Médecins Sans Frontières (MSF) when offered to be transferred to a Libyan medical facility. ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Exclusive: Libyan wealth fund to hire auditors in push to unfreeze assets - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-libya-swf-exclusive/exclusive-libyan-wealth-fund-to-hire-auditors-in-push-to-unfreeze-assets-idUSKCN1NR1I3</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBKr-kBgHTnIB1I_yR_XJ2sqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 13:14:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-libya-swf-exclusive/exclusive-libyan-wealth-fund-to-hire-auditors-in-push-to-unfreeze-assets-idUSKCN1NR1I3" target="_blank"&gt;Exclusive: Libyan wealth fund to hire auditors in push to unfreeze assets&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Libya's sovereign wealth fund will appoint auditors within weeks and conclude a wide-ranging examination of its assets by 2019 as part of its efforts to get billions of dollars of assets unfrozen, the fund's head told Reuters. Ali Mahmoud Hassan Mohamed, the chairman and chief executive of the Libyan Investment Authority (LIA), said financial auditing and consulting company PriceWaterhouseCoopers (PwC) was one of the firms the fund was considering. About 70 percent of the LIA's $67 billion worth of assets have been frozen under United Nations sanctions since the toppling of veteran ruler Mu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Tunisia-Libya towards agreement on oil in exchange for goods - Agenzia ANSA</title><link>http://www.ansamed.info/ansamed/en/news/sections/energy/2018/11/16/tunisia-libya-towards-agreement-on-oil-in-exchange-for-goods_feefee94-2445-43b3-aa7f-ed8918326c5c.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHnOuHhB5Rq6onIqpSlAM4gqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowsP-hCTCXv5cCMIWA0QU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 10:44:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.ansamed.info/ansamed/en/news/sections/energy/2018/11/16/tunisia-libya-towards-agreement-on-oil-in-exchange-for-goods_feefee94-2445-43b3-aa7f-ed8918326c5c.html" target="_blank"&gt;Tunisia-Libya towards agreement on oil in exchange for goods&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Agenzia ANSA&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(ANSAmed) - TUNIS, NOVEMBER 16 - A Tunisian delegation is currently in Libya to finalize an agreement to exchange Libyan oil for Tunisian consumer goods, Tunisia's Foreign Minister Khemaies Jhinaoui said during an audition at the parliamentary commission on rights, freedom and external relations. He added that ''talks are still ongoing but we have agreed with the Libyan brothers on a return to exchange operations with oil for consumer goods''. Over the past few months, Tunisian Trade Minister Omar Behi had announced an accord on ''Oil for food'' with Libya, sparking a controversy with the L...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.ansamed.info">Agenzia ANSA</source></item><item><title>Egypt and Sudan set up joint patrols against cross-border threats - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-egypt-sudan-defence/egypt-and-sudan-set-up-joint-patrols-against-cross-border-threats-idUSKCN1NU0T2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENyRRdLbJdms1tFhJfy8wbUqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2018 16:28:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-egypt-sudan-defence/egypt-and-sudan-set-up-joint-patrols-against-cross-border-threats-idUSKCN1NU0T2" target="_blank"&gt;Egypt and Sudan set up joint patrols against cross-border threats&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Egypt and Sudan, which face cross-border threats from militias operating in Libya, agreed on Sunday to set up joint military patrols on their border, Sudan's chief of staff said following talks between the countries' defense ministers. Libya, with which Egypt and Sudan have a joint border, has been riven by internal strife since Muammar Gaddafi was toppled in 2011 and a power vacuum has grown that has allowed rival militias and armed Islamist groups to grow. "It was agreed to establish joint military patrols between the two countries' borders, establish mechanisms to control the border and ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Libya could hold elections next spring: Italy's foreign minister - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-libya-election-moavero/libya-could-hold-elections-next-spring-italys-foreign-minister-idUSKCN1NJ0SN</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJoo8lMxvY5GGlDyQWPpLF4qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 07:52:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-libya-election-moavero/libya-could-hold-elections-next-spring-italys-foreign-minister-idUSKCN1NJ0SN" target="_blank"&gt;Libya could hold elections next spring: Italy's foreign minister&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Libya could hold elections next spring, Italian Foreign Affairs Minister Enzo Moavero said on Wednesday, after Italy hosted a two-day conference in Palermo to try to stabilize the troubled North African country. Libya's two main rival leaders met for the first time in more than five months in Sicily on Tuesday and its prime minister endorsed a United Nations plan for an election next year. A previous U.N plan for elections next month was shelved last week. (Reporting by Giselda Vagnoni; Editing by Andrew Heavens)&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Migrants forced off ship after refusing to return to Libya - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/0866c2612f5647a5a356a7887068a1b5</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECPazRh4csh40qdfkvBJSOoqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 09:36:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/0866c2612f5647a5a356a7887068a1b5" target="_blank"&gt;Migrants forced off ship after refusing to return to Libya&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;CAIRO (AP) — Libyan authorities forcibly removed dozens of migrants who had barricaded themselves in a container ship in the port city of Misrata for the past 10 days after being picked up at sea. The migrants had refused to disembark, saying Libya is too dangerous for them. They were attempting to cross the Mediterranean Sea to Europe earlier this month when they were rescued at sea by a cargo ship, Nivin, that was already bound for Misrata. Human Rights Watch said some migrants were taken to hospital late Tuesday while others were taken to a detention center in Misrata. Libya's navy spoke...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Libyan Sufis celebrate Prophet's birthday despite security fears - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-religion-prophet-libya/libyan-sufis-celebrate-prophets-birthday-despite-security-fears-idUSKCN1NP1SX?feedType=RSS&amp;feedName=worldNews&amp;utm_source=feedburner&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=Feed%3A+Reuters%2FworldNews+%28Reuters+World+News%29</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHWYqJUVZSNIQNrzwtsiMmUqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 21:48:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-religion-prophet-libya/libyan-sufis-celebrate-prophets-birthday-despite-security-fears-idUSKCN1NP1SX?feedType=RSS&amp;feedName=worldNews&amp;utm_source=feedburner&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=Feed%3A+Reuters%2FworldNews+%28Reuters+World+News%29" target="_blank"&gt;Libyan Sufis celebrate Prophet's birthday despite security fears&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hundreds of Libyan Sufis packed the narrow streets of Tripoli's walled old city to celebrate the Prophet Mohammad's birthday on Tuesday, chanting hymns to the beat of drums and cymbals. Participants dressed in traditional robes said it was the biggest turnout for the celebration of Mawlid in the Libyan capital for several years, after poor security and pressure from hardliners prevented previous large processions. In Benghazi, Libya's second city, men, women and children also celebrated the holiday in greater numbers than in recent years, holding processions in the morning and evening in fo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Gunmen hit Libyan el Sharara oilfield sub-station, output not affected: NOC - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-libya-energy-attack/gunmen-hit-libyan-el-sharara-oilfield-sub-station-output-not-affected-noc-idUSKCN1NQ1UR</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH2pUj_5GtJtuESvegIzt2sqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 14:53:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-libya-energy-attack/gunmen-hit-libyan-el-sharara-oilfield-sub-station-output-not-affected-noc-idUSKCN1NQ1UR" target="_blank"&gt;Gunmen hit Libyan el Sharara oilfield sub-station, output not affected: NOC&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gunmen on Tuesday attacked a sub-station at Libya's el Sharara oilfield but production was not affected, state oil firm National Oil Corporation (NOC) said on Wednesday. “The armed group stole three company vehicles and the mobile phones of Akakus employees on-site who were later evacuated to safety,” NOC subsidiary Akakus said in a statement sent to Reuters. Sharara, which is Libya’s largest oilfield, has suffered repeated security problems around the perimeter of the field though production has been relatively stable in recent months. In September, the NOC's headquarters were attacked by ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Italy orders seizure of migrant rescue ship over 'HIV-contaminated' clothes - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/20/italy-orders-seizure-aquarius-migrant-rescue-ship-hiv-clothes</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENchhFApv6RkV1zZW7eKBjgqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 12:59:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/20/italy-orders-seizure-aquarius-migrant-rescue-ship-hiv-clothes" target="_blank"&gt;Italy orders seizure of migrant rescue ship over 'HIV-contaminated' clothes&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Italian authorities have ordered the seizure of the migrant rescue ship Aquarius after claiming that discarded clothes worn by the migrants on their voyage from Libya to Italy could have been contaminated by HIV, meningitis and tuberculosis. Prosecutors from Catania, eastern Sicily, alleged that the waste was illegally labelled by the ship’s crew as “special waste” rather than “toxic waste”. Related: Italy's Salvini forced into U-turn over school lunches for immigrant children The Aquarius is currently docked in Marseilles, France, where so far it is beyond the reach of the Italian authorit...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Libya uses tear gas, rubber bullets to force migrants off ship - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/libya-tear-gas-rubber-bullets-force-migrants-ship-181120172005338.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFYkGl2eC0tLncRywg_9s4UqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 18:24:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/libya-tear-gas-rubber-bullets-force-migrants-ship-181120172005338.html" target="_blank"&gt;Libya uses tear gas, rubber bullets to force migrants off ship&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Libyan authorities have used rubber bullets and tear gas to forcibly disembark more than 90 refugees and migrants who had refused to leave a cargo ship docked in the port of Misrata. The Panama-flagged ship rescued them off the Libyan coast 10 days ago, as their boat began sinking, and brought them to Misrata. Once there, 14 disembarked willingly but, in the first documented case of its kind, the other 92 refused to leave. "A joint force raided the cargo ship and used rubber bullets and tear gas to force [them off the ship]," the commander of the central region coastguards, Tawfiq Esskair, ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Barricaded refugees 'ready to die' than return to Libya detention - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/barricaded-refugees-ready-die-return-libya-detention-181118162855287.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIpz9W4ZlgVsuOEPG60YeDgqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:39:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/barricaded-refugees-ready-die-return-libya-detention-181118162855287.html" target="_blank"&gt;Barricaded refugees 'ready to die' than return to Libya detention&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Refugees and migrants refusing to leave a cargo boat in a Libyan port are pleading to be taken to Europe, saying they are prepared to die than be returned to detention in the North African country. As the standoff with Libyan authorities in Misrata entered its ninth day, two of those on board said on Sunday it was too dangerous to go back to Libyan detention centres, where they risk being abused and sold to people smugglers while having little hope of being evacuated. "All people are saying now we don't want to go outside until we die here," Kai, an 18-year-old from South Sudan, told Al Jaz...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Libya: No rivalry with Italy - French ambassador - Agenzia ANSA</title><link>http://www.ansamed.info/ansamed/en/news/sections/politics/2018/11/22/libya-no-rivalry-with-italy-french-ambassador_52098288-61f3-4113-a1da-dbe88a531cf9.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDAvfjhXfmQM1MkrLToE4eQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowsP-hCTCXv5cCMIWA0QU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 11:25:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.ansamed.info/ansamed/en/news/sections/politics/2018/11/22/libya-no-rivalry-with-italy-french-ambassador_52098288-61f3-4113-a1da-dbe88a531cf9.html" target="_blank"&gt;Libya: No rivalry with Italy - French ambassador&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Agenzia ANSA&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(ANSAmed) - ROME, NOVEMBER 22 - The conference in Palermo on Libya ''was the demonstration that there is no rivalry between Italy and France'', the French ambassador to Italy, Christian Masset, told an ANSA Forum. ''France was beside Italy in sharing the objective of stability that is necessary to the Libyan people, and working together''. ''Rivalry did not exist even before Palermo'', added the ambassador, stressing that the Conference was ''very helpful'' because ''the international community and the main Libyan actors have pledged to follow up the plan of UN envoy Ghassam Salamè''. (ANSA...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.ansamed.info">Agenzia ANSA</source></item><item><title>Exclusive: Libya sees currency stabilizing next year, squeezing militia - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-libya-security-economy-exclusive-idUSKCN1NP23L</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEkUtYL9J9_lvk4D7PdbsvMqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 17:08:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-libya-security-economy-exclusive-idUSKCN1NP23L" target="_blank"&gt;Exclusive: Libya sees currency stabilizing next year, squeezing militia&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Libya expects to end a long-running liquidity crisis by early 2019 as a foreign currency tax helps the official and black market exchange rates converge at less than 3 dinars to the dollar, the Tripoli-based deputy prime minister said. The chasm between the two rates has enabled armed groups and their allies to reap vast profits to fund the conflict that has engulfed Libya since 2011, when a NATO-backed uprising overthrew Muammar Gaddafi after more than four decades in power. Meanwhile ordinary Libyans, reliant on imports of everything from milk to cars, have seen living standards crumble. ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Libya death toll rises to 8 in IS attack on police station - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/ee2d8b7a65464cd49720591e6d73ee72</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENbQ4rOv61E6r1B2KH-tgCsqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2018 16:57:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/ee2d8b7a65464cd49720591e6d73ee72" target="_blank"&gt;Libya death toll rises to 8 in IS attack on police station&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BENGHAZI, Libya (AP) — The official death toll has risen in an attack on a police station in the southeastern Libyan oasis town of Tazirbu, which authorities are attributing to Islamic State radicals. In a Saturday statement, the United Nations said at least eight civilians were killed in the attack a day earlier, with nine wounded, three abducted and nine still missing and believed to be kidnapped. The U.N.'s mission to Libya condemned the attack, and called for the immediate release of the kidnapped and their safe return to their families. It said that conflicting parties in Libya should ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Migration at top of agenda of Spanish PM's 1st Morocco visit - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/19421bcdc2ba48b58ccba465cf1b56d8</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKIqdV-EBXEjh9bxympiq1UqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 21:02:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/19421bcdc2ba48b58ccba465cf1b56d8" target="_blank"&gt;Migration at top of agenda of Spanish PM's 1st Morocco visit&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;RABAT, Morocco (AP) — Spanish Prime Minister Pedro Sanchez urged greater cooperation on migration while making his first visit Monday to Morocco, a jumping-off point for a growing number of migrants trying to reach Spain and get a foothold in Europe. Spain is one of the North African kingdom's strongest European allies, and enhanced collaboration on all levels was a focus of Sanchez's visit. It was among the topics discussed at a lunch hosted by Moroccan King Mohammed VI, the official MAP news agency said. Controlling migration from Morocco to Spain was the focus of Sanchez's talks with Mor...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Dozens of Migrants Refuse to Leave Container Ship in Libya - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/dozens-of-migrants-refuse-to-leave-container-ship-in-libya/4658145.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMu-XdkXmE_Epi3LxK9MeSUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 14:48:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/dozens-of-migrants-refuse-to-leave-container-ship-in-libya/4658145.html" target="_blank"&gt;Dozens of Migrants Refuse to Leave Container Ship in Libya&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dozens of migrants have barricaded themselves in a container ship in the Libyan port city of Misrata for the past five days after being picked up at sea, and refuse to disembark, saying Libya is too dangerous for them. Loaded with cars, the ship Nivin was already bound for Misrata when it picked up 93 migrants in a foundering raft in the Mediterranean Sea late on Friday and continued toward its destination. They have been in the Misrata port ever since, with the captain and crew taking refuge on the upper decks. By late Wednesday, at least 77 remained on board after more than a dozen of the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>UN heartened by Libya commitments ahead of 2019 conference - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/18c98953fc0649de84b191d862d52c07</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMEqBt7Nja-ElIyPR8793DMqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 17:30:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/18c98953fc0649de84b191d862d52c07" target="_blank"&gt;UN heartened by Libya commitments ahead of 2019 conference&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PALERMO, Sicily (AP) — The U.N. envoy for Libya said Tuesday he was encouraged by support from Libyan factions and the international community for a national conference planned for early 2019 to chart a path to greater stability and elections in the lawless country. Ghassan Salame praised the "louder sound of unity" among key regional players and "a much higher level of conviviality" between Libyan rivals that he sensed during a two-day meeting in Sicily. "So I do consider this conference as a success and as an important milestone in our common struggle to bring back peace, security and pro...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Rival Libya leaders meet for first time since May, PM OKs 2019 vote - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-libya-security-idUSKCN1NI12Y</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGzIqdLTgHolQecyoQb3BXUqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 17:27:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-libya-security-idUSKCN1NI12Y" target="_blank"&gt;Rival Libya leaders meet for first time since May, PM OKs 2019 vote&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Libya's two main rival leaders met for the first time in more than five months at a conference hosted by Italy on Tuesday and the prime minister endorsed a United Nations plan for an election next year. More than seven years after long-serving dictator Muammar Gaddafi was toppled by Western-backed rebels with NATO air support, no central authority has asserted control over oil-producing Libya and armed groups control the streets. That Tuesday's meeting in Palermo, Sicily took place at all could be seen as a success in a fraught diplomatic environment in which factions on the ground in Libya...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Libyan commander Haftar will attend meetings in Italy, not conference: Haftar’s command - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-libya-security-conference-idUSKCN1NI0PP</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPE4FnBwx310_aafKXhbKfgqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 09:14:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-libya-security-conference-idUSKCN1NI0PP" target="_blank"&gt;Libyan commander Haftar will attend meetings in Italy, not conference: Haftar’s command&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eastern Libyan commander Khalifa Haftar has arrived in Italy for meetings with heads of state, but will not attend a conference on Libya hosted by Rome, his command said on Tuesday. Italy organized the conference in Palermo, hoping it would resurrect U.N. efforts to stage elections in Libya. Haftar arrived in Palermo late on Monday but did not take part in the opening dinner. (Reporting by Ayman al-Warfalli; Editing by Andrew Heavens)&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Libya says Manchester bomber's brother will be extradited this year - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2018/nov/14/libya-manchester-bomber-brother-hashem-abedi-extradited-this-year</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBmjDXwK2vbSszmi9zTSLpYqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDJ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 19:07:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2018/nov/14/libya-manchester-bomber-brother-hashem-abedi-extradited-this-year" target="_blank"&gt;Libya says Manchester bomber's brother will be extradited this year&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The younger brother of the Manchester bomber, Salman Abedi, will be extradited to Britain before the end of the year, according to the Libyan prime minister. Hashem Abedi, 20, was arrested in Libya shortly after his older brother blew himself up at the Manchester Arena on 22 May last year, killing 22 people. In an interview with the BBC in Italy, Fayez al-Sarraj said Libya was working with British authorities. The prime minister said: “I think from here to the end of this year we will finish all the legal procedure in Libya. We are fully cooperating because we understand the suffering of th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Italy's Conference on Libya in Disarray - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/italy-conference-on-libya-in-disarray/4656376.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBuP3C-5kQELFR7TymAP9sQqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw-pwi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 15:00:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/italy-conference-on-libya-in-disarray/4656376.html" target="_blank"&gt;Italy's Conference on Libya in Disarray&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Italy's efforts to host a summit on stabilizing Libya after its seven-year-old conflict appeared to fall flat Tuesday, as organizers on the second and final day of the meeting in Sicily failed to even confirm whether representatives of the main factions were attending. One major player, General Khalifa Haftar, commander of the self-styled Libyan National Army that controls much of eastern Libya, arrived on the island late Monday, but it was unclear whether he would take part in the talks. Earlier media reports quoted him as saying the conference lacks a clear agenda. The conference in the S...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Italy Brings Together Libya Rivals on Conference Sidelines - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/italy-brings-together-libya-rivals-on-conference-sidelines/4656197.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIlEDQFo90ZaA3E4UaAW7EcqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw-pwi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 12:26:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/italy-brings-together-libya-rivals-on-conference-sidelines/4656197.html" target="_blank"&gt;Italy Brings Together Libya Rivals on Conference Sidelines&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Italy's premier hosted a meeting Tuesday of Libya's rival leaders on the sidelines of a conference aiming to help its former colony crack down on Islamic militants and human trafficking. Photos of the encounter show Premier Giuseppe Conte presiding over a handshake between the Tripoli-based U.N.-backed prime minister, Fayez Serraj, and rival Gen. Khalifa Hifter, commander of the self-styled Libyan National Army that is based in Libya's east. FILE - Gen. Khalifa Hifter, military chief of Libya's internationally recognized government, shown in Amman, Jordan, Aug. 24, 2015. Other leaders atten...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Libya conference: Conte brings together Sarraj, Haftar - Agenzia ANSA</title><link>http://www.ansamed.info/ansamed/en/news/sections/politics/2018/11/13/libya-conference-conte-brings-together-sarraj-haftar_d7b09ade-0490-4486-8642-08153d323e1e.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF07AWIRFSLOFyAP2j-4X4UqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowsP-hCTCXv5cCMIWA0QU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 10:08:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.ansamed.info/ansamed/en/news/sections/politics/2018/11/13/libya-conference-conte-brings-together-sarraj-haftar_d7b09ade-0490-4486-8642-08153d323e1e.html" target="_blank"&gt;Libya conference: Conte brings together Sarraj, Haftar&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Agenzia ANSA&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(ANSAmed) - PALERMO, NOVEMBER 13 - Italian Premier Giuseppe Conte on Tuesday morning is meeting with Libyan Prime Minister Fayez al Sarraj and Marshal Khalifa Belqasim Haftar, whose Libyan National Army controls much of the east of the country, at Villa Igiea in Palermo, according to well-informed sources. The meeting, which is taking place on the sidelines of the conference for Libya in Sicily, is also attended by Russian Premier Dmitri Medvedev, Egyptian President Abdel Fatah el-Sisi, Tunisian President Beji Caid Essebsi, EU Council President Donald Tusk, French Foreign Minister Jean-Yves...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.ansamed.info">Agenzia ANSA</source></item><item><title>Libya to extradite brother of Manchester bomber 'by end of year' - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/11/14/libya-extradite-brother-manchester-bomber-end-year/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAaya7jLumNVUwQP6Hye7uIqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 20:24:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/11/14/libya-extradite-brother-manchester-bomber-end-year/" target="_blank"&gt;Libya to extradite brother of Manchester bomber 'by end of year'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Libya is planning to extradite the brother of Manchester Arena bomber by the end of the year, Fayez al-Sarraj, the nation’s UN-backed prime minister, told the BBC on Wednesday. Britain last year submitted a request to extradite Hashem Abedi after the bombing at an Ariana Grande pop concert in May 2017 in which 22 people – many of them young pop fans – were killed. Salman Abedi detonated the bomb, killing himself, outside one of the arena exits shortly after the end of a concert by Ariana Grande. Both brothers travelled to Libya in April, before Salman returned alone to carry out the attack....&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Leaders meet in Italy to find settlement in Libya - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/1ae3c9f33b3b4cce84ed514bdbca0a06</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENmZZ8gX09B5Cgy7HYVKo8QqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwu4lR</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 19:58:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/1ae3c9f33b3b4cce84ed514bdbca0a06" target="_blank"&gt;Leaders meet in Italy to find settlement in Libya&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PALERMO, Sicily (AP) — Representatives of Libya's quarrelling factions and of countries keen on stabilizing the North African nation started meetings in Sicily on Monday, as Italy encourages a political settlement that could bolster the fight against Islamic militants and stop illegal migrants from crossing the Mediterranean to Europe's southern shores. Italy's anti-migrant populist government organized the two-day conference in Palermo with an eye to making progress on a long-elusive goal of ending years of lawlessness in Libya. Rival Libyan administrations jockey for power, militias clash...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Shipbound migrants in Libya port say would rather die than disembark - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-europe-migrants-libya/shipbound-migrants-in-libya-port-say-would-rather-die-than-disembark-idUSKCN1NJ2QY</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKnShgARSJJdxgDw6Vf_bxsqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 19:12:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-europe-migrants-libya/shipbound-migrants-in-libya-port-say-would-rather-die-than-disembark-idUSKCN1NJ2QY" target="_blank"&gt;Shipbound migrants in Libya port say would rather die than disembark&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Migrants refusing to leave a cargo ship docked in Libya said on Wednesday they would rather die than be returned to land, as the coast guard began disembarking some of those on board. In the first documented case of its kind, the migrants have been stranded on the ship since it intercepted them off Libya's western coast on Saturday and brought them to the port of Misrata. A Sudanese on board, Biktor, said his brother and friend had both died at the hands of smugglers in Bani Walid, a smuggling hub south of Tripoli. "How come you want me to leave the ship and stay in Libya?" the 17-year-old ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Manchester bomber's brother will be extradited this year, says Libyan prime minister - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/africa/manchester-bomber-brother-salman-hashem-abedi-extradite-libya-pm-a8634211.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHY-f5uEOaJqxf6F0wEB2MkqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 21:39:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/africa/manchester-bomber-brother-salman-hashem-abedi-extradite-libya-pm-a8634211.html" target="_blank"&gt;Manchester bomber's brother will be extradited this year, says Libyan prime minister&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The brother of Manchester arena bomber Salman Abedi could be extradited to the UK by the end of the year, Libyan prime minister Fayez al-Sarraj has said. Hashem Abedi was arrested in Libya shortly after the 2017 attack that killed 22 people, many of them children, as they left and Ariana Grande concert. Mr Sarraj denied that Libya had delayed Mr Abedi’s extradition and insisted his country was “fully cooperating” with British officials - Read more Police officers and others to be honoured for Manchester bomb response Legal procedures were reaching their conclusion, he said, adding that it w...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Libya: 'Haftar expected' at Palermo conference, sources - Agenzia ANSA</title><link>http://www.ansamed.info/ansamed/en/news/sections/politics/2018/11/12/libya-haftar-expected-at-palermo-conference-sources_de25d4d1-08dc-4e64-afc9-3403f8c636d8.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHzOO1Cw5Yog-OdSlWT2fk4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowsP-hCTCXv5cCMIWA0QU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 16:11:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.ansamed.info/ansamed/en/news/sections/politics/2018/11/12/libya-haftar-expected-at-palermo-conference-sources_de25d4d1-08dc-4e64-afc9-3403f8c636d8.html" target="_blank"&gt;Libya: 'Haftar expected' at Palermo conference, sources&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Agenzia ANSA&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(ANSAmed) - PALERMO, NOVEMBER 12 - Libyan General Khalifa Haftar, the strongman of Cyrenaica, is expected in Palermo where a Conference for Libya is opening on Monday night, Libyan sources in Palermo have told ANSA. ''I expect Haftar to be present'', Italian Premier Giuseppe Conte told Turin daily La Stampa in a front-page article. ''His vision certainly does not coincide with that of president Sarraj'', the prime minister also said, but ''Mandela has observed that 'compromise is the art of leadership and compromises are made with adversaries, not with friends''. Egyptian president, Andel F...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.ansamed.info">Agenzia ANSA</source></item><item><title>Exclusive: U.N. envoy wants Libya election by June after Libyans decide format - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-libya-security-election-exclusive/exclusive-un-envoy-wants-libya-election-by-june-after-libyans-decide-format-idUSKCN1NH1DT</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECUrlg_UvUIr2EAtVx6aiKIqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 12:14:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-libya-security-election-exclusive/exclusive-un-envoy-wants-libya-election-by-june-after-libyans-decide-format-idUSKCN1NH1DT" target="_blank"&gt;Exclusive: U.N. envoy wants Libya election by June after Libyans decide format&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The U.N. envoy for Libya hopes another attempt to hold an election will take place by June after he scrapped a December plan, but said Libyans should first use a national conference in early 2019 to decide on the poll's format. U.N. Special Envoy Ghassan Salame decided to abandon a plan to hold elections on Dec. 10 after a spike in violence in Libya, which has been gripped by conflict and paralyzed by political deadlock since the overthrow of Muammar Gaddafi in 2011. Salame was speaking to Reuters before the start of a conference in Palermo organized by Rome with the aim of pushing forward ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Haftar may not attend Palermo summit on Libya - Agenzia ANSA</title><link>http://www.ansamed.info/ansamed/en/news/sections/politics/2018/11/12/haftar-may-not-attend-palermo-summit-on-libya_80818397-8af3-4787-9859-f1f4b9596908.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHJXGaCqTLYWkfYO5h-O8qoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowsP-hCTCXv5cCMIWA0QU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 09:07:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.ansamed.info/ansamed/en/news/sections/politics/2018/11/12/haftar-may-not-attend-palermo-summit-on-libya_80818397-8af3-4787-9859-f1f4b9596908.html" target="_blank"&gt;Haftar may not attend Palermo summit on Libya&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Agenzia ANSA&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(by Luca Mirone). (ANSAmed) - ROME, NOVEMBER 12 - Khalifa Haftar has decided to boycott the Italian-organized conference on Libya in Palermo. Rumors of a quick visit by Italian prime minister Giuseppe Conte to Benghazi to convince the general to change his mind have been forcefully denied by the prime minister's office. The summit is turning out to be more action-filled than expected, but without the strong man of Cyrenaica, there is the risk of it falling through even before starting. Meanwhile, opposition groups are protesting in Rome, accusing the government of making yet another ''bad i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.ansamed.info">Agenzia ANSA</source></item><item><title>Italy's PM expects Libyan commander Haftar to join Palermo conference - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-libya-security-conference-idUSKCN1NH0PD</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENKEyZk8JOhUskkZEL7YRMkqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 08:33:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-libya-security-conference-idUSKCN1NH0PD" target="_blank"&gt;Italy's PM expects Libyan commander Haftar to join Palermo conference&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Italy's Prime Minister Giuseppe Conte expects Libyan commander Khalifa Haftar to join a two-day conference starting in Palermo on Monday to push forward a new U.N. plan to stabilize Libya, he was cited as saying by a newspaper. Italian officials were scrambling at the weekend to secure Haftar's attendance at the conference organized by Rome. If he shows up, it will be his first meeting with the Tripoli-based Prime Minister Fayez al-Serraj since a Paris summit in May, analysts said. "I expect him (Haftar) to be present since there is no doubt that he is one of the decisive players of the sta...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Italy to host Libyan conference in fresh push for elections - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/12/italy-to-host-libyan-conference-in-fresh-push-for-elections</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOO-pAvUOiCjAFayD9rF6gkqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 05:00:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/12/italy-to-host-libyan-conference-in-fresh-push-for-elections" target="_blank"&gt;Italy to host Libyan conference in fresh push for elections&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many of Libya’s leading factions will meet on Monday in Palermo, southern Italy, in an effort to reunite the country’s institutions and find a new path to elections that a previous French-convened conference failed to achieve. The two-day conference symbolises an Italian determination to regain diplomatic responsibility for Libya after the French president, Emmanuel Macron, convened a surprise summit in Paris in May in a bid to push for Libyan elections on 10 December. Italy, in the midst of forming a government at the time, was aghast at Macron unilaterally trying to stamp his brand on Lib...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Inside Libyan detention 'hell' where refugee burned himself alive - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/libyan-detention-hell-refugee-burned-alive-181110102329706.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJknX9b88SrAX3mEof6JEosqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 09:42:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/libyan-detention-hell-refugee-burned-alive-181110102329706.html" target="_blank"&gt;Inside Libyan detention 'hell' where refugee burned himself alive&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's been nearly three weeks since Abdulaziz, a 28-year-old Somali, doused himself in petrol before burning himself to death in Triq al Sikka migrant detention centre in Libyan capital, Tripoli. Other detainees, who witnessed what happened, said he killed himself shortly after a visit from the United Nations Refugee Agency (UNHCR), claiming officials had told him he had no chance of being evacuated from Libya. Abdulaziz had been in the detention centre for nine months, and felt completely hopeless, they said. "First, he started in secret, then he was shouting, people were running, then, it...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item></channel></rss>