<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Democratic Party - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIggKIhxDQkFTRHdvSkwyMHZNR1F3TnpWdEVnSmxiaWdBUAE?hl=en-NG&amp;gl=NG&amp;ceid=NG:en</link><language>en-NG</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 11:29:54 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Pelosi recalls Arizona's former US Rep. Pastor at funeral - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/1b99bf177fca4ac2a9257b1209c95469</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOrVWzmwLJYppW_a21bWAX0qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvKadAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 00:09:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/1b99bf177fca4ac2a9257b1209c95469" target="_blank"&gt;Pelosi recalls Arizona's former US Rep. Pastor at funeral&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PHOENIX (AP) — Dozens of mourners on Friday bid farewell to Arizona's first Hispanic member of Congress, the former U.S. Rep. Ed Pastor, who was remembered as a devoted public servant and doting family man in a ceremony that filled a large Phoenix church with laughter and sometimes tears. House Democratic leader Nancy Pelosi remembered Pastor on Friday as a lawmaker whose humor united people from both sides of the political aisle. "Everything he did, he was always making it more wonderful," said Pelosi, a Democrat from California. The service at St. Francis Xavier Catholic Church in Phoenix...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Top Democrat: Moscow Has Closed Cyber Gap With US - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/top-democrat-moscow-has-closed-cyber-gap-with-us/4691679.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOe3rP-b0SpzaQq77W23sToqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 22:07:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/top-democrat-moscow-has-closed-cyber-gap-with-us/4691679.html" target="_blank"&gt;Top Democrat: Moscow Has Closed Cyber Gap With US&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The top Democrat on the Senate Intelligence Committee warns the United States is being outgunned in cyberspace, already having lost its competitive advantage to Russia while China is rapidly closing in. "When it comes to cyber, misinformation and disinformation, Russia is already our peer and in the areas of misinformation or disinformation, I believe is ahead of us," Senator Mark Warner told an audience Friday in Washington. "This is an effective methodology for Russia and it's also remarkably cheap," he added, calling for a realignment of U.S. defense spending. Warner, calling Russia's el...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Effort to weaken governors stirs separation-of-powers debate - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/20a04ae0546d487881bb77a6d97b74ba</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFFsX13uI6SWWV_JTGtheBgqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvKadAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 23:14:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/20a04ae0546d487881bb77a6d97b74ba" target="_blank"&gt;Effort to weaken governors stirs separation-of-powers debate&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MILWAUKEE (AP) — If Democrats sue to prevent Republicans from diluting the powers of newly elected governors and attorneys general in Wisconsin and Michigan, the lawsuits will probably center on one question: Are lawmakers usurping authority that belongs to the executive branch? The legal threat arose after Republicans passed bills Wednesday that would give lawmakers leverage over actions previous governors and attorneys general could carry out on their own. If the bills are signed by outgoing GOP Gov. Scott Walker, lawmakers will decide when the state can withdraw from lawsuits, and the ne...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Dem leader: Infrastructure bills must tackle climate change - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/ec36a5d16ae04c42bd6b46465e1c2a47</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAFZKWZ0D-n_PX1vF0-H1FAqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwv7tQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:52:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/ec36a5d16ae04c42bd6b46465e1c2a47" target="_blank"&gt;Dem leader: Infrastructure bills must tackle climate change&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Democratic leaders in Congress demanded Friday that major legislation on roads, bridges and other infrastructure include efforts to curb global warming, complicating prospects for a deal with President Donald Trump on a jobs-boosting bill that both parties have targeted as a priority. Schumer said Friday in a letter to Trump that climate change will cause "untold human suffering and significant damage to the U.S. economy" if left unchecked. The New York Democrat called for permanent tax credits to boost production of wind and solar energy and to make homes and offices more...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Comey Rips Panels For Grilling Him On 'Whole Lotta' Clinton Emails, 'For Heaven's Sakes' - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/james-comey-hillary-clinton-emails_us_5c0b0910e4b035a7bf5b3b2c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEzJNKY1kXR0r7I6auclW6IqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 02:53:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/james-comey-hillary-clinton-emails_us_5c0b0910e4b035a7bf5b3b2c" target="_blank"&gt;Comey Rips Panels For Grilling Him On 'Whole Lotta' Clinton Emails, 'For Heaven's Sakes'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Former FBI Director James Comey complained Friday that members of the House Judiciary and Oversight committees spent hours quizzing him on a “whole lotta” Hillary Clinton emails that were part of an FBI investigation concluded two years ago. “When you read the transcript, you will see that we are talking again about Hillary Clinton’s emails, for heaven’s sakes, so I’m not sure we need to do this at all,” he told reporters after his six-hour closed-door session facing committee members. “But I’m trying to respect the institution and to answer questions in a respectful way.” Comey, who was fi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Trump demands border wall money; shutdown showdown nears - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/37597934930b48a39a51151c7dc3d7ff</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ9iFjEnKGGO6oAUCJY8eEoqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvKadAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 20:02:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/37597934930b48a39a51151c7dc3d7ff" target="_blank"&gt;Trump demands border wall money; shutdown showdown nears&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KANSAS CITY, Mo. (AP) — President Donald Trump said Friday that Congress should provide all the money he wants for his promised U.S.-Mexico border wall, and he called illegal immigration a "threat to the well-being of every American community." Trump spoke hours after signing a short-term spending bill that covers key government departments for two more weeks, until Dec. 21, setting up a pre-Christmas showdown over the wall. The president wants the next spending package to include at least $5 billion for the proposed wall. House Democratic leader Nancy Pelosi of California rejected that a d...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Here’s what Heitkamp could do with the millions left over from her failed Senate campaign - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/heres-what-heitkamp-could-do-with-the-millions-left-over-from-her-failed-senate-campaign-2018-12-07</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIx174kd9eJEI9Irb_qYq3cqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwiJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 20:56:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/heres-what-heitkamp-could-do-with-the-millions-left-over-from-her-failed-senate-campaign-2018-12-07" target="_blank"&gt;Here’s what Heitkamp could do with the millions left over from her failed Senate campaign&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;CAPITOL REPORT By Victor Reklaitis ‘So much money was flowing into North Dakota that it appears she had trouble spending all of it’ Sen. Heidi Heitkamp is shown speaking last year. Getty Images Heidi Heitkamp looks well-positioned to help her fellow Democrats or even run for office again, as the soon-to-be-former senator’s campaign has reported $6.8 million in leftover funds. The North Dakota lawmaker’s unspent money, disclosed Thursday in a regulatory filing, isn’t a record but is on the high side for an outgoing senator. Former Sen. Evan Bayh, an Indiana Democrat who decided not to seek r...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Trump Justice pick likely to be queried on Mueller comments - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/089bf90df8c04950a7fb14215fca87dd</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEkgmPaJ_FGqb0IJ9a7J0_wqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwu4lR</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 21:20:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/089bf90df8c04950a7fb14215fca87dd" target="_blank"&gt;Trump Justice pick likely to be queried on Mueller comments&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump on Friday picked former Attorney General William Barr to once again serve as America's top law enforcement official. But while his experience and mainstream background may boost his prospects for confirmation, Democrats are raising alarms about his comments on the Russia investigation and Hillary Clinton. Barr has expressed concerns about political donations made by prosecutors on special counsel Robert Mueller's team and has supported calls for an investigation into a uranium deal approved while Clinton was secretary of state, a pet issue of Trump s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Republicans in Wisconsin, Michigan move to curb Democrats' power - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/republicans-wisconsin-michigan-move-curb-democrats-power-181207171032406.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAZnkkB3KghsMs3nuaekFnkqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 20:41:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/republicans-wisconsin-michigan-move-curb-democrats-power-181207171032406.html" target="_blank"&gt;Republicans in Wisconsin, Michigan move to curb Democrats' power&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Republican-controlled legislatures in Wisconsin and Michigan this week sought to curb the power of recently-elected Democratic governors and others, eliciting howls of protest from critics who called it a power grab after President Donald Trump's party lost ground in November's midterm elections. The Republican efforts, which echoed actions taken by politicians in North Carolina in 2016, threatened to further deepen political rancor in the key Midwestern battleground states. "While you can find isolated incidents where legislatures have tried to hamstring governors before, there has been no...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>North Carolina board calls political operative a 'person of interest' in election fraud probe - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/07/politics/north-carolina-election/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGCmvBPZSgiSiWzR6CRIbukqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 01:51:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/07/politics/north-carolina-election/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;North Carolina board calls political operative a 'person of interest' in election fraud probe&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;North Carolina's State Board of Elections on Friday named Leslie McCrae Dowless Jr., a political operative who worked for Republican candidate Mark Harris, as "a person of interest in connection with an alleged absentee ballot operation in the congressional district." The news comes as the Wake County District Attorney's office and the North Carolina State Bureau of Investigation investigate criminal allegations that Dowless used absentee ballots to alter the vote in Bladen County in the race for North Carolina's 9th Congressional District. Harris leads Democrat Dan McCready by only 905 vot...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Another Democrat flips to supporting Pelosi for speaker - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/07/politics/stephen-lynch-vote-pelosi-house-speaker/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPX5j6RapBJatxEkD0HGn6sqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 16:57:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/07/politics/stephen-lynch-vote-pelosi-house-speaker/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Another Democrat flips to supporting Pelosi for speaker&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rep. Stephen Lynch, one of the 16 Democrats who signed a letter vowing not to vote for Rep. Nancy Pelosi for House speaker on the floor, announced Friday that he'll support Pelosi, following what he described as "one of the best conversations" he's had with her since he was in Congress. "I believe Leader Pelosi understands not only the job that needs to be done, but also how to bring disparate voices in our party together to make good things happen for the people we represent," the Massachusetts Democratic congressman said in a statement. "I'm happy to be supporting her and look forward to ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>‘Biggest attack on freedom of speech in decades’ – WikiLeaks hits back against DNC lawsuit - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/usa/445917-wikileaks-counters-dnc-lawsuit/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP2tgWoD54U7NRfcumdhpYsqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww_oMo</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 05:59:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/usa/445917-wikileaks-counters-dnc-lawsuit/" target="_blank"&gt;‘Biggest attack on freedom of speech in decades’ – WikiLeaks hits back against DNC lawsuit&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WikiLeaks is taking the fight to the Democratic National Committee, accusing the party of an unprecedented assault on the First Amendment in a legal filing that underlined both the absurdity and the overreach of its lawsuit. Prosecuting WikiLeaks for publishing “truthful information of public interest” would have a disastrous effect on press freedom, opening the door to prosecution of any and all media organizations that dare to speak truth to power, the embattled publishers wrote. “All that would remain would be a shell of the First Amendment practiced by a cowed and self-censoring media i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Comey faces off with GOP over Clinton emails, alleged bias - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/734284dd1aa746c19bf209770ae1ce54</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECLXK0gOuO8NJj29_LUpJwUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwv7tQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 02:39:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/734284dd1aa746c19bf209770ae1ce54" target="_blank"&gt;Comey faces off with GOP over Clinton emails, alleged bias&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Former FBI Director James Comey spoke to House investigators behind closed doors for almost seven hours Friday, begrudgingly answering questions about the Justice Department's decisions during the 2016 presidential election. Comey, who appeared under subpoena, announced after the meeting that he would return for more questioning Dec. 17. Appearing annoyed, he said "we're talking about Hillary Clinton's emails, for heaven's sake, so I'm not sure we needed to do this at all." A transcript of the interview, expected to be released shortly, "will bore you," Comey said. Two GOP...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Absentee vote changes may have invited 'ballot harvesting' - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/e30f0334da7d4186bed7079f4188ac3b</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBLL88MvhnTWLleRl5ArBFwqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwu4lR</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 04:53:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/e30f0334da7d4186bed7079f4188ac3b" target="_blank"&gt;Absentee vote changes may have invited 'ballot harvesting'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;RALEIGH, N.C. (AP) — Changes made to absentee voting procedures five years ago in North Carolina may have emboldened workers to run the type of illegal "ballot-harvesting" operation alleged to have been used in a disputed congressional race, election experts and lawmakers said. Some observers are concerned that the changes made it possible for more people to apply for absentee ballots. Then so-called harvesters could collect unsealed ballots and manipulate them or throw out ones from minority voters who might have otherwise gone to the polls. The heavily Republican Legislature crafted the 2...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Wisconsin and Michigan Republicans try to curb incoming Democratic attorneys general - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/wisconsin-and-michigan-republicans-try-to-curb-incoming-democratic-attorneys-general-2018-12-07</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFbMkNqpzDhASYQAxaw_G4wqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwiJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 16:39:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/wisconsin-and-michigan-republicans-try-to-curb-incoming-democratic-attorneys-general-2018-12-07" target="_blank"&gt;Wisconsin and Michigan Republicans try to curb incoming Democratic attorneys general&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ASSOCIATED PRESS By Associated Press Efforts also afoot to rein in governors’ powers after election of Democrats State Sen. Tim Carpenter, a Democrat from Milwaukee, questions a list of appointment referrals submitted to the State Senate during its lame-duck session this week. Associated Press MADISON, Wis. (AP) — Republicans pushing to hang on to power in Wisconsin and Michigan aren’t stopping at curbing the authority of incoming Democratic governors. They’re also trying to hamstring Democrats who are about to take over as attorneys general. The moves underscore how attorneys general have ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Harvard's Bipartisan Congressional Orientation Under Fire For Being Too Corporate - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/alexandria-ocasio-cortez-freshman-progressives-criticize-harvard-orientation_us_5c0ab004e4b0ab8cf6930a91</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKYNBNr-Qy_cL8h45kPxiFYqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMOGXAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 18:57:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/alexandria-ocasio-cortez-freshman-progressives-criticize-harvard-orientation_us_5c0ab004e4b0ab8cf6930a91" target="_blank"&gt;Harvard's Bipartisan Congressional Orientation Under Fire For Being Too Corporate&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;CAMBRIDGE, Mass. ― Congratulations! You’ve been elected to Congress! You’re now a member of one of the most powerful institutions in the world, and to usher you into your new job, you get to attend an orientation at Harvard University, one of the most prestigious universities in the world. Rep. Mark Pocan (D-Wis.) still remembers what it felt like to attend the bipartisan gathering in 2012, hosted by the Kennedy School’s Institute of Politics: “I was so excited to be a member of a branch of government for the most awesome country on the planet.” And indeed, the gathering still had that effe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>The Latest: Comey says lawmakers focused on Clinton emails - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/f7ff98589ce54741ab9d2efdff62d3ca</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC0kybxHR6eCGrkkUGf1bb4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwv7tQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 22:15:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/f7ff98589ce54741ab9d2efdff62d3ca" target="_blank"&gt;The Latest: Comey says lawmakers focused on Clinton emails&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Latest on former FBI Director James Comey's closed-door interview by House Republicans (all times local): 5 p.m. Former FBI Director James Comey says he testified again about Hillary Clinton's emails during a closed-door interview Friday with two House committees. Comey says House Republicans asked about Clinton's use of a private email server while she was secretary of state. He says GOP lawmakers focused "a whole lot" on Clinton's emails, telling reporters that a transcript of the six-hour interview "will bore you." Republicans say Comey and other Justice Department ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Trump picks attorney general and U.N. envoy in fresh staff shake-up - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-idUSKBN1O61YN</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBrJFrWAUVrSesDVbt1bqPcqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 20:30:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-idUSKBN1O61YN" target="_blank"&gt;Trump picks attorney general and U.N. envoy in fresh staff shake-up&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In another senior staff shake-up inside his often turbulent administration, U.S. President Donald Trump said on Friday he has picked the two people he wants to be the next U.S. attorney general and the next U.S. ambassador to the United Nations. He said he will nominate William Barr, who was attorney general under former President George H.W. Bush in the 1990s, to fill that top job again at the U.S. Justice Department. Barr would replace Acting Attorney General Matthew Whitaker, who has been in that position since Trump forced out Jeff Sessions as attorney general a month ago. Trump said he...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Senate passes bill making it easier to kill sea lions - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/c189aac7655a439389e35e6ca74e6e34</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKHug8d1SPxqsXXjuQ7fqssqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvKadAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 00:18:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/c189aac7655a439389e35e6ca74e6e34" target="_blank"&gt;Senate passes bill making it easier to kill sea lions&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SEATTLE (AP) — A bill that would make it easier to kill sea lions that feast on imperiled salmon in the Columbia River has cleared the U.S. Senate. State wildlife managers say rebounding numbers of sea lions are eating more salmon than ever and their appetites are undermining billions of dollars of investments to restore endangered fish runs. Senate Bill 3119, which passed Thursday by unanimous consent, would streamline the process for Washington, Idaho, Oregon and several Pacific Northwest Native American tribes to capture and euthanize potentially hundreds of sea lions found in the river ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Ocasio-Cortez Claps Back At Trump Jr.’s Meme With Reminder Of Democrats’ Subpoena Power - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/ocasio-cortez-trump-jr-democrats-subpoena-power_us_5c0af5b9e4b035a7bf5b2eda</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENkf0GEaMAwKtksviIHXSMMqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 00:51:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/ocasio-cortez-trump-jr-democrats-subpoena-power_us_5c0af5b9e4b035a7bf5b2eda" target="_blank"&gt;Ocasio-Cortez Claps Back At Trump Jr.’s Meme With Reminder Of Democrats’ Subpoena Power&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Firebrand Rep.-elect Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez (D-N.Y.) scorched Donald Trump Jr. on Friday for sharing a weird meme on Instagram suggesting that progressives like her will have America eating dogs. “Please, keep it coming Jr — it’s definitely a ‘very, very large brain’ idea to troll a member of a body that will have subpoena power in a month,” Ocasio-Cortez, 29, tweeted. “Have fun!” I have noticed that Junior here has a habit of posting nonsense about me whenever the Mueller investigation heats up. Please, keep it coming Jr - it’s definitely a “very, very large brain” idea to troll a member...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Kelly may depart in expected White House shakeup - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/4c38f72d4dee48c0b7b7e17fbfb5ee70</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECU9qNdj6p1Iz0aRXlWEk6gqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwv7tQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 05:36:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/4c38f72d4dee48c0b7b7e17fbfb5ee70" target="_blank"&gt;Kelly may depart in expected White House shakeup&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump is inching closer to his long-teased major White House shake-up, gearing up for the twin challenges of battling for re-election and dealing with the Democrats' investigations once they take control of the House. The biggest piece of the shifting picture: Chief of Staff John Kelly's departure now appears certain. Trump announced Friday he was picking a new U.S. attorney genera l and a new ambassador to the U.N. , and at the same time two senior aides departed the White House to beef up his 2020 campaign. But the largest changes were still to come. Kel...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>North Carolina elections board identifies 'person of interest' in fraud probe - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-election-north-carolina/north-carolina-elections-board-identifies-person-of-interest-in-fraud-probe-idUSKBN1O62BQ</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHW1zUgpDE56pEzCDbCPiIAqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 01:21:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-election-north-carolina/north-carolina-elections-board-identifies-person-of-interest-in-fraud-probe-idUSKBN1O62BQ" target="_blank"&gt;North Carolina elections board identifies 'person of interest' in fraud probe&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;North Carolina's board of elections named political consultant Leslie McCrae Dowless as a person of interest on Friday amid a probe of possible absentee ballot fraud in a disputed U.S. congressional election. The board has refused to certify Republican Mark Harris as the winner of the Nov. 6 election for a seat in the U.S. House of Representatives as it investigates possible fraud involving absentee ballots from two rural counties. In a statement, the board said it has assigned four investigators to the probe and issued subpoenas to the Red Dome Group, a consulting firm that Dowless perform...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>House Democrats may not seat North Carolina Republican | Schumer says infrastructure deal must address climate change - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/house-democrats-may-not-seat-north-carolina-republican-schumer-says-infrastructure-deal-must-address-climate-change-2018-12-07</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEALWQjj_8_ibGEZ4rYceR2kqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwiJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 14:33:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/house-democrats-may-not-seat-north-carolina-republican-schumer-says-infrastructure-deal-must-address-climate-change-2018-12-07" target="_blank"&gt;House Democrats may not seat North Carolina Republican | Schumer says infrastructure deal must address climate change&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;CAPITOL REPORT By Victor Reklaitis Trump administration to ease drilling rules that were put in place to protect the sage grouse Republican Mark Harris addresses a crowd in October as President Donald Trump looks on. Getty Images House Democrats may not seat North Carolina Republican due to probe: Democratic lawmakers set to take control of the House in January have said they may refuse to seat North Carolina Republican Mark Harris until an investigation into alleged voting fraud in his House race is resolved, according to a Wall Street Journal report. State officials are looking into alleg...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Prosecutors: Illegal hush-money paid at Trump's 'direction' - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/f47819630d1045768a8fe9c68054c676</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIoUy6c1EWzNrQj1ItRseUIqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwv7tQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 05:18:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/f47819630d1045768a8fe9c68054c676" target="_blank"&gt;Prosecutors: Illegal hush-money paid at Trump's 'direction'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Justice Department says that President Donald Trump directed illegal payments to buy the silence of two women whose claims of extramarital affairs threatened his presidential campaign, the first time prosecutors have connected Trump to a federal crime. In a court filing, prosecutors said former Trump lawyer and fixer Michael Cohen arranged the secret payments at the height of the 2016 campaign "in coordination with and at the direction of" Trump. Cohen has previously said Trump was involved in the hush-money scheme, but court documents filed ahead of Cohen's sentencing...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>GOP support for Pelosi as speaker? Don't hold your breath - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/7718ece462be410fbe829d6d8a81f970</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDOXUtI9a0v-simegBwhIXQqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwv7tQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 05:59:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/7718ece462be410fbe829d6d8a81f970" target="_blank"&gt;GOP support for Pelosi as speaker? Don't hold your breath&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Wondering if Republicans will push Nancy Pelosi over the top in her drive to become House speaker next year? Despite supportive words from President Donald Trump, it's implausible. Twice since Democrats won House control in last month's elections, Trump has said the California Democrat deserves to regain the post she held from 2007 to early 2011 as the first female speaker. He's offered to help her win GOP votes, if needed, when the new House elects its speaker Jan. 3. One Republican lawmaker says he'd consider helping her. Still, it's a far-fetched scenario that she's pub...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Rosenstein, Justice Department vets celebrate Barr nomination - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/07/politics/doj-rod-rosenstein-william-barr-nomination/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHDn_zqqprDKgFwmt8z0CVkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMJrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 21:44:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/07/politics/doj-rod-rosenstein-william-barr-nomination/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Rosenstein, Justice Department vets celebrate Barr nomination&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Justice Department veterans on Friday celebrated President Donald Trump's announcement that he would select William Barr, a member of the Justice Department's old guard and a former attorney general under George H.W. Bush, to be his next attorney general. Barr, who worked his way from a night school law student and up through the ranks of the Department of Justice, is widely viewed by legal observers as a deeply experienced attorney with bipartisan respect. Deputy Attorney General Rod Rosenstein is said to be "elated" by the choice of Barr and former Attorney General Jeff Sessions has alway...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Appeals to Scott Walker: Don't stain legacy, veto bills - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/7b001b3a2c6547b4b334bd26c9d146ad</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEbmv9UpbURxleCgZESTLWcqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwu4lR</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 04:16:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/7b001b3a2c6547b4b334bd26c9d146ad" target="_blank"&gt;Appeals to Scott Walker: Don't stain legacy, veto bills&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MADISON, Wis. (AP) — A bipartisan group of political figures appealed to Gov. Scott Walker to avoid staining his legacy and behaving like a sore loser by signing legislation that would weaken the powers of the Democrat who defeated him. Rather than notching another partisan victory in his final weeks in office, they said, Walker should think bigger. Think of your recently deceased father, they pleaded. Think of former President George H.W. Bush. Think of Christ. "You can have a long, successful career ahead," longtime Republican and major GOP donor Sheldon Lubar wrote to Walker in a deeply ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>US election 2020: The Democrat candidates who could run against Trump, from Beto O'Rourke to Oprah and Kamala Harris - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/us-politics/us-election-2020-democrat-candidates-leader-donald-trump-biden-booker-warren-harris-a8670956.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP5r0msepzjYmzZCq6-grG4qFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCRx_0F</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 13:38:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/us-politics/us-election-2020-democrat-candidates-leader-donald-trump-biden-booker-warren-harris-a8670956.html" target="_blank"&gt;US election 2020: The Democrat candidates who could run against Trump, from Beto O'Rourke to Oprah and Kamala Harris&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The 2020 presidential race is right around the corner, with analysts predicting as many as 40 Democrat candidates may launch bids against Donald Trump for the White House. Dozens of legislators, billionaire activists and former officials have played coy in recent weeks over whether or not they plan to run for president in 2020. Still, there are at countless candidates who have reportedly been considering hitting the campaign trail against the Republican incumbent, meeting with top donors and visiting key states just before the new year. As the president eggs on his high-profile political op...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Michigan's Lame-Duck Republicans Waddle Away from Democracy - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/michigans-lame-duck-republicans-waddle-away-from-democracy</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAvrmBzEFpwKPI-UuReCVowqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMPGMAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 10:07:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/michigans-lame-duck-republicans-waddle-away-from-democracy" target="_blank"&gt;Michigan's Lame-Duck Republicans Waddle Away from Democracy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photo Illustration by Elizabeth Brockway/The Daily Beast You’ve read about what Republicans are doing in Wisconsin, North Carolina, and Michigan, where GOP-held legislatures are to varying degrees trying to undo things the voters did on Nov. 6 that don’t suit them. Wisconsin has attracted national attention because outgoing Governor Scott Walker is a man liberals love to hate, and North Carolina because the state’s Moral Monday protests have enjoyed national attention for two years now. But what’s happening in Michigan may be the most egregious of the three. Consider: On one front, the Repu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez warns Donald Trump Jr not to troll somebody who's about to have subpoena power over him - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/us-politics/ocasio-cortez-donald-trump-jr-twitter-subpoena-power-democrats-house-of-representatives-tweet-a8673371.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHmWCevur8YBGKRJcaO6mWUqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 20:09:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/us-politics/ocasio-cortez-donald-trump-jr-twitter-subpoena-power-democrats-house-of-representatives-tweet-a8673371.html" target="_blank"&gt;Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez warns Donald Trump Jr not to troll somebody who's about to have subpoena power over him&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez, the new Democratic darling in Washington DC, has poked fun at Donald Trump’s eldest son, suggesting it is not wise to troll a member of a body that will soon have subpoena powers over him. Earlier this week, Donald Trump JR sought to mock the 29-year-old congresswoman-elect – apparently hated by conservatives as much as she is loved by progressives – with a meme he posted to his Instagram page. The Washington Post reported the meme implied Ms Ocasio-Cortez’s democratic socialist views would lead to Americans eating dogs. Consisting of two images that had been place...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Speier says Dems could subpoena Trump Jr., Kushner as part of Russia inquiries - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/07/politics/jackie-speier-donald-trump-jr-jared-kushner-cnntv/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMKAb4zU6aFi-EkCH8iT3qQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 22:15:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/07/politics/jackie-speier-donald-trump-jr-jared-kushner-cnntv/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Speier says Dems could subpoena Trump Jr., Kushner as part of Russia inquiries&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Democrat who sits on the House Intelligence Committee suggested Friday that Democrats could subpoena Donald Trump Jr. and White House senior adviser Jared Kushner next year as part of investigations into Russian meddling in the 2016 election. Asked by CNN's Brianna Keilar on CNN's "Right Now" about whether the House Intelligence Committee will bring in Kushner and Trump Jr. to be interviewed again once the Democrats take control of the House, Rep. Jackie Speier, D-California, said, "We will certainly subpoena their records." "I think they will be subpoenaed if they don't come voluntarily,...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Midterm election night lasted one month. Harry Enten explains why. - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/06/media/rs-podcast-harry-enten/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELfX51iWJgeDB3F9iY0u048qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 03:12:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/06/media/rs-podcast-harry-enten/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Midterm election night lasted one month. Harry Enten explains why.&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Midterm election night was really just the beginning. At the end of the night's nonstop news coverage, the picture was incomplete, with millions of votes still to be counted. Now, one month later, the picture has been filled in, and the results are more positive for Democrats than initially believed. And that's prompting some conversations in newsrooms about how to cover election nights differently in the future. Perhaps journalists need to be "more transparent" on election nights "and admit where we don't necessarily know where everything's going to end up," Harry Enten said on this week's...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Russia Probe Democrats Want Another Shot at Erik Prince - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/russia-probe-democrats-want-another-shot-at-erik-prince</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF2oxd0UziZ8j4YiFIGGS3kqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMPGMAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 00:10:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/russia-probe-democrats-want-another-shot-at-erik-prince" target="_blank"&gt;Russia Probe Democrats Want Another Shot at Erik Prince&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MCT House intelligence committee members are eager to have the founder of mercenary company Blackwater back for another round of interviews about Donald Trump’s ties to Russia, according to three members of its incoming majority. Democrats have lots of outstanding questions about Erik Prince’s curious January 2017 trip to the Seychelles, where, at the invitation of a coterie around the crown prince of the United Arab Emirates, he met with an influential Russian moneyman. They also have concerns about Prince’s candor during their prior interview last year. But Prince, through a spokesperson,...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Rep. Ted Lieu: It's 'Too Late' For Trump To Shut Down The Russia Probe - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/ted-lieu-donald-trump-shut-down-mueller-probe_us_5c099821e4b0de79357b1d57</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPIs5BwbQsudA1Z8pTwGyBQqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 00:12:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/ted-lieu-donald-trump-shut-down-mueller-probe_us_5c099821e4b0de79357b1d57" target="_blank"&gt;Rep. Ted Lieu: It's 'Too Late' For Trump To Shut Down The Russia Probe&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A prominent Democrat on the House Judiciary Committee says it’s “too late” for President Donald Trump to stop investigations into his 2016 campaign’s possible collusion with the Russian government. In an interview on SiriusXM Progress that aired Tuesday, Rep. Ted Lieu (D-Calif.) told me that Democrats’ new majority in the House of Representatives means they now have the power to keep an investigation going, no matter what happens to special counsel Robert Mueller. “In terms of the Judiciary Committee, one of our main missions will be to continue to protect the independence of special counse...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Trump says he’ll nominate Barr to serve as attorney general - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/trump-says-hell-nominate-barr-to-serve-as-attorney-general-2018-12-07</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECCmd54CIVCgGPEJR_JvhggqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUw2JS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 15:55:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/trump-says-hell-nominate-barr-to-serve-as-attorney-general-2018-12-07" target="_blank"&gt;Trump says he’ll nominate Barr to serve as attorney general&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ASSOCIATED PRESS By Associated Press William Barr Bloomberg President Donald Trump said Friday he will nominate William Barr, the late President George H.W. Bush’s attorney general, to serve in the same role. Trump made the announcement while departing the White House for a trip to Missouri. He called Barr “a terrific man” and “one of the most respected jurists in the country.” “I think he will serve with great distinction,” Trump said. If confirmed by the Senate, Barr would succeed Attorney General Jeff Sessions, who was forced out by Trump in November following an acrimonious tenure. Sess...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Landmark environmental protections being rolled back - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/b313482683f14439b78d985b758b51e1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENZNKIiyLHvIubKOqN384IsqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwu4lR</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 05:32:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/b313482683f14439b78d985b758b51e1" target="_blank"&gt;Landmark environmental protections being rolled back&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — One after another, landmark U.S. protections for climate, air and land are in the crosshairs of the Trump administration as his agency leaders move past early fumbles and scandals to start delivering on a succession of promised environmental rollbacks. On Thursday, the Interior Department proposed easing rules on oil and gas drilling for millions of acres of range in the West. And as soon as next week, the Environmental Protection Agency is expected to unveil its proposed rewrite of a major 2015 Obama rule that extended federal protections to thousands of waterways and wet...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Comey Finishes Testimony to House Committees - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/james-comey-to-testify-before-house-committee/4690546.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHXkLfsxlKHW0Q8sEDt5KUYqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 09:50:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/james-comey-to-testify-before-house-committee/4690546.html" target="_blank"&gt;Comey Finishes Testimony to House Committees&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lawmakers from two House committees interviewed former FBI Director James Comey behind closed doors Friday, likely the last time they will do so before Republicans in the chamber cede power to Democrats in January. House Republicans indicated they were not satisfied with Comey's answers and said they might try to bring him back another day. House Democrats accused the Republicans of asking politically motivated questions. Comey spoke to reporters after the conclusion of the interview, criticizing both the content of the questions and the fact that the hearing was behind closed doors. "After...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>North Carolina: Democrat withdraws concession in congressional race - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/dec/06/north-carolina-democrat-withdraws-concession-congress</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBw-PK006l39-hD1PXIwiLcqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCtvxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 03:31:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/dec/06/north-carolina-democrat-withdraws-concession-congress" target="_blank"&gt;North Carolina: Democrat withdraws concession in congressional race&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Democrat trailing in a North Carolina congressional race withdrew his concession on Thursday as state election officials investigated allegations of absentee ballot fraud. Dan McCready’s reversal came as a top leader at the state’s Republican party said it would support a new election in the unresolved ninth congressional district race if an investigation showed that wrongdoing swayed its outcome. Unofficial totals have the Republican Mark Harris leading McCready by 905 votes. But the state elections board refused to certify the results last week because of allegations of “irregularitie...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Mark Harris Would Support A New Election In North Carolina If Election Fraud Is Proved - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/mark-harris-election-fraud-new-election_us_5c0ad08ae4b0ab8cf69328c6</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELd8Erd_o40PxsEBc_S3j84qFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJ3knAY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 21:16:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/mark-harris-election-fraud-new-election_us_5c0ad08ae4b0ab8cf69328c6" target="_blank"&gt;Mark Harris Would Support A New Election In North Carolina If Election Fraud Is Proved&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mark Harris, the Republican candidate in a disputed race for North Carolina’s 9th Congressional District, said Friday that he would support a new election should allegations that his campaign benefited from election fraud be proved true. In a video Harris released on Twitter Friday afternoon, the candidate acknowledges recent news reports detailing allegations of election fraud that may have favored his campaign. “If this investigation finds proof of illegal activity on either side to such a level that it could have changed the outcome of the election, then I would wholeheartedly support a ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Will the Republican Party turn on Trump? - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/07/opinions/will-the-republican-party-turn-on-trump-zelizer/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHrmJqv6T-GapI4GOTS2H3oqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMKrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 05:17:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/07/opinions/will-the-republican-party-turn-on-trump-zelizer/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Will the Republican Party turn on Trump?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Julian Zelizer is a professor of history and public affairs at Princeton University and author of "The Fierce Urgency of Now: Lyndon Johnson, Congress, and the Battle for the Great Society." The opinions expressed in this commentary are his own. View more opinion at CNN. Court filings on Friday regarding Paul Manafort and Michael Cohen reveal the ways in which the special counsel's investigation can endanger President Trump's future. Special Counsel Robert Mueller also revealed on Tuesday that former national security adviser Michael Flynn offered "substantial assistance" to the Russia inve...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Trump picks former Attorney General Barr to return to head Justice Department - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-barr-idUSKBN1O61PR</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMVIeaal5_1b11G4KyDgtZ8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 18:20:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-barr-idUSKBN1O61PR" target="_blank"&gt;Trump picks former Attorney General Barr to return to head Justice Department&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;President Donald Trump said on Friday he had chosen former U.S. Attorney General William Barr to once again lead the Justice Department, a role that would put him in charge of the federal probe into Russian election interference. If confirmed by the Senate, Barr would take over from Matthew Whitaker, who has been serving in an acting capacity since Trump forced out Jeffrey Sessions a month ago. Whitaker had been Sessions' chief of staff. Barr was "my first choice from day one," and "a terrific man, a terrific person, a brilliant man," Trump said, speaking to reporters outside the White Hous...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Speier: Kushner, Trump Jr. may face subpoenas - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/politics/2018/12/07/jackie-speier-subpeona-kushner-trump-jr-sot-brianna-keilar-crn-vpx.cnn</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELnllR3yHbBwzVMgJrTfrv8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 22:05:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/politics/2018/12/07/jackie-speier-subpeona-kushner-trump-jr-sot-brianna-keilar-crn-vpx.cnn" target="_blank"&gt;Speier: Kushner, Trump Jr. may face subpoenas&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rep. Jackie Speier (D-CA) tells CNN's Brianna Keilar that both Jared Kushner and Donald Trump Jr. may be subpoenaed to testify if they do not do so voluntarily. ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A WarnerMedia Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Correction: Wisconsin-Legislature-Lame-Duck story - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/02dd4f5766da4c9a955c3a6ac47398fe</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKP6Lx12uRNAQF3celZUpLsqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvKadAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 16:48:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/02dd4f5766da4c9a955c3a6ac47398fe" target="_blank"&gt;Correction: Wisconsin-Legislature-Lame-Duck story&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MADISON, Wis. (AP) — In a story Dec. 5 about lame-duck legislation approved by Wisconsin lawmakers that would curtail powers of the incoming Democratic governor and attorney general, The Associated Press reported erroneously that Gov. Scott Walker would have 10 days from the date the bills reach his desk to sign or veto them. Walker would have six days to act. A corrected version of the story is below: Next governor will ask Walker to veto lame-duck legislation Next Wisconsin governor will ask Walker to veto GOP legislation to weaken new administration By SCOTT BAUER and TODD RICHMOND Assoc...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>If You Like Trump’s 'Wall,' Thank Obama And Bush. It’s Basically Just Their Fence. - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/trump-fence-wall_us_5c099defe4b04046345a7446</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECF54u7aN0X-q6GRCq8oO0YqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMOGXAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 10:45:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/trump-fence-wall_us_5c099defe4b04046345a7446" target="_blank"&gt;If You Like Trump’s 'Wall,' Thank Obama And Bush. It’s Basically Just Their Fence.&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON — Unable to get a single dollar to build the “great wall” he promised on the campaign trail, President Donald Trump has settled on a new strategy: repairing and upgrading the existing fence and calling that his “wall.” Trump has claimed repeatedly over the past nine months that he has already started construction. “And we have a lot of it built and it’s going up,” he said at a rally in Mississippi late last month after attendees began a favorite chant: “Build that wall!” In reality, not a single mile of new barrier has yet been built along the Mexican border. There were 654 miles...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Dems to probe citizenship question in U.S. census - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/video/2018/12/06/dems-to-probe-citizenship-question-in-us?videoId=488768136</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC7lkVBx5xM_kuIRxAtsv5IqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMI3s7wU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 06:36:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/video/2018/12/06/dems-to-probe-citizenship-question-in-us?videoId=488768136" target="_blank"&gt;Dems to probe citizenship question in U.S. census&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The likely incoming Democratic chairman of the congressional panel overseeing the U.S. census said on Tuesday he aims to pressure the Trump administration into removing a question about citizenship from the 2020 census questionnaire.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Bernie Sanders Explains to Colbert Why Trump Is No George H.W. Bush - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/bernie-sanders-explains-to-colbert-why-trump-is-no-george-hw-bush</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBs5_alHav1anGSlC71pQI8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMPGMAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 07:01:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/bernie-sanders-explains-to-colbert-why-trump-is-no-george-hw-bush" target="_blank"&gt;Bernie Sanders Explains to Colbert Why Trump Is No George H.W. Bush&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scott Kowalchyk/CBS Senator Bernie Sanders is one of the many progressives “seriously considering” a run for the presidency in 2020. And he took one step closer to that eventuality on The Late Show with Stephen Colbert Thursday night. Ostensibly, Sanders was there to promote his latest book, Where We Go from Here: Two Years in the Resistance, but really he was there to pump up his base. Asked how he’s feeling after the midterm elections, Sanders answered, “A lot better now than before the midterms. Democrats won 40 seats, now control the House, won several governors’ seats and several hundr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Boston Globe to Sen. Elizabeth Warren: Don't Run in 2020 - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/boston-globe-to-sen-elizabeth-warren-dont-run-in-2020</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN2om00TZQi1B60at4tGrvUqFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMLXUiQY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 01:07:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/boston-globe-to-sen-elizabeth-warren-dont-run-in-2020" target="_blank"&gt;Boston Globe to Sen. Elizabeth Warren: Don't Run in 2020&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chip Somodevilla/Getty, The Boston Globe's editorial board has said Sen. Elizabeth Warren (D-MA) should sit out the 2020 election after she “missed her moment” in 2016. In the Thursday piece, the Globe suggested Warren’s political mojo might be wearing off and she will be too weak to be a 2020 hit. “While Warren won reelection, her margin of victory in November suggests there’s a ceiling on her popularity,” the editorial board wrote. “While Warren is an effective and impactful senator with an important voice nationally, she has become a divisive figure. A unifying voice is what the country ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Trump: ‘Go for it Mitch!’ on Sentencing Bill - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/trump-go-for-it-mitch-on-sentencing-bill/4692140.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMEnQkOEgaG-LLJwo2IJ_UUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 10:08:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/trump-go-for-it-mitch-on-sentencing-bill/4692140.html" target="_blank"&gt;Trump: ‘Go for it Mitch!’ on Sentencing Bill&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell’s reluctance to hold a vote on a popular criminal justice bill has angered top Republican senators and created an unusual rift with a longtime GOP ally, Sen. Chuck Grassley of Iowa. And on Friday, it also brought on a tweet from President Donald Trump. Minutes later Grassley tweeted that he and the president had spoken about “the growing support” for the legislation. “Pres Trump told me he wants it done THIS CONGRESS,” Grassley tweeted. FILE - Senate Judiciary Committee Chairman Chuck Grassley of Iowa chairs a meeting of the committee on Capitol Hill i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Trump's Justice Department Pick Has Criticized Special Counsel Probes - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/trump-s-justice-department-pick-has-criticized-special-counsel-probes-/4691725.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPe3STZv3vXVBe22UNX7yjgqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 23:29:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/trump-s-justice-department-pick-has-criticized-special-counsel-probes-/4691725.html" target="_blank"&gt;Trump's Justice Department Pick Has Criticized Special Counsel Probes&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By tapping former Attorney General William Barr to head the Justice Department again, President Donald Trump has picked a highly respected lawyer with a wealth of experience leading a major government department and overseeing high-profile independent investigations. But Barr, 68, who led the Justice Department from 1991 to 1993 under the late President George H.W. Bush, has long been skeptical of sweeping probes of government officials and voiced support for a strong executive branch. While at the Justice Department, Barr oversaw two independent investigations. The first, a sprawling inqui...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Swalwell: Open to 2020 ticket with Biden - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/politics/2018/12/07/eric-swalwell-joe-biden-2020-sot-tsr-vpx.cnn</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJRSNEUcakMhe9VX0Jk8ZTgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 01:50:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/politics/2018/12/07/eric-swalwell-joe-biden-2020-sot-tsr-vpx.cnn" target="_blank"&gt;Swalwell: Open to 2020 ticket with Biden&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rep. Eric Swalwell (D-CA) revealed that he is "open to entertaining both variations" of a presidential ticket featuring himself and former Vice President Joe Biden. ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A WarnerMedia Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Boston Globe: Elizabeth Warren Should Reconsider 2020 Presidential Run - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/boston-globe-elizabeth-warren-2020_us_5c09cff3e4b0b6cdaf5d8883</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO7zD43FXTp27_bxHsNkfJ0qFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 03:39:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/boston-globe-elizabeth-warren-2020_us_5c09cff3e4b0b6cdaf5d8883" target="_blank"&gt;Boston Globe: Elizabeth Warren Should Reconsider 2020 Presidential Run&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Three years ago, the Boston Globe’s editorial board urged Sen. Elizabeth Warren (D-Mass.) to run for president. Now the board is offering her much different advice: Don’t do it. In an editorial published Thursday, the Boston Globe said Warren had “missed her moment in 2016” and cast skepticism on how well the progressive Democrat, whose recent public feuding with President Donald Trump boosted her popularity, would perform as a Democratic presidential candidate for the 2020 election. “While Warren is an effective and impactful senator with an important voice nationally, she has become a div...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>In The Trump Era, Democrats Look More Kindly On Past GOP Presidents - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/in-the-trump-era-democrats-look-more-kindly-on-past-gop-presidents_us_5c09a8dde4b0de79357b334a</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMBnT8ku-5AoqMtSoJqaIwMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMOGXAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 00:03:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/in-the-trump-era-democrats-look-more-kindly-on-past-gop-presidents_us_5c09a8dde4b0de79357b334a" target="_blank"&gt;In The Trump Era, Democrats Look More Kindly On Past GOP Presidents&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;President Donald Trump is viewed far more harshly by the public than his five most recent predecessors, according to a new HuffPost/YouGov survey. Americans say by an 11-percentage-point margin that they disapprove of Trump’s job performance. Barack Obama, George W. Bush, Bill Clinton and Ronald Reagan, by contrast, all score retroactively positive ratings, with the top honors going to George H.W. Bush, who passed away shortly before the survey was conducted. The results are largely to be expected: Americans have a tendency to warm toward former presidents, and many may be especially unwill...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>CNN and The Des Moines Register to partner for Iowa polling - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/06/politics/cnn-des-moines-register-iowa-poll/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAjVx4R4UT8gO40OU-lr7FQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 19:49:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/06/politics/cnn-des-moines-register-iowa-poll/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;CNN and The Des Moines Register to partner for Iowa polling&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;CNN will partner with The Des Moines Register on "The Iowa Poll" in the lead-up to the state's 2020 presidential caucuses, the news organizations announced Thursday. The partnership, in collaboration with financial sponsor Mediacom, will see CNN and the Des Moines Register "exercise joint editorial control" over "The Iowa Poll," which was founded by the Register in 1943. The poll will be conducted by Selzer &amp; Company. "The Iowa Poll," which is closely watched by political observers, will give insight into the important Iowa caucuses, which take place on February 3, 2020. The caucuses will b...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Joe Manchin Faces Opposition From Left Over Top Senate Committee Post - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/joe-manchin-senate-energy-committee_us_5c097b83e4b0b6cdaf5d2fe5</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPb6dWsFa6O6kwzIx2XR6J0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMOGXAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 22:59:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/joe-manchin-senate-energy-committee_us_5c097b83e4b0b6cdaf5d2fe5" target="_blank"&gt;Joe Manchin Faces Opposition From Left Over Top Senate Committee Post&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON ― High profile progressives and climate advocates are urging Senate Democrats not to give coal-friendly Sen. Joe Manchin (D-W.Va.) a top post on the Senate Energy and Natural Resources Committee, which deals with much of the nation’s energy policy and use of federal lands. But the prospect of Manchin, who famously used a rifle to shoot a greenhouse gas emission cap-and-trade bill in a 2010 campaign ad, as the committee’s senior Democrat next year did not appear to alarm some of the party’s most influential voices in the Senate on climate change. “I think he’ll find a way to work ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Beto O'Rourke lands big Obama fundraiser -- but many elite donors are playing the field in 2020 - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/07/politics/obama-bundlers-beto-orourke-2020-presidential-campaign/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFPuiEVFSC3khO7OSVozCGkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 11:01:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/07/politics/obama-bundlers-beto-orourke-2020-presidential-campaign/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Beto O'Rourke lands big Obama fundraiser -- but many elite donors are playing the field in 2020&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the Democratic Party's most prolific fundraisers says he has pledged to raise campaign money for rising political star Beto O'Rourke should the Texas Democrat seek the presidency in 2020. Chicago financier Louis Susman, who served as finance chairman of John Kerry's 2004 presidential bid and was an early backer of President Barack Obama's White House ambitions in 2008, told CNN in a telephone interview he has met with O'Rourke on a number of occasions and that he is encouraging him to run. "It's time to pass the torch to a new generation," said Susman, a former US Ambassador to Unite...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Ocasio-Cortez and Trump Jr. trade social media barbs - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/07/politics/aoc-tweet-donald-trump-jr-large-brain-subpoenas/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM7DFnwgIoNTbwOAAKCHUnMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMJrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 05:06:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/07/politics/aoc-tweet-donald-trump-jr-large-brain-subpoenas/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Ocasio-Cortez and Trump Jr. trade social media barbs&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rep.-elect Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez blasted Donald Trump Jr. on Friday for insulting her and in turn drew the ire of conservatives who saw her counterattack as a power-abusing threat to the eldest son of President Donald Trump. "I have noticed that Junior here has a habit of posting nonsense about me whenever the Mueller investigation heats up," the Democratic Socialist from New York tweeted. "Please, keep it coming Jr - it's definitely a 'very, very large brain' idea to troll a member of a body that will have subpoena power in a month. Have fun!" The "brain" line appeared to reference Pres...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Comey testifies at House hearing he calls 'desperate' attack on investigators - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/dec/07/comey-testifies-at-house-hearing-he-calls-desperate-attack-on-investigators</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJHhjrpgQQREHYR2dhhESfgqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCtvxU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 02:25:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/dec/07/comey-testifies-at-house-hearing-he-calls-desperate-attack-on-investigators" target="_blank"&gt;Comey testifies at House hearing he calls 'desperate' attack on investigators&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;James Comey, the former FBI director called to testify before members of the House of Representatives on Friday, called the hearing a “desperate attempt to find anything that can be used to attack the institutions of justice investigating this president”. Comey, who was subpoenaed, spoke to the GOP-led House judiciary and oversight and government reform committees for nearly seven hours behind closed doors, later telling reporters that they were “talking again about Hillary Clinton’s emails, for heaven’s sakes”. “I’m not sure we need to do this at all. But I’m trying to respect the institut...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Elizabeth Warren's Native-American heritage reveal was just as bad as you thought it was - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/06/politics/elizabeth-warren-native-american/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJTqbOTf1cuRBcSRf_nqdmIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 16:50:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/06/politics/elizabeth-warren-native-american/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Elizabeth Warren's Native-American heritage reveal was just as bad as you thought it was&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;When Elizabeth Warren unveiled a 5-minute video aimed at putting to rest questions as to whether she actually was Native American in mid-October, it was, um, not well-received. It turns out that the damage done to Warren's political prospects in 2020 was significant, and has forced her allies to consider more drastic methods to take the issue off the table. Wrote Astead W. Herndon in The New York Times on Thursday: "Advisers close to Ms. Warren say she has privately expressed concern that she may have damaged her relationships to Native American groups and her own standing with activists, p...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Rep. Wasserman Schultz supports Epstein investigation wherever it leads - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/tv/2018/12/06/lead-debbie-wasserman-schultz-on-labor-secy-concerns-live-jake-tapper.cnn</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHulim1u7FaLe6yhUTZcnhgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 22:36:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/tv/2018/12/06/lead-debbie-wasserman-schultz-on-labor-secy-concerns-live-jake-tapper.cnn" target="_blank"&gt;Rep. Wasserman Schultz supports Epstein investigation wherever it leads&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Democratic Rep. Debbie Wasserman Schultz joins The Lead. ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A WarnerMedia Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>New Democratic governors show shift on US charter schools - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/90ac614ab07c48f99c3436f99a14e634</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEKxF5So0eSK7ZKqJla92QMqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwm4pR</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 19:21:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/90ac614ab07c48f99c3436f99a14e634" target="_blank"&gt;New Democratic governors show shift on US charter schools&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Education Secretary Betsy DeVos was not on the ballot in the Michigan governor's race, but her legacy loomed over the campaign in her home state, which has the country's highest concentration of for-profit charter schools. Republican Bill Schuette, a DeVos ally and the state's attorney general, ultimately lost to Gretchen Whitmer, a Democrat and former state lawmaker who pledged on the campaign trail to "put an end to the DeVos agenda." She has promised to stop new for-profit schools from opening and to demand more accountability from charter schools. Michigan was one of several key states ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Donald Trump nominates William Barr as next attorney general - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/dec/07/donald-trump-nominates-william-barr-attorney-general</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOon7C1FtVVmnB-lzgLD5usqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCtvxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 16:28:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/dec/07/donald-trump-nominates-william-barr-attorney-general" target="_blank"&gt;Donald Trump nominates William Barr as next attorney general&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Donald Trump has named William Barr as his next attorney general, a move that raises fresh concerns about the future of special counsel Robert Mueller’s investigation into Russian election interference. Related: Trump to nominate new attorney general and UN ambassador as Kelly eyes exit – live If confirmed by the Senate, Barr – who held the same role under the late George HW Bush from 1991 to 1993 – will take over from Matthew Whitaker, who has served in an acting capacity since Jeff Sessions was forced out a month ago. Democrats have threatened to examine whether Whitaker can legally serve...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>One fewer woman in Trump's Cabinet - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/07/politics/trump-cabinet-women/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECvdvy4rh27pDWdx80CsjNEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMJrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 18:05:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/07/politics/trump-cabinet-women/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;One fewer woman in Trump's Cabinet&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the one hand, President Donald Trump announced he would nominate a woman to replace US Ambassador to the UN Nikki Haley, who is slated to leave by the end of the year. On the other hand, it became clear the position would be downgraded and removed from his Cabinet. The net effect is one fewer woman in Trump's official Cabinet. The President announced Friday he would nominate State Department spokeswoman Heather Nauert to replace Haley. According to reporting by CNN's Kaitlan Collins, Secretary of State Mike Pompeo has told aides he wants the position downgraded from Cabinet level, which ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Swalwell says he's open to running on a 2020 ticket with Biden - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/06/politics/eric-swalwell-joe-biden-2020-cnntv/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE_eeez6IekuP5maym3VYZ8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMJrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 01:51:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/06/politics/eric-swalwell-joe-biden-2020-cnntv/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Swalwell says he's open to running on a 2020 ticket with Biden&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rep. Eric Swalwell said Thursday that he is "open to entertaining both variations" of a presidential ticket featuring himself and former Vice President Joe Biden in 2020. "You tweeted in support of a proposal of a Biden-Swalwell ticket in 2020," Wolf Blitzer said to the California Democrat on CNN's "The Situation Room." "Are you prepared to run in 2020 as either a presidential or a vice presidential candidate?" "Yeah, or Swalwell-Biden, Wolf," Swalwell responded. "I'm open to entertaining both variations." On Thursday, Swalwell responded in support of a tweet suggesting he could run as Bide...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Kelly expected to resign soon, no longer on speaking terms with Trump - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/07/politics/john-kelly-chief-of-staff-donald-trump/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELywJqD1Pkzf5P6AMvDdgosqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMJrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 01:13:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/07/politics/john-kelly-chief-of-staff-donald-trump/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Kelly expected to resign soon, no longer on speaking terms with Trump&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;John Kelly is expected to resign as White House chief of staff in the coming days, two sources familiar with the situation unfolding in the West Wing tell CNN. Seventeen months in, Kelly and President Donald Trump have reached a stalemate in their relationship and it is no longer seen as tenable by either party. Though Trump asked Kelly over the summer to stay on as chief of staff for two more years, the two have stopped speaking in recent days. Trump is actively discussing a replacement plan, though a person involved in the process said nothing is final right now and ultimately nothing is ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>GOP House candidate would back new election if fraud shown - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/87dc85596faf45de8d2ac110d03dc815</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHHZ5X6A83ybNym5XOPlEIQqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwv7tQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 22:47:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/87dc85596faf45de8d2ac110d03dc815" target="_blank"&gt;GOP House candidate would back new election if fraud shown&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;RALEIGH, N.C. (AP) — The Republican candidate in North Carolina's unresolved congressional race said Friday that he would support a new election if it's proved that fraud changed the outcome of a contest that was decided by 905 votes. Mark Harris released a video statement addressing allegations of absentee ballot fraud less than a day after his campaign acknowledged in a federal filing that it owes $34,310 to a political consultant for work in a county where mail-in ballot problems emerged. The state Board of Elections has refused to certify election results that give Harris a slim lead wh...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Lawmaker aims to get citizenship question removed from U.S. census - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-congress-connolly-census/lawmaker-aims-to-get-citizenship-question-removed-from-us-census-idUSKBN1O32R8</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHu355uPvS-ddfrgg2tzaLQqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMMT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 01:25:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-congress-connolly-census/lawmaker-aims-to-get-citizenship-question-removed-from-us-census-idUSKBN1O32R8" target="_blank"&gt;Lawmaker aims to get citizenship question removed from U.S. census&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The likely incoming Democratic chairman of the congressional panel overseeing the U.S. census said on Tuesday he aims to pressure the Trump administration into removing a question about citizenship from the 2020 census questionnaire. Representative Gerald Connolly said that when Democrats assume leadership of the House of Representatives in January, they plan to call Commerce Secretary Wilbur Ross to testify about the citizenship question, which has spurred criticism and lawsuits. Ross earlier "lied to Congress" about why the question was added to the census, Connolly told Reuters in an int...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Kamala Harris aide resigns after harassment accusations surface - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/06/politics/larry-wallace-kamala-harris-resignation/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJuxMnF6BX41yOlF_ybnQMAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMJrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 14:33:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/06/politics/larry-wallace-kamala-harris-resignation/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Kamala Harris aide resigns after harassment accusations surface&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;California Democratic Sen. Kamala Harris accepted the resignation of one of her staffers, Larry Wallace, on Wednesday after accusations of harassment surfaced from the time that he was working for her at the California Department of Justice. "We were unaware of this issue and take accusations of harassment extremely seriously. This evening, Mr. Wallace offered his resignation to the senator and she accepted it," Lily Adams, Harris's spokeswoman told CNN in a statement. Wallace resigned after the The Sacramento Bee inquired about a $400,000 harassment and retaliation settlement from his time...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>House Dems just had their best election since Watergate - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/06/politics/2018-house-democratic-gains/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB25deFfG6HPrp9fSaKdl-8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 00:31:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/06/politics/2018-house-democratic-gains/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;House Dems just had their best election since Watergate&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The end came just before 5 p.m. Eastern Time on December 6, 2018. "Despite the outcome of this election, we must remain deliberate in our efforts to improve our community," said California Rep. David Valadao (R) in conceding his 21st District House seat. "There is always work to be completed and I can't wait to see what else our community can accomplish." With that, the 2018 election has all but ended. And not a moment too soon for Republicans who, with Valadao's defeat, lost 40 seats -- and their House majority. (As the Cook Political Report's David Wasserman notes, the 9.7 million raw vot...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Democratic 2020 campaign revving up quickly - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/122d7e0fd8cf402e8533a07c737d064b</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJpgtgA3kYdemRTEi4WQHlcqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwu4lR</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 05:19:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/122d7e0fd8cf402e8533a07c737d064b" target="_blank"&gt;Democratic 2020 campaign revving up quickly&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Democrats are hitting fast forward. The first major presidential campaign announcements could come before year's end. The Democratic National Committee plans to announce a debate framework by then featuring 15 to 20 candidates. The first primary debate could happen as early as May, a full three months before the premiere debate of the 2016 cycle. And long-rumored White House hopefuls are already bowing out. Like it or not, the 2020 presidential season has arrived. For some potential contenders, there's an increasing sense of urgency to be in the first wave of declared candid...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Michigan Republicans following Wisconsin's lead in curbing Democrats' power - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-politics-states/michigan-republicans-following-wisconsins-lead-in-curbing-democrats-power-idUSKBN1O5289</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECjGhR0uhlP6X14PLhjwXkkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 23:00:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-politics-states/michigan-republicans-following-wisconsins-lead-in-curbing-democrats-power-idUSKBN1O5289" target="_blank"&gt;Michigan Republicans following Wisconsin's lead in curbing Democrats' power&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A day after Wisconsin Republicans approved a package of bills intended to restrict the powers of incoming Democratic leaders, Republican lawmakers in Michigan advanced a similar effort despite an outcry from Democrats. The Michigan state Senate voted on Thursday to strip the power to oversee campaign finance from the newly elected Democratic secretary of state, Jocelyn Benson, instead handing the authority to a bipartisan commission. The vote came after the state House of Representatives on Wednesday passed a bill that would allow lawmakers to sidestep the attorney general in litigation inv...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item></channel></rss>