<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Golden Globe Award - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIggKIhxDQkFTRHdvSkwyMHZNREV4WHpkZkVnSmxiaWdBUAE?hl=en-NG&amp;gl=NG&amp;ceid=NG:en</link><language>en-NG</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 13:15:03 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Hollywood awards season kicks off with Golden Globes nominations - Pulse Nigeria</title><link>https://www.pulse.ng/entertainment/movies/hollywood-awards-season-kicks-off-with-golden-globes-noms-id9172503.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">52780126894879</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 14:43:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.pulse.ng/entertainment/movies/hollywood-awards-season-kicks-off-with-golden-globes-noms-id9172503.html" target="_blank"&gt;Hollywood awards season kicks off with Golden Globes nominations&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Pulse Nigeria&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.bellanaija.com/2018/12/black-panther-lady-gaga-regina-king-mahershala-ali-nominated-for-2019-golden-globes-see-full-list/" target="_blank"&gt;Black Panther, Lady Gaga, Regina King, Mahershala Ali Nominated for 2019 Golden Globes | See Full List&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;BellaNaija&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://comicbook.com/marvel/2018/12/07/black-panther-golden-globes-nominations-chadwick-boseman-thanks/" target="_blank"&gt;Chadwick Boseman Thanks HFPA for ‘Black Panther’ Golden Globes Nominations&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Comicbook.com&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JPWZs16K14E" target="_blank"&gt;Golden Globes 2019 Nominations: Snubs And Surprises&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;International Business Times UK&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://popculture.com/tv-shows/2018/12/07/golden-globe-2019-biggest-nomination-surprises/" target="_blank"&gt;Golden Globe 2019: Biggest Nomination Surprises&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;PopCulture.com&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/stories/CAAqbAgKImZDQklTUmpvSmMzUnZjbmt0TXpZd1Nqa0tFUWlmOXR1bGpZQU1FUTltYV9RSkVFZE1FaVF5TURFNUlFZHZiR1JsYmlCSGJHOWlaU0J1YjIxcGJtVmxjeUJoYm01dmRXNWpaV1FvQUFQAQ?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;View full coverage on Google News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;</description><source url="https://www.pulse.ng">Pulse Nigeria</source></item><item><title>Sandra Oh and Andy Samberg will team up to host 2019 Golden Globe Awards - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/05/entertainment/2019-golden-globes-hosts-sandra-oh-andy-samberg/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENVu_ohPyKKgShjTv_KkFHkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMNHPpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 11:50:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/05/entertainment/2019-golden-globes-hosts-sandra-oh-andy-samberg/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Sandra Oh and Andy Samberg will team up to host 2019 Golden Globe Awards&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oh, yes. On the eve of Golden Globe nominations, the Hollywood Foreign Press Association announced it has tapped "Killing Eve" star Sandra Oh and "Brooklyn Nine-Nine's" Andy Samberg to host the 2019 awards ceremony. It will mark Oh and Samberg's first time co-hosting together, but it will not be their first time appearing on a big stage side by side. Oh and Samberg presented an award together at the Emmy Awards in September, executing a well-timed banter that earned their short appearance praise. Apparently, it was enough to earn them an even bigger gig. Samberg previously served as sole ho...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Who got a nod for the Golden Globes - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-07/golden-globes-nominees-announced/10592234</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDqw2bFI3NjQvQnA7IJ2zGAqFwgEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDoiokG</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 22:16:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-07/golden-globes-nominees-announced/10592234" target="_blank"&gt;Who got a nod for the Golden Globes&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Political comedy Vice has led movie nominations for the Golden Globes with six nods, followed by musical A Star is Born, starring Lady Gaga and Bradley Cooper. Historical comedy The Favourite and road trip movie Green Book have also earned multiple nominations. Limited series The Assassination of Gianni Versace won the most nominations in the television category with four nods. The Golden Globes, chosen by the Hollywood Foreign Press Association, will be handed out at a ceremony in Beverly Hills on January 6. Vice, a satirical look at the career of former United States vice-president Dick C...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Sacha Baron Cohen Trolls Sarah Palin With Cheeky Golden Globes Request - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/sacha-baron-cohen-sarah-palin-golden-globes_us_5c0a3ea2e4b04046345ae4eb</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAd9UZrojonxpFQgwEoG7jkqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 10:27:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/sacha-baron-cohen-sarah-palin-golden-globes_us_5c0a3ea2e4b04046345ae4eb" target="_blank"&gt;Sacha Baron Cohen Trolls Sarah Palin With Cheeky Golden Globes Request&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sacha Baron Cohen risked reigniting his feud with former GOP vice presidential candidate Sarah Palin after he cheekily asked her to be his date at the Golden Globes 2019 awards ceremony. Palin slammed the British comedian’s “evil, exploitive, sick ‘humor’” in July after he conducted an interview with her, while in disguise, for his satirical Showtime series “Who Is America?” The segment with the former Alaska governor never actually ended up airing, but credits for the final episode mockingly listed her as “Special Publicity Consultant” because of the coverage the show garnered from her cri...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Golden Globes 2019: Benedict Cumberbatch, Rosamund Pike and 'Bodyguard' lead list of British nominees - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/films/news/golden-globes-2019-nominations-british-uk-richard-madden-bodyguard-emily-blunt-mary-poppins-returns-a8670696.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKJ9kwf7s2-JM-OBY1l8yTIqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 15:06:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/films/news/golden-globes-2019-nominations-british-uk-richard-madden-bodyguard-emily-blunt-mary-poppins-returns-a8670696.html" target="_blank"&gt;Golden Globes 2019: Benedict Cumberbatch, Rosamund Pike and 'Bodyguard' lead list of British nominees&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Golden Globes 2019 nominations are in – and British performers and works have been singled out in several key categories. Benedict Cumberbatch, Rosamund Pike, and Richard Madden are among those in the running to walk away with an award during the ceremony on 6 January. British films and series – or works with significant ties to the UK – have also scored important nominations. Bodyguard, the BBC's acclaimed drama series, is a contender in the Best Television Series – Drama category. It has also earned Madden, who plays the lead role, a nomination for the Best Performance by an Actor in ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Women headline holiday movies but still face 'celluloid ceiling' - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/07/entertainment/women-movies/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELoNdHzzipP3ydgoO2SsqMwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 18:44:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/07/entertainment/women-movies/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Women headline holiday movies but still face 'celluloid ceiling'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Women play starring roles in a flurry of films that will carry through the holiday season. But when it comes to the status of women in Hollywood, as Thursday's Golden Globe nominations suggested, it often feels like there's a step back -- or at least a pause -- for every step forward. A shortage of quality roles for women -- especially older women -- has been a longstanding concern in the movie business, prompting many actresses to migrate to television. Still, this year's roster of year-end films -- many chasing awards consideration -- has yielded what feels like an unusually strong crop o...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>The Latest: 'Vice' director jokes he'll take down 'Poppins' - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/06ef77d066e648dab650e6a34d14fb63</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDianogqIhKgLNJYpjnxmwIqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwu4lR</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 17:14:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/06ef77d066e648dab650e6a34d14fb63" target="_blank"&gt;The Latest: 'Vice' director jokes he'll take down 'Poppins'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BEVERLY HILLS, Calif. (AP) — The Latest on the announcement of nominations for the 76th annual Golden Globe Awards in Beverly Hills, California (all times local): 9 a.m. "Vice" director Adam McKay says he's only competitive with one movie in the best comedy or musical film category: "Mary Poppins Returns." Speaking from London about his film's leading six Golden Globe nominations Thursday, McKay deadpanned that "we will take 'Mary Poppins' out." He added: "Dick Cheney is going for her." McKay's film about the former vice president also got nominations for stars Christian Bale, Amy Adams and...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Golden Globes 2019: Vice leads pack with six nominations - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/film/2018/dec/06/golden-globes-2019-vice-leads-pack-with-six-nominations</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEArxQFUk2yz9LzHmYgWUU5IqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCOvRU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 14:02:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/film/2018/dec/06/golden-globes-2019-vice-leads-pack-with-six-nominations" target="_blank"&gt;Golden Globes 2019: Vice leads pack with six nominations&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dick Cheney may never have officially ruled over America, but Vice, a new biopic about the power-hungry politician, is the surprise leader going into next year’s Golden Globe awards. The comedy stars Christian Bale – who gained 40lb and wears a bald-cap for the role – as George W Bush’s deputy, and has been nominated for best actor, best director, best motion picture (comedy or musical), best screenplay, best supporting actor (for Sam Rockwell, who plays Bush), and best supporting actress (for Amy Adams, who plays Cheney’s wife Lynne). The film is the Anchorman director Adam McKay’s follow-...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Constance Wu Had A Crazy, Funny Reaction To Her Golden Globe Nomination - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/constance-wu-was-pretty-much-the-last-person-to-know-about-her-golden-globe-nomination_us_5c094cd6e4b069028dc79190</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIful8Sw-36iTjH6zYyU9gYqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/constance-wu-was-pretty-much-the-last-person-to-know-about-her-golden-globe-nomination_us_5c094cd6e4b069028dc79190" target="_blank"&gt;Constance Wu Had A Crazy, Funny Reaction To Her Golden Globe Nomination&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was a quite the morning for “Crazy Rich Asians” star Constance Wu to have her phone on silent. The actress scored a Golden Globe nomination for Best Actress in a Motion Picture - Musical or Comedy on Thursday morning for her work in the Jon M. Chu-directed romantic comedy that swept audiences off their feet and into movie theater seats. But Wu revealed she had her phone on “Do Not Disturb” all morning, which led to all her “Crazy Rich Asians” co-stars sending over congratulations before she even found out she was nominated. “I’m ecstatic but also in shock!” she wrote on Twitter after the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>'Black Panther' Is First Superhero Movie To Score Golden Globes Best Picture Drama Nod - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/black-panther-golden-globes-nomination-best-picture_us_5c093af7e4b069028dc75389</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHXTXB3HaB9dmqMDnwMMHxgqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 16:52:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/black-panther-golden-globes-nomination-best-picture_us_5c093af7e4b069028dc75389" target="_blank"&gt;'Black Panther' Is First Superhero Movie To Score Golden Globes Best Picture Drama Nod&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The history-making “Black Panther” just made history again. The Ryan Coogler-directed film has become the first superhero movie to be nominated for best picture in the drama category at the Golden Globes. A slew of stars, including the film’s own Danai Gurira, announced on Thursday the nominations for the 76th annual ceremony to be held in January in Beverly Hills, California. The film, which became the highest-grossing solo superhero film to date earning $1.3 billion worldwide, was also nominated for best original song for Kendrick Lamar’s “All The Stars” featuring SZA and best original sc...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Golden Globes 2019: Here's The Full List Of Nominations - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/golden-globes-2019-heres-the-full-list-of-nominations_us_5c084527e4b069028dc63cb4</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJvr3TFIUm_XuPzxaTAw1tUqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMKOXAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 12:55:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/golden-globes-2019-heres-the-full-list-of-nominations_us_5c084527e4b069028dc63cb4" target="_blank"&gt;Golden Globes 2019: Here's The Full List Of Nominations&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;There can be 100 people in the room ― but all it takes is 90-plus foreign journalists from the Hollywood Foreign Press Association to believe in you to get a Golden Globe. Ready or not, awards season has officially arrived with the nominations for the 76th annual Golden Globes to be hosted by Andy Samberg and Sandra Oh announced at the Beverly Hilton Hotel in Beverly Hills, California, on Thursday morning. Golden Globes winners are chosen by international journalists based in Southern California who cover the entertainment industry. Terry Crews, Danai Gurira, Leslie Mann, and Christian Slat...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Golden Globes 2019: 10 of the biggest snubs - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/films/news/golden-globes-snubs-surprises-nominations-2019-full-list-westworld-widows-jane-the-virgin-atlanta-a8671301.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELwY6MqDu0DU-8NZwjwNK2gqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCRx_0F</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 18:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/films/news/golden-globes-snubs-surprises-nominations-2019-full-list-westworld-widows-jane-the-virgin-atlanta-a8671301.html" target="_blank"&gt;Golden Globes 2019: 10 of the biggest snubs&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This year's Golden Globes nominations singled out deserving films and TV series – but some of the most acclaimed works of the past 12 months failed to make the cut. Fans of Vice will be thrilled to see the film as one of the frontrunners in this year's pool of nominees. The inclusion of Black Panther and Pose, two works of important cultural significance, were saluted – and rightfully so. Some, however, lamented the exclusion of works such as Steve McQueen's Widows, as well as TV shows Atlanta and Maniac, from the list. Here are 10 of the most significant snubs from this year's Golden Globe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Golden Globes 2019 nominations in full as Vice, A Star is Born and The Favourite dominate - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/films/news/golden-globes-nominations-2019-full-list-star-is-born-lady-gaga-roma-favourite-a8669991.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAMyID1KMMrg9Bw4P0eSLf8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 14:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/films/news/golden-globes-nominations-2019-full-list-star-is-born-lady-gaga-roma-favourite-a8669991.html" target="_blank"&gt;Golden Globes 2019 nominations in full as Vice, A Star is Born and The Favourite dominate&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nominations for 2019's Golden Globes have been revealed in full – celebrating the very best in the worlds of both film and television. Adam McKay's Dick Cheney film, Vice, surprisingly leads the pack with six nominations, ahead of more expected fair like A Star Is Born, The Favourite and Green Book, which all have five nominations each. Nominations were more widely spread in the television categories, with The Assassination of Gianni Versace: American Crime Story in the lead with four nominations. You can catch up with the biggest talking points from the awards here. Golden Globes 2019 ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Politics, race, music dominate diverse Golden Globe film nominations - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-awards-goldenglobes-nominations/politics-race-music-dominate-diverse-golden-globe-film-nominations-idUSKBN1O51JE</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELYKXr3QyhuWBaPPi7k2W8YqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 20:30:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-awards-goldenglobes-nominations/politics-race-music-dominate-diverse-golden-globe-film-nominations-idUSKBN1O51JE" target="_blank"&gt;Politics, race, music dominate diverse Golden Globe film nominations&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Movies about race, politics and music dominated nominations for the Golden Globe awards on Thursday, setting the stage for a lively Hollywood awards season leading up to the Oscars in February. Dark comedy "Vice," a scathing look at the rise to power of former U.S. Vice President Dick Cheney, led all comers with six nods. It was followed by the Lady Gaga musical remake of "A Star is Born," British historical comedy "The Favourite" and road trip movie through 1960s segregated America "Green Book" with five nods apiece. Several expected contenders, including female-led heist thriller "Widows,...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Constance Wu's Golden Globe nomination is a big deal - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/06/entertainment/crazy-rich-asians-constance-wu-golden-globe-nomination/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDB3aCVqVm_ycPpK82RXuvwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMNHPpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 17:38:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/06/entertainment/crazy-rich-asians-constance-wu-golden-globe-nomination/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Constance Wu's Golden Globe nomination is a big deal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;As Constance Wu and "Crazy Rich Asians" scored Golden Globe nominations on Thursday morning, the reaction from large corners of the Internet was one of crazy excitement. "Crazy Rich Asians" was nominated for best comedy or musical, and Wu was nominated for best performance by an actress in a musical or comedy motion picture. Both accomplishments can be seen as significant moments for an industry that has scrambled to catch up to a movie audience hungry for inclusive stories. Wu's nomination is also notable on its own, as it ends a streak that has lasted almost half a century. The last perso...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Golden Globes 2019: full list of nominations - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/films/0/golden-globes-2019-full-list-nominations/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB-QFmPTQIJOYtKmiXY_idsqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDf2rcF</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 14:02:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/films/0/golden-globes-2019-full-list-nominations/" target="_blank"&gt;Golden Globes 2019: full list of nominations&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Awards season is officially off to the races with today’s Golden Globe Awards nominations. The Hollywood Foreign Press Association (HFPA) announced late last night that Killing Eve actress Sandra Oh and Brooklyn Nine-Nine actor-comedian Andy Samberg would be hosting the awards ceremony, which are often seen as a predictor of the Oscars (although the Globes hands out awards for both film and TV). The pair had presented the Emmy for Best Direction of a Comedy Series in September, and had a crackling comedic spark. Last year's nominees included the films The Post, Three Billboards Outside Ebbi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Factbox: Key film nominees for the 2019 Golden Globe awards - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-awards-goldenglobes-nominations-list-idUSKBN1O51KH</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG2yNT_DbbJ-bL9qsCqVKtAqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 15:46:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-awards-goldenglobes-nominations-list-idUSKBN1O51KH" target="_blank"&gt;Factbox: Key film nominees for the 2019 Golden Globe awards&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nominations were announced on Thursday for the 2019 Golden Globe awards for movies and television. The Golden Globes, organized by the Hollywood Foreign Press Association, will be presented at a gala dinner hosted by Canadian actress Sandra Oh and U.S. comedian Andy Samberg in Beverly Hills, California, on Jan. 6. Following is a list of key film nominations: BEST DRAMA "A Star is Born" "Bohemian Rhapsody" "If Beale Street Could Talk" "Black Panther" "BlacKkKlansman" BEST COMEDY OR MUSICAL "Mary Poppins Returns" "Crazy Rich Asians" "The Favourite" "Green Book" "Vice" BEST ACTOR, DRAMA Bradle...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>'Black Panther' breaks through at Golden Globes, with an eye on Oscars - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/06/entertainment/black-panther-golden-globes/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI9TJaz9INzOUTuiAIxzwd4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 15:16:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/06/entertainment/black-panther-golden-globes/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;'Black Panther' breaks through at Golden Globes, with an eye on Oscars&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Black Panther" is looking like the answer to Hollywood's prayers as the industry embarks on awards season, adding blockbuster sizzle to an annual ritual that has been reluctant to acknowledge its costume-clad box-office stars. With its latest accolades -- a Golden Globe nomination as outstanding drama on Thursday, and recognition from the American Film Institute's annual 10-best list -- the next hurdle would be the Academy Awards, which would represent a breakthrough for superhero movies. Already the third-highest-grossing movie of all time in the US, behind only "Star Wars: The Force Awak...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Julia Roberts, more movie stars snare Golden Globe TV nods - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/e76b7e5827fe417f875d0b5d2ae8c25d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEVKluK0zhroHrj_tJ3muSwqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwruxQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 20:53:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/e76b7e5827fe417f875d0b5d2ae8c25d" target="_blank"&gt;Julia Roberts, more movie stars snare Golden Globe TV nods&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — Even the sometimes-offbeat Golden Globe Awards are unable to resist the allure of movie stars who dabble in television work. Julia Roberts, Amy Adams, Jim Carrey and Michael Douglas were among the nominees announced Thursday for next month's awards voted by the Hollywood Foreign Press Association. Television's increasing artistic prestige has persuaded more big-screen talent to add it to their portfolio. But not every film actor made the awards cut, with Emma Stone and Jonah Hill out of the running for Netflix's "Maniac." Also snubbed was "This Is Us," one of the few broa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>19 Biggest Golden Globes Snubs and Surprises: ‘Atlanta,’ Sacha Baron Cohen and More - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/19-biggest-golden-globes-snubs-and-surprises-atlanta-sacha-baron-cohen-and-more</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ6dty-ajbaCrmjcUi0h3z0qFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMKv-lwI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 15:29:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/19-biggest-golden-globes-snubs-and-surprises-atlanta-sacha-baron-cohen-and-more" target="_blank"&gt;19 Biggest Golden Globes Snubs and Surprises: ‘Atlanta,’ Sacha Baron Cohen and More&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photo Illustration by Sarah Rogers/The Daily Beast The Golden Globe Award nominations are, as always, absurd. A perpetually-mystifying exhibit of stargazing and idiosyncratic taste, it’s not uncommon for some of the worst films and TV series of the year to score huge nominations while future Oscar winners are left off completely. The Hollywood Foreign Press gonna do the Hollywood Foreign Press. This year’s nominations have their fair share of the admirable and the baffling, depending on your love for Queen, Dick Cheney, and priests grappling with global-warming paranoia—Bohemian Rhapsody sc...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>No Sam Elliott and more Golden Globes nomination shockers - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/644783d99f9747e2b16cca7e838fd942</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECW6CyZ8eu5vEEszl92cA20qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwruxQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 17:12:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/644783d99f9747e2b16cca7e838fd942" target="_blank"&gt;No Sam Elliott and more Golden Globes nomination shockers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — There's no such thing as a sure thing when it comes to the mercurial Hollywood Foreign Press Association and its Golden Globe nominations, but this year saw a number of surprises, like the dominance of Adam McKay's Dick Cheney film "Vice," and a number of truly shocking exclusions. ___ THEY CHOSE THE WRONG SAM This was supposed to be Sam Elliott's year. The veteran character actor delivered a powerful performance as Jackson Maine's brother in "A Star Is Born," which many still think will earn the 74-year-old his first ever Oscar nomination. But the HFPA had a different pl...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Political Comedy 'Vice' Leads Golden Globe Film Nominations with 6 Nods - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/political-comedy-vice-leads-golden-globe-film-nominations-with-6-nods/4689367.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG50FFv2_l2E5i1aN6f1xH0qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwmp0i</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 15:49:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/political-comedy-vice-leads-golden-globe-film-nominations-with-6-nods/4689367.html" target="_blank"&gt;Political Comedy 'Vice' Leads Golden Globe Film Nominations with 6 Nods&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Political comedy "Vice" led movie nominations for the Golden Globes on Thursday with six nods, followed by musical "A Star is Born," historical comedy. "The Favourite" and road trip movie "Green Book" with five nods apiece. Limited FX series "The Assassination of Gianni Versace" won the most nominations in the television category with four nods. The Golden Globes, chosen by the small Hollywood Foreign Press Association, will be handed out at a ceremony in Beverly Hills on Jan 6. "Vice," a satirical look at the career of former U.S. Vice President Dick Cheney, won nominations in all major ca...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Golden Globes 2019 nominations: Vice leads pack, Widows snubbed – and 6 other talking points - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/golden-globes-2019-nominations-live-full-list-time-date-when-favourites-predictions-a8669871.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB8zguK9Z8FE4VRnsZMW_44qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 14:44:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/golden-globes-2019-nominations-live-full-list-time-date-when-favourites-predictions-a8669871.html" target="_blank"&gt;Golden Globes 2019 nominations: Vice leads pack, Widows snubbed – and 6 other talking points&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Awards season has officially kicked into gear with the announcement of the Golden Globe nominations – the full list of which you can find here. The films and television shows vying for success at the annual awards ceremony were revealed today (6 December) by Terry Crews, Leslie Mann, Christian Slater and The Walking Dead star Danai Gurira who earned acclaim this year for her role in Black Panther. Below are the main talking points from the list of nominees, including new frontrunner Vice, the success of hit BBC series Bodyguard and the continued lack of women directors. Bale’s Cheney biopic...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Dick Cheney biopic 'Vice' tops Golden Globes nominations - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/d47620b3896e4f47b82aac1ec5069554</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDd4yDcF5fyloeYzUVKKUxEqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwu4lR</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 22:41:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/d47620b3896e4f47b82aac1ec5069554" target="_blank"&gt;Dick Cheney biopic 'Vice' tops Golden Globes nominations&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Adam McKay's Dick Cheney biopic "Vice" staged an awards-season coup Thursday, landing a leading six nominations from the 76th annual Golden Globe Awards to narrowly edge more expected favorites like Bradley Cooper's tear-jerking revival "A Star Is Born," the interracial road-trip drama "Green Book" and the period romp "The Favourite." "Vice" topped all contenders in the nominations that were announced at the Beverly Hilton Hotel in Beverly Hills, California, including best picture, comedy and best actor nominations for Christian Bale's nearly unrecognizable performance as th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Factbox: With pride, shock, stars react to Golden Globe nominations - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-awards-goldenglobes-nominations-react-idUSKBN1O51YH</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHoeGB7mEzNXVamlumpbzesqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 20:30:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-awards-goldenglobes-nominations-react-idUSKBN1O51YH" target="_blank"&gt;Factbox: With pride, shock, stars react to Golden Globe nominations&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A satirical political comedy, two racial injustice films, a superhero epic, biographies and musicals were among the crop of movies and TV shows that earned Golden Globe nominations on Thursday. Following are some reactions through statements, phone calls and social media to the nominations, which are chosen by the Hollywood Foreign Press Association. Bradley Cooper, best actor and best director nominee for "A Star is Born" "I am very grateful 'A Star is Born' has touched so many people. ... I wanted to tell stories through film for as long as I can remember and I feel lucky even to have had...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Sandra Oh and Andy Samberg announced as Golden Globes hosts - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/films/2018/12/06/sandra-oh-andy-samberg-announced-golden-globes-hosts/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEf-4phZWPIpYh_KTQ8ra6AqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDf2rcF</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 07:50:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/films/2018/12/06/sandra-oh-andy-samberg-announced-golden-globes-hosts/" target="_blank"&gt;Sandra Oh and Andy Samberg announced as Golden Globes hosts&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sandra Oh and Andy Samberg will share host duties at the Golden Globe Awards. On Wednesday , producers announced the co-hosts for the ceremony, which will take place on January 6. The Globes are hosted by the Hollywood Foreign Press Association, which presents awards for film and TV. Nominees will be announced Thursday morning. Oh won a 2006 Golden Globe for Grey's Anatomy. This year, she became the first actress of Asian ethnicity to receive an Emmy nomination for drama series lead, for Killing Eve. Samberg won two Golden Globes in 2014 for Brooklyn Nine-Nine, for best comedy actor and as ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Golden Globes 2019: Who might be nominated for the film and TV awards? - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/films/news/golden-globes-2019-nominations-list-awards-movies-tv-a-star-is-born-first-man-a8666161.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFBTz4TuiMx3vVjPcdwarvgqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 08:16:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/films/news/golden-globes-2019-nominations-list-awards-movies-tv-a-star-is-born-first-man-a8666161.html" target="_blank"&gt;Golden Globes 2019: Who might be nominated for the film and TV awards?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nominations for the 76th Golden Globe Awards will be announced on 6 December 2018. The ceremony itself will be held in Hollywood on 7 January 2019, hosted by Sandra Oh and Andy Samberg and kick off cinema’s awards season in earnest, establishing the early front runners ahead of the BAFTAs and Academy Awards. Here’s how you can follow Thursday’s event in Los Angeles and our best guesses as to who might be in contention. How can I follow the Golden Globe nominations? The Independent‘s Culture team will be liveblogging the big reveal on our site from 1pm. The Hollywood Foreign Press Associatio...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Nicole Kidman and more react to Golden Globe nominations - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/06/entertainment/golden-globes-reactions-2019/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKpLicaZkuWzxubXz-C9_CsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMNHPpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 19:51:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/06/entertainment/golden-globes-reactions-2019/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Nicole Kidman and more react to Golden Globe nominations&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hollywood woke up to Golden Globe nominations news on Thursday morning. The lucky nominees are celebrating and here's a sample of their reactions: Nicole Kidman, Best Performance by an Actress in a Motion Picture, Drama for "Destroyer" "I am so grateful to be nominated for such an untraditional female character. Erin Bell is complicated, raw and dangerous, and it was a privilege to portray her. I share this with Karyn Kusama as well as all of the cast and crew. It was truly a passion project for all of us. A huge thank you to The Hollywood Foreign Press." Emily Blunt, Best Actress in a Moti...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Golden Globes 2019 nominations: the full list - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/film/2018/dec/06/full-list-of-nominations-for-golden-globes-2019</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOy_Lvrfin3Qh7IE6glFrtoqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCOvRU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 14:08:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/film/2018/dec/06/full-list-of-nominations-for-golden-globes-2019" target="_blank"&gt;Golden Globes 2019 nominations: the full list&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Film Best film – drama Black Panther BlacKkKlansman Bohemian Rhapsody If Beale Street Could Talk A Star Is Born Best actress – drama Glenn Close – The Wife Lady Gaga – A Star Is Born Nicole Kidman – Destroyer Melissa McCarthy – Can You Ever Forgive Me? Rosamund Pike – A Private War Best actor – drama Bradley Cooper – A Star Is Born Willem Dafoe – At Eternity’s Gate Lucas Hedges – Boy Erased Rami Malek – Bohemian Rhapsody John David Washington – BlacKkKlansman Nominated for best supporting actor … Mahershala Ali in Green Book. Photograph: Universal Pictures/AP Best supporting actress Amy Ada...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Golden Globe Nominations: ‘Vice’ Leads with 6 Nods - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/amy-adams-patricia-arquette-and-connie-britton-lead-golden-globe-nominations</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENUHa6d2-5Kw_fzHtBPzqRoqFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMLXUiQY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 13:32:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/amy-adams-patricia-arquette-and-connie-britton-lead-golden-globe-nominations" target="_blank"&gt;Golden Globe Nominations: ‘Vice’ Leads with 6 Nods&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Danny Moloshok / Reuters Amy Adams, Patricia Arquette, Connie Britton, Laura Dern and Regina King lead Thursday’s Golden Globe nominations announcement, as all of them vie for Best Actress in a Limited Series or TV Movie. Alan Arkin, Kieran Culkin, Edgar Ramirez, Ben Whishaw, and Henry Winkler will compete for Best Actor in a Limited Series or TV Movie. Barry, The Good Place, Kidding, The Kominsky Method, and The Marvelous Mrs. Maisel will go head-to-head in the Best Comedy TV Series category. Earlier this week, Sandra Oh and Andy Samberg were announced as the evening’s hosts. The Alienist,...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>For absolutely no reason, here are 29 women directors who made outstanding films in 2018 - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90277567/for-absolutely-no-reason-here-are-29-women-directors-who-made-outstanding-films-in-2018</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAO7yPGukxWsDSo22wA5CAQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOGbAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 11:50:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90277567/for-absolutely-no-reason-here-are-29-women-directors-who-made-outstanding-films-in-2018" target="_blank"&gt;For absolutely no reason, here are 29 women directors who made outstanding films in 2018&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Earlier this year, Lady Bird filmmaker Greta Gerwig became the fifth woman in history ever to be nominated for a Best Director Oscar. Ever! That’s one hand!” she told USA Today, summing up the sadly small club she’d just entered. Although the argument for better female representation behind the camera has been raging for years, the glaring rareness of Gerwig’s achievement became a flashpoint. Of all the great movies ever made by women, how could only a single handful ever have been deemed worthy of nomination? (And with only one winner!) Headlines seized on the unfortunate notoriety of Gerw...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcompany.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>Golden Globes 2019: Andy Samberg and Sandra Oh named as hosts for awards ceremony - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/films/news/golden-globes-2019-andy-samberg-sandra-oh-hosts-presenters-nominations-date-when-a8669926.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAOWFNcFNcs7SSSKKo3QEOEqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 09:03:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/films/news/golden-globes-2019-andy-samberg-sandra-oh-hosts-presenters-nominations-date-when-a8669926.html" target="_blank"&gt;Golden Globes 2019: Andy Samberg and Sandra Oh named as hosts for awards ceremony&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Canadian actress Sandra Oh and US comedian Andy Samberg have been named as the hosts of the 2019 Golden Globe Awards, the organisers have announced. The pair, who recently presented a prize at the Emmy awards, will the making their debut as hosts for the ceremony, which is due to take place at the Beverly Hills Hilton on January 6. Nominations for the awards, which honour the film the television industries, will be announced on Thursday. “Sandra and Andy are the perfect choices to host this world-class event,” Paul Telegdy and George Cheeks, co-chairmen of NBC Entertainment, said in a state...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Golden Globe Nominees 2019: The Full List - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/natalierobehmed/2018/12/06/golden-globe-nominees-2019-the-full-list/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPrdOJ70KLrjxRYBKm8SJd0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 13:31:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/natalierobehmed/2018/12/06/golden-globe-nominees-2019-the-full-list/" target="_blank"&gt;Golden Globe Nominees 2019: The Full List&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amy Adams was nominated for Best Actress in a limited series or TV movie for her role in “Sharp Objects.” The Hollywood Foreign Press Association (HFPA) today announced its nominees for 2018′s best movies and television shows ahead of January’s 76th Golden Globe Awards. Nominations were selected by the roughly 90 members of the HFPA, a Los Angeles-based group of journalists. New to the show this year: A special achievement award to honor TV’s biggest names and brightest talents for outstanding accomplishments. The 76th Annual Golden Globe Awards ceremony will air on NBC on Sunday, January 6...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Sandra Oh, Andy Samberg to host Golden Globe ceremony - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/e05180330ee44921ae38351761da576c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG0Ru0qN7vN9o8DaQsETmQoqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwruxQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 01:55:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/e05180330ee44921ae38351761da576c" target="_blank"&gt;Sandra Oh, Andy Samberg to host Golden Globe ceremony&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — Sandra Oh and Andy Samberg will share host duties at the Golden Globe Awards. Producers on Wednesday announced the co-hosts for the Jan. 6 ceremony. The Globes are hosted by the Hollywood Foreign Press Association, which presents awards for film and TV. Nominees will be announced Thursday morning. Oh won a 2006 Golden Globe for "Grey's Anatomy." This year, she became the first actress of Asian ethnicity to receive an Emmy nomination for drama series lead, for "Killing Eve." Samberg won two Golden Globes in 2014 for "Brooklyn Nine-Nine," for best comedy actor and as a prod...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Factbox: Key television nominations for the 2019 Golden Globe awards - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-awards-goldenglobes-nominations-telev/factbox-key-television-nominations-for-the-2019-golden-globe-awards-idUSKBN1O51RZ</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELDNdLevffEzgT7gosJO-YkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 15:14:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-awards-goldenglobes-nominations-telev/factbox-key-television-nominations-for-the-2019-golden-globe-awards-idUSKBN1O51RZ" target="_blank"&gt;Factbox: Key television nominations for the 2019 Golden Globe awards&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nominations were announced on Thursday for the 2019 Golden Globe awards for movies and television. The Golden Globes, organized by the Hollywood Foreign Press Association, will be presented on Jan. 6 at a gala dinner hosted by Canadian actress Sandra Oh and U.S. comedian Andy Samberg in Beverly Hills, California. Following is a list of key television nominations: BEST TV DRAMA SERIES "The Americans" - FX "Bodyguard" - Netflix "Homecoming" - Amazon Prime "Killing Eve" - BBC America "Pose" - FX BEST TV COMEDY/MUSICAL SERIES "Barry" - HBO "The Good Place" - NBC "Kidding" - Showtime "The Komins...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Golden Globes 2019: it's Dick Cheney v Lady Gaga in a surreal title fight - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/film/2018/dec/06/golden-globes-2019-vice-lady-gaga-favourite-nominations</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJfVgVCHUxHzNPx0T3XjOvMqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 17:34:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/film/2018/dec/06/golden-globes-2019-vice-lady-gaga-favourite-nominations" target="_blank"&gt;Golden Globes 2019: it's Dick Cheney v Lady Gaga in a surreal title fight&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;While the critical consensus has been building around A Star Is Born, Roma and The Favourite, the Golden Globes nomination list has launched a surprise new frontrunner. Leading the field with six nods, including actor and director, is Adam McKay’s enjoyable, if flashily self-aware political comedy Vice, with its glowering portrayal of former vice-president, big oil nabob and war-on-terror enthusiast Dick Cheney, who the film shows effectively leading America throughout the presidency of George W Bush. Christian Bale has put on considerable amounts of weight and latex for the role and the re...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Black films show up strong in Golden Globe noms - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/06/entertainment/black-films-golden-globes/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHC1MSrISADRgC_Tlv-DCiAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 15:27:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/06/entertainment/black-films-golden-globes/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Black films show up strong in Golden Globe noms&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nominations for the 76th Golden Golden Globe Awards showcase strong work by black directors this past year. "Black Panther," "BlacKkKlansman" and "If Beale Street Could Talk" were all directed by black men -- Ryan Coogler, Spike Lee and Barry Jenkins, respectively. The films were nominated for top drama, along with "Bohemian Rhapsody" and " A Star Is born." Progress toward inclusion has been notoriously slow in Hollywood, but 2018 has seen some forward momentum. Marvel's "Black Panther" tells the story of the superhero T'Challa/ Black Panther, a new king who must save his homeland of Wa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Kendrick Lamar, Cooper and Lady Gaga earn Golden Globe nods - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/2aa9a53d16834aaa960eed08d64501f8</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP6lFuyMioCSAptDyh8fMQcqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwruxQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 22:30:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/2aa9a53d16834aaa960eed08d64501f8" target="_blank"&gt;Kendrick Lamar, Cooper and Lady Gaga earn Golden Globe nods&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — The Golden Globe nominations recognized Lady Gaga and Bradley Cooper's talents as actors, but Thursday's announcement also came with a nod for their soulful duet "Shallow" from "A Star is Born." They join an impressive roster of music stars who earned Globe nominations Thursday, including Kendrick Lamar, SZA, Dolly Parton, Annie Lennox and Troye Sivan and Jonsi. Cooper and Gaga were each nominated for best drama acting honors for their performances in "A Star is Born," and Cooper also earned a directing nod. "Shallow" co-writer Mark Ronson received his first Golden Globe ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Andy Samberg And Sandra Oh To Host The 2019 Golden Globes - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/andy-samberg-sandra-oh-golden-globes_us_5c084cdfe4b069028dc64354</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEISJXfSPakrQQpbaplE_GAkqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 00:20:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/andy-samberg-sandra-oh-golden-globes_us_5c084cdfe4b069028dc64354" target="_blank"&gt;Andy Samberg And Sandra Oh To Host The 2019 Golden Globes&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Actress Sandra Oh and comedian Andy Samberg will reunite onstage as hosts of the 2019 Golden Globe Awards, set to air Jan. 6 on NBC. In an announcement on Wednesday, NBC Entertainment co-chairmen Paul Telegdy and George Cheeks called Oh and Samberg the “perfect choices” for the prestigious event. “They bring wit, charm and style to a room filled with the very best of film and television,” the executives said. The “Killing Eve” star and “Brooklyn Nine-Nine” comedian stole the show earlier this year while presenting an award at the Emmys together, leaving fans wanting more. Meher Tatna, presi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Golden Globe nominees announced - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/entertainment/2018/12/06/golden-globe-nominees-2019-mxp-vpx.cnn</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJwcRQASx10H-DJhJDPsgs0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 14:29:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/entertainment/2018/12/06/golden-globe-nominees-2019-mxp-vpx.cnn" target="_blank"&gt;Golden Globe nominees announced&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nominations for the 76th Golden Globe Awards have been announced, with movies like "Black Panther," "BlackKKKlansman" "Bohemian Rhapsody," and "A Star is Born" making the cut. ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A WarnerMedia Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Andy Samberg and Sandra Oh to Host 2019 Golden Globes - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/andy-samberg-and-sandra-oh-to-host-2019-golden-globes</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGmtzuKQuR6XNlYvR01GYdwqFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMLXUiQY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 22:40:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/andy-samberg-and-sandra-oh-to-host-2019-golden-globes" target="_blank"&gt;Andy Samberg and Sandra Oh to Host 2019 Golden Globes&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mario Anzuoni/Reuters,Actors Andy Samberg and Sandra Oh are set to host the 2019 Golden Globe Awards on Jan. 6. The surprise duo was locked down with only 32 days to go until the live show airs on NBC. Oh and Samberg presented together at the 2018 Emmys and came through with one of the night’s better comedic offerings. Oh won a Golden Globe in 2006 for her beloved portrayal of doctor Christina Yang on Grey’s Anatomy and was nominated for outstanding lead actress in a drama series last year for her performance in the BBC America drama Killing Eve. Samberg, who stars on the NBC comedy Brookly...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Sandra Oh and Andy Samberg to co-host 2019 Golden Globes - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/film/2018/dec/05/sandra-oh-andy-samberg-2019-golden-globes-co-host</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDCfzfSLBdUtkNCflyVrhkkqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCOvRU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 22:41:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/film/2018/dec/05/sandra-oh-andy-samberg-2019-golden-globes-co-host" target="_blank"&gt;Sandra Oh and Andy Samberg to co-host 2019 Golden Globes&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sandra Oh and Andy Samberg have been announced as hosts of the 2019 Golden Globes. The Killing Eve star and the Brooklyn Nine-Nine comedian will follow in the footsteps of this year’s host, Seth Meyers, next January. The pair presented together at that ceremony, ridiculing the La La Land snafu in a warmly received skit. Related: Oscars host Kevin Hart's homophobia is no laughing matter | Benjamin Lee “We’re excited to welcome Sandra Oh and Andy Samberg as co-hosts of Hollywood’s party of the year,” said the Hollywood Foreign Press Association (HFPA) president, Meher Tatna. “Both Golden Glob...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>How and when to watch the 2019 Golden Globe nominations - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90276302/how-and-when-to-watch-the-2019-golden-globe-nominations</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENAbtdQ81Pr3KFWh9DQZrKAqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOGbAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 06:00:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90276302/how-and-when-to-watch-the-2019-golden-globe-nominations" target="_blank"&gt;How and when to watch the 2019 Golden Globe nominations&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The 76th Annual Golden Globes will kick off awards season on Sunday, January 6, 2019. Before you can start planning your nominee-themed Golden Globes party menu (Atlanta-style barbecue, House of Abundance tablescape inspired by Pose, Barry pie, and Killing Eve cocktails?), you’ll need to know who the actual nominees are. To get a jump on it, tune into the ceremony where the Hollywood Foreign Press Association will announce the nominees for its film and TV awards, which is taking place this week. When are the Golden Globes nomination announcements? The nods will be announced on Thursday, Dec...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcompany.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>Golden Globes could go Gaga for 'popular' films - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/04/entertainment/golden-globes-preview/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMAOhAeqG4HVfl3ztya4yxUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 14:19:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/04/entertainment/golden-globes-preview/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Golden Globes could go Gaga for 'popular' films&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Golden Globe Awards historically have a taste for star power, hit movies, musicals, and international talent. Happily for the broader awards-industrial complex, this year's roster of contenders includes an abundance of all of them, in a year where the Oscars flirted with creating a "popular film" category. The Hollywood Foreign Press Assn., the group of roughly 90 journalists who wield outsized influence because of the Globes, will unveil its annual nominations in movies and TV on Thursday, marking what amounts to the kickoff of an official three-month "awards season," with all the shar...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Nicole Kidman: ‘To hear women being believed makes me cry’ - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/film/2018/dec/02/nicole-kidman-to-hear-women-being-believed-makes-me-cry-destroyer-boy-erased-big-little-lies</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHpY-uZQ3QfPzTcZqN8D5h0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCOvRU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 08:00:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/film/2018/dec/02/nicole-kidman-to-hear-women-being-believed-makes-me-cry-destroyer-boy-erased-big-little-lies" target="_blank"&gt;Nicole Kidman: ‘To hear women being believed makes me cry’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nicole Kidman began this year, her 51st, accepting a Golden Globe award as best actress for her unforgettable role in the TV series Big Little Lies. In her speech she thanked her mother – a nurse who wished she’d been a doctor – for never setting limits on what her daughters could be, declaring: “My achievements are her achievements.” She also paid tribute to her friend Reese Witherspoon, with whom she had produced the series, and the actors they had starred with in it, Laura Dern, Shailene Woodley, Zöe Kravitz. “Wow,” she said, “the power of women!” It seemed like a good moment to be makin...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Idris Elba's daughter named Golden Globe Ambassador - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/32e2ca68912c4a508e64ff99eb5afdb9</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK8S4KV6ZlS6i6Ka3pj_OPwqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwruxQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 02:36:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/32e2ca68912c4a508e64ff99eb5afdb9" target="_blank"&gt;Idris Elba's daughter named Golden Globe Ambassador&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — Idris Elba's daughter has been chosen as the Golden Globe Ambassador to assist with the glitzy awards ceremony. The Hollywood Foreign Press Association announced Wednesday that 16-year-old Isan Elba will assume the ambassador title for the 76th annual Golden Globes Awards in January. Her 46-year-old father was named Sexiest Man Alive by People magazine last week. An ambassador is traditionally the child of a celebrity and assists with award presentations, handing out trophies to winners and escorting them off stage. Elba is the second ambassador chosen after last year's s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Will Smith Teases New 'Aladdin' Movie With First Look At Poster - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/will-smith-teases-new-aladdin-movie_us_5bbec3c6e4b0c8fa1367fbbb</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA7EimJVGRE4DG_YLaCRHTgqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMKOXAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 04:41:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/will-smith-teases-new-aladdin-movie_us_5bbec3c6e4b0c8fa1367fbbb" target="_blank"&gt;Will Smith Teases New 'Aladdin' Movie With First Look At Poster&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Will Smith gave the world its first look at the first tease for the “Aladdin” live-action remake Wednesday when he showed off a cryptic poster on Instagram. The poster shows a magic lamp emitting wisps of blue smoke and says simply, “Choose Wisely.” “LEMME OUT!!” wrote Smith, who plays Genie in the movie. “Can’t wait for y’all to see Me BLUE!” In eight hours, the post received more than 2.6 million “likes” and more than 85,000 comments. The Disney movie, scheduled to hit theaters in May, is a live-action remake of Disney’s 1992 animated version in which Robin Williams voiced the character G...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Drew Barrymore's 'bizarre' interview with inflight magazine: Real or not? - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/04/celebrities/drew-barrymore-inflight-magazine-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEODa_lI4N2U4M2CXqJ9DPZsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2018 12:59:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/04/celebrities/drew-barrymore-inflight-magazine-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Drew Barrymore's 'bizarre' interview with inflight magazine: Real or not?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Having acted since she was a small child, Drew Barrymore is no stranger to the celebrity profile. Few though, have sparked as much attention as what was billed as an interview with the "ET" star in an inflight magazine, which has been described as insulting, grammatically incorrect and fake. Yemen expert Adam Barow first made the discovery on Tuesday, sharing images on Twitter of what he describes as a "surreal" interview in EgyptAir's magazine, Horus, in which the 43-year-old actress is claimed to have made a series of comments on weight loss, motherhood and the status of women. Confusion ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Versace's celebrity admirers - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/style/gallery/versace-celebrities/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHDDCac8HNf1RYvScaGm7n4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMIbnyQU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 14:48:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/style/gallery/versace-celebrities/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Versace's celebrity admirers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Versace has been popular with celebrities from the beginning, when founder Gianni Versace aligned himself with supermodels and Hollywood stars. Here, he poses with Linda Evangelista, Christy Turlington, Claudia Schiffer and Carla Bruni after a 1991 Versace show. PAT/ARNAL/Gamma-Rapho/Getty Images Elton John (wearing Versace) and Donatella Versace in New York in 1991. Sonia Moskowitz/Images/Getty Images Gianni Versace with models Naomi Campbell, Carla Bruni, Karen Mulder, Christy Turlington after the designer's Spring-Summer 1992 show. Bertrand Rindoff Petroff/Getty Images Elizabeth Hurley a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Barbara Harris, Nashville and Freaky Friday actor, dies at 83 - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/film/2018/aug/21/barbara-harris-nashville-freaky-friday-actor-dies-at-83</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEYws_VBqIqzHi3JP0VK0QwqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCOvRU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2018 19:48:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/film/2018/aug/21/barbara-harris-nashville-freaky-friday-actor-dies-at-83" target="_blank"&gt;Barbara Harris, Nashville and Freaky Friday actor, dies at 83&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Barbara Harris, the award-winning star of stage and screen, has died at the age of 83. The actor, who had left the film industry in the 90s, died of lung cancer in Scottsdale, Arizona, where she had lived for many years. Harris was known for roles in Robert Altman’s Nashville, Francis Ford Coppola’s Peggy Sue Got Married and Alfred Hitchcock’s Family Plot. She also played the mother to Jodie Foster in 1976’s Freaky Friday and to John Cusack in 1997’s Grosse Point Blank. She was nominated for a best supporting actress Oscar for her role alongside Dustin Hoffman in 1971’s Who Is Harry Kellerm...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Who's the greatest action hero of all time? We crunched the data - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-08-03/who-is-the-greatest-action-hero-of-all-time-films/10056308</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMN7crrSLPTNwx-jHLeEkhcqFwgEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDoiokG</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 01:03:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-08-03/who-is-the-greatest-action-hero-of-all-time-films/10056308" target="_blank"&gt;Who's the greatest action hero of all time? We crunched the data&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Patrick Wood Bart Simpson might have summed it up best in 1995 when he said: "Want results? You have to go to the Schwarzeneggers, the Stallones, and to a lesser extent, the Van Dammes." These guys were the bona fide action heroes of their time whose flicks were full of stunts, jumps, guns and explosions. A year after Bart uttered those lines Tom Cruise released the first Mission: Impossible film. This week, he's back with his sixth instalment in the franchise and is still running and gunning. It all begs the question: who is the greatest action hero of all time? To determine who should ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Laverne Cox's Style Through The Years, In 45 Glorious Photos - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/laverne-cox-style-evolution_us_5b608cc2e4b0de86f49b54ff</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJlzJhOhE2z5pog9H1xtTBsqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2018 09:45:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/laverne-cox-style-evolution_us_5b608cc2e4b0de86f49b54ff" target="_blank"&gt;Laverne Cox's Style Through The Years, In 45 Glorious Photos&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;If we had to describe Laverne Cox’s style in three words, we’d call it sparkly, sexy and glamorous. Since her early days working in TV, the “Orange Is the New Black” star has had a penchant for glitter, often opting for gowns and minidresses covered in sequins or other sparkling embellishments. In 2013, the year “OITNB” premiered on Netflix, Cox really started letting her inner glamazon shine and stepped up her style game with classic-yet-sexy gowns (like the white number she wore to the 2015 BET Awards). She’s also tried out more trendy pieces, like jumpsuits and Kardashian-esque matching ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Reese Witherspoon pelting ice cream at Meryl Streep is everything - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/08/02/entertainment/reese-witherspoon-ice-cream-meryl-streep-big-little-lies/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPGbO0sYyttyt6QxyYwD-e4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2018 16:22:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/08/02/entertainment/reese-witherspoon-ice-cream-meryl-streep-big-little-lies/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Reese Witherspoon pelting ice cream at Meryl Streep is everything&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reese Witherspoon was caught on camera preparing to throw ice cream at Meryl Streep. But don't worry, they aren't really feuding. The ice cream showdown is apparently for the upcoming second season of "Big Little Lies." And if there were any concerns about Witherspoon's aim, she put them to rest in a tweet on Wednesday. Streep is cast as Mary Louise Wright in the HBO drama, the mother-in-law of Nicole Kidman's character on the show. Related: Nicole Kidman posts first look of Meryl Streep in 'Big Little Lies' The gig marks a rare TV role for Streep, who won an Emmy in 2004 for her work in th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Golden Globe Awards set for Jan. 6, well ahead of Oscars - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/4d51f04ce7b748e0be1e2768a50bf8fb</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEJL1ERnNdgU7xgcqqMgA6AqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwruxQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2018 17:18:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/4d51f04ce7b748e0be1e2768a50bf8fb" target="_blank"&gt;Golden Globe Awards set for Jan. 6, well ahead of Oscars&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — The Hollywood Foreign Press Association says it has picked a date for next year's Golden Globe Awards. The association said Monday that the 76th annual awards ceremony will be held Jan. 6 in Beverly Hills, California, its usual posh setting. Nominations for the Golden Globes movie and television categories will be announced Dec. 6. The Globes, once dismissed by critics for some puzzling movie nominees, increasingly are in step with the Academy Awards. The academy previously announced the Oscars will be held Feb. 24, 2019. The Hollywood Foreign Press Association says its m...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Robin Williams possessions being auctioned in New York to raise funds for charity - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/robin-williams-auction-nyc-daniel-radcliffe-sothebys-charity-possessions-harry-potter-a8457101.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENiTj7iZI3QHshwOdPtMZOsqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2018 16:33:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/robin-williams-auction-nyc-daniel-radcliffe-sothebys-charity-possessions-harry-potter-a8457101.html" target="_blank"&gt;Robin Williams possessions being auctioned in New York to raise funds for charity&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Four years after his death in California’s Paradise City, personal belongings, movie memorabilia and art work belong to Robin Williams are to be auctioned in New York. Sotheby's confirmed that hundreds of items, including paintings by Banksy and up to 40 watches from the Oscar-winning actor’s personal collection will come under the hammer. They will be sold along items belonging to his second wife, the movie producer Marsha Garces Williams, with much of the proceeds going to charities the couple supported. Among the many items that will intrigue and delight film fans, is a so-called Gryffin...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Golden Globe 2 - 500px</title><link>https://500px.com/photo/264444343/golden-globe-2-by-deen-mohammad</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECwEEh7k3jKhvHr9UUFrWgAqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow26UBMPBEMMD7CQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 13:12:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://500px.com/photo/264444343/golden-globe-2-by-deen-mohammad" target="_blank"&gt;Golden Globe 2&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;500px&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;So sorry friends, the previous upload couple of minutes back with same title was a mistake (Repeat) i am very very sorry for your precious time.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://500px.com">500px</source></item><item><title>As Will Young puts two of his Brit Awards up for sale: how much are second-hand awards really worth? - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/music/news/will-young-puts-two-brit-awards-sale-much-second-hand-awards/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDSWzauwMTFKWcCPmZjgWQUqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDW0bcF</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 17:59:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/music/news/will-young-puts-two-brit-awards-sale-much-second-hand-awards/" target="_blank"&gt;As Will Young puts two of his Brit Awards up for sale: how much are second-hand awards really worth?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Singer Will Young, the first person to win Pop Idol, is the latest early noughties’ star to sell on his Brit awards. Young is hoping to offload his two Brit Awards, one for British Breakthrough Act in 2003 and the other for Best Single in 2005, for just £10,000, which might seem a measly amount compared to other celebrity sales. But Young isn’t in it for the money - he’s donating all the proceeds to a dog shelter in Thailand. In a previous interview with the Telegraph, Young hinted that a sale was on the cards. "Paul from S Club 7 sold his Brit for £60,000," he said. "Bloody brilliant. I wa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Oprah Winfrey tells Vogue that a 2020 presidential run 'would kill me' - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/07/03/entertainment/oprah-winfrey-vogue-trnd/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBuIRPN68Zu9UmH8QX2Z02UqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMNHPpgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2018 15:02:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/07/03/entertainment/oprah-winfrey-vogue-trnd/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Oprah Winfrey tells Vogue that a 2020 presidential run 'would kill me'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oprah Winfrey is again dampening speculation that she may be planning to run for president. When she received the Cecil B. DeMille Award for her impact on the world of entertainment at this year's Golden Globe Awards in January, she gave a much-praised speech, saying "a new day is on the horizon." People speculated that she might be thinking about running for president. Many even hoped for Oprah 2020. But Winfrey, 64, tells British Vogue in a new interview that she couldn't stomach a presidential run. Oprah Winfrey on next month's cover of British Vogue. From Vogue UK "In that political str...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Brendan Fraser: Golden Globes Org Called My Sexual Assault 'A Joke' - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/brendan-fraser-sexual-assault_us_5b193633e4b0734a993b971e</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEERdZWh0WPgz7YZ6yDZrCP0qFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 18:24:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/brendan-fraser-sexual-assault_us_5b193633e4b0734a993b971e" target="_blank"&gt;Brendan Fraser: Golden Globes Org Called My Sexual Assault 'A Joke'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brendan Fraser says the organization behind the Golden Globes brushed off his alleged sexual assault at the hands of its former president as “a joke.” The star of the “The Mummy” trilogy and “George of the Jungle” is speaking out again after he told GQ earlier this year that Philip Berk, the former president of the Hollywood Foreign Press Association, groped him at a 2003 luncheon in Beverly Hills. In a new interview published Wednesday, Fraser told GQ’s Zach Baron that the association recently concluded its investigation into the incident by finding Berk’s actions did not constitute sexual...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Nicole Kidman posts first look of Meryl Streep in 'Big Little Lies' - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/04/05/entertainment/meryl-streep-big-little-lies/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF2UdXDFwevTqMkZE-btogcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMNHPpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2018 21:07:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/04/05/entertainment/meryl-streep-big-little-lies/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Nicole Kidman posts first look of Meryl Streep in 'Big Little Lies'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nicole Kidman showed her Instagram followers the first glimpse of Meryl Streep in character from the second season of HBO's "Big Little Lies." "First day on the set with Meryl and 'my' darling boys!" Kidman said in the photo caption. Streep will play Mary Louise Wright, the mother-in-law of Kidman's character, Celeste Wright. The gig marks a rare TV role from Streep, who won an Emmy in 2004 for her part in the HBO miniseries "Angels in America." HBO revealed in January that season two of "Big Little Lies" will pick up with Mary Louise arriving in Monterey, California, after becoming "concer...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Claire Foy on The Crown pay gap dispute: 'It is very, very odd' - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/tv-and-radio/2018/mar/26/claire-foy-on-the-crown-pay-gap-dispute-it-is-very-very-odd</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBIE1BpPjL5UAcce4dEiphsqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 11:03:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/tv-and-radio/2018/mar/26/claire-foy-on-the-crown-pay-gap-dispute-it-is-very-very-odd" target="_blank"&gt;Claire Foy on The Crown pay gap dispute: 'It is very, very odd'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Claire Foy has commented on The Crown gender pay gap dispute, saying she is not surprised the news her co-star Matt Smith was paid more than her has caused so much interest. “I’m surprised because I’m at the centre of it, and anything that I’m at the centre of like that is very very odd, and feels very very out of ordinary,” Foy told Entertainment Weekly. “But I’m not [surprised about the interest in the story] in the sense that it was a female-led drama. I’m not surprised that people saw [the story] and went: ‘Oh, that’s a bit odd.’ But I know that Matt feels the same that I do, that it’s ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Should The Queen In The Crown Sue Netflix Over Her Pay Gap? - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ceciliarodriguez/2018/03/15/should-the-queen-in-the-crown-sue-netflix-over-her-pay-gap/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA2jDvedIXd-Rv4UhvVgFHoqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 19:13:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ceciliarodriguez/2018/03/15/should-the-queen-in-the-crown-sue-netflix-over-her-pay-gap/" target="_blank"&gt;Should The Queen In The Crown Sue Netflix Over Her Pay Gap?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Claire Foy at the 68th Berlinale International Film Festival Photo: Stephane Cardinale/Corbis/Getty Images It all started when Netflix let “the cat out of the bag” early this week at the INTV conference in Jerusalem, admitting that Claire Foy, the actress playing the lead role of Queen Elizabeth in the two first seasons of the ultra-popular series The Crown, was paid far less than her co-star Matt Smith, who portrayed Prince Philip. In Britain the announcement of the pay gap has been received with outrage and, as thousands of fans have taken to social media to express their fury, le...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>In praise of Frances McDormand’s refreshingly low key approach to red carpet style - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/fashion/people/praise-frances-mcdormands-relaxed-approach-red-carpet-style/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJM20bOz4Gj_ULbEDhD1oTwqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCq098D</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Mar 2018 08:02:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/fashion/people/praise-frances-mcdormands-relaxed-approach-red-carpet-style/" target="_blank"&gt;In praise of Frances McDormand’s refreshingly low key approach to red carpet style&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Frances McDormand, star of Three Billboards Outside Ebbing, Missouri, didn’t bother to walk the red carpet before tonight’s Oscars. The first time we got to see anything of the 60 year-old nominee was when the television cameras panned to her, already inside the venue, sitting with her co-stars as host Jimmy Kimmel opened the show. It afforded only a shoulders-up glimpse of her gold intarsia dress. Have you ever heard of such a thing; a Best Actress nominee who isn’t the slightest bit interested in capturing the fashion moment of her life for the next day’s front pages? It is, evidently, en...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>E! Producer Says She Was Fired For Allowing An Actress's Criticism Of The Network To Air - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/e-producer-fired-debra-messing-golden-globe-interview_us_5a99c88ae4b089ec353a40ce</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGyr4iC0Ps66845fUtH3qLsqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2018 00:24:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/e-producer-fired-debra-messing-golden-globe-interview_us_5a99c88ae4b089ec353a40ce" target="_blank"&gt;E! Producer Says She Was Fired For Allowing An Actress's Criticism Of The Network To Air&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A former producer at E! has filed a claim with the Equal Employment Opportunity Commission, saying she was unfairly terminated because she allowed a clip of a celebrity being critical of the network to air during its Golden Globes red-carpet show in January. The producer, Aileen Gram-Moreno, told The New York Times that the network asked her to flag celebrity interviews during the event, keeping an eye out specifically for celebrities who mentioned former E! host Catt Sadler. After Gram-Moreno mistakenly let an interview with Debra Messing slip through in which Messing did exactly that, she...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Brendan Fraser accuses former Golden Globes head of sexual assault - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/films/2018/02/23/brendan-fraser-accuses-former-golden-globes-head-sexual-assault/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGBd3hdO1CX6odg26XH0_p4qFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDf2rcF</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 16:32:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/films/2018/02/23/brendan-fraser-accuses-former-golden-globes-head-sexual-assault/" target="_blank"&gt;Brendan Fraser accuses former Golden Globes head of sexual assault&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The actor Brendan Fraser has said he is "still frightened" to this day, after being sexually assaulted in 2003 by Philip Berk, former head of the organisation behind the Golden Globe film awards. The 49-year-old became a household name in the Nineties with starring roles in blockbusters such as The Mummy and George of the Jungle, before slipping into obscurity. In a new interview with GQ Magazine, he claims his career "withered on the vine" after he was groped by Berk, a former president of the Hollywood Foreign Press Association (HFPA), which administers the Golden Globes. The actor said h...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Brendan Fraser alleges that he was groped - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/entertainment/2018/02/23/brendan-fraser-goping-allegation-gq-orig-vstop-bdk.cnn</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG2Bg1GNFyVrJZQEzIQEe8cqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 15:03:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/entertainment/2018/02/23/brendan-fraser-goping-allegation-gq-orig-vstop-bdk.cnn" target="_blank"&gt;Brendan Fraser alleges that he was groped&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Actor Brendan Fraser is alleging that former Hollywood Foreign Press Association President Philip Berk groped him at a 2003 event. ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A Time Warner Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>'I thought I was going to cry': Actor Brendan Fraser alleges Hollywood heavyweight groped him - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-02-23/brendan-fraser-claims-his-acting-career-was-derailed-after-sexu/9479476</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEL2NM4sFbrgj1aCDytIpZwqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 09:18:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-02-23/brendan-fraser-claims-his-acting-career-was-derailed-after-sexu/9479476" target="_blank"&gt;'I thought I was going to cry': Actor Brendan Fraser alleges Hollywood heavyweight groped him&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Actor Brendan Fraser says he wondered if he was "blacklisted" after he was allegedly groped by a former president of the organisation that hosts the Golden Globes. Key points: - Brendan Fraser says he was groped in a crowded room in 2003 - Former Hollywood Foreign Press Association president Philip Berk denies wrongdoing - Fraser became depressed, wondered if he was 'blacklisted' after alleged incident The Mummy trilogy star told men's magazine GQ he did not have the courage to speak up until now because of the risk of humiliation and damage to his career. "Am I still frightened? Absolutely...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>'Three Billboards' Gets Oscar Boost From BAFTA Awards - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/markbeech/2018/02/18/three-billboards-gets-oscar-boost-from-bafta-awards/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOxR3r0d0R2Ok64R8Y_1tGwqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2018 21:47:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/markbeech/2018/02/18/three-billboards-gets-oscar-boost-from-bafta-awards/" target="_blank"&gt;'Three Billboards' Gets Oscar Boost From BAFTA Awards&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Producer Peter Czernin (L), British-Irish filmmaker Martin McDonagh (C) and British producer Graham Broadbent (R) pose with their awards for an Outstanding British Film for the film ‘Three Billboards Outside Ebbing Missouri’ at the BAFTA British Academy Film Awards at the Royal Albert Hall in London on February 18, 2018. / AFP PHOTO / Ben STANSALL (Photo credit should read BEN STANSALL/AFP/Getty Images) Three Billboards Outside Ebbing, Missouri has received a crucial Oscar boost. Just as Academy Award voters start voting, the movie was named Best Picture at the 71st British Academy Film Awa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Trump challenges ‘insecure’ Oprah to run for president - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/trump-challenges-insecure-oprah-to-run-for-president-2018-02-19</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPpIoh_rm-zlbWs6fuHBSHkqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwiJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2018 11:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/trump-challenges-insecure-oprah-to-run-for-president-2018-02-19" target="_blank"&gt;Trump challenges ‘insecure’ Oprah to run for president&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE NEW YORK POST By Joe Tacopino Twitter blast comes after TV legend Oprah Winfrey leads a panel discussion on Trump’s performance on CBS’s “60 Minutes” Oprah Winfrey gave an inspirational speech at the Golden Globe Awards last month. Getty Images President Donald Trump slammed TV legend Oprah Winfrey on Sunday night as “insecure” saying he hopes for the opportunity to “defeat” the billionaire businesswoman at the ballot box. “Just watched a very insecure Oprah Winfrey, who at one point I knew very well, interview a panel of people on ‘60 Minutes,’” President Trump tweeted late Sunday. “Th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item></channel></rss>