<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Mazie Hirono - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIggKIhxDQkFTRHdvSkwyMHZNRE0xTjJOa0VnSmxiaWdBUAE?hl=en-NG&amp;gl=NG&amp;ceid=NG:en</link><language>en-NG</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 11:29:52 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>‘This is why Trump got elected’: Dems ‘too smart’ for average voters, says Hawaiian senator (VIDEO) - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/usa/445624-democrats-too-smart-for-voters/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEESPO_i6Yopj1BxYf3rdIb8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww7oMo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 11:20:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/usa/445624-democrats-too-smart-for-voters/" target="_blank"&gt;‘This is why Trump got elected’: Dems ‘too smart’ for average voters, says Hawaiian senator (VIDEO)&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Democrats managed to retake the House in November’s midterm elections but it didn’t quite amount to the impending ‘blue wave’ that was prophesied. One Democrat senator believes she knows the reason why. Speaking to Canadian-American writer and journalist Dahlia Lithwick at a conference in Washington DC Tuesday, Senator Mazie Hirono (D-Hawaii) argued that Democrats were more adept at appealing to voters’ minds than their hearts when asked how Democrats could improve voter turnout. “We’re really good at shoving out all the information that touch people here [pointing to her head] but not ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Hawaii's false missile alert leads to new recommendations - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/91e77c66a92d445691fee7fe8ab39133</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP95b8Yqvfvkyhct5EphvlsqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvKadAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 01:17:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/91e77c66a92d445691fee7fe8ab39133" target="_blank"&gt;Hawaii's false missile alert leads to new recommendations&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;HONOLULU (AP) — The U.S. Department of Homeland Security's inspector general has recommended changes to the nation's emergency alert system after Hawaii officials in January mistakenly warned the public about an incoming ballistic missile. The report issued last week calls for mandating that software vendors include message preview and cancelling features in their alert software. It recommends requiring that software vendors provide training to officials using their products. A Hawaii Emergency Management Agency employee mistakenly sent the missile alert to cellphones and broadcasters on Ja...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Top Senate Democrat Wants Probe of Whitaker's White House Contacts - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/top-senate-democrat-wants-probe-of-whitaker-white-house-contacts/4666618.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOsIoVMUfAAJpSez-J7Ts58qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 18:36:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/top-senate-democrat-wants-probe-of-whitaker-white-house-contacts/4666618.html" target="_blank"&gt;Top Senate Democrat Wants Probe of Whitaker's White House Contacts&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The top Democrat in the U.S. Senate, Chuck Schumer, called Tuesday for the Justice Department's internal investigator to review communications between acting Attorney General Matthew Whitaker and the White House. Senate Minority Leader Schumer said he wants the Justice Department's inspector general to look into Whitaker's interactions with the White House since last year when he was named chief of staff to then-Attorney General Jeff Sessions. President Donald Trump picked Whitaker earlier this month to become the country's top law enforcement official after ousting Sessions, whom he had lo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Senate Democrats file lawsuit against Matthew Whitaker's appointment - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/nov/19/matthew-whitaker-appointment-lawsuit-senate-democrats</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEIAFacG_UMDsmcSFO_vUcwqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCtvxU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 17:31:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/nov/19/matthew-whitaker-appointment-lawsuit-senate-democrats" target="_blank"&gt;Senate Democrats file lawsuit against Matthew Whitaker's appointment&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Three leading Democratic US senators filed a lawsuit on Monday accusing Donald Trump of illegally appointing Matthew Whitaker as acting attorney general, saying the president violated the US constitution and denied the Senate its right to approve the nomination. The lawsuit was filed in US district court for the District of Columbia by senators Richard Blumenthal, Sheldon Whitehouse and Mazie Hirono. It is the most high-profile litigation so far to be brought challenging Whitaker’s appointment. Trump named Whitaker acting attorney general on the day he asked Jeff Sessions for his resignatio...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Senate Dems urge Trump to make key appointments amid North Korea crisis - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/2017/09/18/politics/senate-democrats-letter-korea-ambassador/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI8Jt7JQIVpvFymHA_lNr_QqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMJrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2017 19:32:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/2017/09/18/politics/senate-democrats-letter-korea-ambassador/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Senate Dems urge Trump to make key appointments amid North Korea crisis&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amid increased tensions with North Korea, a group of Senate Democrats have written a letter to President Donald Trump urging him to make appointments to several unfilled posts with responsibility for the region, including the ambassador to South Korea. The letter's 10 authors, including members of the Intelligence, Armed Services, and Foreign Relations committees, expressed "deep concern" that no ambassador had been nominated. "As North Korea continues its illegal nuclear weapons program, commits blatant violations of international law, and makes threats to our country and allies, the confi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>3 Democratic US Senators Sue to Block Whitaker Appointment - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/two-democratic-us-senators-sue-to-challenge-whitaker-appointment/4664995.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMANhzJHTQD5kBuYyyvCZ4QqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 18:10:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/two-democratic-us-senators-sue-to-challenge-whitaker-appointment/4664995.html" target="_blank"&gt;3 Democratic US Senators Sue to Block Whitaker Appointment&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Three U.S. Democratic senators have sued to block President Donald Trump's appointment of acting Attorney General Matthew Whitaker, alleging the appointment was made to undermine the ongoing criminal investigation of the 2016 Trump campaign's alleged links to Russia. Senators Richard Blumenthal of Connecticut, Sheldon Whitehouse of Rhode Island and Mazie Hirono of Hawaii filed the lawsuit Monday in a federal court in Washington. The suit is the fourth legal challenge of Trump's appointment of Whitaker, following the ouster earlier this month of Attorney General Jeff Sessions, whom Trump had...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Democratic senators sue over Whitaker's appointment as AG - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/fb0d046e52494591b5e2bef3e485493f</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAT5XsDkMvkmecq9WXpFNnMqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwu4lR</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 16:55:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/fb0d046e52494591b5e2bef3e485493f" target="_blank"&gt;Democratic senators sue over Whitaker's appointment as AG&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Three Senate Democrats filed a lawsuit Monday arguing that Acting Attorney General Matthew Whitaker's appointment is unconstitutional and asking a federal judge to remove him. The suit, filed by Sens. Richard Blumenthal of Connecticut, Mazie Hirono of Hawaii and Sheldon Whitehouse of Rhode Island, argues that Whitaker's appointment violates the Constitution because he has not been confirmed by the Senate. Whitaker was chief of staff to Attorney General Jeff Sessions and was elevated to the top job after Sessions was ousted by President Donald Trump on Nov. 7. The Constitut...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Democratic senators sue to block Trump acting attorney general - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-justice-whitaker/democratic-senators-sue-to-block-trump-acting-attorney-general-idUSKCN1NO1YN</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHr8HzZqbHD31G1mVLLGq2EqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 18:37:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-justice-whitaker/democratic-senators-sue-to-block-trump-acting-attorney-general-idUSKCN1NO1YN" target="_blank"&gt;Democratic senators sue to block Trump acting attorney general&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Three Democratic senators launched a new legal challenge on Monday to President Donald Trump's naming of Matthew Whitaker as acting attorney general, accusing Trump of depriving the U.S. Senate of its constitutional power to act on such appointments. The lawsuit, filed by Senators Richard Blumenthal, Sheldon Whitehouse and Senator Mazie Hirono, asks a federal court in Washington to deem the appointment unconstitutional and bar Whitaker from serving as the top U.S. law enforcement official. The senators are members of the Senate Judiciary Committee, which customarily reviews attorney general...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Trump is dominating get-out-the-vote push in key state of Nevada - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/31/politics/nevada-midterms-trump-gotv/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIUnyOTUsD2th52Rhvsdws4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMJrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 16:30:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/31/politics/nevada-midterms-trump-gotv/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Trump is dominating get-out-the-vote push in key state of Nevada&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The midterms are a referendum on President Donald Trump, and no place is that clearer than in Nevada. In one of the midterms' political hotbeds, Republicans and Democrats are testing the limits of using Trump as a motivating force for voters who might otherwise sit the election out. Candidates in the state's competitive House, Senate and governor's races are all trying to galvanize their bases in the middle of a crucial week of early voting by touting their support, or opposition, to Trump's agenda and style. With control of both chambers of Congress on the line, Nevada is a must-win for De...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>The Senate Judiciary Committee's Only 4 Women Reflect On Kavanaugh's Confirmation - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/the-only-4-women-on-the-judiciary-committee-reflect-on-kavanaughs-confirmation_us_5bc4a2b9e4b040bb4e847663</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFswRISYNvSE52_YgnUmsv0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMOGXAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 16:05:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/the-only-4-women-on-the-judiciary-committee-reflect-on-kavanaughs-confirmation_us_5bc4a2b9e4b040bb4e847663" target="_blank"&gt;The Senate Judiciary Committee's Only 4 Women Reflect On Kavanaugh's Confirmation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The only four female members of the Senate Judiciary Committee are angry that Brett Kavanaugh was confirmed to the Supreme Court despite allegations of sexual assault and misconduct. “Women have had to put up with this bullshit for way too long,” Sen. Mazie Hirono (D-Hawaii) told New York magazine’s blog The Cut as part of the publication’s new Women and Power series. Hirono, along with Sens. Kamala Harris (D-Calif.), Amy Klobuchar (D-Minn.) and Dianne Feinstein (D-Calif.) ― the only women among the committee’s 21 members ― reflected on the controversial confirmation of Kavanaugh after Palo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>After outpouring of personal stories, Congress still grappling with Kavanaugh confirmation fallout - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/20/politics/metoo-congress-women-harassment-assault/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIIGsx-nrAMEfS00UepJ8xwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMJrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 13:42:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/20/politics/metoo-congress-women-harassment-assault/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;After outpouring of personal stories, Congress still grappling with Kavanaugh confirmation fallout&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;When Christine Blasey Ford said she could not remember certain details about her alleged assault by Brett Kavanaugh, Rep. Ann McLane Kuster could relate. The New Hampshire Democrat says she experienced something similar after she was sexually assaulted some 40 years ago. Like Ford, Kuster can't pinpoint the exact date of the event. But the two women say they remember other aspects of the incident vividly. Ford told the Senate Judiciary Committee she is "100%" certain Kavanaugh assaulted her, while Kuster has said that she will never forget her assailant, whom she has described as "a classma...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>These 5 female senators who shaped Kavanaugh hearings could run for president in 2020 - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/us-politics/kavanaugh-2020-election-susan-collins-kamala-harris-mazie-hirono-lisa-murkowski-klobuchar-trump-a8574806.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI6SZdAcM9gDfbjBZ1xgEzgqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2018 19:26:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/us-politics/kavanaugh-2020-election-susan-collins-kamala-harris-mazie-hirono-lisa-murkowski-klobuchar-trump-a8574806.html" target="_blank"&gt;These 5 female senators who shaped Kavanaugh hearings could run for president in 2020&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The female senators who played prominent roles Brett Kavanaugh's Supreme Court confirmation battle could see their support boosted if they decide to take on Donald Trump and run for the White House in 2020 as a result, some political commentators have suggested. The president's nominee divided opinion after Professor Christine Blasey Ford testified that he had sexually assaulted her at a party when they were teenagers. - Read more Republicans face midterms backlash from women furious over Kavanaugh As protests erupted across Capitol Hill, women on both sides of the political divide were for...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Senate confirms 15 judges in deal that allows lawmakers leave DC to campaign - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/11/politics/senators-leaders-judge-nominee/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELGZw7lldyHwdEFqiFqYEvAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 22:42:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/11/politics/senators-leaders-judge-nominee/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Senate confirms 15 judges in deal that allows lawmakers leave DC to campaign&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Republican and Democratic Senate leaders reached a broad deal Thursday to confirm a package of 15 judges that will allow the senators to depart Washington until after Election Day. Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell made the agreement public when he announced votes on three circuit court judges and 12 district court judges. The deal is a significant victory for McConnell, who has made clearing a long list of President Donald Trump's nominees, especially judges, a top priority this year. It is also a boon for senators seeking re-election, especially those 10 Democrats running in states w...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Sen. Hirono: Susan Collins 'Insulting' Ford By Saying Someone Else Assaulted Her - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/kavanaugh-collins-hirono-ford_us_5bba0d59e4b028e1fe3e5f88</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBKg56MfRd_vN62_vpyaU5IqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMOGXAg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 07 Oct 2018 15:16:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/kavanaugh-collins-hirono-ford_us_5bba0d59e4b028e1fe3e5f88" target="_blank"&gt;Sen. Hirono: Susan Collins 'Insulting' Ford By Saying Someone Else Assaulted Her&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sen. Mazie Hirono (D-Hawaii) said Sen. Susan Collins (R-Maine) is “insulting” Christine Blasey Ford by saying she believes the psychology professor was sexually assaulted by someone other than newly confirmed Supreme Court Justice Brett Kavanaugh. “She says that Dr. Ford thinks that she was assaulted, which is even more insulting than saying that she gave a very credible account,” Hirono told CNN on Sunday of her GOP colleague, who helped pave the way for Kavanaugh’s confirmation by a 50-48 Senate vote on Saturday. “To say that she thinks that Dr. Ford thinks that she was assaulted, what is...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Hirono: Women should focus 'like a laser beam' on 2018 - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/politics/2018/10/07/sotu-hirono-full.cnn</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIrBKn0FNerOJ-jx7u8ikyAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 07 Oct 2018 15:32:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/politics/2018/10/07/sotu-hirono-full.cnn" target="_blank"&gt;Hirono: Women should focus 'like a laser beam' on 2018&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hawaii Senator Mazie Hirono reacts to Senator Susan Collin's remarks on not believing Christine Blasey Ford's assault allegations against now-confirmed Supreme Court Justice Brett Kavanaugh. ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A WarnerMedia Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Sen. Hirono: Sen. Collins' comments on Ford 'insulting' to survivors - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/07/politics/hirono-kavanaugh-sotu-cnntv/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECtgj7a6TaabDyUIRkEjslkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 07 Oct 2018 15:58:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/07/politics/hirono-kavanaugh-sotu-cnntv/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Sen. Hirono: Sen. Collins' comments on Ford 'insulting' to survivors&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Democratic Sen. Mazie Hirono called Republican Sen. Susan Collins' comments on Christine Blasey Ford "insulting" to Ford and other victims of sexual assault. "She said that Dr. Ford thinks that she was assaulted, which is even more insulting than saying that she gave a very credible account ..." Hirono said. "What is that? Is [Ford] mistaken?" Ford alleged that newly confirmed Supreme Court Justice Brett Kavanaugh sexually assaulted her while the two were at a party in high school, and other accusers soon came forward. Kavanaugh has denied all the allegations. The Hawaii Democrat criticized...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Sen. Mazie Hirono Calls FBI Investigation 'A Sham' As Kavanaugh Vote Nears - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/mazie-hirono-fbi-investigation-kavanaugh_us_5bb75847e4b0876eda9d67d5</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHFJKU95mHTTHHyi2m4U1McqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMOGXAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 13:59:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/mazie-hirono-fbi-investigation-kavanaugh_us_5bb75847e4b0876eda9d67d5" target="_blank"&gt;Sen. Mazie Hirono Calls FBI Investigation 'A Sham' As Kavanaugh Vote Nears&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sen. Mazie Hirono (D-Hawaii) expressed strong opposition to Supreme Court nominee Brett Kavanaugh on Thursday night, calling the FBI’s investigation into Christine Blasey Ford’s allegation that Kavanaugh sexually assaulted her in high school “a sham.” “It is simply impossible after seeing the results of the FBI supplemental work — and I hesitate to call it an investigation — that anybody could think that it was in any way shape or form the comprehensive investigation the president promised,” said Hirono, one of only four women on the Senate Judiciary Committee. “This so-called investigation...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Republicans say bitter Kavanaugh fight energizing base as Collins defends vote - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/law/2018/oct/07/brett-kavanaugh-supreme-court-susan-collins-defends-vote</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP01EfWOblyUqWWBp7Ww8WAqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Sun, 07 Oct 2018 15:26:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/law/2018/oct/07/brett-kavanaugh-supreme-court-susan-collins-defends-vote" target="_blank"&gt;Republicans say bitter Kavanaugh fight energizing base as Collins defends vote&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Susan Collins, the moderate US senator from Maine whose vote to put Brett Kavanaugh on the supreme courtwas decisive, despite sexual assault allegations, defended herself on Sunday against charges of betraying women and the #MeToo movement – as the Republican leader, Mitch McConnell, boasted that the bitter fight on Capitol Hill has given his party a late advantage in the forthcoming midterm elections. Related: Brett Kavanaugh's confirmation to US supreme court gives Trump a major victory A day after Justice Kavanaugh, as he is now titled, was granted the ninth seat on the nation’s highest ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Sen. Mazie Hirono Says Trump Jr.'s Kavanaugh Remarks Come From 'Fear, Mistrust Of Women' - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/sen-mazie-hirono-donald-trump-jr-brett-kavanaugh-fear-mistrust-of-women_us_5bb381dbe4b0ba8bb2114b39</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJxaPv942AtUSWPjOZN1pDkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMOGXAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 15:34:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/sen-mazie-hirono-donald-trump-jr-brett-kavanaugh-fear-mistrust-of-women_us_5bb381dbe4b0ba8bb2114b39" target="_blank"&gt;Sen. Mazie Hirono Says Trump Jr.'s Kavanaugh Remarks Come From 'Fear, Mistrust Of Women'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sen. Mazie Hirono rejected the idea that women are coming forward with allegations of sexual assault only in an effort to target men, calling recent comments made to this effect by Donald Trump Jr. fearful and an example of “mistrust of women.” “It falls from a belief that, unfortunately, too many people have, especially men, that women just sit around making these stories up. It’s not true,” Hirono (D-Hawaii) said on CNN’s “New Day” on Tuesday morning. Host John Berman asked the senator about a recent Washington Post article discussing male fury and the alleged fear rising in the GOP in d...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Senate panel advances judicial nominee rated 'not qualified' by American Bar Association - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/11/politics/judicial-nominee-controversy-senate/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG-elwj9M67UpL5_H8UxiXIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMJrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 18:00:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/11/politics/judicial-nominee-controversy-senate/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Senate panel advances judicial nominee rated 'not qualified' by American Bar Association&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Senate Judiciary Committee on Thursday advanced a slate of judicial nominees to the floor for a vote, including Jonathan Kobes to be a US Circuit Judge for the Eighth Circuit, despite the fact that he was rated "not qualified" to serve on the circuit court by the American Bar Association. The nomination was approved by the committee by an 11-10 vote. Democratic Sen. Mazie Hirono of Hawaii criticized the move, saying after the vote that the White House had "nominated someone profoundly unfit to serve for a lifetime on the circuit court, but who will nonetheless be confirmed basically on ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Hirono: A lot of angry, determined women here - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/politics/2018/10/03/senator-hirono-trump-scary-time-for-men-comment-t-sot-ac360-vpx.cnn</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECoX1fufm3QLUOMGDCdDGAcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 03:17:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/politics/2018/10/03/senator-hirono-trump-scary-time-for-men-comment-t-sot-ac360-vpx.cnn" target="_blank"&gt;Hirono: A lot of angry, determined women here&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;CNN's Anderson Cooper speaks to Sen. Mazie Hirono (D-HI) about President Trump's comments calling the current political climate a "very scary time" for men. ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A Time Warner Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>One Of You Should Just Leak Me The FBI Report - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/please-leak-fbi-kavanaugh-report-senators_us_5bb79bade4b01470d05146cd</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMNwRrgiGXanTyHV7QA2_KcqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMOGXAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 21:13:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/please-leak-fbi-kavanaugh-report-senators_us_5bb79bade4b01470d05146cd" target="_blank"&gt;One Of You Should Just Leak Me The FBI Report&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;We do not know what was in the FBI’s most recent background check into Supreme Court nominee Brett Kavanaugh. The report was locked away in a secure room in the basement of the Capitol Visitor Center, where Democratic and Republican senators read it over in alternating shifts, applying or ignoring the evidence contained therein to a decision that will affect millions and millions of lives. The only thing less democratic about the process here is basically everything else about the Supreme Court. But we do know how this profound deficit of the old democratic spirit could be remedied: Senator...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Brett Kavanaugh Is Proof Republicans Will Never Hold The Elite Accountable - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/republicans-elite-accountable_us_5bb68509e4b01470d04feba8</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAAvN7pN6gak0m6k5Z8hJMMqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 20:37:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/republicans-elite-accountable_us_5bb68509e4b01470d04feba8" target="_blank"&gt;Brett Kavanaugh Is Proof Republicans Will Never Hold The Elite Accountable&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In his Senate testimony last week, Supreme Court nominee Brett Kavanaughrepeatedly lied under oath to defend himself against a credible allegation of sexual assault. He lied about the extent of his drinking. He lied about “boofing” and threesomes. He lied about using his high school yearbook profile to sexually humiliate another classmate. These would be unseemly but irrelevant facts about the distant past were Kavanaugh not accused of committing a drunken sexual assault in high school. The question now facing senators is whether this pattern of dishonesty should disqualify him from a lifet...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Hirono: Kavanaugh FBI investigation must cover 'the 3 credible' accusations - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/09/28/politics/hirono-fbi-investigation-three-credible-allegations-cnntv/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAZnQIYVr-DHRVeb5J-2ye4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMJrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 23:05:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/09/28/politics/hirono-fbi-investigation-three-credible-allegations-cnntv/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Hirono: Kavanaugh FBI investigation must cover 'the 3 credible' accusations&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sen. Mazie Hirono, a Democrat from Hawaii, said Friday that the FBI's supplemental investigation into Supreme Court nominee Brett Kavanaugh must cover what she called "the three credible" reports of misconduct. "It certainly should cover the three credible reports that have come forward, and it has to be complete," Hirono told CNN's Wolf Blitzer on "The Situation Room." "It has to be the kind of job that we expect the FBI to do -- and I believe that they can do it." Hirono was referring to the accounts brought forward by Christine Blasey Ford, Deborah Ramirez and Julie Swetnick, who have le...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Democrats suggest evidence of inappropriate behavior in Kavanaugh's prior background checks - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/03/politics/senate-judiciary-twitter-kavanaugh/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDOpbHqvnDkL9OHzYE0JCOIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2018 00:01:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/03/politics/senate-judiciary-twitter-kavanaugh/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Democrats suggest evidence of inappropriate behavior in Kavanaugh's prior background checks&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eight Democrats on the Senate Judiciary Committee sent a letter to GOP Judiciary Chairman Chuck Grassley of Iowa suggesting there could have been something in previous FBI background checks on Supreme Court nominee Brett Kavanaugh related to inappropriate sexual behavior or alcohol abuse. The Democratic senators accuse Republicans of mishandling confidential background investigation information, and call for Republican staff on the Judiciary Committee to correct what they say is an inaccurate statement in a tweet posted Tuesday that said "nowhere" in the prior background checks was there a ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Sen. Mazie Hirono On Christine Blasey Ford: 'I Believe Her' - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/sen-mazie-hirono-christine-blasey-ford-credibility_us_5bab8eafe4b0f143d10f2b66</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEgkdSob8X0Y2HMMl1g2AjYqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMOGXAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 15:00:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/sen-mazie-hirono-christine-blasey-ford-credibility_us_5bab8eafe4b0f143d10f2b66" target="_blank"&gt;Sen. Mazie Hirono On Christine Blasey Ford: 'I Believe Her'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sen. Mazie Hirono (D-Hawaii) just publicly and undoubtedly stated her support for Christine Blasey Ford, the woman who accused Supreme Court nominee Brett Kavanaugh of sexual assault. “The credibility is there for her. So I believe her,” Hirono told The New York Times of the Palo Alto University professor, who goes by Christine Blasey professionally, on Tuesday. “This whole idea that the Republicans have, that women just sit around making these things up, that is not borne out by the reality,” she added, referring to the dozens of comments from Republicans questioning Blasey’s story. Two wo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Democrats' new tack: Go hard after Kavanaugh's credibility - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/6bbd19a9e7124fbead3da03cb6f2e7f9</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDd2cQirdgM_i18Vknjmln4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwv7tQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 00:49:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/6bbd19a9e7124fbead3da03cb6f2e7f9" target="_blank"&gt;Democrats' new tack: Go hard after Kavanaugh's credibility&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Democrats are raising new questions about the truthfulness of Brett Kavanaugh's sworn testimony to the Senate, shifting tactics against President Donald Trump's Supreme Court nominee as they await the results of the FBI's background investigation into sexual misconduct allegations. Chuck Schumer, the Senate Democrats' leader from New York, accused Kavanaugh of delivering a "partisan screed" during the Judiciary Committee hearing last week. He said Kavanaugh seemed willing to "mislead senators about everything from the momentous to the mundane" to ensure his ascension to th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Dem Senators Walk Out of Judiciary Committee Hearing in Protest - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/dem-senators-walk-out-of-judiciary-committee-hearing-in-protest</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKJAZVREiVJr_9kj0tmby90qFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMLXUiQY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 14:08:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/dem-senators-walk-out-of-judiciary-committee-hearing-in-protest" target="_blank"&gt;Dem Senators Walk Out of Judiciary Committee Hearing in Protest&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brendan Smialowski/AFP/Getty Immediately following the Senate Judiciary Committee’s vote to ignore democratic motions to subpoena Mark Judge and proceed with Kavanaugh’s confirmation process, four democratic senators walked out of the hearing room while chairman Chuck Grassley (R-IL) was speaking. Senators Sheldon Whitehouse (D-RI), Kamala Harris (D-CA), Richard Blumenthal (D-CT), and Mazie Hirono (D-HI) all left the room in protest. Sen. Dianne Feinstein (D-CA) then ripped into the committee’s handling of the hearing. “This was not about ensuring a fair process,” she said. “This was about ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Democrat apologizes for fundraising off Kavanaugh allegations - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/09/27/politics/mazie-hirono-brett-kavanaugh-fundraising/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC4YWM202VN-fELV7uA1pT0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2018 16:26:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/09/27/politics/mazie-hirono-brett-kavanaugh-fundraising/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Democrat apologizes for fundraising off Kavanaugh allegations&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Democratic Sen. Mazie Hirono's re-election campaign on Thursday apologized for sending a fundraising email regarding the assault allegations made against Supreme Court Justice nominee Brett Kavanaugh by professor Christine Blasey Ford. The email, which was titled "Asking for a minute to explain (Kavanaugh)" and cast the Hawaii senator as too busy to fundraise because she was entirely focused on investigating Kavanaugh, was sent shortly after Ford began her testimony for the Senate Judiciary Committee. Hirono has been one of the most outspoken Democrats on the allegations against President D...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>New questions emerge over FBI investigation of Kavanaugh - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/01/politics/white-house-kavanaugh-confirmation-postponement/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDW7mgeEMFBydhOqEiJAfp0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMJrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 09:27:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/01/politics/white-house-kavanaugh-confirmation-postponement/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;New questions emerge over FBI investigation of Kavanaugh&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The White House is fighting to regain control of the confirmation of Supreme Court pick Brett Kavanaugh, but a controversy is widening over its role in an FBI investigation into allegations against the nominee of sexual assault and misconduct. New signs emerged Sunday that the administration is taking steps to make sure the probe is narrow and focused -- as Republicans seek to forestall further delays to the confirmation process or another erosion of the judge's position. So while President Donald Trump may have been forced to reopen an FBI background check on Kavanaugh, it is clear he is d...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Sexual Assault Survivors Confront Jeff Flake On CNN: 'Don't Look Away From Me' - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/jeff-flake-cnn-protester-kavanaugh_us_5bae303be4b0425e3c22e899</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOfVTkPFJASoRXdx32ipo4cqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 14:01:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/jeff-flake-cnn-protester-kavanaugh_us_5bae303be4b0425e3c22e899" target="_blank"&gt;Sexual Assault Survivors Confront Jeff Flake On CNN: 'Don't Look Away From Me'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two sexual assault survivors confronted Sen. Jeff Flake (R-Ariz.) on live TV Friday, shortly after the senator announced he would vote to confirm Supreme Court nominee Brett Kavanaugh. “You’re telling all women that they don’t matter,” said one woman between tears as Flake tried to leave in an elevator with his head down. “Look at me when I’m talking to you!” she shouted. “You’re telling me that my assault doesn’t matter.” “Look at me and tell me that it doesn’t matter what happened to me!” the woman added. “That you’ll let people like that go into the highest court in the land and tell eve...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Here's how the Senate Judiciary Committee voted - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/09/28/politics/kavanaugh-judiciary-committee-votes/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIq7IeDhLITcL4obZ3oRQd8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 18:51:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/09/28/politics/kavanaugh-judiciary-committee-votes/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Here's how the Senate Judiciary Committee voted&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The 21 members of the Senate Judiciary Committee voted 11-10 on Friday to move Judge Brett Kavanaugh's nomination to the full Senate. All Republicans senators voted yes and all Democrats voted no. Sen. Jeff Flake called for a one-week delay in Kavanaugh's nomination vote so that an FBI investigation can occur. See how the committee voted below. Those in favor of advancing the nomination Sen. Chuck Grassley, R-Iowa Sen. Orrin Hatch, R-Utah Sen. Lindsey Graham, R-South Carolina Sen. John Cornyn, R-Texas Sen. Mike Lee, R-Utah Sen. Ted Cruz, R-Texas Sen. Ben Sasse, R-Nebraska Sen. Jeff Flake, R...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Dianne Feinstein explains why she cannot vote for Brett Kavanaugh after America's 'national moment' hearing - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/us-politics/dianne-feinstein-brett-kavanaugh-vote-senate-supreme-court-womens-rights-a8559641.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ5Q-YqE7K0ZKIsNkOrs2qEqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCRx_0F</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 16:26:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/us-politics/dianne-feinstein-brett-kavanaugh-vote-senate-supreme-court-womens-rights-a8559641.html" target="_blank"&gt;Dianne Feinstein explains why she cannot vote for Brett Kavanaugh after America's 'national moment' hearing&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The senior Democrat on the committee that will determine the fate of Supreme Court nominee Brett Kavanaugh, has said she will not vote for him because of his views on women’s rights, gun control and presidential authority. Agreeing that the testimony of Mr Kavanaugh and Christine Blasey Ford, who accused him of sexually assaulting her three decades ago, had been a “national moment”, Senator Dianne Feinstein said she was not concerned about Mr Kavanaugh’s qualifications, but rather his views about fundamental issues that could have a powerful and lasting impact on the country. “It was broadc...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Brett Kavanaugh Nomination Moves Ahead Despite Sexual Assault Allegations - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/brett-kavanaugh-senate-judiciary-committee-vote_us_5bae2526e4b09d41eba0c3f7</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAFW0LevdJXtJn3KU0W5_EcqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 18:01:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/brett-kavanaugh-senate-judiciary-committee-vote_us_5bae2526e4b09d41eba0c3f7" target="_blank"&gt;Brett Kavanaugh Nomination Moves Ahead Despite Sexual Assault Allegations&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Senate Judiciary Committee on Friday voted to advance the Supreme Court nomination of Brett Kavanaugh, one day after testimony from Kavanaugh and Christine Blasey Ford, who has accused him of sexually assaulting her when they were in high school. The full Senate could vote as soon as Saturday to proceed with Kavanaugh’s nomination, and a final vote may come next week. It was unclear, however, whether that timeline would hold. Sen. Jeff Flake (R-Ariz.) sought a one-week delay in the full Senate’s vote for an FBI investigation into sexual assault claims that have been made against Kavanau...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>The Latest: Biden hails Ford's 'courageous' testimony - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/6cd0cc2774d94da68fc9b92b6f2dae42</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECKjyybdE9D3c08oFzaYICMqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwv7tQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2018 00:09:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/6cd0cc2774d94da68fc9b92b6f2dae42" target="_blank"&gt;The Latest: Biden hails Ford's 'courageous' testimony&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Latest on the Supreme Court nomination of Brett Kavanaugh (all times local): 8 p.m. Former Vice President Joe Biden is praising senators for delaying further action on Brett Kavanaugh's Supreme Court nomination until the FBI can investigate charges of sexual misconduct. Biden says Christine Blasey Ford, who accused Kavanaugh of sexual assault, "gave courageous, credible and powerful testimony" before the Senate Judiciary Committee Thursday. He says he believed Ford and "the country believed her." He says Ford "deserves an FBI investigation today." On the other hand, Bi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Guilty until proven innocent? Dem senator won't say Kavanaugh should have 'presumption of innocence' - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/usa/439229-hirono-kavanaugh-presumed-guilty/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC07JDwpVc2td50PoVgwa64qFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww7oMo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 15:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/usa/439229-hirono-kavanaugh-presumed-guilty/" target="_blank"&gt;Guilty until proven innocent? Dem senator won't say Kavanaugh should have 'presumption of innocence'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;US Democratic Senator Mazie Hirono has refused to say that Supreme Court nominee Brett Kavanaugh should enjoy a presumption of innocence regarding recent sexual misconduct allegations, citing the judge’s “credibility issues”. In an interview with CNN’s Jake Tapper, Hirono was asked about a Wall Street Journal editorial in which the paper argued that the presumption of innocence — “a core tenet of American law” — was being ignored by her and other Democrats in the Kavanaugh case. The paper’s editorial board claimed that the Democrats’ standard for sexual assault allegations was that they sho...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Senator reveals what she'll ask Kavanaugh - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/politics/2018/09/23/mazie-hirono-brett-kavanaugh-christine-blasey-ford-questions-sotu-vpx.cnn</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH8sVpOoJVWX2nDOP-H8K9IqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 01:19:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/politics/2018/09/23/mazie-hirono-brett-kavanaugh-christine-blasey-ford-questions-sotu-vpx.cnn" target="_blank"&gt;Senator reveals what she'll ask Kavanaugh&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sen. Mazie Hirono (D-HI) previewed what she plans to ask Supreme Court nominee Brett Kavanaugh during a hearing to address a sexual assault allegation levied against him. ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A Time Warner Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Hirono on Ford: 'I believe her' - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/politics/2018/09/23/sotu-mazie-hirono-full.cnn</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENZATyEtrmv7jMOeTPukuacqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2018 16:09:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/politics/2018/09/23/sotu-mazie-hirono-full.cnn" target="_blank"&gt;Hirono on Ford: 'I believe her'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jake Tapper interviews the Democratic Senator from Hawaii, Mazie Hirono, to discuss the sexual assault allegations against Supreme Court nominee Brett Kavanaugh and his accuser's credibility. ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A Time Warner Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Democrat addresses criticism over DNC co-chair - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/politics/2018/09/23/mazie-hirono-keith-ellison-allegations-sot-sotu-vpx.cnn</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENlJ9PJVKfqM-OrkMXGufqUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2018 14:59:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/politics/2018/09/23/mazie-hirono-keith-ellison-allegations-sot-sotu-vpx.cnn" target="_blank"&gt;Democrat addresses criticism over DNC co-chair&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sen. Mazie Hirono (D-HI) addresses criticism that Democrats might have more credibility with accusations against Supreme Court nominee Brett Kavanaugh if they were similarly outspoken when accusations were made against other Democrats. ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A Time Warner Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Call for men to 'step up' puts Sen. Hirono in the spotlight - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/2540edad251549d5b0b19333e3f36ef3</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENgSYIw2JSk7PFaNXL3AFaQqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwv7tQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 10:05:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/2540edad251549d5b0b19333e3f36ef3" target="_blank"&gt;Call for men to 'step up' puts Sen. Hirono in the spotlight&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Hawaii Sen. Mazie Hirono, one of only four women on the 21-member Senate Judiciary Committee, asked Supreme Court nominee Brett Kavanaugh the same questions on sexual harassment she has asked dozens of other nominees. Had Kavanaugh "made unwanted requests for sexual favors" or committed verbal or physical harrassment of a sexual nature since he became a legal adult? And had he ever faced discipline or settled with anyone over that kind of conduct? Kavanaugh said "no" to both questions at his confirmation hearing earlier this month. But few in the room, or watching on telev...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>‘Cut off that pesky penis of his’: Satire and reality blur as Kavanaugh debacle drags on - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/usa/439317-kavanaugh-kimmel-satire-reality/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEjs9dSXgHMO-eh4ZugS62cqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww7oMo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2018 14:05:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/usa/439317-kavanaugh-kimmel-satire-reality/" target="_blank"&gt;‘Cut off that pesky penis of his’: Satire and reality blur as Kavanaugh debacle drags on&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whether it’s from late night comedians or Democrat politicians, hysteria around Supreme Court nominee Brett Kavanaugh’s sexual assault allegations has climaxed and it’s hard to tell what’s real and what’s satire anymore. Kavanaugh’s confirmation vote has been stalled, first by Christine Blasey Ford’s allegation that Kavanaugh forced himself on her at a high-school party in the early 1980s; and then by a slew of subsequent, and also fantastically conveniently timed, allegations from his college years. With nothing proven and the vote frozen, liberal comedian Jimmy Kimmel gave his two cents o...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Activists corner Sen. Flake, protest in Senate building ahead of Kavanaugh vote - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/usa/439878-kavanaugh-vote-protests-flake/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED-8GrfCEJX2YEnWnSOzxH8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww7oMo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 18:06:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/usa/439878-kavanaugh-vote-protests-flake/" target="_blank"&gt;Activists corner Sen. Flake, protest in Senate building ahead of Kavanaugh vote&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;As the Senate Judiciary Committee votes to confirm Supreme Court nominee Brett Kavanaugh, Democrats walked out of the hearing and hordes of protesters made one last gasp at disrupting the bitter confirmation process. After hearing testimony from Kavanaugh and the woman accusing him of sexual assault – Christine Blasey Ford – on Thursday, the 11-Republican, 10-Democrat committee met on Friday to vote on Kavanaugh’s confirmation. With most of the committee planning on voting along party lines, Sen. Jeff Flake triggered a wave of anger when he announced that he would vote in favor of Kavanaugh...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Graham expresses doubt over Kavanaugh accuser’s story, says it won’t sway his vote - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/graham-expresses-doubt-over-kavanaugh-accusers-story-says-it-wont-sway-his-vote-2018-09-23</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF14YYEMxwVMiXFb6WWfgE8qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwiJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2018 19:46:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/graham-expresses-doubt-over-kavanaugh-accusers-story-says-it-wont-sway-his-vote-2018-09-23" target="_blank"&gt;Graham expresses doubt over Kavanaugh accuser’s story, says it won’t sway his vote&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KEY WORDS By Michelle Coffey Sen. Lindsey Graham, R-S.C. Getty Images South Carolina Sen. Lindsey Graham said Sunday he will listen to the testimony of Christine Blassey Ford, who has accused Supreme Court nominee Brett Kavanaugh of sexual assault, but it will likely not change his vote on the nomination. “What am I supposed to do? Go ahead and ruin this guy’s life based on an accusation? I don’t know when it happened, I don’t know where it happened, and everybody named in regard to being there said it didn’t happen,” Graham said Sunday on “Fox News Sunday” with Chris Wallace. ‘Unless there...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>What Senate Democrats did with the new Kavanaugh allegation - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/09/24/politics/senate-democrats-brett-kavanaugh-allegations/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMljTzIg12VdzO-cdvI6AM4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMJrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 17:54:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/09/24/politics/senate-democrats-brett-kavanaugh-allegations/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;What Senate Democrats did with the new Kavanaugh allegation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last week, rumors began to circulate on Capitol Hill about an incident in college involving President Donald Trump's Supreme Court nominee where Brett Kavanaugh allegedly exposed himself at a party at Yale, making their way to Senate Democrats who referred the matter to an attorney in Colorado. Among the offices aware of the allegation was Hawaii Democratic Sen. Mazie Hirono's, who told CNN Monday she passed the information along to the office of California Sen. Dianne Feinstein, the top Democrat on the Senate Judiciary Committee, the panel tasked with vetting Kavanaugh's nomination. But Se...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Brett Kavanaugh accuser will testify before Congress on Thursday - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/sep/23/brett-kavanaugh-accuser-set-to-testify-before-congress</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO-4IswzPKHXTkw5Gpmz1HQqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2018 16:47:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/sep/23/brett-kavanaugh-accuser-set-to-testify-before-congress" target="_blank"&gt;Brett Kavanaugh accuser will testify before Congress on Thursday&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Christine Blasey Ford, the woman who has accused supreme court nominee Brett Kavanaugh of sexual assault, will testify before the Senate judiciary committee on Thursday, in proceedings likely to become a decisive moment in the confirmation of the conservative judge. Related: Amy Chua denies telling female students to be 'model-like' for Brett Kavanaugh A statement issued on Sunday by lawyers for the professor at Palo Alto University, who alleges Kavanaugh assaulted her at a part in the early 1980s, said an open hearing would take place at 10am on Thursday. Kavanaugh, who has denied the alle...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Other controversial judicial nominees set for vote same day as Kavanaugh - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/09/28/politics/trump-judicial-nominees/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFeLS6hEhDaqvQrB9t0p5qQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMJrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 10:43:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/09/28/politics/trump-judicial-nominees/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Other controversial judicial nominees set for vote same day as Kavanaugh&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Senate Judiciary Committee is slated to vote on Brett Kavanaugh's nomination to the Supreme Court Friday morning — but he's not the only judge hoping for a positive outcome from the committee. Nine additional judicial nominees of President Donald Trump also appear on the docket for Friday morning, eight of whom are up for federal district court seats and one who's up for a federal appeals court spot. While the controversy over sexual assault allegations against Kavanaugh, which he has repeatedly denied, came to a head during Thursday's fiery and emotional hearing, three other Trump judi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Mazie Hirono Demands Men 'Shut Up And Step Up' In The Face Of Kavanaugh Accusation - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/mazie-hirono-men-shut-up-and-step-up-brett-kavanaugh-accusation_us_5ba23b96e4b013b09780ce67</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC0XKDEAkvBjjzzxR04dovAqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMOGXAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 13:47:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/mazie-hirono-men-shut-up-and-step-up-brett-kavanaugh-accusation_us_5ba23b96e4b013b09780ce67" target="_blank"&gt;Mazie Hirono Demands Men 'Shut Up And Step Up' In The Face Of Kavanaugh Accusation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sen. Mazie Hirono (D-Hawaii) has an important message for men in the wake of the recent sexual assault accusation against Supreme Court nominee Brett Kavanaugh. “I just want to say to the men in this country, just shut up and step up. Do the right thing for a change,” Hirono said during a press event on Tuesday. Hirono is part of the Senate Judiciary Committee tasked to hear testimony from Kavanaugh and vote on his nomination. She’s one of only four women on the committee. The hearings, which began earlier this month, have been scheduled to continue next week after Christine Blasey Ford, wh...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Mazie Hirono Says It's 'Bulls**t' That GOP Has Tried Everything To Contact Kavanaugh Accuser - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/mazie-hirono-says-its-bullshit-that-gop-has-tried-everything-to-contact-kavanaugh-accuser_us_5ba3a818e4b0375f8f9aaf7b</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO3HDHfX9tNZMTmowBPpsUAqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2018 15:08:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/mazie-hirono-says-its-bullshit-that-gop-has-tried-everything-to-contact-kavanaugh-accuser_us_5ba3a818e4b0375f8f9aaf7b" target="_blank"&gt;Mazie Hirono Says It's 'Bulls**t' That GOP Has Tried Everything To Contact Kavanaugh Accuser&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sen. Mazie Hirono (D-Hawaii) is once again not holding back her thoughts on how the Senate Judiciary Committee is dealing with the recent sexual assault accusation against Supreme Court nominee Brett Kavanaugh. “I would like us to come together and figure out what is the best way to proceed,” Hirono told ABC News on Wednesday evening. “Not this seat-of-the-pants stuff,” she added. “The latest, being a letter from the chairman to the Democrats saying, ‘We have done everything we can to contact her.’ That is such bullshit, I can’t hardly stand it.” Hirono was referring to a letter from Senate...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Senator to men: Shut up and step up - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/politics/2018/09/19/mazie-hirono-men-shut-up-kavanaugh-sexual-assault-vpx.cnn</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEUBaEnBsS1JawC0qzcFdKQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 23:16:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/politics/2018/09/19/mazie-hirono-men-shut-up-kavanaugh-sexual-assault-vpx.cnn" target="_blank"&gt;Senator to men: Shut up and step up&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sen. Mazie Hirono (D-HI) said her message to men in the United States is to "just shut up and step up. Do the right thing," following the sexual assault allegation against Supreme Court nominee Brett Kavanaugh. ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A Time Warner Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Mazie Hirono: Kavanaugh accuser is hesitating to testify because she's afraid of a GOP 'railroad job' - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/09/19/politics/mazie-hirono-railroad-job-brett-kavanaugh-christine-blasey-ford-cnntv/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJQFDhpEMylR26OGf1VaGvgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 14:40:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/09/19/politics/mazie-hirono-railroad-job-brett-kavanaugh-christine-blasey-ford-cnntv/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Mazie Hirono: Kavanaugh accuser is hesitating to testify because she's afraid of a GOP 'railroad job'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hawaii Democratic Sen. Mazie Hirono said Wednesday that there should be some attempt to corroborate an allegation of sexual assault against Supreme Court nominee Brett Kavanaugh before the Senate Judiciary Committee hears from the woman who is accusing him. On Tuesday, Christine Blasey Ford's attorneys argued in a letter to the committee that the FBI should investigate the alleged incident, which Ford says occurred while she and Kavanaugh were in high school, before senators hold a hearing on the allegation. Kavanaugh has said he "categorically and unequivocally" denies the allegation, whic...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Gillibrand and Hirono criticize GOP's handling of Kavanaugh sexual assault allegation - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/09/20/politics/mazie-hirono-kirsten-gillibrand-republicans-brett-kavanaugh/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENm301Nb8JGqvpwEhTbm2O0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2018 20:43:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/09/20/politics/mazie-hirono-kirsten-gillibrand-republicans-brett-kavanaugh/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Gillibrand and Hirono criticize GOP's handling of Kavanaugh sexual assault allegation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Democratic Sens. Mazie Hirono and Kirsten Gillibrand on Thursday heavily criticized GOP senators' handling of a sexual assault allegation against Supreme Court Justice nominee Brett Kavanaugh and asserted that the incident, as well as death threats against the woman making the accusation, should be investigated by the FBI. "Why isn't Judge Kavanaugh asking for an FBI investigation if (he has) nothing to hide?" Hirono asked during a news conference introducing a letter from 1,000 alumnae of the Holton-Arms School supporting Christine Blasey Ford, who was attending the school when she alleges...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Sen. Hirono's message to men: 'Just shut up and step up. Do the right thing.' - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/09/18/politics/senator-mazie-hirono-men-shut-up-brett-kavanaugh-sexual-assault/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKaSZSIxb2WFGepXvrwSQpsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMJrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 20:43:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/09/18/politics/senator-mazie-hirono-men-shut-up-brett-kavanaugh-sexual-assault/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Sen. Hirono's message to men: 'Just shut up and step up. Do the right thing.'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sen. Mazie Hirono said her message to men in this country is to "just shut up and step up. Do the right thing for a change" following the sexual assault allegation against Supreme Court nominee Brett Kavanaugh. Asked Tuesday about being one of just four women on the Senate Judiciary Committee and how that will affect the nomination proceedings, the Hawaii Democrat said, "Of course it helps that there are women on that committee. ... But really, guess who's perpetuating all of these kinds of actions? It's the men in this country. And I just want to say to the men in this country: Just shut u...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Dems’ Plan for Kavanaugh-Ford Hearings: Lean Heavily on Two Female Senators - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/dems-plan-for-kavanaugh-ford-hearings-lean-heavily-on-two-female-senators</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPY02G5jAwEwX9eURxmjEvMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMPGMAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 01:07:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/dems-plan-for-kavanaugh-ford-hearings-lean-heavily-on-two-female-senators" target="_blank"&gt;Dems’ Plan for Kavanaugh-Ford Hearings: Lean Heavily on Two Female Senators&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Melina Mara/The Washington Post via Getty On Thursday afternoon, lawyers for Christine Blasey Ford, the woman accusing Supreme Court nominee Brett Kavanaugh of sexual assault, said she would be willing testify before the Senate Judiciary Committee next week under certain conditions. If those conditions are met, Democrats have a plan for how to handle the highly delicate proceedings: they’ll lean heavily on two female members to do the brunt of the questioning, aides tell The Daily Beast. Sens. Kamala Harris (D-CA) and Amy Klobuchar (D-MN) are among the more junior members on the judiciary c...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Brett Kavanaugh nomination: Senator tells men to 'shut up and step up' over sexual assault allegations - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/us-politics/brett-kavanaugh-nomination-mazie-hirono-senate-supreme-court-sexual-assault-men-shut-up-step-up-a8544656.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOnumcwlOFZVGc_M2ccNatMqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 12:10:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/us-politics/brett-kavanaugh-nomination-mazie-hirono-senate-supreme-court-sexual-assault-men-shut-up-step-up-a8544656.html" target="_blank"&gt;Brett Kavanaugh nomination: Senator tells men to 'shut up and step up' over sexual assault allegations&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A US senator has called on the men of her country to “shut up and step up” over the sexual assault allegation surrounding Brett Kavanaugh’s nomination to the Supreme Court. While Donald Trump has staunchly defended Mr Kavanaugh, who he nominated for the Supreme Court, Republicans and Democrats in the Senate have fought over who should testify at a hearing on the allegation. It remains unclear whether Christine Blasey Ford, who has accused Mr Kavanaugh of attacking her and trying to remove her clothing while he was drunk at a high school party in 1982, will appear at a Judiciary Committee he...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Kavanaugh's Supreme Court Fight Unfolds in Spotlight of #MeToo - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/brett-kavanaugh-supreme-court-metoo-anita-hill-clarence-thomas/4580364.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOtFq8RJfRefyiPkblulPAsqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 10:30:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/brett-kavanaugh-supreme-court-metoo-anita-hill-clarence-thomas/4580364.html" target="_blank"&gt;Kavanaugh's Supreme Court Fight Unfolds in Spotlight of #MeToo&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Allegations of sexual misconduct against U.S. Supreme Court nominee Brett Kavanaugh have thrown his Senate confirmation into turmoil. And the treatment of his accuser, Christine Blasey Ford, has sparked an emotional debate across the country on how legislators should handle abuse claims in the #MeToo era. President Donald Trump has named Kavanaugh to a lifetime position on the nation's highest court. The nominee is on the brink of becoming one of the nine U.S. judges who will decide cases for decades to come on immigration, the environment, finance, civil rights, and Roe v. Wade, the 1973 ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>‘Rules for thee, not for me’ Democrats pick &amp; choose sex assault abusers to believe - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/usa/438837-democrats-sexual-assault-kavanaugh-ellison/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC8pjO9cS4_DeVxxRghx1mgqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww7oMo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 15:22:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/usa/438837-democrats-sexual-assault-kavanaugh-ellison/" target="_blank"&gt;‘Rules for thee, not for me’ Democrats pick &amp; choose sex assault abusers to believe&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A woman accusing Democrat Rep. Keith Ellison (Minnesota) of abuse says the party abandoned her – a far cry from top Democrats’ public show of support for Supreme Court nominee Brett Kavanaugh’s accuser. Karen Monahan said that she was “smeared, threatened, (and) isolated” by the Democratic party when she came forward with allegations of physical and emotional abuse against Rep. Ellison, the Democratic National Committee deputy chair and Minnesota attorney general candidate. “I’ve been smeared, threatened, isolated from my own party,” Monahan tweeted Monday. “I provided medical records from ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Senate Democrats Support Christine Blasey Ford's Request for FBI Probe - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/senate-democrats-support-christine-blasey-ford-request-fbi-probe_us_5ba1a32fe4b04d32ebfdae77</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAuzgWfkodklaKZuw6EnL7QqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 02:55:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/senate-democrats-support-christine-blasey-ford-request-fbi-probe_us_5ba1a32fe4b04d32ebfdae77" target="_blank"&gt;Senate Democrats Support Christine Blasey Ford's Request for FBI Probe&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A number of Senate Democrats came out Tuesday in support of Christine Blasey Ford’s request for an FBI investigation into her sexual assault accusation against Supreme Court nominee Brett Kavanaugh before she testifies in front of the Senate Judiciary Committee. The Northern California psychology professor, who goes by Christine Blasey professionally, alleges that Kavanaughassaulted her at a party when they were teenagers, over 35 years ago. Judiciary committee chairman Chuck Grassley (R-Iowa) had scheduled Blasey and Kavanaugh to testify in front of the committee on Monday. Blasey, however...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Here Is What Brett Kavanaugh Said About Sexual Misconduct In His Hearings - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/brett-kavanaugh-sexual-misconduct_us_5b9ea46fe4b013b0977bc6fe</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKPAxWzUU4qNa2CwkiT5YJQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMOGXAg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2018 20:13:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/brett-kavanaugh-sexual-misconduct_us_5b9ea46fe4b013b0977bc6fe" target="_blank"&gt;Here Is What Brett Kavanaugh Said About Sexual Misconduct In His Hearings&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brett Kavanaugh is facing an allegation that he attempted to sexually assault a woman when they were both in high school, a revelation that has shaken what appeared to be his smooth confirmation path to the Supreme Court. On Sunday, Christine Blasey Ford stepped forward and said she is now willing to go public with her accusations. She alleges that when she was 15, she was at a house party when Kavanaugh, who was then 17, and a friend of his locked her in a room. They turned up the music, and Kavanaugh, who was drunk, held her down and tried to remove her clothes, she alleges. At one point,...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Republicans Appear Ready To Push For Brett Kavanaugh Vote Despite Sexual Assault Claim - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/republicans-brett-kavanaugh-vote_us_5b9ebcb5e4b04d32ebf985cb</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBVnXqXQZknYgd3WWCb69hEqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2018 21:53:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/republicans-brett-kavanaugh-vote_us_5b9ebcb5e4b04d32ebf985cb" target="_blank"&gt;Republicans Appear Ready To Push For Brett Kavanaugh Vote Despite Sexual Assault Claim&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Republican members of the Senate Judiciary Committee appear ready to move forward with a vote this week on whether to advance Brett Kavanaugh’s Supreme Court confirmation to the full Senate, despite one woman’s sexual assault allegation against him. The Washington Post on Sunday published an interview with Christine Blasey Ford, who alleged Kavanaugh held her down and groped her when they were high school students. Senate Judiciary Committee Republicans responded by calling into question her motive for coming forward. “It’s disturbing that these uncorroborated allegations from more than 35 ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Senate Unanimously Passes Bill To Honor Forgotten Chinese-American WWII Veterans - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/senate-bill-chinese-american-wwii-veterans_us_5b9c00a3e4b04d32ebf8482b</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDO6QuEuY7f2UOLdLDnxTGoqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 20:57:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/senate-bill-chinese-american-wwii-veterans_us_5b9c00a3e4b04d32ebf8482b" target="_blank"&gt;Senate Unanimously Passes Bill To Honor Forgotten Chinese-American WWII Veterans&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The government is another step closer to properly honoring Chinese-American veterans who served during World War II. The Senate unanimously passed a bill last week that would allow Congress to award the veterans with a Congressional Gold Medal for their service during a time of anti-Chinese discrimination. While it’s estimated that more than 13,000 Chinese-Americans served the U.S. during that time, their contributions and achievements have largely been left out of the mainstream media. And Sen. Tammy Duckworth (D-Ill.), who introduced the bill last year with Sen. Mazie Hirono (D-Hawaii), t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Kavanaugh nomination descends into chaos - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/09/18/politics/brett-kavanaugh-christine-blasey-ford-hearing-grassley/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHS9tj4BEJncm1eD5_RTX2kqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMJrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 21:48:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/09/18/politics/brett-kavanaugh-christine-blasey-ford-hearing-grassley/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Kavanaugh nomination descends into chaos&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Plans for a dramatic, clarifying hearing featuring Supreme Court pick Brett Kavanaugh and the woman who accused him of sexual assault have descended into chaos and partisan bitterness. The confusion and bickering between Democrats and Republicans set off by Christine Blasey Ford's allegations are casting a darkening cloud over Kavanaugh's hopes of being swiftly confirmed and cementing a conservative majority on the court in a huge win for President Donald Trump. Senate Democrats are demanding a delay in the hearing scheduled for Monday to allow for time for an FBI probe into the allegations...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Woman accuses Kavanaugh of assault in letter to senator - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/09/14/politics/kavanaugh-letter-assault-supreme-court/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJRMdR5QNzqwovCzxU9n9YoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 20:10:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/09/14/politics/kavanaugh-letter-assault-supreme-court/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Woman accuses Kavanaugh of assault in letter to senator&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A woman is accusing Supreme Court nominee Brett Kavanaugh of assaulting her when they were in high school in the early 1980s, according to a source familiar with the allegations, which were relayed in a letter to Sen. Dianne Feinstein earlier this summer. The letter details an incident when the woman, who has not come forward publicly, attended a party with Kavanaugh and others in a suburban Maryland home. Feinstein, the top Democrat on the Senate Judiciary Committee, has referred the letter to the FBI. Kavanaugh physically pushed her into a bedroom, the accuser said. Along with another mal...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Dems call for delay of Kavanaugh vote after accuser comes forward - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/09/16/politics/democrats-brett-kavanaugh-diane-feinstein/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEh9_x3ZyuvH5CWVE2Yp2IgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMJrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2018 22:57:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/09/16/politics/democrats-brett-kavanaugh-diane-feinstein/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Dems call for delay of Kavanaugh vote after accuser comes forward&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Democratic senators on Sunday called for the Senate Judiciary Committee to delay its planned vote on Brett Kavanaugh's nomination for the Supreme Court after a woman who accused him of sexual misconduct revealed her identity. The woman who went public, Christine Blasey Ford, previously described the alleged incident in a letter to Democratic Sen. Dianne Feinstein, the ranking member of the committee. Feinstein said she referred the matter to the FBI and that the woman had requested confidentiality. The California senator said in a statement after Ford went public that she backs her decision...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Ruth Bader Ginsburg Slams Senate Hearings As A 'Highly Partisan Show' - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/ruth-bader-ginsburg-senate-supreme-court-hearings_us_5b999d0fe4b0162f4733cf91</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMWrVwpD8L_V4lp0uOZkJj0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMOGXAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 04:48:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/ruth-bader-ginsburg-senate-supreme-court-hearings_us_5b999d0fe4b0162f4733cf91" target="_blank"&gt;Ruth Bader Ginsburg Slams Senate Hearings As A 'Highly Partisan Show'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Justice Ruth Bader Ginsberg has a problem with the way this Congress handles Supreme Court confirmation hearings. The 85-year-old justice was asked Wednesday how the hearings of Supreme Court nominee Brett Kavanaugh compared with her own during an event at George Washington University Law School. President Bill Clinton nominated Ginsburg to the Supreme Court in June 1993, and the U.S. Senate voted 96-3 to confirm her two months later. “The way it was was right. The way it is is wrong,” Ginsburg said. During Kavanaugh’s hearing before the Senate Judiciary Committee, Democrats have pushed bac...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Actress Piper Perabo: I was arrested for what I believe in - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/09/09/opinions/i-was-arrested-for-what-i-believe-perabo/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDizp-RyOCuHL9zBxKWg0PIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMKrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 22:03:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/09/09/opinions/i-was-arrested-for-what-i-believe-perabo/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Actress Piper Perabo: I was arrested for what I believe in&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Piper Perabo is an actress known for her role as CIA agent Annie Walker in the TV series "Covert Affairs," for which she received a Golden Globe nomination in 2010. She has appeared in numerous films, including "Looper," "The Prestige," "Imagine Me and You," and her breakout role in "Coyote Ugly." Perabo is also a political activist and voice of advocacy for the International Rescue Committee. The opinions expressed in this commentary are solely those of the author. View more opinions on CNN. I got arrested last Tuesday, and it wasn't a scene in a movie. I grew up thinking most people get a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Read the email Mazie Hirono released on Brett Kavanaugh - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/09/06/politics/hirono-kavanaugh-emails/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFhjgTHeiVqaafOv9DW_pMYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2018 17:59:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/09/06/politics/hirono-kavanaugh-emails/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Read the email Mazie Hirono released on Brett Kavanaugh&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brett Kavanaugh wrote that government programs targeting Native Hawaiians "as a group" is "of questionable validity under the Constitution" and would be "subject to strict scrutiny" in an email sent during his time in the Bush White House. Kavanaugh was responding to upcoming testimony from a Treasury Department official regarding investment in "Indian Country." "I think the testimony needs to make clear that any program targeting Native Hawaiians as a group is subject to strict scrutiny and of questionable validity under the Constitution," Kavanaugh wrote in 2002. The email, marked "commit...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Cory Booker Releases Confidential Documents During Kavanaugh Hearing - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/cory-booker-kavanaugh-documents-confidential_us_5b91326ee4b0cf7b003d4cbe</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMeEXZ_ZP_VkbAoC6_fE-8MqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2018 14:12:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/cory-booker-kavanaugh-documents-confidential_us_5b91326ee4b0cf7b003d4cbe" target="_blank"&gt;Cory Booker Releases Confidential Documents During Kavanaugh Hearing&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sens. Cory Booker (D-N.J.) and Mazie Hirono (D-Hawaii) released formerly confidential emails from Supreme Court nominee Brett Kavanaugh about racial profiling and racial discrimination at the start of the third day of confirmation hearings on Thursday,around an hour after threatening to do so. The dramatic move appeared to defy Republicans who had shielded the documents from public view, and it seemed to risk breaking Senate rules. Senate Judiciary Committee staffers for Republican and Democratic officials told The Washington Post, however, that the committee cleared the documents for publi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Read The Brett Kavanaugh Emails Democrats Pressured Republicans To Release - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/cory-booker-brett-kavanaugh-email_us_5b913f68e4b0cf7b003d6363</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECerv8CKHQMP2HPDIeGxMf0qFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2018 15:10:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/cory-booker-brett-kavanaugh-email_us_5b913f68e4b0cf7b003d6363" target="_blank"&gt;Read The Brett Kavanaugh Emails Democrats Pressured Republicans To Release&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Holy shit Cornyn reads a rule saying "any senator...who discloses the secret or confidential business or proceedings of the senate" shall be expelled or dismissed from the senate Booker looks him dead in the eye and says, "Bring it." pic.twitter.com/eOdx2Z1RST — Melanie Schmitz (@MelsLien) September 6, 2018 Sens. Cory Booker (D-N.J.) and Mazie Hirono (D-Hawaii) on Thursday released copies of emails from Supreme Court nominee Brett Kavanaugh that Republicans had previously refused to make public. The documents were released shortly after a heated confrontation between Democrats and Republica...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Read The Latest From Brett Kavanaugh's Supreme Court Confirmation Hearing - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/brett-kavanaugh-hearing_us_5b911f74e4b0162f472a7b7a</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBaQJt5kpJ2sRelQm5-q1TkqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2018 13:35:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/brett-kavanaugh-hearing_us_5b911f74e4b0162f472a7b7a" target="_blank"&gt;Read The Latest From Brett Kavanaugh's Supreme Court Confirmation Hearing&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Judge Brett Kavanaugh has a third day of questioning in his Supreme Court confirmation hearing. Kavanaugh’s stretch before the Senate Judiciary Committee began Tuesday, and he was questioned by senators all day Wednesday. He was tapped in July by President Donald Trump to fill the seat of retiring Supreme Court Justice Anthony Kennedy. Read live updates from the third day of the hearing below. (You may need to refresh the page to see the latest updates.): 7:14 p.m. ET Harris continued asking Kavanaugh to clarify his stance on Roe v. Wade and to say whether he thinks it’s constitutional for ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Democrats Go Nuclear for Kavanaugh Documents - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/democrats-go-nuclear-for-kavanaugh-documents</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIPOAGYkfVCZC3zjHy26SoEqFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMPrwlwI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2018 14:23:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/democrats-go-nuclear-for-kavanaugh-documents" target="_blank"&gt;Democrats Go Nuclear for Kavanaugh Documents&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zach Gibson/Getty It was kitchen-sink day at the Senate Judiciary Committee, and from the beginning Democrats seemed intent on demonstrating that they were going big. And if that meant some theater was necessary, so be it. The third day of Supreme Court nominee Brett Kavanaugh’s confirmation hearings had barely begun when Sen. Cory Booker (D-NJ) declared that he was committing an act of “civil disobedience” by releasing documents that had been deemed “committee confidential” and, therefore, not available to the public. The outspoken senator called it his “I am Spartacus” moment. But it quic...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item></channel></rss>