<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Pope Francis - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIggKIhxDQkFTRHdvSkwyMHZNRFZ1WjNReUVnSmxiaWdBUAE?hl=en-NG&amp;gl=NG&amp;ceid=NG:en</link><language>en-NG</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 13:09:48 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Invite Pope Francis to the game - MARCA.com</title><link>https://www.marca.com/en/football/international-football/2018/12/01/5c027b7446163f5f398b456c.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiYWh0dHBzOi8vd3d3Lm1hcmNhLmNvbS9lbi9mb290YmFsbC9pbnRlcm5hdGlvbmFsLWZvb3RiYWxsLzIwMTgvMTIvMDEvNWMwMjdiNzQ0NjE2M2Y1ZjM5OGI0NTZjLmh0bWzSAacBaHR0cHM6Ly9hbXAtbWFyY2EtY29tLmNkbi5hbXBwcm9qZWN0Lm9yZy92L3MvYW1wLm1hcmNhLmNvbS9lbi9mb290YmFsbC9pbnRlcm5hdGlvbmFsLWZvb3RiYWxsLzIwMTgvMTIvMDEvNWMwMjdiNzQ0NjE2M2Y1ZjM5OGI0NTZjLmh0bWw_YW1wX2pzX3Y9MC4xI3dlYnZpZXc9MSZjYXA9c3dpcGU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 12:22:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marca.com/en/football/international-football/2018/12/01/5c027b7446163f5f398b456c.html" target="_blank"&gt;Invite Pope Francis to the game&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MARCA.com&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;As I wrote here recently, there will come a day when we are reminded of the urgency for Spain to host an Olympic Games because they look for anyone...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marca.com">MARCA.com</source></item><item><title>Vatican investigates after nuns report sex abuse by priests - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/6d7fa7a4afc040ae9b987425fc49a7c2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPVoaRq3qXp2NfdTtmKk1EMqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwu4lR</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 16:12:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/6d7fa7a4afc040ae9b987425fc49a7c2" target="_blank"&gt;Vatican investigates after nuns report sex abuse by priests&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;VATICAN CITY (AP) — The Vatican has launched an investigation into a small Chilean religious order of nuns after some sisters denounced sexual abuse at the hands of priests and mistreatment by their superiors, a turning point that shows the Holy See is now willing to investigate allegations of sexual violence against nuns. The scandal at the Institute of the Good Samaritan was revealed publicly in an investigative report by Chilean national television earlier this year at the height of outrage over how Chilean Catholic hierarchy covered up decades of sexual abuse of children by priests. In ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Pope Unlikely to Visit North Korea Next Year, Vatican Says - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/pope-unlikely-to-visit-north-korea-next-year-vatican-says/4692064.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK_IJqzXPaFOs1rKs6yad7cqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 01:36:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/pope-unlikely-to-visit-north-korea-next-year-vatican-says/4692064.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pope Unlikely to Visit North Korea Next Year, Vatican Says&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In what appeared to be a setback for Seoul's diplomacy to ease tensions on the Korean peninsula and nudge North Korea into embracing openness, the Vatican said Friday Pope Francis is unlikely to visit North Korea next year. The possibility of the landmark visit was raised when South Korean President Moon Jae-in, during a private meeting with the pope in October, conveyed North Korean leader Kim Jong Un's desire for a papal visit to the isolated country. The Vatican responded positively, saying a formal invitation from North Korea was necessary. Given the necessary preparations and the pope'...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Pope to visit UAE in first-ever trip to Arabian Peninsula - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/34b3f993ff3c4ddb927948d7d4de4f13</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMsUDvr4723qKZHsydU0pT4qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 16:22:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/34b3f993ff3c4ddb927948d7d4de4f13" target="_blank"&gt;Pope to visit UAE in first-ever trip to Arabian Peninsula&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;VATICAN CITY (AP) — Pope Francis plans to visit the United Arab Emirates in February to push for Christian-Muslim dialogue and peace in the first-ever papal visit to the Arabian Peninsula. The Feb. 3-5 trip to Abu Dhabi centers around an interfaith meeting, the Vatican said Thursday. Francis will also have the chance to meet with political leaders as well as the UAE's Catholic community, which is made up almost exclusively of foreign workers. It's the latest trip to be announced in what is shaping up to be one of Francis' busiest years for foreign travel, with trips to Central America, Nort...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>2 Jesuit provinces releases 153 names of accused abusers - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/0b2d824d2fb747f08a257b7b8a4aae53</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJe81cm0BiEwHKuw84tZp50qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvKadAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 19:04:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/0b2d824d2fb747f08a257b7b8a4aae53" target="_blank"&gt;2 Jesuit provinces releases 153 names of accused abusers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ST. LOUIS (AP) — Two Roman Catholic Jesuit provinces that cover nearly half the U.S. released the names Friday of more than 150 priests and other ministry leaders who were found to have "credible allegations" of sexual abuse made against them dating to the 1950s. Jesuits West, which covers 10 western states, said its internal investigation found credible allegations against 111 priests, brothers or priests in training who were connected to it dating back to 1950. No one on the list is involved in public ministry any longer, it said. Hours earlier, the Jesuits U.S. Central and Southern Provi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Pope Francis to visit UAE in historic trip to the Gulf - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/pope-francis-visit-uae-historic-trip-gulf-181206113104777.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELv0bxkMo3BLgksqJLxCz84qFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 14:24:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/pope-francis-visit-uae-historic-trip-gulf-181206113104777.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pope Francis to visit UAE in historic trip to the Gulf&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pope Francis will make a historic visit to Abu Dhabi in the United Arab Emirates in February to attend an interfaith meeting, the Vatican announced on Thursday. The trip, the latest by the pope to a Muslim nation, will take place from February 3-5. The Vatican said the pope had accepted an invitation from Sheikh Mohammed bin Zayed Al Nahyan, crown prince of Abu Dhabi, and the Catholic community there. "This visit, like the one to Egypt, shows the fundamental importance the Holy Father gives to inter-religious dialogue," spokesman Greg Burke said. "Pope Francis visiting the Arab world is a p...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Francis to become first pope to visit Arabian peninsula - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-pope-uae/francis-to-become-first-pope-to-visit-arabian-peninsula-idUSKBN1O515R</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKNvn9kD243Jgt2IxiCSbuUqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 15:19:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-pope-uae/francis-to-become-first-pope-to-visit-arabian-peninsula-idUSKBN1O515R" target="_blank"&gt;Francis to become first pope to visit Arabian peninsula&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first visit by a pope to the Arabian peninsula will take place in February when Francis travels to Abu Dhabi in the United Arab Emirates, the Vatican said on Thursday. The Feb. 3-5 trip, Francis' latest to a predominantly Muslim nation, will be centered around the theme of inter-religious peace. The Vatican said the pope had accepted an invitation from Sheikh Mohammed bin Zayed al-Nahyan, Crown Prince of Abu Dhabi, and the tiny Catholic community there. He will attend an inter-faith meeting. In a statement, Bishop Paul Hinder, head of the Roman Catholic Arabian Vicariate of Southern Ara...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Pope Criticizes Homosexuality Among Catholic Clergy - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/pope-criticizes-homosexuality-among-catholic-clergy/4689288.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC5yDAXRslVnqI0rv1qEGdUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw-pwi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 14:53:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/pope-criticizes-homosexuality-among-catholic-clergy/4689288.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pope Criticizes Homosexuality Among Catholic Clergy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pope Francis has expressed serious concern about homosexual behavior among some members of the Catholic clergy, saying this is happening as homosexuality becomes fashionable in society. He said the Church must be demanding in choosing its candidates for the priesthood and stressed that the vow of celibacy must be observed. His comments were made in a long interview with a Spanish missionary priest published this week in a book titled The Strength of Vocation, released in several languages. Pope Francis has made his clearest comments on homosexuality in a new interview saying there is no p...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Australian ex-archbishop cleared of child abuse cover-up charges - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/australian-archbishop-cleared-child-abuse-cover-charges-181206094122808.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPYeiWFJU35PGOJXsdcFh88qFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 14:25:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/australian-archbishop-cleared-child-abuse-cover-charges-181206094122808.html" target="_blank"&gt;Australian ex-archbishop cleared of child abuse cover-up charges&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;An Australian court has overturned the conviction of a former archbishop who was the world's most senior Catholic cleric held guilty of concealing child sex abuse. The court on Thursday said the prosecutors failed to prove their case against Philip Wilson, 68, beyond reasonable doubt. Wilson was charged with concealing crimes by late paedophile priest Jim Fletcher in the Hunter region of New South Wales in the 1970s. Wilson was sentenced to 12-month imprisonment in May, becoming one of the highest-ranked Australian church officials convicted of covering up child sex abuse. 181020150529306 "...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Pope reforms Vatican City State govt - Agenzia ANSA</title><link>http://www.ansa.it/english/news/vatican/2018/12/06/pope-reforms-vatican-city-state-govt_77fcca5a-e0bf-43b2-8fe7-17eea40bfb80.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI__FOpcVu7mJfdwpAUwJCAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowsP-hCTCXv5cCMJSC0QU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 16:19:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.ansa.it/english/news/vatican/2018/12/06/pope-reforms-vatican-city-state-govt_77fcca5a-e0bf-43b2-8fe7-17eea40bfb80.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pope reforms Vatican City State govt&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Agenzia ANSA&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(ANSA) - Vatican City, December 6 - The Holy See said Thursday that Pope Francis has reformed how the Vatican City State is governed via a motu proprio document. The document, signed November 25, brings in a new law for the tiny state's government that will come into force on June 7, 2019, and replace previous regulation dating back to 2002. Cardinal Giuseppe Bertello, the president of the Governorate of Vatican City State, worked on the document with a special commission. The aim of the reform is pursue the aims of "rationalization, economizing, simplification". Read the full arti...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.ansa.it">Agenzia ANSA</source></item><item><title>Pope to visit Abu Dhabi in February - Agenzia ANSA</title><link>http://www.ansamed.info/ansamed/en/news/sections/politics/2018/12/06/pope-to-visit-abu-dhabi-in-february_d832c244-f8f8-4855-8e76-5d9615e2e4eb.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPXLsyW9UW_4j5yyeKpvJq0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowsP-hCTCXv5cCMIWA0QU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 12:10:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.ansamed.info/ansamed/en/news/sections/politics/2018/12/06/pope-to-visit-abu-dhabi-in-february_d832c244-f8f8-4855-8e76-5d9615e2e4eb.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pope to visit Abu Dhabi in February&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Agenzia ANSA&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(ANSAmed) - Vatican City, December 6 - The Vatican said Thursday that Pope Francis will visit Abu Dhabi in February. "In response to the invitation of His Highness Sheikh Mohammed bin Zayed Al Nahyan, Crown Prince of Abu Dhabi, His Holiness Pope Francis will visit Abu Dhabi (United Arab Emirates) from 3 to 5 February 2019, to participate in the International Interfaith Meeting on 'Human Fraternity'," Vatican spokesman Greg Burke said in a statement. "The visit will take place also in response to the invitation of the Catholic Church in the United Arab Emirates". Read the full article on Ans...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.ansamed.info">Agenzia ANSA</source></item><item><title>Queer Catholics Condemn Pope's Claim That Being Gay Has Become 'Fashionable' - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/pope-francis-homosexuality-fashionable-gay-priests_us_5c06a557e4b0cd916fb08010</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMg3DF58xn9gEX3bAz1xTUYqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJ2HuAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 22:06:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/pope-francis-homosexuality-fashionable-gay-priests_us_5c06a557e4b0cd916fb08010" target="_blank"&gt;Queer Catholics Condemn Pope's Claim That Being Gay Has Become 'Fashionable'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pope Francis has suggested that being gay has become “fashionable” in some modern-day societies ― a remark that has prompted concern among queer Catholics. In an interview with a Spanish priest about religious vocations, Francis reportedly said that there is “no place for this kind of affection” in the lives of Roman Catholic priests, religious brothers and religious sisters. “In our societies, it even seems homosexuality is fashionable. And this mentality, in some way, also influences the life of the church,” Francis was quoted as saying in the interview, according to the Associated Press....&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Advent a time to make peace says Pope - Agenzia ANSA</title><link>http://www.ansa.it/english/news/2018/12/04/advent-a-time-to-make-peace-says-pope_159ade81-9cc3-4cf8-9e8e-fadd33ff82af.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECZU-nAf4ae7jqRfTD812oQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowsP-hCTCXv5cCMJSC0QU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 14:10:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.ansa.it/english/news/2018/12/04/advent-a-time-to-make-peace-says-pope_159ade81-9cc3-4cf8-9e8e-fadd33ff82af.html" target="_blank"&gt;Advent a time to make peace says Pope&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Agenzia ANSA&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(ANSA) - Vatican City, December 4 - At his morning Mass at the Casa Santa Marta on Tuesday, Pope Francis spoke about how Christians can prepare for Christmas during Advent by building peace in one's soul, in the family and in the world through humility, according to Vatican News. The Pope said that peacemaking consists in not talking evil of and harming others, a bit like imitating God, who humbled Himself. Pointing to the pastoral scene evoked by Isaiah in the first reading, where the wolf and the lamb, and the leopard and the kid live side by side harmlessly, the Pope said the prophet ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.ansa.it">Agenzia ANSA</source></item><item><title>Philippines' Duterte: Kill those 'useless' Catholic bishops - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/philippines-duterte-kill-useless-catholic-bishops-181205132220894.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPiG4xFFfro9SScp2tYMzFsqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 18:18:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/philippines-duterte-kill-useless-catholic-bishops-181205132220894.html" target="_blank"&gt;Philippines' Duterte: Kill those 'useless' Catholic bishops&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Philippine President Rodrigo Duterte said his country's Catholic bishops are "useless fools" and should be "killed" as the controversial leader stepped up his attack on the church, which has opposed his deadly war on drugs in the Southeast Asian archipelago. In a speech at the presidential palace on Wednesday, Duterte was quoted in local news reports as saying in a mix of Filipino and English: "These bishops that you guys have, kill them. They are useless fools. All they do is criticise." In an address to government officials later, Duterte also called the Catholic Church "the most hypocrit...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>‘Kill them’: Duterte loses patience with ‘useless fools’ at Catholic Church - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/news/445697-duterte-attacks-catholic-church/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAG2sC8o0IVYc7-LpbguLYIqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww_oMo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 04:11:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/news/445697-duterte-attacks-catholic-church/" target="_blank"&gt;‘Kill them’: Duterte loses patience with ‘useless fools’ at Catholic Church&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Philippines President Rodrigo Duterte is letting everyone know he's had enough with the Catholic Church's opposition to his policies, deriding its leaders as "useless fools" who worship a "stupid" god. Slamming the Catholic Church as "the most hypocritical institution" for casting doubt on his extrajudicial drug war, the outspoken leader ridiculed Catholic bishops as "useless fools," exhorting his people to "kill them" in a speech on Wednesday. He also claimed that 90 percent of priests are homosexuals lacking any standing to "postulate on my morality." These bishops that you guys have, kil...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Pope's accuser returns to accuse brother in inheritance saga - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/cb0683ee85c54871a9e00f48f9c7b13a</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIUxb9xyW_WWM0pYqzSLSTYqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 18:07:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/cb0683ee85c54871a9e00f48f9c7b13a" target="_blank"&gt;Pope's accuser returns to accuse brother in inheritance saga&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;VATICAN CITY (AP) — The retired Vatican ambassador who convulsed the Holy See with accusations of sex abuse cover-up is offering his side of the story in a different scandal: a family fight over a multi-million dollar inheritance. Archbishop Carlo Maria Vigano is trying to explain an Italian court ruling requiring him to pay his brother, who also is a priest, 1.8 million euros. The court's decision generated headlines given Vigano's unprecedented call for Pope Francis to resign over alleged failures in addressing clergy sex abuse. In a statement Monday, Vigano said his brother had originall...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>It's time for Catholics to demand this from the church - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/03/opinions/catholics-sex-abuse-crisis-pope-francis-snyder/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENeJyEPR0Qt6-Iz3-T8z-q8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 22:51:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/03/opinions/catholics-sex-abuse-crisis-pope-francis-snyder/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;It's time for Catholics to demand this from the church&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Paul Snyder is a Catholic deacon in the Diocese of Buffalo, New York. He is also the Chairman of Snyder Corp., a privately held investment company founded in 1958 with interests in the hospitality, real estate, software and transportation industries, and a Henry Crown Fellow of the Aspen Institute. The opinions expressed in this commentary are solely those of the author. View more opinion on CNN. We all regret some decisions in life; for me, it was my choice not to learn Spanish. So, in my search to find the one word that could capture the essence of Pope Francis, it is with much irony that...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Disobedient nun saved my life, pope says in new book - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-pope-nun-book/disobedient-nun-saved-my-life-pope-says-in-new-book-idUSKBN1O10MT</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC4MOxehPT4As9ELszhuoccqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 10:49:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-pope-nun-book/disobedient-nun-saved-my-life-pope-says-in-new-book-idUSKBN1O10MT" target="_blank"&gt;Disobedient nun saved my life, pope says in new book&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A hard-headed hospital nun who disobeyed doctor's orders saved the life of Pope Francis some six decades ago when he risked dying of pneumonia, the pope reveals in a new book. When Francis was studying for the priesthood in Latin America in the 1950s he caught pneumonia, but it was mis-diagnosed by the seminary's doctor, who thought is was the flu, and one day had to be rushed to hospital "on the point of death," he says. A doctor at the hospital realized it was pneumonia and ordered staff to give the young Jorge Mario Bergoglio two types of antibiotics. But a hospital nun named Cornelia Ca...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Pope, Abbas Discuss Jerusalem at First Meeting After US Embassy Move - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/pope-mahmoud-abbas-discuss-jerusalem-at-first-meeting-after-us-embassy-move/4685157.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEYQgASZHlmGHbqUD2r5yp4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw6pwi</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 22:25:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/pope-mahmoud-abbas-discuss-jerusalem-at-first-meeting-after-us-embassy-move/4685157.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pope, Abbas Discuss Jerusalem at First Meeting After US Embassy Move&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Vatican expressed concern Monday over the status of Jerusalem as Pope Francis and Palestinian President Mahmoud Abbas held their first meeting since the United States stirred international anxiety by moving its embassy there. The two embraced and kissed on the cheek as the pontiff welcomed Abbas to a library in the Vatican's Apostolic Palace for a private, 20-minute meeting. "Particular attention was reserved for the status of Jerusalem, underlining the importance of recognizing and preserving its identity and the universal value of the holy City for the three Abrahamic religions," a Va...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Two States, Jerusalem at center of Pope and Abbas meeting - Agenzia ANSA</title><link>http://www.ansamed.info/ansamed/en/news/sections/politics/2018/12/03/two-states-jerusalem-at-center-of-pope-and-abbas-meeting_18cc81b2-99b3-4d54-88ee-a7e73cec493f.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEpXYAEEI1eoyewRLIp-m_4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowsP-hCTCXv5cCMIWA0QU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 15:18:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.ansamed.info/ansamed/en/news/sections/politics/2018/12/03/two-states-jerusalem-at-center-of-pope-and-abbas-meeting_18cc81b2-99b3-4d54-88ee-a7e73cec493f.html" target="_blank"&gt;Two States, Jerusalem at center of Pope and Abbas meeting&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Agenzia ANSA&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(ANSAmed) - VATICAN CITY, DECEMBER 3 - Pope Francis and Palestinian President Mahmoud Abbas on Monday spoke about ''the reconciliation path within the Palestinian population as well efforts to reactivate the peace process between Israelis and Palestinians to reach a two-State solution'', the Vatican said. ''Particular attention was devoted to the status of Jerusalem, stressing the importance of recognizing and preserving the identity and universal value of the holy city for the three Abrahamic religions''. The Vatican described the hearing as ''cordial'' and said the pontiff and the Palesti...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.ansamed.info">Agenzia ANSA</source></item><item><title>Catholic priests must resist ‘fashionable’ homosexuality or leave clergy – Pope Francis - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/news/445417-pope-francis-fashionable-homosexuality/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGq0BhaOEK5hzUW6eU7GGvYqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww_oMo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 07:59:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/news/445417-pope-francis-fashionable-homosexuality/" target="_blank"&gt;Catholic priests must resist ‘fashionable’ homosexuality or leave clergy – Pope Francis&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pope Francis has bemoaned the allure of “fashionable” homosexuality, stressing that gay priests must forever remain in the closet – or leave the Catholic Church. The pontiff likens homosexuality to a modern – and apparently dangerous – trend in his new book, ‘The Strength of a Vocation’, which is set to be released Monday in 10 languages. “In our societies it even seems that homosexuality is fashionable and that mentality, in some way, also influences the life of the church,” Francis wrote. “Therefore, the Church recommends that people with that kind of ingrained tendency should not be acce...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Be celibate or leave the priesthood, pope tells gay priests - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-pope-homosexuals-book/be-celibate-or-leave-the-priesthood-pope-tells-gay-priests-idUSKBN1O10K7</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPC-D-hxGmhUbbEJfh08hNoqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 11:19:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-pope-homosexuals-book/be-celibate-or-leave-the-priesthood-pope-tells-gay-priests-idUSKBN1O10K7" target="_blank"&gt;Be celibate or leave the priesthood, pope tells gay priests&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Men with deep-rooted homosexual tendencies should not be admitted to the Catholic clergy, and it would be better for priests who are actively gay to leave rather than lead a double life, Pope Francis says in a new book. While he has previously spoken of the need for better screening of candidates for the religious life, his comments suggesting that priests who cannot keep their vows of celibacy should leave are some of his clearest to date. Francis made the comments in a book-length interview with Spanish priest Fernando Prado called "The Strength of Vocation", in which he discusses the cha...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Pope, Abbas discuss Jerusalem at first meeting after U.S. embassy move - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-mideast-vatican-abbas/pope-abbas-discuss-jerusalem-at-first-meeting-after-us-embassy-move-idUSKBN1O21XS</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEINVY62UAlc7NgJyoUv7xnkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 16:03:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-mideast-vatican-abbas/pope-abbas-discuss-jerusalem-at-first-meeting-after-us-embassy-move-idUSKBN1O21XS" target="_blank"&gt;Pope, Abbas discuss Jerusalem at first meeting after U.S. embassy move&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Vatican expressed concern over the status of Jerusalem on Monday as Pope Francis and Palestinian President Mahmoud Abbas held their first meeting since the United States stirred international anxiety by moving its embassy there. The two embraced and kissed on the cheek as the pontiff welcomed Abbas to a library in the Vatican's Apostolic Palace for a private, 20-minute meeting. "Particular attention was reserved for the status of Jerusalem, underlining the importance of recognizing and preserving its identity and the universal value of the holy City for the three Abrahamic religions," a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Strip clubs are out as Vatican discusses what to do with growing number of deconsecrated churches - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/11/29/strip-clubs-vatican-discusses-do-growing-number-deconsecrated/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN1AwhYrw8GHUVfLa7FG8icqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 15:33:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/11/29/strip-clubs-vatican-discusses-do-growing-number-deconsecrated/" target="_blank"&gt;Strip clubs are out as Vatican discusses what to do with growing number of deconsecrated churches&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;From strip joints to nightclubs and pizzerias, the Vatican is urging Catholic countries around the world not to allow deconsecrated churches to be used for profane purposes, in the first conference dedicated to the issue. Falling congregations, a lack of clergy and crippling maintenance costs means that thousands of Catholic churches around the world are being decommissioned and turned into restaurants, pubs, cafes and even skateboarding venues. More than 500 Catholic churches have closed down in Germany since 2000, while in Canada one fifth of Catholic churches were deconsecrated in the sa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Pope Francis Goes Full Homophobic, Now ‘Very Worried’ About Homosexuality in the Church - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/pope-francis-goes-full-homophobic-now-very-worried-about-homosexuality-in-the-church</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK6KnPsHzsfllsrmi--aadgqFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMLzdlwI</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 15:37:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/pope-francis-goes-full-homophobic-now-very-worried-about-homosexuality-in-the-church" target="_blank"&gt;Pope Francis Goes Full Homophobic, Now ‘Very Worried’ About Homosexuality in the Church&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tiziana Fabi/AFP/GETTY ROME—Remember back in 2013, shortly after Pope Francis was elected when he shocked the world with his words: “If a person seeks God and has goodwill, then who am I to judge,” when asked about a gay priest? What was then seen to be a change in decades of dogma sent shockwaves around the world, landing the pontiff on the cover of Advocate and winning him praise among LGBTQ groups and lapsed Catholics. In some ways, Francis has been eating his words ever since, constantly called to explain by conservatives in the church what he meant. Now it seems Francis isn't mincing h...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Pope Francis says being gay is a 'fashion' to which the clergy is susceptible - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/12/02/pope-francis-says-gay-fashion-clergy-susceptible/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGVHZQkIUU_qDeEyBbIPoaMqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 14:48:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/12/02/pope-francis-says-gay-fashion-clergy-susceptible/" target="_blank"&gt;Pope Francis says being gay is a 'fashion' to which the clergy is susceptible&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pope Francis is "concerned" about what he described as the "serious issue" of homosexuality, saying in an interview published Saturday that being gay was a "fashion" to which the clergy is susceptible. "The issue of homosexuality is a very serious issue that must be adequately discerned from the beginning with the candidates," the pontiff said with regards to would-be priests. "In our societies it even seems that homosexuality is fashionable and that mentality, in some way, also influences the life of the church," he says in the book 'The Strength of a Vocation', released in Italy on Saturd...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Pope Francis says gay people in Catholic clergy ‘worries’ him in new book - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/europe/pope-francis-gay-people-catholic-clergy-homosexuality-lgbt-clergy-vatican-interview-a8662841.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEj1YGW6_QLr5njG5ctuQmsqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 18:37:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/europe/pope-francis-gay-people-catholic-clergy-homosexuality-lgbt-clergy-vatican-interview-a8662841.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pope Francis says gay people in Catholic clergy ‘worries’ him in new book&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pope Francis has been quoted in a soon-to-be published book saying that having gay people in the clergy "is something that worries me" and remarking that some societies are considering homosexuality a "fashionable" lifestyle. Italian newspaper Corriere della Sera's website ran excerpts of the book on Saturday in the form of an interview that Pope Francis gave about religious vocations. Pope Francis was quoted as describing homosexuality within the walls of seminaries, convents and other religious places where clergy live as "a very serious question." "In our societies, it even seems homosex...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Pope says he's worried about homosexuality in the priesthood - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/420b7a6215874971bff9c98577b6c5c5</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELI9vHqdnIJMLrLLGAhw74oqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 15:32:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/420b7a6215874971bff9c98577b6c5c5" target="_blank"&gt;Pope says he's worried about homosexuality in the priesthood&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;VATICAN CITY (AP) — Pope Francis has been quoted in a soon-to-be published book as saying that having gays in the clergy "is something that worries me" and remarking that some societies are considering homosexuality a "fashionable" lifestyle. Italian daily Corriere della Sera's website Saturday ran excerpts of the book in the form of an interview that Francis gave about religious vocations. Francis was quoted as describing homosexuality within the walls of seminaries, convents and other religious places where clergy live as "a very serious question." "In our societies, it even seems homosex...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Homosexuality in clergy concerns me-pope - Agenzia ANSA</title><link>http://www.ansa.it/english/news/vatican/2018/11/30/homosexuality-in-clergy-concerns-me-pope_bea4be4b-163d-4fc6-a983-1a88919ab162.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIVAAVknTQEgLsfTO-ewNPsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowsP-hCTCXv5cCMJSC0QU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 18:41:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.ansa.it/english/news/vatican/2018/11/30/homosexuality-in-clergy-concerns-me-pope_bea4be4b-163d-4fc6-a983-1a88919ab162.html" target="_blank"&gt;Homosexuality in clergy concerns me-pope&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Agenzia ANSA&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(ANSA) - Rome, November 30 - Pope Francis is concerned about homosexuality in the clergy, the pope says in a forthcoming book-interview with Claretian missionary Fernando Prado entitled La Forza della Vocazione (The Force of Vocation). Homosexuality in the clergy and the consecrated life "is something that concerns me," he says. "It is a very serious issue", the pope says. "In our societies it even seems that homosexuality is fashionable and this mentality, in some ways, also influences the life of the Church". Read the full article on ANSA English&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.ansa.it">Agenzia ANSA</source></item><item><title>Pope lets young boy roll around on Vatican stage - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-29/little-boy-joins-pope-francis-on-stage/10565872</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECgOplIqh_-0YEVsHvg5OekqFwgEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDD7kIkG</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 00:41:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-29/little-boy-joins-pope-francis-on-stage/10565872" target="_blank"&gt;Pope lets young boy roll around on Vatican stage&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A young boy has hilariously upstaged Pope Francis at the Vatican as he went on stage and rolled around the floor during the weekly general audience. He also took a keen interest towards the colourful Swiss guard on the platform. Pope Francis was addressing the packed hall as the boy freely walked up the marble stairs towards him. The child broke through security and went to pull on the sleeve of a Swiss guard on the podium, just metres from the Pope, it appeared as if he was checking to see if the guard was real. At one stage the boy was joined by a little girl, presumably his sister, who d...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Pope hails economic, moral value of work - Agenzia ANSA</title><link>http://www.ansa.it/english/news/vatican/2018/11/28/pope-hails-economic-moral-value-of-work_ebd593b6-e17e-4657-9635-661c6194e666.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDPOZUalNfA-UX27qodP9g8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowsP-hCTCXv5cCMJSC0QU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 14:32:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.ansa.it/english/news/vatican/2018/11/28/pope-hails-economic-moral-value-of-work_ebd593b6-e17e-4657-9635-661c6194e666.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pope hails economic, moral value of work&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Agenzia ANSA&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(ANSA) - Vatican City, November 28 - Pope Francis on Wednesday hailed the "economic and moral value" of work. Speaking at his weekly general audience in the Paul VI Hall, Francis also said "you cannot follow Jesus if you are weighed down by baggage". He also recalled a Polish family wiped out for having helped Jews in WWII. The pope also thanked some Franciscan monks from Syria saying he understood and shared their suffering. During the audience, a young boy climbed onto the pope's said, prompting Francis to quip, "he's undisciplined, he's Argentinian". Read the full article on ANS...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.ansa.it">Agenzia ANSA</source></item><item><title>'Unruly' young boy upstages Pope Francis - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-pope-boy/unruly-young-boy-upstages-pope-francis-idUSKCN1NX18J</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKXQlFRZVct4CcSkWs5kLxgqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:54:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-pope-boy/unruly-young-boy-upstages-pope-francis-idUSKCN1NX18J" target="_blank"&gt;'Unruly' young boy upstages Pope Francis&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A young boy upstaged Pope Francis on Wednesday, escaping from his mother and running onto the papal podium at a general audience, tugging on the hand of a Swiss guardsman and playing behind the pontiff's chair. The boy's mother briefly spoke to the pope as she tried to pull the child away, saying that he was mute. Pope Francis told her to let him carry on playing. "This child cannot speak. He is mute. But he can communicate," the pope told hundreds of pilgrims. "And he has something that got me thinking: he is free. Unruly ... but he is free," he added to laughter. "Let's ask the grace (of ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Christians must provide credible witness - Agenzia ANSA</title><link>http://www.ansa.it/english/news/vatican/2018/11/30/christians-must-provide-credible-witness_79ae189f-a6c4-4e31-81dc-db77d685cb34.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEr52-7yxpsbJxLnWs-UbIYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowsP-hCTCXv5cCMJSC0QU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 13:40:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.ansa.it/english/news/vatican/2018/11/30/christians-must-provide-credible-witness_79ae189f-a6c4-4e31-81dc-db77d685cb34.html" target="_blank"&gt;Christians must provide credible witness&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Agenzia ANSA&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ANSA) - Vatican City, November 30 - Christians must provide credible witness with their lives, POpe Francis said Friday, according to Vatican News. On the Feast of St Andrew Pope Francis addressed believers at Mass in the Casa Santa Marta urging them to be close to the Church of Constantinople, of which Saint Andrew the Apostle is the patron. Pope Francis invited the faithful to "leave everything in order to go forward in proclamation and witness, just as Peter and Andrew did". The Pope also invited Christians to be close to the Church of Constantinople and he prayed for unity betw...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.ansa.it">Agenzia ANSA</source></item><item><title>Church assets can be sold to help poor if necessary - Pope - Agenzia ANSA</title><link>http://www.ansa.it/english/news/vatican/2018/11/29/church-assets-cd-be-sold-for-poor-pope_510b9c44-053e-404b-86a8-c093392b2a4a.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENPx0Sd4pyFEkojdsXn8Fw8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowsP-hCTCXv5cCMJSC0QU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 13:38:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.ansa.it/english/news/vatican/2018/11/29/church-assets-cd-be-sold-for-poor-pope_510b9c44-053e-404b-86a8-c093392b2a4a.html" target="_blank"&gt;Church assets can be sold to help poor if necessary - Pope&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Agenzia ANSA&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(ANSA) - Vatican City, November 29 - Pope Francis has mooted the idea of Catholic Church assets being sold in some cases to help the poor, while stressing that this is only one of several options. "The (Church's) cultural assets are directed towards the charitable activities carried out by the ecclesiastical community," the pope said in a message to participants at a conference on decommissioning places of worship and management of ecclesiastical cultural heritage at the Pontifical Gregorian University. While stressing the "duty to protect and conserve the assets of the Church, in particula...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.ansa.it">Agenzia ANSA</source></item><item><title>Search warrant at Texas archdiocese seeks 'secret archives' of priest accused of sex abuse - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/28/us/archdiocese-galveston-houston-abuse-raid/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPc4vje_JoFG7QIQo__9JLEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMIrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 18:54:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/28/us/archdiocese-galveston-houston-abuse-raid/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Search warrant at Texas archdiocese seeks 'secret archives' of priest accused of sex abuse&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The "secret archives" of a Catholic priest accused of sexual abuse were the subject of a search warrant executed Wednesday at the Archdiocese of Galveston-Houston in Texas, according to a prosecutor. The warrant is the fourth executed in the investigation of abuse allegations against the Rev. Manuel LaRosa-Lopez, who was accused of sexually abusing an unnamed woman in Conroe, Texas, in 2000. The woman's father reported the alleged abuse to the church before the family left the country, and LaRosa-Lopez was moved from the parish, according to the arrest warrant filed in September. Investigat...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Polish Church asks for forgiveness for pedophilia cases - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-poland-church-paedhophilia-idUSKCN1NO2D6</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO91CS3l4Aa55Don35L9jMsqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 21:03:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-poland-church-paedhophilia-idUSKCN1NO2D6" target="_blank"&gt;Polish Church asks for forgiveness for pedophilia cases&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Poland's Catholic Church on Monday asked victims of sexual abuse by the clergy for forgiveness, a month after an appeal court upheld a ruling stating the Church was responsible for the crimes of one if its priests. The Catholic Church worldwide is reeling from crises involving sexual abuse of minors, damaging confidence in the Church in Chile, the United States, Australia and Ireland and other countries. The Polish court of appeal upheld last month a landmark ruling granting a million zloty ($260,000) in compensation to a victim of sexual abuse by a Catholic priest, accepting that the Churc...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Pope to meet with young inmates, AIDS patients in Panama - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/37d20ce211964365bf54ce71d0efbee2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELb0aofWBi006SjmRHLxgV8qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 17:46:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/37d20ce211964365bf54ce71d0efbee2" target="_blank"&gt;Pope to meet with young inmates, AIDS patients in Panama&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;VATICAN CITY (AP) — The Vatican is confirming Pope Francis will travel to Panama in January for the Catholic Church's big youth rally, and says he'll also spend time there with juvenile delinquents and people suffering from AIDS. History's first Latin American pope will be making his first visit to Central America, though he has been to Mexico, Cuba and several countries in South America. The Jan. 23-28 trip includes meetings with Panamanian authorities, the region's bishops and activities of World Youth Day, the once-every-three-year rally instituted by St. John Paul II to invigorate Catho...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Sins born from evil desires says pope - Agenzia ANSA</title><link>http://www.ansa.it/english/news/vatican/2018/11/21/sins-born-from-evil-desires-says-pope_300a5a1f-461c-4cdd-864f-43a6f6ff9a80.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECdbgVBqCjMH3W6a8iK-I3sqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowsP-hCTCXv5cCMJSC0QU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 13:21:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.ansa.it/english/news/vatican/2018/11/21/sins-born-from-evil-desires-says-pope_300a5a1f-461c-4cdd-864f-43a6f6ff9a80.html" target="_blank"&gt;Sins born from evil desires says pope&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Agenzia ANSA&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(ANSA) - Vatican City, November 21 - All sins are born from evil desires, Pope Francis told his weekly general audience on Wednesday. "Free yourselves" from these desires, he told the faithful in a packed St Peter's Square. Read the full article on ANSA English&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.ansa.it">Agenzia ANSA</source></item><item><title>Pope Taps Experts, US Cardinal to Help Prep for Abuse Summit - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/pope-taps-experts-us-cardinal-to-help-prep-for-abuse-summit/4671140.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAgWVxVKI6v8BnQwPG_zqH4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 16:32:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/pope-taps-experts-us-cardinal-to-help-prep-for-abuse-summit/4671140.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pope Taps Experts, US Cardinal to Help Prep for Abuse Summit&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pope Francis named the Vatican's top sex abuse investigator and a close U.S. ally to an organizing committee for a February abuse prevention summit whose stakes have grown after the Holy See blocked U.S. bishops from taking action to address the scandal. Abuse survivors and women working at the Vatican will also contribute to the preparatory committee. Notably absent from the lineup announced Friday was Boston Cardinal Sean O'Malley, who heads the pope's sex abuse advisory commission, though one of his members, the Rev. Hans Zollner, is the point-person for the group. In addition to Zollner...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Mute boy storms stage at Pope Francis audience, steals the show by playing &amp; annoying Swiss Guard - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/news/445077-child-steals-show-pope-vatican/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELMxe92J_6h3qRFpumhqLYsqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww_oMo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 16:44:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/news/445077-child-steals-show-pope-vatican/" target="_blank"&gt;Mute boy storms stage at Pope Francis audience, steals the show by playing &amp; annoying Swiss Guard&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;When Pope Francis is in the room all eyes are usually focused on him – but that wasn’t the case Wednesday when one very excited little boy stole the limelight, breaking through crowds to play and roll around at the Pope’s feet. To the horror of his mother, the boy managed to get free of her clutches and ran onto the papa podium during a general audience with the Pope at the Vatican. The child ran on for a closer look – and began pulling on the sleeves of a Swiss guardsman and playing behind the pontiff’s chair. In an attempt to reign in her wild child, the boy’s mother approached the podium...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Pope calls for Christian statesmen - Agenzia ANSA</title><link>http://www.ansa.it/english/news/vatican/2018/11/23/pope-calls-for-christian-statesmen_f809bb84-9bf0-45ce-b5e3-6037112b2003.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE2gKDlQ77uMCe4BjBRzsecqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowsP-hCTCXv5cCMJSC0QU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 13:08:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.ansa.it/english/news/vatican/2018/11/23/pope-calls-for-christian-statesmen_f809bb84-9bf0-45ce-b5e3-6037112b2003.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pope calls for Christian statesmen&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Agenzia ANSA&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(ANSA) - Rome, November 23 - Pope Francis on Friday said today's complex political times called for Christian politicians of caliber. "The complexity of Italian and international political life requires lay faithful and statesman of high human and Christian substance at the service of the common good," Francis said during an audience with members of the Giorgio La Pira foundation. The Argentine pontiff said that politicians should not "give into temptation" and seek personal profit rather than pursuing the interests of the whole community. Read the full article on ANSA English&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.ansa.it">Agenzia ANSA</source></item><item><title>Pope decries that 'wealthy few' feast on what belongs to all - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/c183ed8b9269499ea0f537d9e8a9f2b6</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED-mjh_5prJpJlUxmgYeJ1IqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 13:55:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/c183ed8b9269499ea0f537d9e8a9f2b6" target="_blank"&gt;Pope decries that 'wealthy few' feast on what belongs to all&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;VATICAN CITY (AP) — Championing the cause of the poor, Pope Francis on Sunday lamented that "the wealthy few" enjoy what, "in justice, belongs to all" and said Christians cannot remain indifferent to the growing cries of the exploited and the indigent, including migrants. Francis invited about 6,000 poor people as well as some of the volunteers who help them to the splendor of St. Peter's Basilica where he celebrated Mass on a day the Catholic Church dedicates to the needy. Later, he sat down with 1,500 of the indigent for a lunch of lasagna, chicken, mashed potatoes and tiramisu in a Vatic...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>We are brothers pope tells Jews - Agenzia ANSA</title><link>http://www.ansa.it/english/news/vatican/2018/11/22/we-are-brothers-pope-tells-jews_3cf788cb-e81b-4565-8358-77273cf059a4.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJqtHfDsYsNcWfgv6PlT5g0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowsP-hCTCXv5cCMJSC0QU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 14:42:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.ansa.it/english/news/vatican/2018/11/22/we-are-brothers-pope-tells-jews_3cf788cb-e81b-4565-8358-77273cf059a4.html" target="_blank"&gt;We are brothers pope tells Jews&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Agenzia ANSA&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(ANSA) - Vatican City, November 22 - Pope Francis on Thursday told Jews "we are bothers and must work together for peace". The pope received in private audience the members of the bilateral commission of the delegations of the Great rabbinate of Israel and the Commission of the Holy See for religious relations with Judaism, who met in Rome on November 18-20 on the theme "The dignity of being human: teachings of Judaism and Catholicism regarding children". "We are brothers and the children of a One God, and we must work together for peace, hand in hand," Francis said. Read the full art...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.ansa.it">Agenzia ANSA</source></item><item><title>Loyalty is free and mature relationship - Agenzia ANSA</title><link>http://www.ansa.it/english/news/vatican/2018/11/20/loyalty-is-free-and-mature-relationship_65a9bc4f-e19c-488b-8ae9-a2a07dfc5cbc.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHyCXy-GKDClkQyO2y6aA6UqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowsP-hCTCXv5cCMJSC0QU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 13:52:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.ansa.it/english/news/vatican/2018/11/20/loyalty-is-free-and-mature-relationship_65a9bc4f-e19c-488b-8ae9-a2a07dfc5cbc.html" target="_blank"&gt;Loyalty is free and mature relationship&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Agenzia ANSA&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(ANSA) - Vatican City, November 20 - Pope Francis tweeted Tuesday that "loyalty is the characteristic of a free, mature responsible human relationship". Read the full article on ANSA English&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.ansa.it">Agenzia ANSA</source></item><item><title>Pope Francis Laments On Day Of The Poor: The Rich Are Winning - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/pope-francis-laments-that-the-rich-are-winning_us_5bf23693e4b0f32bd58ac948</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKK-K70qr7uiOL6PL3K-v-oqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:48:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/pope-francis-laments-that-the-rich-are-winning_us_5bf23693e4b0f32bd58ac948" target="_blank"&gt;Pope Francis Laments On Day Of The Poor: The Rich Are Winning&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pope Francis warned Sunday in his weekly sermon that calls for help from the poor are growing stronger — yet they continue to be ignored as the wealthy grab more resources that belong to everyone. “The cry of the poor daily becomes stronger, but heard less, drowned out by the din of the rich few, who grow ever fewer and more rich,” he said, the Vatican reported. “It is the cry of all those forced to flee their homes and native land for an uncertain future. It is the cry of entire peoples, deprived even of the great natural resources at their disposal ... while the wealthy few feast on what...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Catholic nuns denounce 'culture of silence and secrecy' surrounding sex abuse in church - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/europe/catholic-church-nuns-sex-abuse-pope-francis-international-union-superiors-general-a8650566.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEChuuvRbmXIrN-e45-_PPdEqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2018 00:28:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/europe/catholic-church-nuns-sex-abuse-pope-francis-international-union-superiors-general-a8650566.html" target="_blank"&gt;Catholic nuns denounce 'culture of silence and secrecy' surrounding sex abuse in church&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Catholic Church‘s global organisation of nuns has denounced the “culture of silence and secrecy” surrounding sexual abuse in the church. The International Union of Superiors General, which represents more than 500,000 sisters worldwide, urged nuns who have been abused to report the crimes to police and their superiors. The group vowed to help nuns who have been abused to find the courage to report it, and pledged to help victims heal and seek justice. The statement, issued on the eve of the UN-designated International Day for the Elimination of Violence Against Women, was the first from...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Pope taps Texan bishop Garcia for Monterey, California - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/86a257ed640c47a0a09b5ae25b73f678</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHjJ-LWKEiHj0seZ6k0mUHYqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 12:25:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/86a257ed640c47a0a09b5ae25b73f678" target="_blank"&gt;Pope taps Texan bishop Garcia for Monterey, California&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;VATICAN CITY (AP) — Pope Francis has named Monsignor Daniel Garcia, currently an auxiliary bishop in Texas, to take over as bishop of Monterey, California. The Vatican said Tuesday that the 58-year-old Garcia would replace Bishop Richard Garcia, who died earlier this year. Bishop Daniel Garcia has been an auxiliary bishop of Austin since 2015. The diocese of Monterey is heavily influenced by the controversial 18th century St. Junipero Serra, who created a mission there as part of a chain of missions up and down California to evangelize Native Americans. Francis canonized Serra during his 20...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>You can't love out of interest - pope - Agenzia ANSA</title><link>http://www.ansa.it/english/news/vatican/2018/11/19/you-cant-love-out-of-interest-pope_3f9eeb91-6ddf-439f-8ee6-f70bbbbb7973.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH9jEGYpT_tOo8Z65ts-QdgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowsP-hCTCXv5cCMJSC0QU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 13:13:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.ansa.it/english/news/vatican/2018/11/19/you-cant-love-out-of-interest-pope_3f9eeb91-6ddf-439f-8ee6-f70bbbbb7973.html" target="_blank"&gt;You can't love out of interest - pope&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Agenzia ANSA&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(ANSA) - Vatican City, November 19 - Pope Francis tweeted Monday "you can't love only as long as it's 'in your interest'; love ,manifests itself beyond the threshold of one's interest, when you give everything without reservations". Read the full article on ANSA English&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.ansa.it">Agenzia ANSA</source></item><item><title>Pope Charmed by 'Undisciplined' Disabled Child - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/pope-charmed-by-undisciplined-disabled-child/4678138.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF9JSDlbduRCo-WPUpP1KsAqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw-pwi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 16:41:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/pope-charmed-by-undisciplined-disabled-child/4678138.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pope Charmed by 'Undisciplined' Disabled Child&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pope Francis praised the freedom — albeit "undisciplined" — of a disabled child who climbed onto the stage Wednesday to play during the pontiff's general audience. The Swiss Guards and Vatican gendarmes stood by Wednesday and gamely let 6-year-old Wenzel Wirth run around Francis as monsignors read out his catechism lesson in various languages in the Vatican audience hall. At one point, the boy's Argentine-Italian mother came on stage to fetch him and explained to Francis that he couldn't speak. Francis told her "Let him be, let him be" and the mother retreated and let Wenzel continue to pla...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Pope to go to Morocco in March 2019 - Agenzia ANSA</title><link>http://www.ansamed.info/ansamed/en/news/sections/politics/2018/11/13/pope-to-go-to-morocco-in-march-2019_6692ca21-8b16-46a3-8b93-deda5ea341ec.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAAS8mHP9D1Z37FYO6efmscqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowsP-hCTCXv5cCMIWA0QU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 17:12:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.ansamed.info/ansamed/en/news/sections/politics/2018/11/13/pope-to-go-to-morocco-in-march-2019_6692ca21-8b16-46a3-8b93-deda5ea341ec.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pope to go to Morocco in March 2019&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Agenzia ANSA&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;VATICAN CITY - Pope Francis will go to Morocco in March 2019, the Vatican said Tuesday. "Accepting the invitation of His Majesty King Mohammed VI, and the bishops," it said, Francis will make an apostolic journey to Morocco from March 30 to 31, visiting the cities of Rabat and Casablanca. The long-awaited visit was announced by the director of the Vatican Press Office, Greg Burke. Read the full article on Ansamed&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.ansamed.info">Agenzia ANSA</source></item><item><title>‘The tongue kills like a knife’: Pope Francis equates gossiping with terrorism - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/news/443981-pope-francis-gossip-terrorism/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMTBYZNFmTYLZzZ1RWbWZy8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww_oMo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 16:32:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/news/443981-pope-francis-gossip-terrorism/" target="_blank"&gt;‘The tongue kills like a knife’: Pope Francis equates gossiping with terrorism&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a strongly worded warning, Pope Francis decried gossip as a form of “terrorism” which ruins reputations, and said that fake news is a modern day scourge of the church faithful. During his Wednesday address to the general public in St. Peter’s Square, the Pope explored the eighth commandment, “Thou shalt not bear false witness against thy neighbor.” “We all live by communicating, and we are continuously on the edge between truth and lies,” Francis said, adding that misinformation is inherently dangerous “because the tongue kills like a knife.” The media-savvy pontiff is known for using hy...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Italy's bishops respond to long-ignored clergy sex abuse - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/e307b68aa64146f6b06d2a4747c617ba</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF2H6gzpa7gW8DD57CsjXSoqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 16:54:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/e307b68aa64146f6b06d2a4747c617ba" target="_blank"&gt;Italy's bishops respond to long-ignored clergy sex abuse&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;VATICAN CITY (AP) — Italy's Catholic bishops are declaring a new era of transparency and truth about clergy sex abuse, as awareness of the scandal that has convulsed much of the Catholic world begins to take hold in a country where it was long ignored. Cardinal Gualtiero Bassetti, president of the Italian bishops' conference, said Thursday that a national advisory center of lay and religious experts is being created to help dioceses educate personnel about protecting children and help bishops investigate abuse reports. Italy's bishops have lagged behind their counterparts in much of the Wes...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Bishops delay votes on combating church sex abuse crisis - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/019008ddb5224948b9f1455cd3f072e1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOP4rY3DNAo3Z8Bbp02Bb80qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 00:38:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/019008ddb5224948b9f1455cd3f072e1" target="_blank"&gt;Bishops delay votes on combating church sex abuse crisis&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BALTIMORE (AP) — At the Vatican's insistence, U.S. Catholic bishops abruptly postponed plans Monday to vote on proposed new steps to address the clergy sex abuse crisis roiling the church. Cardinal Daniel DiNardo of Galveston-Houston, the president of the U.S. Conference of Catholic Bishops, said he was told on the eve of the bishop's national meeting to delay action until after a Vatican-convened global meeting on sex abuse in February. "We are not ourselves happy about this," DiNardo told reporters in an unusual public display of frustration at a Vatican pronouncement. "We are working ver...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>US bishops cancel votes on tackling sex abuse after pope intervenes - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/12/us-catholic-bishops-conference-sex-abuse-vote-vatican-pope-francis-intervenes</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDP7XWlMMBgu2Fsd5KH6cSIqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 19:30:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/12/us-catholic-bishops-conference-sex-abuse-vote-vatican-pope-francis-intervenes" target="_blank"&gt;US bishops cancel votes on tackling sex abuse after pope intervenes&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In an abrupt change of plans, a US conference of Catholic bishops has delayed any votes on proposed new steps to address the clergy sex abuse crisis following an intervention from the Vatican. The president of the US Conference of Catholic Bishops opened the group’s national meeting on Monday by announcing it will delay any votes on the issue that has been rocking the church for at least several months. Related: Top Catholic bishop to be questioned over child abuse scandal Cardinal Daniel DiNardo, of Galveston-Houston, said the delay was requested by the Holy See, which asked that the US bi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>US Bishops to Delay Votes on Steps to Combat Sex Abuse Crisis - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/us-bishops-to-delay-votes-on-steps-to-combat-sex-abuse-crisis/4654976.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAFF2U85r0CW_ouFTWkiCxIqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw-pwi</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 16:47:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/us-bishops-to-delay-votes-on-steps-to-combat-sex-abuse-crisis/4654976.html" target="_blank"&gt;US Bishops to Delay Votes on Steps to Combat Sex Abuse Crisis&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In an abrupt change of plans, the president of the U.S. Conference of Catholic Bishops opened the group's national meeting Monday by announcing it will delay for at least several months any votes on proposed new steps to address the clergy sex abuse crisis that is rocking the church. Cardinal Daniel DiNardo, of Galveston-Houston, said the delay was requested by the Vatican, which asked that the U.S. bishops wait until after a Vatican-convened global meeting on sex abuse in February. DiNardo expressed disappointment but told the U.S. bishops, “I remain hopeful that this additional consultati...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Catholic bishops' meeting nears end, no vote on abuse plan - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/073c4967da9c4e50a3af2b87406fc527</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHzFn7gVWpqsLq1xtLKL8kUqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvKadAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 02:06:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/073c4967da9c4e50a3af2b87406fc527" target="_blank"&gt;Catholic bishops' meeting nears end, no vote on abuse plan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BALTIMORE (AP) — U.S. Catholic bishops made clear their frustrations Wednesday as a national assembly focused on clergy sex-abuse neared its conclusion without strong new steps to combat the multifaceted crisis. Avoiding any direct confrontation with the Vatican, the U.S. Conference of Catholic Bishops ended the public sessions of its three-day meeting without any vote on two major anti-abuse proposals that had been drafted weeks ago. On the eve of this week's meeting, the Vatican issued a surprise order for such action to be delayed until after a global meeting on sex abuse scheduled for F...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Italian priest who doubted Francis excommunicated for heresy - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/62ff600cdd614f55ae19f13bc2480ac3</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI2oIGc-dZa8q5DqiS9nYTEqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 17:32:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/62ff600cdd614f55ae19f13bc2480ac3" target="_blank"&gt;Italian priest who doubted Francis excommunicated for heresy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ROME (AP) — An Italian Catholic priest who considers Pope Francis an antipope and claims to have supernatural communications with angels, saints and the Madonna has been excommunicated. The archdiocese of Monreale, Sicily said the Rev. Alessandro Minutella was informed Tuesday of his excommunication for spreading "heresy and schism." Monreale Archbishop Michele Pennisi issued a public notice in 2015 warning the faithful that they risked "grave danger to their souls" by listening to Minutella. Pennisi said the priest was suspected of manipulating parishioners with his prophesies and "serious...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Bishops weigh anti-abuse strategy after delay set by Vatican - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/1f0ba6a1e50c4c5784b1f46c9b601eda</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEML7I3-_RBP9xZkewQKdPKsqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvKadAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 22:27:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/1f0ba6a1e50c4c5784b1f46c9b601eda" target="_blank"&gt;Bishops weigh anti-abuse strategy after delay set by Vatican&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BALTIMORE (AP) — Several Roman Catholic bishops on Tuesday urged colleagues at their national meeting to take some sort of action on the clergy sex abuse crisis despite a Vatican order to delay voting on key proposals. Bishop Thomas Paprocki of Springfield, Illinois, suggested a nonbinding vote to convey a sense of the bishops' aspirations regarding anti-abuse efforts. "We are not branch managers of the Vatican," he said. "Our people are crying out for some action." Bishop George Murry of Youngstown, Ohio, echoed Paprocki's call, saying parishioners and priests in his diocese are "very, ver...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Unhealthy water 'immense shame' - pope - Agenzia ANSA</title><link>http://www.ansa.it/english/news/vatican/2018/11/08/unhealthy-water-immense-shame-pope_2d1df3f9-de6a-4f22-8993-be76597fbf5c.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL6TxhpS7yOsKeHbARWIdXUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowsP-hCTCXv5cCMJSC0QU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 11:59:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.ansa.it/english/news/vatican/2018/11/08/unhealthy-water-immense-shame-pope_2d1df3f9-de6a-4f22-8993-be76597fbf5c.html" target="_blank"&gt;Unhealthy water 'immense shame' - pope&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Agenzia ANSA&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(ANSA) - Vatican City, November 8 - Unhealthy drinking water is an "immense shame" in the 21st century, Pope Francis said Thursday. In a message to an international conference in Rome entitled "The management of a common good: access to drinking water for all", he said more and better access to water must be provided worldwide. The one-day conference is being held at the Pontifical Urbaniana University and has been organized by the Dicastery for Promoting Integral Human Development in collaboration with the Embassies accredited to the Holy See of France, Italy, Monaco and the United Stat...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.ansa.it">Agenzia ANSA</source></item><item><title>Vatican orders US bishops to delay taking action on sexual abuse crisis - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/12/us/conference-of-catholic-bishops-vatican/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPo5KX949gd74Ak-1898PT0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMIrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 12:04:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/12/us/conference-of-catholic-bishops-vatican/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Vatican orders US bishops to delay taking action on sexual abuse crisis&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Vatican has told the US Conference of Catholic Bishops to delay voting on measures to hold bishops accountable for failing to protect children from sexual abuse, the president of the conference said in a surprise announcement Monday morning. In announcing the decision to his fellow bishops, Cardinal Daniel DiNardo said he was disappointed by the Vatican's interference, which he said he learned of on Sunday afternoon. "At the insistence of the Holy See, we will not be voting on the two action items in our docket regarding the abuse crisis," said DiNardo. For weeks, the US Catholic bishop...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Vatican orders US bishops to postpone crucial vote on sexual abuse crisis - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/catholic-church-us-sex-abuse-scandal-vatican-bishops-pope-francis-a8630776.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBY_HLp3y2LhcLq-39-u2qkqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCRx_0F</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 22:06:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/catholic-church-us-sex-abuse-scandal-vatican-bishops-pope-francis-a8630776.html" target="_blank"&gt;Vatican orders US bishops to postpone crucial vote on sexual abuse crisis&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Vatican has instructed US Catholic bishops to postpone plans to vote on proposed new steps to address the clergy sex abuse crisis embroiling the church. The US Conference of Catholic Bishops (USCCB) was planning to vote on a referendum that would hold bishops responsible for failing to protect children from sexual abuse in the church. In an announcement to his fellow Catholic clergymen, USCCB President Cardinal Daniel DiNardo said the Holy See requested the conference to hold off their vote until February when the Vatican will hold their global meeting on sexual abuse. - Read more Pope ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Top Catholic bishop to be questioned over child abuse scandal - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2018/nov/10/vincent-nichols-catholic-church-child-sex-abuse-cover-up-independent-inquiry</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOWIThp4X40Q9ASMEuqF7woqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 14:00:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2018/nov/10/vincent-nichols-catholic-church-child-sex-abuse-cover-up-independent-inquiry" target="_blank"&gt;Top Catholic bishop to be questioned over child abuse scandal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Roman Catholic church in England will come under intense scrutiny this week over its handling of child sexual abuse and the cover-up of predatory priests by bishops and other senior figures. Survivors of rape and assault will testify over five days at an independent inquiry into child sexual abuse, along with church leaders, officials and child protection experts in a case study examining the archdiocese of Birmingham. Cardinal Vincent Nichols, the archbishop of Westminster, will give evidence in person on Tuesday – the first time that the most senior Catholic in England has been cross-...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>D.C. attorney general launches investigation into Catholic Church - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/23/us/dc-catholic-investigation/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFZeRsoic2Bw86fv07pYK8MqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 16:10:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/23/us/dc-catholic-investigation/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;D.C. attorney general launches investigation into Catholic Church&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Washington, D.C., Attorney General Karl Racine announced Tuesday he has launched a civil investigation into whether the Archdiocese of Washington violated the law by covering up the sexual abuse of minors. "While we generally don't talk publicly about our confidential enforcement activity, I can report that our office has launched a civil investigation into whether the Archdiocese -- which is a nonprofit institution -- violated the District's Nonprofit Act by potentially covering up allegations of sexual abuse of minors," Racine said in a statement provided to CNN by a representative. "Acco...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>A broadband church? Vatican expert urges priests to get online - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-portugal-websummit-vatican-idUSKCN1NB2E7</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJOcLscIn42yvTHOw18MnWMqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 17:47:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-portugal-websummit-vatican-idUSKCN1NB2E7" target="_blank"&gt;A broadband church? Vatican expert urges priests to get online&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Priests should get online if they want to connect with people who may no longer attend church but can still be reached via social media, the Vatican's digital expert said on Tuesday. Monsignor Paul Tighe, who helped develop Pope Francis' online presence, urged Catholic clergy across the world to embrace social media to reach believers and non-believers. "Young people are, unfortunately, less present in our churches," Tighe, Secretary of the Pontifical Council for Culture, told Reuters on Tuesday at a technology conference in Lisbon. "Social media is a mechanism that allows us to engage in c...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>French Bishops launch 'independent' commission on sex abuse in Catholic Church - CNN</title><link>https://edition.cnn.com/2018/11/08/europe/french-bishops-sexual-abuse-commission-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJw2lfdPZEtI5Rok-WOjmYYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 06:36:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://edition.cnn.com/2018/11/08/europe/french-bishops-sexual-abuse-commission-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;French Bishops launch 'independent' commission on sex abuse in Catholic Church&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;French bishops have announced plans to establish an "independent" commission to look into the sexual abuse of minors within the Catholic Church dating back as far as 1950. The appointed panel would "seek to understand the reasons which led to the way these cases were handled" by the Church, the Conference of French Bishops said in a statement on Wednesday. The conference pledged to publish a report outlining the commission's findings within two years. Details, including the name of the person spearheading the investigation, will be announced in the coming days, it added. The statement came ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://edition.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Sex abuse crisis tops agenda as US Catholic bishops convene - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/8d0513c0364b4b24b226825c4d3b958d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB9uZQVT_xQEWlh3WnRzTNgqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvKadAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 20:41:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/8d0513c0364b4b24b226825c4d3b958d" target="_blank"&gt;Sex abuse crisis tops agenda as US Catholic bishops convene&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;As U.S. Catholic bishops gather for their national assembly next week, the clergy sex abuse crisis dominates their agenda amid calls from critics that church leaders finally bring about meaningful reforms to root out misbehaving priests. The three-day assembly that starts Monday in Baltimore comes after a series of abuse scandals this year that have been stunning in their magnitude and number. Bishops have several reforms under consideration to craft a stronger response to the scandals, but some Catholic activists are demanding further steps, including releasing the names of all clergy accu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Guam Catholic Church to file bankruptcy amid abuse lawsuits - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/717d8e867f5347ab9a4590c91f665dfb</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHJqF_tX3_E-8HxW2o0lxdAqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvKadAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 19:04:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/717d8e867f5347ab9a4590c91f665dfb" target="_blank"&gt;Guam Catholic Church to file bankruptcy amid abuse lawsuits&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;HAGATNA, Guam (AP) — Guam's Catholic Church will file for bankruptcy — a move that will allow the archdiocese to avoid trial in dozens of lawsuits alleging child sexual abuse by priests and move toward settlements. Archbishop Michael Byrnes announced Wednesday that mediation efforts that began in September led the church to bankruptcy. "This path will bring the greatest measure of justice to the greatest number of victims," Byrnes said. "That's the heart of what we're doing." Byrnes said the bankruptcy will provide "finality for victim survivors that they've been heard and understood." Atto...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Pope decries attack on Christian worshippers in Egypt - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/35d1e3823ed742cf8880c780240669f0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFelwYm_CkpHGWDRD6PmyXQqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 13:08:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/35d1e3823ed742cf8880c780240669f0" target="_blank"&gt;Pope decries attack on Christian worshippers in Egypt&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;VATICAN CITY (AP) — Pope Francis has decried the attack on pilgrims in Egypt, saying they were killed "for being Christians." Francis invited faithful in St. Peter's Square Sunday to pray with him for the seven slain as they were making their way to a remote Orthodox Coptic monastery. Christians make up about 10 percent of Egypt's population and have long complained about discrimination. Francis voiced "sorrow for the terrorist attack which two days ago struck the Coptic Orthodox church in Egypt." He said he was praying for the "pilgrims killed for the sole fact of being Christians," asking...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>East Timor president slams parliament for blocking trip to meet pope - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-timor-politics-pope-idUSKCN1NC11K</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBuk6QBWDhVnl4TPZN1e7KcqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 09:01:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-timor-politics-pope-idUSKCN1NC11K" target="_blank"&gt;East Timor president slams parliament for blocking trip to meet pope&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;East Timor's ruling coalition in parliament has voted to block a planned trip by President Francisco Guterres to the Vatican, where he was due to meet Pope Francis, saying the president must first break a political deadlock at home. The predominantly Roman Catholic nation has struggled to achieve stable government, and the stalemate has persisted since Guterres rejected some ministers proposed by Prime Minister Jose Maria de Vasconcelos after May elections over graft inquiries. In a statement on Wednesday, Guterres said he deeply regretted this week's vote by the ruling Alliance of Change f...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>French priest says bishops punished him for abuse petition - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/d67ba70cabbd49d2b6f237495f2560e0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECd3fYUlK2g3GV994Jz4CwsqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 13:12:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/d67ba70cabbd49d2b6f237495f2560e0" target="_blank"&gt;French priest says bishops punished him for abuse petition&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PARIS (AP) — A Catholic priest said Friday that he has been punished by church leaders in France after he gathered more than 100,000 signatures for a petition calling for a cardinal to resign over his handling of child sexual abuse cases. The Rev. Pierre Vignon said he learned in an email Thursday that he would no longer be considered for the church court where he has served as a judge since 2002. In a phone interview, Vignon said the decision showed church leaders are of two minds about how to deal with sex predators within the Catholic clergy. "They say, 'We want to do everything,' but to...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item></channel></rss>