<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Travel visa - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIggKIhxDQkFTRHdvSkwyMHZNREYzZEhKckVnSmxiaWdBUAE?hl=en-GB&amp;gl=GB&amp;ceid=GB:en</link><language>en-GB</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 12:43:51 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Duped With Tourist Over Work Visas, 14 Indians Stranded In Saudi Arabia - NDTV News</title><link>https://www.ndtv.com/indians-abroad/14-indians-stranded-in-saudi-arabia-after-being-duped-with-tourist-over-work-visas-1956536</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM9Gee-Xoj0XqaW0BYVErIwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowj8n_CjDIrfkCMPGi6AU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 20:30:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ndtv.com/indians-abroad/14-indians-stranded-in-saudi-arabia-after-being-duped-with-tourist-over-work-visas-1956536" target="_blank"&gt;Duped With Tourist Over Work Visas, 14 Indians Stranded In Saudi Arabia&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;NDTV News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fourteen Indians are stranded in Saudi Arabia with most of them in the country's jails after two local travel agents allegedly sent them to work in the Middle East ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ndtv.com">NDTV News</source></item><item><title>Guatemalan father of slain North Carolina teen denied visa to attend her funeral - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/07/us/north-carolina-teen-funeral-visa-denied/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM9wbRdVp9RDHZfXHIT8gKgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 10:54:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/07/us/north-carolina-teen-funeral-visa-denied/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Guatemalan father of slain North Carolina teen denied visa to attend her funeral&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;When 13-year-old Hania Aguilar is laid to rest in North Carolina on Saturday her father will be nearly 3,000 miles away. The US State Department has denied a temporary visa for Noé Aguilar to travel from Guatemala to attend services for his teenage daughter, according to the father's attorney. "I had hoped they would find it in their hearts to let me be there for my daughter's funeral," Aguilar told CNN in a brief phone interview Friday. "It's very sad. She was my princess. She will always be my princess." Immigration attorney Naimeh Salem said US embassy officials in Guatemala denied the t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Ending ‘golden visas’ for oligarchs is a start – but not a solution - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/dec/07/golden-visa-oligarch-super-rich-british-citizenship-global</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC_cr9gixNTYtEOcDLq6AzIqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTC9vBU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 15:46:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/dec/07/golden-visa-oligarch-super-rich-british-citizenship-global" target="_blank"&gt;Ending ‘golden visas’ for oligarchs is a start – but not a solution&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The government has finally stopped a programme that sells British visas for a £2m investment in UK bonds, but anyone who thinks this will free London of the influence of kleptocrats is mistaken. The UK’s “golden visa” programme began back in 1994, when the Conservative government sought to woo wealthy Hong Kong residents, and was boosted by Labour in 2008. The programme has brought billions into the bond market over the past 24 years, primarily from Chinese and Russian applicants. Since 2015, applicants have had to pass banks’ due diligence tests, but no one in government has ever bothered ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>What Are Britain’s ‘Golden Visas’ and Why Are They Being Suspended? - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/12/06/world/europe/uk-golden-visa-suspended.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH_XQSIccSiglIJTPbIUlygqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzww9oAY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 05:02:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/12/06/world/europe/uk-golden-visa-suspended.html" target="_blank"&gt;What Are Britain’s ‘Golden Visas’ and Why Are They Being Suspended?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;LONDON — The British government is preparing to suspend a special visa program that allows wealthy investors to fast-track their settlement in the country, part of a new drive to crack down on money laundering. The Tier 1 visas will be suspended from midnight on Dec. 7 until the Home Office introduces tighter restrictions to tackle corruption and organized crime. “We will not tolerate people who do not play by the rules and seek to abuse the system,” Immigration Minister Caroline Nokes said in a statement on Thursday. What are Tier 1 visas? They are not called “golden visas” for nothing. Th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>Bucking a Global Trend, Japan Seeks More Immigrants. Ambivalently. - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/12/07/world/asia/japan-parliament-foreign-workers.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELzBKOWh2z6W3jaEOtdbfc4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzww5oEY</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 00:24:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/12/07/world/asia/japan-parliament-foreign-workers.html" target="_blank"&gt;Bucking a Global Trend, Japan Seeks More Immigrants. Ambivalently.&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KASHIWA, Japan — Vexed by labor shortages in their rapidly aging country, lawmakers relaxed Japan’s longstanding insularity early Saturday by authorizing a sharp increase in the number of foreign workers. Under a bill approved by Parliament’s upper house in the early-morning hours, more than a quarter-million visas of five-year duration will be granted to unskilled guest laborers for the first time, starting in 2019. The measure is a remarkable turn for Japan, surprising neighbors and maybe even itself. A nation that once embraced draconian limits on immigration is now reluctantly moving in...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>Father of Hania Aguilar, Killed at 13, Is Denied Funeral Visa - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/12/06/us/hania-aguilar-father-visa-denied.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFgtSimhfKh19-1XdbRelwkqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzwwloEY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 22:34:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/12/06/us/hania-aguilar-father-visa-denied.html" target="_blank"&gt;Father of Hania Aguilar, Killed at 13, Is Denied Funeral Visa&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The State Department denied a temporary visa to a Guatemalan father trying to attend the funeral on Saturday for his teenage daughter, who was kidnapped outside her North Carolina home last month and was later found dead off a rural road, the man’s lawyer said on Thursday. The father of the girl, 13-year-old Hania Aguilar, traveled to the United States Embassy in Guatemala City on Monday and asked for expedited approval for a visa to fly to the United States. The father, Noé Aguilar, was denied on the spot because American officials worried he lacked strong ties to Guatemala, his native cou...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>Guatemalan father of girl who was kidnapped and killed in US denied visa for her funeral, lawyer says - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/hania-aguilar-killed-kidnapped-funeral-father-denied-visa-guatemala-north-carolina-a8671966.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHvhpfFTxCyODyV6XehAGEMqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 11:49:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/hania-aguilar-killed-kidnapped-funeral-father-denied-visa-guatemala-north-carolina-a8671966.html" target="_blank"&gt;Guatemalan father of girl who was kidnapped and killed in US denied visa for her funeral, lawyer says&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Guatemalan father trying to attend the funeral of his teenage daughter who was kidnapped outside her home in North Carolina and later found dead near a road has been denied a temporary visa, according to his lawyer. Noé Aguilar, the father of 13-year-old Hania Aguilar, travelled to the US embassy in Guatemala City on Monday and asked for expedited approval for a visa to fly to the United States. But he was denied on the spot because US officials worried he lacked strong ties to Guatemala and might not return, according to his lawyer Naimeh Salem. “To tell you the truth, with past administ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>This is the most powerful passport in the world (it’s not American) - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/this-is-the-most-powerful-passport-in-the-world-its-not-american-2018-12-05</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBiO8Cc2WA3DZSKNH2IGI84qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwiJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 11:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/this-is-the-most-powerful-passport-in-the-world-its-not-american-2018-12-05" target="_blank"&gt;This is the most powerful passport in the world (it’s not American)&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Quentin Fottrell The U.S. made it to No. 14 on a ranking that measured the ease of access for gaining a second citizenship Which passport is the most powerful of them all? It’s not the U.S. Getty Images The most powerful passport in the world is not American. The United Arab Emirates was No. 1 on the list on a ranking that went to 167, according to a compilation by the “Global Passport Ranking,” created by Arton Capital a Montreal–based organization that helps high-net-worth clients gain second citizenship and/or residency. This was followed by Singapore, Germany, Denmark and Sweden, Fin...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Japan’s immigration reforms still treat foreign workers as nothing more than cheap labor - Quartz</title><link>https://qz.com/1487291/japan-is-close-to-passing-immigration-reform-for-foreign-workers/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP41dRZg5hlMP4NeksotMfUqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowi4-MATDXsRUwhP2ZAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 09:57:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://qz.com/1487291/japan-is-close-to-passing-immigration-reform-for-foreign-workers/" target="_blank"&gt;Japan’s immigration reforms still treat foreign workers as nothing more than cheap labor&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Quartz&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Japan is about to implement the most radical overhaul of its immigration policy in order to allow more workers into the country as its population shrinks. But even strong supporters of allowing more foreign workers argue that the plan is deeply flawed and should be reconsidered. Critics say that the plan doesn’t go far enough to address the problems plaguing foreign blue-collar workers who are currently employed in Japan under conditions that make them prone to exploitation. Opposition lawmakers have tried to stymie the passage of the vote through Japan’s parliament on those grounds, but af...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://qz.com">Quartz</source></item><item><title>Many U.S.-bound caravan migrants disperse as asylum process stalls - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-immigration-caravan-idUSKBN1O62IF</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEQQJOX4pu8b7RBlFIS0xNAqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 01:19:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-immigration-caravan-idUSKBN1O62IF" target="_blank"&gt;Many U.S.-bound caravan migrants disperse as asylum process stalls&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thousands of Central American migrants spent weeks traveling north through Mexico in caravans, walking and hitching rides when possible, only for many to give up hope and turn back when they met resistance at the U.S. border. Others hopped the border fence, often directly into the hands of immigration authorities on the U.S. side, while still others dug in at temporary lodgings in Tijuana for the long process of seeking asylum from a reluctant U.S. government. As rain poured down on a former music venue in Tijuana that holds a diminished crowd of 2,500 migrants, Jessica, 18, grabbed her fev...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>'Golden visas' allowing Russian and Chinese investors to settle in UK suspended over money laundering - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/home-news/investor-visas-tier-one-uk-suspended-money-laundering-financial-crime-immigration-russia-china-a8670876.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPrWg740yrC0KgD_VMYBgCYqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 16:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/home-news/investor-visas-tier-one-uk-suspended-money-laundering-financial-crime-immigration-russia-china-a8670876.html" target="_blank"&gt;'Golden visas' allowing Russian and Chinese investors to settle in UK suspended over money laundering&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Golden visas” that have been criticised for allowing the super-rich to buy the right to live in the UK are being suspended in a crackdown on money laundering and serious organised crime. Tier one investor visas, which were introduced a decade ago to attract investment from outside the EU, have proved popular with Russian and Chinese applicants. They allow anyone investing at least £2m in government bonds to work or study in Britain. For £5m, they can apply for indefinite leave to remain after three years, and for £10m it can be done in two. Read more - UK Government plans Bitcoin crackdown...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>UK 'golden visa' scheme to be suspended due to corruption fears - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2018/dec/06/restrictions-for-2m-golden-visa-to-be-reformed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMvbaFpJE1hmxQZyhjJKkvYqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 00:43:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2018/dec/06/restrictions-for-2m-golden-visa-to-be-reformed" target="_blank"&gt;UK 'golden visa' scheme to be suspended due to corruption fears&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The global super-rich hoping to live and invest in the UK will face new visa restrictions as part of Home Office reforms designed to tackle organised crime and money laundering. The tier 1 visa, which provides a fast track route to settlement for people willing to invest millions in the UK, will be suspended from Friday until new rules are put in place in 2019. Related: The ‘golden visa’ deal: ‘We have in effect been selling off British citizenship to the rich’ The reformed visa will require applicants to provide comprehensive audits of their financial and business interests, and show they ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>UK cracks down on investor visas - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/793c5ea0-f935-11e8-af46-2022a0b02a6c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK0LOB44lXHm1fUlRxgNfygqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw8tp6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 09:59:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/793c5ea0-f935-11e8-af46-2022a0b02a6c" target="_blank"&gt;UK cracks down on investor visas&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wealthy investors seeking a fast-track route to settlement in the UK are to face new restrictions under a Home Office crackdown on money laundering. Under the scheme, which is particularly popular among Russian and Chinese nationals, an investment of £2m provides a five-year track to permanent residence, while those paying £5m wait only three years, and investors of £10m can apply after two years. The investments can be made in gilts, government bonds, or UK companies. About 1,000 such visas were issued in 2017. However, following concerns that the scheme is being used to launder money, the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>World's Three Best Retiree Residency Options - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/kathleenpeddicord/2018/12/05/worlds-three-best-retiree-residency-options/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKeQlWadLfF4-PIRx3F_ZlgqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLKAAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 18:58:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/kathleenpeddicord/2018/12/05/worlds-three-best-retiree-residency-options/" target="_blank"&gt;World's Three Best Retiree Residency Options&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two active seniors reading a map together while venturing around their new retirement destination. When retiring overseas, one of the big issues to address is legal residency, the right to be physically present in a country indefinitely. You can avoid having to qualify for legal residency by staying only as long as a tourist is permitted to remain in the country (usually 30 to 90 days). If you want to stay longer or don’t want to have to worry about restrictions on your comings and goings, you’ll need more permanent status. Qualifying for residency can mean other benefits—tax breaks, the ri...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Misstated 'fact' used by Minister to argue for sending migrants to regions - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-06/regional-visa-argument-misstated-fact-sydney-melbourne/10554282</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOR-ke9sGD-Ft0Jh5Of_pOQqFwgEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDD6kIkG</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 22:31:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-06/regional-visa-argument-misstated-fact-sydney-melbourne/10554282" target="_blank"&gt;Misstated 'fact' used by Minister to argue for sending migrants to regions&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The minister tasked by the Prime Minister to "bust" congestion has massively inflated the number of skilled migrants moving to Melbourne and Sydney. Key points: - Minister for Cities incorrectly claimed 87 per cent of skilled migrants moved to Sydney and Melbourne - Statistic was used in argument for sending more migrants to regions - Critics say existing regional migration programs have been neglected The mistaken "fact", as Cities Minister Alan Tudge described it, has been used as a central justification for a plan to force migrants to the regions. But the latest Migration Program Report ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Britain suspends $2.5 million golden visas to tackle money laundering - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-britain-immigration-visas/britain-suspends-2-5-million-golden-visas-to-tackle-money-laundering-idUSKBN1O50ZN</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ_L2Hg8Zt5UZMzLx9nNH90qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 10:59:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-britain-immigration-visas/britain-suspends-2-5-million-golden-visas-to-tackle-money-laundering-idUSKBN1O50ZN" target="_blank"&gt;Britain suspends $2.5 million golden visas to tackle money laundering&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Britain will suspend its top tier investor visas, which require 2 million pounds ($2.55 million) in investment, as part of a drive to crack down on organized crime and money laundering. From Russian oligarchs and Middle Eastern oil barons to newly-minted Chinese entrepreneurs, the wealthy have flocked to London over the past two decades, snapping up everything from opulent homes to soccer clubs. The influx of super-rich has brought tens of billions of pounds in investment and helped London preserve its position as one of the world's top two global financial capitals, though the government h...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>He’s a U.S. soldier deployed on the southern border — and an unlawful immigrant - The Washington Post</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/national-security/2018/12/05/hes-us-soldier-deployed-southern-border-an-unlawful-immigrant/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECrIEmm_IT2I5M4t7J6E_7EqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjtSUCjC30XQw36e5AQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 19:33:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/national-security/2018/12/05/hes-us-soldier-deployed-southern-border-an-unlawful-immigrant/" target="_blank"&gt;He’s a U.S. soldier deployed on the southern border — and an unlawful immigrant&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Washington Post&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Marine strings concertina wire on the southern border. (U.S. Marine Corps)Public Domain The U.S. soldier was ready to deploy across the world at a moment’s notice, but when the orders came down weeks ago to mobilize on the southern border, it sparked a flash of concern. He knew the mission was in support of border agents combing harsh borderland terrain to arrest anyone unlawfully in the country. People like him. “I’m an illegal immigrant,” the Chinese-born soldier told The Washington Post by phone. His duties do not often intersect with Customs and Border Protection agents, he said, but ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.washingtonpost.com">The Washington Post</source></item><item><title>Ethiopian Airlines will start helping Chinese travelers move easier across Africa - Quartz</title><link>https://qz.com/africa/1483564/ethiopian-airlines-begins-african-visa-hub-for-chinese-tourists/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED3ytJb2All2iiUy_meY_9gqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowi4-MATDXsRUwhP2ZAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 11:19:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://qz.com/africa/1483564/ethiopian-airlines-begins-african-visa-hub-for-chinese-tourists/" target="_blank"&gt;Ethiopian Airlines will start helping Chinese travelers move easier across Africa&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Quartz&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ethiopian Airlines will start helping Chinese visitors process visas to travel across Africa. Beginning in 2019, Africa’s No.1 airline will set up a hub that will allow travelers from China to apply for visas to 35 African countries, the airline’s chief Tewolde Gebremariam told Chinese news agency Xinhua. The scheme is aimed at reducing the process of application especially for citizens who have to travel to embassies located in the capital, Beijing. Chinese passport holders can get visas on arrival in Ethiopia’s capital Addis Ababa. “The visa scheme will facilitate easier air travel for Ch...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://qz.com">Quartz</source></item><item><title>Mexico Suggests Work Visas for Central Americans - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/mexico-suggests-work-visas-for-central-americans/4688483.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAeng5CplS90bE0gn0mFZ_8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 23:15:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/mexico-suggests-work-visas-for-central-americans/4688483.html" target="_blank"&gt;Mexico Suggests Work Visas for Central Americans&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mexican President Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador proposed on Wednesday offering more work visas for Central Americans and said the United States should do the same, part of a negotiation aimed at stemming the northward flow of migrants. Lopez Obrador, who took office Saturday, said he would discuss immigration with U.S. President Donald Trump in coming days, including increasing investment in southern Mexico and Central America. "We are proposing investment in productive projects and in job creation, and not only that, also work visas for Mexico and for the United States," he told a news confe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>US law against encouraging illegal immigration struck down - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/344dab0d2df44a6f995f2773ed61f636</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKgMr1lja2VZc97EiFDRwOEqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvKadAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 01:59:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/344dab0d2df44a6f995f2773ed61f636" target="_blank"&gt;US law against encouraging illegal immigration struck down&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SAN FRANCISCO (AP) — A U.S. appeals court struck down a federal immigration law Tuesday that opponents warned could be used to criminalize a wide range of statements involving illegal immigration. The law made it a felony for people to encourage an immigrant to enter or live in the U.S. if they know the person would be doing so illegally. The law violates the First Amendment because it criminalizes a substantial amount of protected speech, a three-judge panel of the 9th U.S. Circuit Court of Appeals said. The statute, for example, would make it illegal for a grandmother to urge her grandson...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Grandfather banned from US holiday after accidentally ticking 'terrorist' box on visa form - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/home-news/john-stevenson-us-visa-ban-terrorist-esta-form-mistake-a8660441.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHj5pyoiKehJ2AVjHhQb6t0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 10:09:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/home-news/john-stevenson-us-visa-ban-terrorist-esta-form-mistake-a8660441.html" target="_blank"&gt;Grandfather banned from US holiday after accidentally ticking 'terrorist' box on visa form&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Scottish couple's festive holiday plans are in disarray after a 70-year-old grandfather accidentally declared himself a terrorist on a crucial visa form. John Stevenson and his wife, Marion, had planned to fly to New York City on 3 December. The couple spent around £2,000 on flights and accommodation for the trip. But Mr Stevenson mistakenly answered a question on the Esta visa form, which asked if he was a terrorist, by declaring that he was one. The couple now fear that the 70-year-old will never be allowed into the US again. - Read more US visa applicants might have to hand over their ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>New H-1B Visa Rules Tilt Toward Holders of Advanced Degrees - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/new-h-1b-visa-rules-tilt-toward-holders-of-advanced-degrees-/4682338.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENaFhYZkHyQo-eJ0Ngy7B6MqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 00:43:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/new-h-1b-visa-rules-tilt-toward-holders-of-advanced-degrees-/4682338.html" target="_blank"&gt;New H-1B Visa Rules Tilt Toward Holders of Advanced Degrees&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;New rules will make it tougher for companies in the U.S. to hire specialty workers on H-1B visas and may alter who gets the visas. H-1B visa holders are required to have specialized knowledge and, at minimum, a bachelor's degree. The new rules, announced Friday by the Department of Homeland Security (DHS), would require companies that seek to hire foreigners to pre-register electronically with U.S. Citizenship and Immigration Services (USCIS) during a designated period in advance of the annual H-1B lottery. The pre-registration will require additional paperwork and subject companies to new ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Canadians, Others Brace As U.S. Shuffles Green Card Deck - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/andyjsemotiuk/2018/12/01/canadians-others-brace-as-u-s-shuffles-green-card-deck/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE8_1ZH89v7IpJmsE6pFpg0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMKGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 03:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/andyjsemotiuk/2018/12/01/canadians-others-brace-as-u-s-shuffles-green-card-deck/" target="_blank"&gt;Canadians, Others Brace As U.S. Shuffles Green Card Deck&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The American and Canadian flags symbolize friendship between the two countires. Lately, however, that friendship has taken a bit of a beating. Recently Canadian Prime Ministr Justin Trudeau grudgingly signed the USMCA agreement while expressing hope U.S. tarrifs on steel and aluminun will be lifted. Now it appears that Canadians may be hurt by a change in American immigration priorities related to green cards for skilled workers. Photocredit: Getty Canadians and other nationals are bracing against a serious new threat to their eligibility to get green cards under American immigration polic...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>New Rule Puts US Trafficking Victims at Higher Risk of Deportation - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/human-trafficking-deportation/4679274.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKx_8mgIWvztNiVBFI56DWUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 04:34:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/human-trafficking-deportation/4679274.html" target="_blank"&gt;New Rule Puts US Trafficking Victims at Higher Risk of Deportation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A U.S. agency is taking steps to deport people who were trafficked illegally into the country if they cannot prove their ordeal, a move likely to have a chilling effect on victims coming forward, experts said on Wednesday. Victims of human trafficking can apply for a special "T visa" that allows them to stay in the country, receive government benefits and even put them on the path to U.S. citizenship, according to anti-trafficking experts. About 1,000 people apply for the visa each year, with 70 percent being granted, according to the U.S. government. The policy change was ordered by Presid...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>'Visa misery almost ruined my holiday' - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/money/jessica-investigates/visa-misery-almost-ruined-holiday/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEIQksxaK8Sezmlkitjoy7UqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCt9LkF</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 06:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/money/jessica-investigates/visa-misery-almost-ruined-holiday/" target="_blank"&gt;'Visa misery almost ruined my holiday'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Earlier this year, I applied for a visa through a website that claimed that the procedure would be done within two hours if all the information submitted was accurate. It did not ask me for anything further, so I assumed that all was in order. As I had not received my visa within this time frame I started a “live chat” online, during which I was told that my application was “in process”. I immediately asked to cancel and for a refund of my £44.71 fee. I applied directly to the relevant country’s authorities and obtained my visa within hours. RA, East Sussex Then you received an email sta...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>UAE now has the most powerful passport in the world - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/middle-east/uae-passport-most-powerful-passport-index-global-ranking-uk-blue-germany-japan-a8664076.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAMX50VvhVJ8jGelUu0g48MqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 19:12:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/middle-east/uae-passport-most-powerful-passport-index-global-ranking-uk-blue-germany-japan-a8664076.html" target="_blank"&gt;UAE now has the most powerful passport in the world&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The United Arab Emirates (UAE) has overtaken Singapore and Germany as the country with the world’s most powerful passport. According to Passport Index, UAE passport holders are now able to gain entry to 167 countries without obtaining a prior visa - 113 countries visa-free, and another 54 using visas on arrival. The oil rich state jumped from third place last month into first after four more countries were added to its list of visa-free destinations on 1 December, Gulf News reported. Read more - British academic jailed by UAE for 'spying' lands back in UK - De La Rue profits slump after los...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>U.S. Asks, Are You a Terrorist? Scottish Grandfather Gives Wrong Answer - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/30/world/europe/terrorist-question-scottish-traveler.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIxAnauoa5MFwu-V9t_nNj0qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzwwt4QY</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 04:32:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/30/world/europe/terrorist-question-scottish-traveler.html" target="_blank"&gt;U.S. Asks, Are You a Terrorist? Scottish Grandfather Gives Wrong Answer&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;LONDON — He could have misspelled his address, or entered an incorrect age — something fairly harmless — but no, the error John Stevenson made in an online form for the United States Department of Homeland Security was clicking on the wrong answer to a question. The question asked whether he was a terrorist. Mr. Stevenson, a Scottish grandfather, said he had made an honest mistake, but it might ruin his plans to fly with his wife to New York City on Monday. He ran into trouble filling out the automated online form on the Electronic System for Travel Authorization, known as ESTA, that allows...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>These charts show visa-free travel for Africans within Africa is still a work in progress - Quartz</title><link>https://qz.com/africa/1478854/africas-visa-openness-improves-but-challenges-persist/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENNhPGToYk6M4SaA6DxK8LEqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowi4-MATDXsRUwhP2ZAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 14:50:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://qz.com/africa/1478854/africas-visa-openness-improves-but-challenges-persist/" target="_blank"&gt;These charts show visa-free travel for Africans within Africa is still a work in progress&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Quartz&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;When it comes to advancing the dream of a more open and prosperous Africa, 2018 has been a good one. Leaders across the continent signed the Continental Free Trade Agreement, which aims to connect a marketplace with 1.2 billion people and a GDP of $2.5 trillion. Another milestone was also marked with the launch of the Single Air Transport Market initiative which outlines a better and faster connected continent through air travel. Many countries from Kenya to Ethiopia, Senegal, and Namibia also relaxed their visa rules for Africans to promote open borders, trade, security and Africa-wide int...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://qz.com">Quartz</source></item><item><title>Trump Labor Dept. To Use New H-1B Form Against Tech Companies - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/stuartanderson/2018/11/26/trump-labor-dept-to-use-new-h-1b-form-against-tech-companies/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEsxnrbV-1EJEpgb7mPXA94qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 05:04:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/stuartanderson/2018/11/26/trump-labor-dept-to-use-new-h-1b-form-against-tech-companies/" target="_blank"&gt;Trump Labor Dept. To Use New H-1B Form Against Tech Companies&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The U.S. Department of Labor is requiring companies to use a new labor condition application for H-1B visas that appears designed to encourage negative media and other attention against high-tech companies that contract out for services. (Photo By Bill Clark/CQ Roll Call) On Monday, November 19, 2018, the U.S. Department of Labor (DOL) began requiring employers to use a new H-1B labor condition application (LCA) form designed largely to inflict reputational harm on high tech employers. The use of government forms to compel information from companies to encourage negative media attention or ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Syrian refugee, stranded seven months in Malaysia airport, lands in Canada - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-canada-immigration-refugees-syria/syrian-refugee-stranded-seven-months-in-malaysia-airport-lands-in-canada-idUSKCN1NW2KN</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJAUr2wCWBZvntFEgZix_YEqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 01:33:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-canada-immigration-refugees-syria/syrian-refugee-stranded-seven-months-in-malaysia-airport-lands-in-canada-idUSKCN1NW2KN" target="_blank"&gt;Syrian refugee, stranded seven months in Malaysia airport, lands in Canada&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Syrian man who spent seven months stranded in a Malaysian airport arrived in Canada this week, ending a months-long ordeal that highlighted asylum seekers' often bizarre quest for refuge. Hassan Al Kontar got stuck in Kuala Lumpur International Airport in March after his Malaysian tourist visa expired and he was not allowed to board a flight to another country. Kontar, 37, who left Syria before that country's civil war erupted in 2011, had worked in the United Arab Emirates for several years but had to leave after his visa ran out. He said he could not return to his homeland because he re...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Germany’s ‘Achilles heel’: Middle East consulates sell forged visas to migrants – media - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/news/444947-germany-consulate-sell-visas-refugees/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOdTxSRQ006u9_JQvHlCMjYqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww_oMo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 07:42:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/news/444947-germany-consulate-sell-visas-refugees/" target="_blank"&gt;Germany’s ‘Achilles heel’: Middle East consulates sell forged visas to migrants – media&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Corrupt officials at German consulates in some Middle Eastern states have been collaborating with people smugglers and literally selling forged visas to migrants seeking to come to Germany as refugees, Der Spiegel revealed. The corrupt schemes “have been run smoothly [by employees] in the visa centers of many German diplomatic missions abroad,” and the Middle East in particular, German Der Spiegel weekly reported, calling the consulates an “Achilles heel” in the fight against people smuggling. The paper also calls the local employees a “weak spot” of German visa departments, as it is they w...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Japan moves forward on plan to let in hundreds of thousands of overseas workers - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/11/29/japan-moves-forward-plan-let-hundreds-thousands-overseas-workers/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFKqAImL1JmYXyXrs1S6XMQqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 01:11:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/11/29/japan-moves-forward-plan-let-hundreds-thousands-overseas-workers/" target="_blank"&gt;Japan moves forward on plan to let in hundreds of thousands of overseas workers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Japan has taken a step towards relaxing its strict immigration laws with a new bill that could pave the way for an influx of hundreds of thousands of overseas workers. The controversial legislation, which opposition parties attempted to block, was pushed through the lower house of parliament by the ruling coalition. The new bill marks a major shift in Japan’s immigration policy, with visas until now issued only to highly skilled foreigners such as doctors and professors. However, the new legislation will permit visas for blue-collar workers from overseas for the first time in a bid to count...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>UAE seeks rich, educated foreigners with long-term visa scheme - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-emirates-visas/uae-seeks-rich-educated-foreigners-with-long-term-visa-scheme-idUSKCN1NU080</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPuufFtdxkQFHj7u2nD2n_4qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2018 08:29:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-emirates-visas/uae-seeks-rich-educated-foreigners-with-long-term-visa-scheme-idUSKCN1NU080" target="_blank"&gt;UAE seeks rich, educated foreigners with long-term visa scheme&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The United Arab Emirates will offer long-term visas to rich property investors, senior scientists and entrepreneurs in an effort to support its economy and real estate market, which have been hurt by low oil prices. Until now, visas for foreigners to live in the Arab world's second biggest economy have generally been valid for only a few years, and have depended on the main visa holder in each family remaining employed. The government said in May it planned to ease that policy. Detailed rules approved by the cabinet on Saturday offer five-year residency to owners of UAE real estate worth at...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Trump administration proposes changes to popular H-1B program - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/30/tech/dhs-h1b-merit-proposal/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJMfGNijACbN_FdNIuhUyfoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 15:18:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/30/tech/dhs-h1b-merit-proposal/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Trump administration proposes changes to popular H-1B program&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Trump administration wants to reform a popular American work visa program. The Department of Homeland Security released a proposal Friday that would increase the number of H-1B visa recipients who have master's degrees or higher level degrees and would move the registration process online. The government has been working to crack down on the H-1B program — a result of President Donald Trump's direction that agencies implement a "Buy American, Hire American" strategy. The H-1B visa is a work visa that's valid for three years and can be renewed for another three years. Many companies use ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Fraudsters who ran fake visa scam and stole £13m from HMRC sentenced to 31 years in jail - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/11/23/fraudsters-ran-fake-visa-scamand-stole-13m-hmrc-sentenced-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEyVJ03C4wpqojGeGVjkTDYqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 21:26:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/11/23/fraudsters-ran-fake-visa-scamand-stole-13m-hmrc-sentenced-31/" target="_blank"&gt;Fraudsters who ran fake visa scam and stole £13m from HMRC sentenced to 31 years in jail&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Five fraudsters who ran a fake Bangladeshi visa scam and falsely claimed £13 million in tax repayments have been sentenced to total of 31 years in jail. London law student Abul Kalam Muhammad Rezaul Karim, 42, was the ringleader in the organised crime group, which set up 79 bogus companies and created fake documentation used by Bangladeshi nationals in fraudulent visa applications. They also used the companies to fraudulently reclaim £13 million in tax repayments from HM Revenue and Customs (HMRC) over a six-year period, the equivalent of 494 new nurses in London for a year. Officers found ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Mammoth Fraud Trial Ends In Jail Sentences For Fraudsters In £13 Million Immigration Scam - HuffPost UK</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.co.uk/entry/mammoth-fraud-trial_uk_5bf81ed2e4b03b230fa12fb7</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEair0bAF6nr8toZaq5vcFUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowmdW_BzCbhUcwuqRp</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 18:24:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.co.uk/entry/mammoth-fraud-trial_uk_5bf81ed2e4b03b230fa12fb7" target="_blank"&gt;Mammoth Fraud Trial Ends In Jail Sentences For Fraudsters In £13 Million Immigration Scam&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost UK&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Five men who ran a multi-million pound tax and immigration scam have been sentenced to more than 31 years in jail after a 35-week trial. The organised crime group claimed £13 million in tax repayments and facilitated around 900 bogus visa applications in an elaborate scheme that spanned six years. The fraud was discovered in 2011 and involved the use of 79 bogus companies to create fake documents that were then used by Bangladeshi nationals in fraudulent visa applications. When applying for visas with a significant financial requirement, the group would claim the applicants were employees ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.co.uk">HuffPost UK</source></item><item><title>Business warns on post-Brexit visa regime for EU migrants - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/f481ee4c-f19a-11e8-9623-d7f9881e729f</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMnbSXY9sS4cI5pLXfqD9j8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 00:02:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/f481ee4c-f19a-11e8-9623-d7f9881e729f" target="_blank"&gt;Business warns on post-Brexit visa regime for EU migrants&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;UK plans to issue low-skilled migrants with short-term visas after Brexit risk aggravating public concerns about immigration while increasing bureaucracy for foreign workers and employers, the engineering consultancy Arup has warned. The government’s long-awaited immigration white paper, due out next week, will outline proposals for a new visa regime which brings EU migrants under the same rules as those from Asia and the US. However, a leaked draft of the paper contains proposals for an 11-month visa with “restricted entitlements and rights”, aimed at roles in sectors such as construction,...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>In First-Of-Its-Kind Lawsuit, Baltimore Sues Trump Over Immigrants' Access To Benefits - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/baltimore-trump-lawsuit-immigrant-benefits-public-charge_us_5bffa782e4b0864f4f6a2aaa</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIL7yVu4lNLn8SDKSdhWd4kqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 10:39:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/baltimore-trump-lawsuit-immigrant-benefits-public-charge_us_5bffa782e4b0864f4f6a2aaa" target="_blank"&gt;In First-Of-Its-Kind Lawsuit, Baltimore Sues Trump Over Immigrants' Access To Benefits&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The city of Baltimore has sued the Trump administration over a State Department policy that the city says has been deterring legal immigrants from claiming benefits they’re entitled to, like food stamps, free school lunches and Medicaid. Baltimore officials filed the suit, described as the first of its kind in the U.S., on Wednesday in collaboration with the nonprofit group Democracy Forward. It accuses the Trump administration of “unlawfully and secretly” expanding the definition of “public charge” in the State Department’s Foreign Affairs Manual, a document used by consular officers to de...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Government accused of massaging immigration statistics in run up to Brexit vote - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/11/24/government-accused-massaging-immigration-statistics-run-brexit/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENBLMJv_34j9ihkeexLDs7wqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2018 16:15:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/11/24/government-accused-massaging-immigration-statistics-run-brexit/" target="_blank"&gt;Government accused of massaging immigration statistics in run up to Brexit vote&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Government has been accused of a cynical attempt to massage immigration statistics after it emerged Theresa May will announce a curb on low-skilled foreign working arriving in Britain. Leaked Cabinet papers revealed how the Home Office has drawn up plan to issue low-skilled migrants with 11-month visas “with restricted entitlements and rights” while they live in the UK. The move was seen as an attempt by the Prime Minister to win support among Eurosceptic Tory MPs in the run up to the Brexit vote. But, immigration experts and campaigners yesterday warned that the proposals would mean th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Illegal immigrants in U.S. at lowest level since 2004: study - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-immigration-population/illegal-immigrants-in-us-at-lowest-level-since-2004-study-idUSKCN1NX07G</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENyCBg-qgwMdqBjtSC7KH7YqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 02:07:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-immigration-population/illegal-immigrants-in-us-at-lowest-level-since-2004-study-idUSKCN1NX07G" target="_blank"&gt;Illegal immigrants in U.S. at lowest level since 2004: study&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The population of unauthorized immigrants in the United States fell to 10.7 million in 2016, its lowest level since 2004, due largely to a decline in the number of people coming from Mexico, a study released on Tuesday said. The report from the Pew Research Center pewrsr.ch/2Qptbid, based on U.S. Census data and other figures from 2016, showed the number of illegal immigrants in the United States has declined steadily since its peak of 12.2 million in 2007. Researchers believe part of the reason for the decline was the economic recession that gripped the United States in 2007 and the slow r...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Most Americans have common ground on immigration. Congress should listen to them. - The Washington Post</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/most-americans-have-common-ground-on-immigration-congress-should-listen-to-them/2018/11/19/2d51946c-ec1d-11e8-baac-2a674e91502b_story.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEARrGociilZxTArmOHZ93rMqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjtSUCjC30XQw_qe5AQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 23:11:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/most-americans-have-common-ground-on-immigration-congress-should-listen-to-them/2018/11/19/2d51946c-ec1d-11e8-baac-2a674e91502b_story.html" target="_blank"&gt;Most Americans have common ground on immigration. Congress should listen to them.&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Washington Post&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Maria Valles Bonilla, 106, during a naturalization ceremony on Nov. 6 in Fairfax, Va.The Associated Press On immigration, a vast area of potential policy compromise lies between the extremes of nativist restriction and open borders. For the time being, however, politicians determined to exploit the emotions that those two positions arouse dominate the debate. President Trump’s vulgar demonization of unauthorized immigrants, coupled with his proposals to slash legal immigration, defines the morally and economically dubious right end of the spectrum. The call to “abolish ICE” — the U.S. Immig...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.washingtonpost.com">The Washington Post</source></item><item><title>Russia may have hacked British visa system to gain documents for agents who poisoned Skripals, investigation claims - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/11/16/russia-may-have-hacked-british-visa-system-gain-documents-agents/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEiF06pHidK-S5DCG2D5bcQqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 16:15:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/11/16/russia-may-have-hacked-british-visa-system-gain-documents-agents/" target="_blank"&gt;Russia may have hacked British visa system to gain documents for agents who poisoned Skripals, investigation claims&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Russia may have hacked the British visa system to gain documents for the agents who attempted to assassinate the Skripals, an investigation has claimed. The probe suggests that Russian intelligence infiltrated the computer infrastructure of a company - TLSContact - that processes British visa applications. The investigation, published Friday by investigative group Bellingcat and Russian website The Insider, aims to show how the two Russian military intelligence agents who have been charged with the Salisbury poisoning may have obtained British visas. The former chief technical officer of a ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Analysis: What's the link between immigration and population? - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-20/permanent-migration-cut-and-population/10513860</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOVzqIy_nnzf7Kt7lgGimxoqFwgEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDoiokG</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 04:55:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-20/permanent-migration-cut-and-population/10513860" target="_blank"&gt;Analysis: What's the link between immigration and population?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By political reporter Jackson Gothe-Snape Most Sydneysiders and Melburnians will barely notice a permanent migration cut flagged by Prime Minister Scott Morrison. Population growth is driven far more by foreign students and births, after all. In May, just as conservative voices in the Liberal Party were calling for a cut to permanent migration, the then-treasurer played down the significance of permanent visas. "The permanent immigration intake is not a big factor when it comes to population growth," he told radio station 3AW. "Temporary immigration and natural increases are 80 per cent of ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Pew: Undocumented in US Hit Lowest Level in Decade in 2016 - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/pew-number-of-undocumented-in-us-drops-/4677120.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHUOca5bcwxyWXSKoRe9GTAqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 23:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/pew-number-of-undocumented-in-us-drops-/4677120.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pew: Undocumented in US Hit Lowest Level in Decade in 2016&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The number of unauthorized immigrants in the U.S. fell to its lowest level in 10 years in 2016, the Pew Research Center reported Tuesday. Using government data, nonpartisan Pew’s “Fact Tank” concluded that from 2007 to 2016, the number of undocumented immigrants in the U.S. fell from a peak of 12.2 million to 10.7 million. Pew attributed the decrease to a sharp drop — by 1.5 million — in the number of Mexicans crossing the U.S. border illegally. However, the number of immigrants from El Salvador, Guatemala and Honduras trying to cross over from Mexico illegally was up, making Central Americ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Home Office admits errors in refusing settlement visas to professionals - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/6a2f199a-ee7a-11e8-8180-9cf212677a57</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMr3LvbCPsHgjn2xuItGsuAqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 18:52:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/6a2f199a-ee7a-11e8-8180-9cf212677a57" target="_blank"&gt;Home Office admits errors in refusing settlement visas to professionals&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Home Office has admitted making errors in refusing settlement visas to professional migrants because of discrepancies in their tax affairs after an internal review found rules had been wrongly applied. The probe was a response to complaints that immigration rules originally intended to tackle serious criminals had been used to refuse over 1,500 highly-skilled workers and entrepreneurs the right to settle in the UK, often over minor tax issues. In a parliamentary debate in June, MPs claimed their constituents faced removal from the UK over discrepancies of as little as £1.20 between sett...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>U.S. Work Visa Options For Entrepreneurs: A Beginner's Guide - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/theyec/2018/11/14/u-s-work-visa-options-for-entrepreneurs-a-beginners-guide/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDGXVqFZC0e31LqICqvj60cqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMKGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/theyec/2018/11/14/u-s-work-visa-options-for-entrepreneurs-a-beginners-guide/" target="_blank"&gt;U.S. Work Visa Options For Entrepreneurs: A Beginner's Guide&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Getty The United States visa system was not established with entrepreneurs in mind. Nonetheless, there are several types of visa that either individually or collectively could serve a foreign entrepreneur’s purpose of entering the United States for any number of purposes. In this guide, I will discuss the popular temporary visitor, employee, financier and trainee visas. Temporary Visitor Or Networker Visa A number of countries have treaties with the United States that include visa waiver programs. This allows individuals from these countries to come to the United States for up to 90 days wi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>The Number of Illegal Immigrants in the U.S. Has Dropped, a Study Says. Here Are 5 Takeaways. - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/27/us/illegal-immigrants-population-study.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOR-XK2AnqRohEmvYKuBiqUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzwwt4QY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 22:17:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/27/us/illegal-immigrants-population-study.html" target="_blank"&gt;The Number of Illegal Immigrants in the U.S. Has Dropped, a Study Says. Here Are 5 Takeaways.&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shortly after then-candidate Donald Trump announced his presidential campaign, he suggested that the number of undocumented immigrants living in the United States could exceed 30 million. But a new study puts the number far lower and shows a significant decline over more than a decade. The study, published by the Pew Research Center on Tuesday, put the number of undocumented immigrants in the United States at 10.7 million in 2016, down from a peak of 12.2 million in 2007. As Pew analyzed new data from recent years, its researchers found that “it wasn’t just that the numbers declined, but al...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>Separated by travel ban, Iranian families reunite at border library - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-immigration-ban-insight/separated-by-travel-ban-iranian-families-reunite-at-border-library-idUSKCN1NX1P2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJUWetRpO38UD3QGILCqWxAqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 17:33:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-immigration-ban-insight/separated-by-travel-ban-iranian-families-reunite-at-border-library-idUSKCN1NX1P2" target="_blank"&gt;Separated by travel ban, Iranian families reunite at border library&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;During the six-hour drive from New York City to a tiny town in northern Vermont, Iranian student Shirin Estahbanati cried at the thought of seeing her father for the first time in nearly three years. Since then, he had suffered a heart attack, and she hadn't dared leave America to comfort him. But as she traveled north, she also couldn't stop worrying. What if she missed the turnoff and drove across the U.S.-Canadian border by mistake? Estahbanati, like many Iranian students in the United States, has a single-entry visa and can't leave the country without risking that she won't be allowed b...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>To bypass H-1B hurdles, Indian IT firms are now hiring on TN visas - Quartz</title><link>https://qz.com/india/1469829/facing-h-1b-woes-indian-it-firms-hire-mexicans-on-tn-visa/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIscTeYZpeE0hprIYlHJDloqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowi4-MATDXsRUwhP2ZAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 09:45:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://qz.com/india/1469829/facing-h-1b-woes-indian-it-firms-hire-mexicans-on-tn-visa/" target="_blank"&gt;To bypass H-1B hurdles, Indian IT firms are now hiring on TN visas&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Quartz&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indian IT outsourcing companies have begun to feel the pinch of the Donald Trump regime’s tough visa stance. During the July-September quarter this year, most Indian tech majors saw a significant year-on-year rise in the share of revenue spent on subcontracting, according to an analysts’ note from Kotak Institutional Equities Research released on Nov. 20. “Subcontracting is employed by IT companies as a short-term measure to fill gaps in supply intended to be filled through H-1B workers or offshoring, to avoid drag on margins,” Kawaljeet Saluja and Sathish Kumar wrote in the note. They expe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://qz.com">Quartz</source></item><item><title>An Excel error could delay Japan’s massive immigration overhaul - Quartz</title><link>https://qz.com/1469572/an-excel-error-could-delay-japans-massive-immigration-overhaul/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIn7Y-Ax2JXA1bofDoxQFfkqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowi4-MATDXsRUwhPieAw</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 03:46:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://qz.com/1469572/an-excel-error-could-delay-japans-massive-immigration-overhaul/" target="_blank"&gt;An Excel error could delay Japan’s massive immigration overhaul&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Quartz&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Japan’s government seems to be in need of some tech support. Its plans to pass a crucial immigration bill that could open the country’s doors further to as many as 340,000 foreign workers from next year might be stymied due to data input errors. Japan’s government had given lawmakers an analysis of why foreign workers in the country are dropping out of an existing work training program, as it argues for the country to create create two new categories of work visas. The justice ministry admitted last week that the data on those workers was incorrect, and blamed the problems on the handling o...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://qz.com">Quartz</source></item><item><title>Regional migration approvals stalling ahead of new five-year bush visa - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-13/regional-migration-approvals-stalling-five-year-bush-visa/10488204</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOav3CYxDSWfH0SyRHczULoqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 23:53:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-13/regional-migration-approvals-stalling-five-year-bush-visa/10488204" target="_blank"&gt;Regional migration approvals stalling ahead of new five-year bush visa&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By political reporter Jackson Gothe-Snape Regional visa approvals have fallen to their lowest levels in a decade as the Federal Government prepares to introduce a scheme requiring new arrivals to work outside the major cities for five years. State-specific and regional visa approvals fell to 36,250 places in 2017-18, according to new figures published by the Government. John Hourigan, the president of the Migration Institute of Australia, said recent restrictions have effectively phased out key parts of the existing regional scheme. Visas approved for the regional sponsored migration scheme...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Impacts From Changing Administrative Rule For H-1B And L1 Work Visas - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/peterbendorsamuel/2018/11/12/impacts-from-changing-administrative-rule-for-h-1b-and-l1-work-visas/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMGIcqPkXrfCJeY8Fx5V6UEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 17:18:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/peterbendorsamuel/2018/11/12/impacts-from-changing-administrative-rule-for-h-1b-and-l1-work-visas/" target="_blank"&gt;Impacts From Changing Administrative Rule For H-1B And L1 Work Visas&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The US Labor Department’s recently announced new regulations for H-1B and L1 work visas focus on the Trump Administration’s ongoing effort to tighten regulations and increase administrative hurdles. Viewed individually no new regulation is a show-stopper; but it’s clear that, collectively, they will have a more material effect. Here’s my take on the significant issues for service providers and their customers. The Administration’s Goal It’s clear that the Trump Administration, through changing the administrative rules, wants to significantly slow down and restrict usage of H-1B and L1 visas...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Brexit: EU to decide whether Britons will need visas in event of no-deal - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/travel/news-and-advice/brexit-news-no-deal-visa-travel-eu-holiday-passport-strasbourg-a8631011.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFU_VCoccThjR5Y4tTgIZ7EqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCRx_0F</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 09:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/travel/news-and-advice/brexit-news-no-deal-visa-travel-eu-holiday-passport-strasbourg-a8631011.html" target="_blank"&gt;Brexit: EU to decide whether Britons will need visas in event of no-deal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;European officials are meeting in Strasbourg to decide if British travellers will need a visa to visit the EU in the event of a no-deal Brexit. These are the key questions. What’s happening? The College of Commissioners – the political leadership of the European Commission, effectively the EU’s cabinet – will decide how the European Union will treat the UK after Brexit, if no agreement is reached on a transition period. What are the options? The default position for a third country is that it joins the “visa required” list, along with people from China, Russia, India, Thailand, and all of A...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Visa policy change will make it easier for Trump administration to deny applications - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/07/16/politics/visa-policy-changes/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJJJ6Sv2XVD3w6GfsXiU0jwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 20:12:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/07/16/politics/visa-policy-changes/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Visa policy change will make it easier for Trump administration to deny applications&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Visa policy change will make it easier Trump administration to deny applications It will soon be easier for the Trump administration to deny visas. In a move that further curbs immigration, the U.S. Citizenship and Immigration Services is giving anyone who reviews visa applications or petitions the discretion to deny requests, without first seeking additional evidence that might be needed to complete an application, or issuing a notice stating the intent to deny a request. The change takes effect September 11. The memo, quietly issued on Friday, means the government can deny visas if applic...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Brexit: UK visitors to Europe will not need visas – for now - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/travel/news-and-advice/brexit-european-union-eu-passport-visa-rules-strasbourg-travel-permit-etas-a8631916.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDUS-HitZ-rlOHrMaEFuUtIqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCRx_0F</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 16:09:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/travel/news-and-advice/brexit-european-union-eu-passport-visa-rules-strasbourg-travel-permit-etas-a8631916.html" target="_blank"&gt;Brexit: UK visitors to Europe will not need visas – for now&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The College of Commissioners – the political leadership of the European Commission, effectively the EU’s cabinet – has announced how British visitors to the EU will be treated in the event of a “no-deal” Brexit. These are the key aspects. What were the options? The default position for a third country is that it joins the “visa required” list, along with people from China, Russia, India, Thailand, and all of Africa. This would have required travellers to apply between three months and 15 days before the intended journey, to provide evidence of travel insurance, and to pay €60 euros for adul...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Brexit: EU says British citizens will not need visas to visit member states in event of no-deal - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/politics/eu-brexit-visas-no-deal-british-citizens-latest-a8631671.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECMRGVzCbUxbSsAWKi4DTOsqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDyxv0F</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 13:57:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/politics/eu-brexit-visas-no-deal-british-citizens-latest-a8631671.html" target="_blank"&gt;Brexit: EU says British citizens will not need visas to visit member states in event of no-deal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;British travellers will not need visas to visit the European Union for short stays even if there is a no-deal Brexit, the European Commission has said. Commissioners made the recommendation to put the UK on the visa-exempt list at a meeting in Strasbourg on Tuesday. The policy is dependent on the UK continuing to offer reciprocal visa-free access for EU citizens. Travel advice issued by the Commission says: “The European Commission has proposed to the EU legislator to exempt UK nationals from visa requirements for short-term stays”. - Read more French government warns on visas after no-deal...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Queen Elizabeth Required To Do This When Traveling Even Without Passport - International Business Times</title><link>https://www.ibtimes.com/queen-elizabeth-ii-required-do-when-traveling-even-without-passport-2731587</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEq_EwBfnNcFAIecpuiPsYoqFwgEKg4IACoGCAow9891MIGZDDCJgrIF</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Nov 2018 08:26:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ibtimes.com/queen-elizabeth-ii-required-do-when-traveling-even-without-passport-2731587" target="_blank"&gt;Queen Elizabeth Required To Do This When Traveling Even Without Passport&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;International Business Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Queen Elizabeth II is still required to do one thing when traveling even though she’s the monarch. It has previously been reported that Her Majesty doesn’t need a passport when traveling by plane because as the head of the monarchy, she is the one that issues the passport to Britons. However, Her Majesty is still required to complete an identity check before boarding the plane. Harriet Mallinson, a journalist for Express, reported that the Queen still has to give her full name, age, address, place of birth, and nationality to the immigration officials to confirm her identity. The informatio...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ibtimes.com">International Business Times</source></item><item><title>'I've been warned about overstaying my US visa – even though I left the country months ago' - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/advice/overstaying-us-visa-warning/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN4Lo1jzzCYvFVzHY6qZxeIqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCy8LkF</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 10:07:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/advice/overstaying-us-visa-warning/" target="_blank"&gt;'I've been warned about overstaying my US visa – even though I left the country months ago'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Peter Hill writes In June my wife and I spent two weeks touring the United States and Canada. We flew from the UK into Seattle and departed for Canada three days later on the fast ferry to Victoria on Vancouver Island. At the end of our trip we flew back to the UK from Calgary. At the end of August we both had an email from US Customs and Border Protection stating that we must leave the US within 10 days to comply with our ESTA visa requirements. It would seem that we were never signed out of the US by the port authorities at Seattle. Three weeks ago I contacted the Department of Homeland S...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Lawsuit Charges USCIS Move Against Foreign Students Is Illegal - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/stuartanderson/2018/11/09/lawsuit-charges-uscis-move-against-foreign-students-is-illegal/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGB5rv5ZdFIzohUEb7jswg0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 05:03:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/stuartanderson/2018/11/09/lawsuit-charges-uscis-move-against-foreign-students-is-illegal/" target="_blank"&gt;Lawsuit Charges USCIS Move Against Foreign Students Is Illegal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The exterior facade of a Washington and Lee University hall. Many U.S. universities are concerned about federal policies toward international students. Some schools have joined a lawsuit against U.S. Citizenship and Immigration Services. (Getty) A U.S. Citizenship and Immigration Services (USCIS) policy memo could bar many international students from the United States. A new lawsuit argues that is actually the goal of the government memo. USCIS has attempted to justify the new action against international students by citing a questionable Department of Homeland Security (DHS) overstay repor...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Backpacker visa relief welcomed by growers, but long-term solution 'still needed' - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/rural/2018-11-05/seasonal-worker-backpacker-visa-changes-announced-scott-morrison/10464972</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEANd6h9A1Sm91_FgkRQ7n_IqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDD9QQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 01:36:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/rural/2018-11-05/seasonal-worker-backpacker-visa-changes-announced-scott-morrison/10464972" target="_blank"&gt;Backpacker visa relief welcomed by growers, but long-term solution 'still needed'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Changes to Australia's seasonal worker program and backpacker visas have been welcomed by Australia's agricultural industry as something that will provide immediate relief, but the industry will not give up the fight for a dedicated agriculture visa. Prime Minister Scott Morrison announced the visa changes today, effective immediately, at a strawberry farm in southern Queensland as part of a four-day tour of the state. Key points: - The changes to the seasonal worker program and backpacker visas are designed to keep workers on farms for longer - Growers have welcomed the changes but say mor...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>The Latest: ACLU files suit to stop Trump new asylum limits - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/2eff798d70024a0d869d966cf8e0588a</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENs7emMjFYNp7bjFatH7SLUqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvKadAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 19:37:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/2eff798d70024a0d869d966cf8e0588a" target="_blank"&gt;The Latest: ACLU files suit to stop Trump new asylum limits&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Latest on President Donald Trump and immigration (all times local): 2:30 p.m. The American Civil Liberties Union has filed a legal challenge to President Donald Trump's order denying asylum to migrants if they cross the U.S.-Mexico border illegally. The lawsuit was filed Friday in federal court in San Francisco and argues the new rules are against the law. Attorney Lee Gelernt says the regulations will put families in danger. The suit seeks to declare the regulations invalid and want a judge to stop rules from going into effect while the litigation is pending. The new ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Scientists angry at UK visa denials for African, Asian researchers - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-science-britain-visas/scientists-angry-at-uk-visa-denials-for-african-asian-researchers-idUSKBN1ND2B0?il=0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHBfuIo9-lzS5pWJRShsFnoqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 16:24:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-science-britain-visas/scientists-angry-at-uk-visa-denials-for-african-asian-researchers-idUSKBN1ND2B0?il=0" target="_blank"&gt;Scientists angry at UK visa denials for African, Asian researchers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scientists in Britain expressed concern on Thursday after at least 17 delegates from Africa and Asia wanting to attend a health conference in London were denied visas. Peter Piot, a Belgian-born microbiologist who was part of a team that discovered the Ebola virus in the 1970s and is now director of the London School of Hygiene &amp; Tropical Medicine, was among those protesting against restrictive criteria for granting short-term business visas. In a letter to the interior minister, Sajid Javid, Piot said the restrictions "represent a significant threat" to the United Kingdom establishing itse...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>EU proposes visa-free travel for Britons after Brexit - Reuters UK</title><link>https://uk.reuters.com/article/uk-britain-eu-commission/eu-executive-to-recommend-exempting-britons-from-visas-after-brexit-sources-idUKKCN1NI1EK</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIdzNWvpTwU_C_8aVOxw00kqGAgEKg8IACoHCAow3MukCjD92Xcwy4jqAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 14:44:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://uk.reuters.com/article/uk-britain-eu-commission/eu-executive-to-recommend-exempting-britons-from-visas-after-brexit-sources-idUKKCN1NI1EK" target="_blank"&gt;EU proposes visa-free travel for Britons after Brexit&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters UK&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The European Union's executive proposed on Tuesday that Britons be allowed to visit the bloc without visas after Brexit and stepped up preparations in case of a no-deal divorce. Speaking after the European Commission sat in Strasbourg, deputy head Frans Timmermans said a Brexit deal with Britain was the bloc's preferred solution. "Very intense negotiations are ongoing. It is clear that although we are making progress, we are not there yet," he told a news conference. "We also discussed a number of issues related to our no-deal planning. You have to do that anyway. We are working very hard f...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://uk.reuters.com">Reuters UK</source></item><item><title>Scouted: Passport Covers For Kids Will Help You Win at Parenting - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/passport-covers-for-kids-will-help-you-win-at-parenting</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENCCjz1jMo6-iIx61apjDzwqFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMJahhgY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/passport-covers-for-kids-will-help-you-win-at-parenting" target="_blank"&gt;Scouted: Passport Covers For Kids Will Help You Win at Parenting&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first thing I bought when I learned I was pregnant was not a crib, nor a pack of swaddles, nor any other product related to the day-to-day logistics of infant care. Rather, it was a $13.99 passport cover—a cute, pastel little thing scrawled with “Off to See the World!” At that point, I didn’t know how to change a diaper, but I did know that I wanted to raise a traveler. According to the State Department, some 60 percent of U.S. citizens don’t own a passport. Couple that with the Trump Administration’s travel ban, visa restrictions, and curtailing of refugees, plus reports that passports...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Backpacker visa extension may make Pacific workers worse off - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-06/pacific-workers-worse-off-backpacker-visa-extension/10469660</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO3XJCIbj69l_7MQiwBmxD0qFwgEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDD6kIkG</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 08:48:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-06/pacific-workers-worse-off-backpacker-visa-extension/10469660" target="_blank"&gt;Backpacker visa extension may make Pacific workers worse off&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are fears the Federal Government's plan to increase the number of backpackers working on Australian farms will severely disadvantage workers from the Pacific. On Monday, Prime Minister Scott Morrison announced an expansion of the working holiday visa (for backpackers) and the Seasonal Worker Programme (for Pacific workers) to help meet labour shortages on farms. The move comes as New Zealand announced on Tuesday it would expand its seasonal workers scheme to 12,850 workers annually, compared to the nearly 8,500 that came to Australia last year. External Link: NZ foreign affairs minist...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Home Office in 'continuous state of disaster management' amid surge in immigration u-turns - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/home-news/home-office-immigration-uk-eu-brexit-media-explosion-u-turns-government-a8612556.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEteH_Ov0fF9hpXAFUeyssAqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 12:04:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/home-news/home-office-immigration-uk-eu-brexit-media-explosion-u-turns-government-a8612556.html" target="_blank"&gt;Home Office in 'continuous state of disaster management' amid surge in immigration u-turns&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Home Office has been accused of operating in a “continuous state of disaster management” as an increasing number of erroneous immigration decisions are being overturned only once they are publicly exposed. A number of recent news stories about individuals being refused entry to the UK or threatened with removal have prompted officials to reverse decisions within hours or even minutes news articles being published online or in print. In the last two weeks alone, The Independent has reported on two such cases. Both in involved people being barred from entering the UK because officials wer...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>State Dept. Improperly Seized Passports of Americans in Yemen, Inquiry Finds - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/02/world/middleeast/state-department-passports-yemen-citizens-.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIo79dvfx0M3FUrNiGy6I9YqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzww5oEY</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2018 00:30:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/02/world/middleeast/state-department-passports-yemen-citizens-.html" target="_blank"&gt;State Dept. Improperly Seized Passports of Americans in Yemen, Inquiry Finds&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON — The State Department improperly seized the passports of at least 31 American citizens trying to obtain vital records and other paperwork from the United States Embassy in Yemen, according to an inspector general’s report released on Friday. The passports were taken between December 2012 and June 2013, just as Yemen’s fragile political system began descending into chaos. Consular officials claimed they confiscated the passports of citizens after finding that their printed names were false or fraudulent. In many cases, the citizens had gone to the embassy to obtain American passp...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>AI lie detectors to be tested by the EU at border points - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/11/01/ai-lie-detectors-tested-eu-border-points/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPJ87yHN_Ez3VRPoCig4A3IqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCuqhU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 11:19:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/11/01/ai-lie-detectors-tested-eu-border-points/" target="_blank"&gt;AI lie detectors to be tested by the EU at border points&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lie detectors equipped with artificial intelligence are set to be tested at border points in Europe as part of an EU-funded project to combat crime and terrorism. Travellers will be asked to upload pictures of their passport, visa and proof of funds, and will then use a webcam to answer questions such as "what is in your suitcase" from a computer-animated border guard. The €4.5m project, called iBorderCtrl, will be tested at the borders of Hungary, Latvia and Greece for six months. The aim of the project is to speed up traffic at the EU's external borders. The UK, Spain, Poland, Germany an...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Henley Index: Japanese passport now world's most powerful - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/travel/article/most-powerful-passport-henley-index-2018/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL8AnglNSUyjHOsKYD8zBuMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMMXoyQU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 18:01:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/travel/article/most-powerful-passport-henley-index-2018/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Henley Index: Japanese passport now world's most powerful&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;World's most powerful passports: Global citizenship and residence advisory firm Henley &amp; Partners has released its quarterly report on the world's most desirable passports. Citizens of Hungary (such as this chap), Slovenia and Malaysia can enjoy seamless travel to 180 destinations. AFP/AFP/AFP/Getty Images 9. Iceland: The wild and wonderful landscape of Iceland has proved a magnet for foreign visitors in recent years, but Icelanders themselves can easily head in the other direction with visa-free or visa-on-arrival access to 181 destinations. Joe Raedle/Getty Images 8. Czech Republic and Ne...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Smart customer service hinges on intelligent help - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/9f207934-db63-11e8-b173-ebef6ab1374a</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECkpnxPLOUJ3Xwr9HPSt26oqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwgtt6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 04:00:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/9f207934-db63-11e8-b173-ebef6ab1374a" target="_blank"&gt;Smart customer service hinges on intelligent help&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last month, in a hurry, I bought a Copenhagen to London ticket on Ryanair — for £13 — only to find, in the confusing blizzard of offers and add-ons, I had given the wrong date and had shown up at the airport exactly a month early. My grandmother’s aphorism, “what is cheap is dear”, came to mind as I paid £277 to get on the correct flight. Last week, however, I made a travel mistake which raised a more interesting issue than careless clicking. I needed to get to New York at short notice. Amid the £700-plus fares I saw one for £368 with Air Canada, with a two-hour stopover in Toronto and the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item></channel></rss>