<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Stonehenge - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIQgKIhtDQkFTRGdvSUwyMHZNRFozWm1jU0FtVnVLQUFQAQ?hl=en-GB&amp;gl=GB&amp;ceid=GB:en</link><language>en-GB</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 13:27:20 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Stonehenge site 'damaged' by engineers working on tunnel - BBC News</title><link>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-england-wiltshire-46465258</link><guid isPermaLink="false">52780129323822</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 09:30:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-england-wiltshire-46465258" target="_blank"&gt;Stonehenge site 'damaged' by engineers working on tunnel&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;BBC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.thetimes.co.uk/article/workers-drilling-into-stonehenge-site-destroy-holy-relics-g0mngjng9" target="_blank"&gt;Workers drilling into Stonehenge site 'destroy holy relics'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://inews.co.uk/news/uk/travesty-sees-ancient-stonehenge-platform-accidentally-destroyed-as-tunnel-built/" target="_blank"&gt;‘Travesty’ sees ancient platform near Stonehenge accidentally destroyed to build tunnel&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;iNews&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.bbc.com/news/uk-england-46465416" target="_blank"&gt;Stonehenge tunnel: The background to the row&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;BBC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/road-workers-drill-through-6-000-year-old-prehistoric-platform-n944671" target="_blank"&gt;Road workers drill through 6,000-year-old prehistoric platform near Stonehenge&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;NBCNews.com&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/stories/CAAqOQgKIjNDQklTSURvSmMzUnZjbmt0TXpZd1NoTUtFUWl1bHZDbWpZQU1FYlc4M3dEYlU5ZmFLQUFQAQ?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;View full coverage on Google News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;</description><source url="https://www.bbc.co.uk">BBC News</source><media:content url="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/proxy/6JPspT0CU0i-7xk355083VSbi3HGsCWo8LWiOMRSPuVtyO9vicun5Y2cK4r9Ur9LKcCjKTYkA5H1K_upqqeLvbF1wf_hh52Q6Jb830qGb6ezB7f59CV2wQb9lOp3ZEocIMO5mIe0oypOj-jSW32V2K-ABXW92P3rYNaAbcxCI_fBRlFc21ZqAS1R946IrwAgXnzqlNdoBad8Z4uan9yzEWlmCGWMk3uE5M0=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Ancient platform 'damaged' during Stonehenge tunnel work - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2018/dec/06/ancient-platform-damaged-during-stonehenge-tunnel-work</link><guid isPermaLink="false">52780127611953</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 00:06:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2018/dec/06/ancient-platform-damaged-during-stonehenge-tunnel-work" target="_blank"&gt;Ancient platform 'damaged' during Stonehenge tunnel work&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/12/05/stonehenge-row-highways-england-work-new-tunnel-damages-mesolithic/" target="_blank"&gt;Stonehenge row with Highways England as work for new tunnel damages mesolithic platform&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Telegraph.co.uk&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7910338/drill-a-hole-into-stonehenge/" target="_blank"&gt;Blundering road workers drill a hole into 6000-year-old site near Stonehenge in tests for controversial tunnel&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Sun&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/stories/CAAqOQgKIjNDQklTSURvSmMzUnZjbmt0TXpZd1NoTUtFUWl4MkllbWpZQU1FZkR5TFoxMDR5OUlLQUFQAQ?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;View full coverage on Google News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>'Careless' engineers accused of damaging site near Stonehenge - Sky News</title><link>https://news.sky.com/story/careless-engineers-accused-of-damaging-site-near-stonehenge-11573065</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiX2h0dHBzOi8vbmV3cy5za3kuY29tL3N0b3J5L2NhcmVsZXNzLWVuZ2luZWVycy1hY2N1c2VkLW9mLWRhbWFnaW5nLXNpdGUtbmVhci1zdG9uZWhlbmdlLTExNTczMDY10gGoAWh0dHBzOi8vbmV3cy1za3ktY29tLmNkbi5hbXBwcm9qZWN0Lm9yZy92L3MvbmV3cy5za3kuY29tL3N0b3J5L2FtcC9jYXJlbGVzcy1lbmdpbmVlcnMtYWNjdXNlZC1vZi1kYW1hZ2luZy1zaXRlLW5lYXItc3RvbmVoZW5nZS0xMTU3MzA2NT9hbXBfanNfdj0wLjEjd2Vidmlldz0xJmNhcD1zd2lwZQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 18:39:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://news.sky.com/story/careless-engineers-accused-of-damaging-site-near-stonehenge-11573065" target="_blank"&gt;'Careless' engineers accused of damaging site near Stonehenge&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Sky News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is feared Blick Mead has been irreparably damaged by work to monitor water levels, but Highways England denies this.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://news.sky.com">Sky News</source></item><item><title>Newgrange: Ireland's amazing feat of Stone Age engineering - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/travel/article/newgrange-ireland-stone-age/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELhn3nVhxqCoH7pDAumHkkwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:29:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/travel/article/newgrange-ireland-stone-age/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Newgrange: Ireland's amazing feat of Stone Age engineering&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Newgrange: Ireland's Newgrange passage tomb is one of the earliest and greatest feats of solar alignment, built 500 years before the Giza pyramids and 1,000 years before Stonehenge. Tourism Ireland Winter Solstice: Each year, between December 19 and 23, hundreds gather at dawn at this prehistoric tomb. A lucky few will have won entry by lottery -- in 2016 just one in 545 applicants got the chance. Brian Lynch/Tourism Ireland Dawn's early light: Shortly before 9 a.m., light strikes through the "roofbox" above the tomb's entrance, creeping along the passageway and eventually flooding the inne...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Summer Solstice 2017 Facts - International Business Times</title><link>http://www.ibtimes.com/summer-solstice-2017-facts-know-about-first-day-summer-2554769</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHyE1iYBNyhzdiHehC2mQWwqFwgEKg4IACoGCAow9891MIGZDDDIhrIF</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2017 12:04:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.ibtimes.com/summer-solstice-2017-facts-know-about-first-day-summer-2554769" target="_blank"&gt;Summer Solstice 2017 Facts&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;International Business Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The longest day of the year, also known as the summer solstice, is Tuesday and marks the first official day of summer in the Northern Hemisphere, when the sun reaches its northernmost point in the sky. The shortest day of the year, known as the winter solstice, occurs between Dec. 20 and 22. Here are some facts to know about the first day of summer. What does solstice mean? The word "solstice" is from the Latin "solstitium" from sol (sun) and stitium (to stop), meaning the sun standing still. It literally means “furthest or culminating point; a turning point.” Read: 17 Best Summer Solstice ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.ibtimes.com">International Business Times</source></item><item><title>Monday’s best TV: Trump – The Kremlin Candidate?, Silent Witness - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/tv-and-radio/2017/jan/16/mondays-best-tv-trump-the-kremlin-candidate-silent-witness</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAdd6IkR1vJNheJGnK8twBgqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCOvRU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2017 06:09:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/tv-and-radio/2017/jan/16/mondays-best-tv-trump-the-kremlin-candidate-silent-witness" target="_blank"&gt;Monday’s best TV: Trump – The Kremlin Candidate?, Silent Witness&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trump: The Kremlin Candidate? – Panorama 8.30pm, BBC1 In the week the world crosses itself and hopes for the best, John Sweeney travels to Russia, Ukraine and the US to investigate the most laughably open secret of recent times – the Kremlin’s marionette-like manipulation of American politics – and ponders that the only thing scarier than Trump and Putin’s friendship will be their falling out. Over on Channel 4, Dispatches casts a sceptical eye over the president-elect’s corporate cabal. Ali Catterall Silent Witness 9pm, BBC1 The body of a woman is recovered from the river Lea, with mystery...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Ancient Stone Tablet Found: Reveals Comet Impact Sparking The Rise Of Civilization - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/trevornace/2017/04/30/ancient-stone-tablet-found-reveals-comet-impact-sparking-the-rise-of-civilization/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIhjZIdfnPH9OaQmRhAbxd8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2017 19:09:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/trevornace/2017/04/30/ancient-stone-tablet-found-reveals-comet-impact-sparking-the-rise-of-civilization/" target="_blank"&gt;Ancient Stone Tablet Found: Reveals Comet Impact Sparking The Rise Of Civilization&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stone carvings show comet hitting Earth, wiping out the Woolly Mammoths and sparking a rise in civilization. Scientists have translated an ancient stone tablet found at a temple in Turkey. The tablet confirms that a comet struck Earth around 11,000BC, leading to global destruction including the extinction of the woolly mammoth and the rise of new civilizations. The carvings were found in Gobekli Tepe in southern Turkey, the world’s oldest known temple and a site for ancient observatory and worship. In fact, the temple dates back to 9,000BC, approximately 6,000 years older than Stonehenge. T...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>National Trust blamed for visitors urinating on Avebury stones after deciding to close loos at 4pm - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/02/20/nationaltrust-blamed-visitors-urinating-avebury-stones-deciding/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJrpD8MB3sTeUrDDFK1gTFEqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2017 12:36:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/02/20/nationaltrust-blamed-visitors-urinating-avebury-stones-deciding/" target="_blank"&gt;National Trust blamed for visitors urinating on Avebury stones after deciding to close loos at 4pm&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The National Trust is being blamed for visitors urinating on Europe's largest stone circle because it shuts its loos early. Locals in the village of Avebury in Wiltshire say the 5,000-year-old monuments are being fouled by tourists who are getting caught short. The residents say it's down to the National Trust only opening the doors to the toilets in its museum from 10am to 4pm in the winter months. The Avebury stonesCredit: Dave Burges They say some of the 250,000 annual visitors to the World Heritage Site in Wiltshire are instead using the rocks as a loo. Tourists are now resorting to re...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Exclusive tours offer behind-the-scenes access to world's busiest attractions - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/2015/10/27/travel/exclusive-behind-the-scenes-tours/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFD1o9wMGAxKtTEL4sjrTGgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2017 19:42:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/2015/10/27/travel/exclusive-behind-the-scenes-tours/" target="_blank"&gt;Exclusive tours offer behind-the-scenes access to world's busiest attractions&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Imagine securing a one-on-one date with Mona Lisa at the Louvre. Or ogling the Sistine Chapel after every other tourist has been kicked out for the night. This type of unimaginable access to global treasures is what Greg Sacks orchestrates for a living. As co-founder of custom-travel outfit Trufflepig, he's helped secure private entry for his clients to some of the world's top attractions. "We've privatized the Sagrada Família in Barcelona, a couple of Michelin-starred restaurants in Andalusia and several museums in Florence and Paris," he explains. "What you need is a big enough group or a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>“What other secrets about our past are still hidden in Brazil’s jungles?” - The New York Times</title><link>http://www.nytimes.com/2016/12/14/world/americas/brazil-amazon-megaliths-stonehenge.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI94owr8osHmCbKKoYZi1F0qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzwwt4QY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2016 10:00:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.nytimes.com/2016/12/14/world/americas/brazil-amazon-megaliths-stonehenge.html" target="_blank"&gt;“What other secrets about our past are still hidden in Brazil’s jungles?”&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;CALÇOENE, Brazil — As the foreman for a cattle ranch in the far reaches of the Brazilian Amazon, Lailson Camelo da Silva was razing trees to convert rain forest into pasture when he stumbled across a bizarre arrangement of towering granite blocks. “I had no idea that I was discovering the Amazon’s own Stonehenge,” said Mr. da Silva, 65, on a scorching October day as he gazed at the archaeological site located just north of the Equator. “It makes me wonder: What other secrets about our past are still hidden in Brazil’s jungles?” After conducting radiocarbon testing and carrying out measureme...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>Stonehenge: Green light for controversial tunnel plan - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/2017/01/12/europe/stonehenge-tunnel-road/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGwFQuErN3Q5TthoS3QC8ewqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 12:40:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/2017/01/12/europe/stonehenge-tunnel-road/" target="_blank"&gt;Stonehenge: Green light for controversial tunnel plan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is one of the most famous landmarks in Britain, an important archeological site, and a sacred place for neo-pagans, but even an ancient monument like Stonehenge can't avoid the modern problem of traffic jams. Visitors to the stone circles in Wiltshire, southern England, frequently have to contend with lengthy queues of cars. Now the UK government has given the green light to £2 billion ($2.4 billion) plans to build a 1.8-mile tunnel under the site and widen the nearby highway. But despite backing from English Heritage, the scheme has enraged archeologists and academics who argue the tunn...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>‘Pembrokeshire is magically out of sync with modern times’ - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/travel/2017/may/26/pembrokehsire-out-of-sync-modern-times-unearthed-festival-tim-rees</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL1cP6gTGtXGU7j9Ke3E2KwqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCw3Gc</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2017 10:22:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/travel/2017/may/26/pembrokehsire-out-of-sync-modern-times-unearthed-festival-tim-rees" target="_blank"&gt;‘Pembrokeshire is magically out of sync with modern times’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Something about Pembrokeshire’s location gives it an otherworldly edge.It’s out on the peninsula, the end of the land surrounded by sea, and sometimes as the mist comes in, it feels as though we’re in some primordial soup – neither water nor land. I was born on a farm here in Cerbid, a fourth generation of farmers. Although I’ve lived around the world, my heart’s always been firmly in Pembrokeshire. I came back in 2010 and have been living here in a yurt ever since. Tim Rees There’s a fierce independence and wildness to the region.Strange traditions are still upheld, especially in the Gwaun...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Summer Solstice 2017: Thousands gather at Stonehenge to witness sun rising - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/home-news/summer-solstice-2017-first-day-of-summer-stonehenge-google-doodle-a7800711.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN9tFT3Kagcs2DCzCy4ZncQqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2017 12:28:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/home-news/summer-solstice-2017-first-day-of-summer-stonehenge-google-doodle-a7800711.html" target="_blank"&gt;Summer Solstice 2017: Thousands gather at Stonehenge to witness sun rising&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thousands of people descended on the prehistoric site of Stonehenge in the early hours of Wednesday morning to witness the dawn of the summer solstice and bring in the first day of summer. An estimated 13,000 sun-worshippers attended the Neolithic monument in Wiltshire in time for the 4:52am sunrise, an increase of around 1,000 people on last year’s solstice event. The ancient monument is believed to have been used as an important religious site by early Britons around 4,000 years ago, and it has become a popular place for pagan celebrations since the start of the 20th century. - Read more ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>The most fleeting natural tourist attractions to enjoy before they’re gone - Quartz</title><link>https://qz.com/1058546/the-most-fleeting-natural-tourist-attractions-to-enjoy-before-theyre-gone/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPWgcdjllkEzYOqXBZrqiH4qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowi4-MATDXsRUwhP2ZAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2017 09:00:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://qz.com/1058546/the-most-fleeting-natural-tourist-attractions-to-enjoy-before-theyre-gone/" target="_blank"&gt;The most fleeting natural tourist attractions to enjoy before they’re gone&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Quartz&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is no more effective tourism slogan than “for a limited time only.” It worked wonders for the first total solar eclipse visible coast-to-coast in the US in almost a century. The moon blocked out the sun today for under three minutes, making the Great American Eclipse one of the most short-lived tourist attractions around, but visitors overwhelmed small towns to catch a (hopefully, protected) glimpse of the solar eclipse. Hotels, home rentals, and camping grounds sold out along the Path of Totality. Expecting a package? Trucking companies changed their schedules ahead of what was expec...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://qz.com">Quartz</source></item><item><title>A Dual Carriageway Tunnel Under Stonehenge Would Be ‘An Act Of Vandalism’ - The Huffington Post UK</title><link>http://www.huffingtonpost.co.uk/entry/stonehenge-a303-road-to-be-moved-into-tunnel-under-ancient-monument_uk_58775f2de4b087dc83e83a1f</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGz4mLjvEKxLiY25SsHkFjoqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowmdW_BzCbhUcwuqRp</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 11:17:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.huffingtonpost.co.uk/entry/stonehenge-a303-road-to-be-moved-into-tunnel-under-ancient-monument_uk_58775f2de4b087dc83e83a1f" target="_blank"&gt;A Dual Carriageway Tunnel Under Stonehenge Would Be ‘An Act Of Vandalism’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Huffington Post UK&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Plans to move a major road which goes past Stonehenge into a tunnel underneath it will be an “act of vandalism”, say campaigners. The Department for Transport (DfT) has announced proposals for the A303, which include building a 1.8mile dual carriageway tunnel as it passes the World Heritage Site in Wiltshire. The road, currently a single carriageway, is a notorious bottleneck on the route to the South West. The tunnel would remove the sight and sound of traffic for people visiting Stonehenge and improve journeys, DfT officials claimed. Transport Secretary Chris Grayling said: “This major in...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.huffingtonpost.co.uk">The Huffington Post UK</source></item><item><title>15 things you didn't know about the world's greatest attractions - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/galleries/15-things-you-didnt-know-about-the-worlds-greatest-attractions/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKpv2oWIQ5SBFXdGBA2c9z8qFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCy8LkF</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2017 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/galleries/15-things-you-didnt-know-about-the-worlds-greatest-attractions/" target="_blank"&gt;15 things you didn't know about the world's greatest attractions&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;18 Jun 2017 15 things you didn't know about the world's greatest attractions Previous slideNext slide1 of 15View AllSkip Ad Think you know everything there is to know about the world's greatest attractions? Think again. Stonehenge, Wiltshire, UK In 1915, Stonehenge was sold at auction and bought by Cecil Chubb for £6,600. It has been suggested that he purchased it as a gift for his wife but she was didn't like it, so he gave it to the nation three years later. - The best hotels in WiltshireGETTY Back to image&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Why Thousands Of Pagans Gather At Stonehenge For The Winter Solstice - The Huffington Post</title><link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/why-thousands-of-pagans-gather-at-stonehenge-for-the-winter-solstice_us_584f38f2e4b04c8e2bb16ead</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMqzJC1S4fxhZf2oCe6NBzIqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 15:02:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/why-thousands-of-pagans-gather-at-stonehenge-for-the-winter-solstice_us_584f38f2e4b04c8e2bb16ead" target="_blank"&gt;Why Thousands Of Pagans Gather At Stonehenge For The Winter Solstice&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Huffington Post&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;While some are buying presents and trimming their tree for Christmas, a very different kind of spiritual celebration gets underway every year at Stonehenge. It’s the winter solstice, also known as Yule in some Pagan circles, and the occasion draws thousands of Pagans, Druids, spiritual seekers and tourists to the prehistoric site for a reverent and ecstatic ceremony. The December solstice marks the longest night and shortest day of the year in the Northern Hemisphere, and this year it falls on Wednesday, December 21 at 5:44 EST. In ancient Pagan traditions, the winter solstice was a time to...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.huffingtonpost.com">The Huffington Post</source></item><item><title>For one day, a fractured country will be united by sun, moon and history - The Washington Post</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/local/for-one-day-a-fractured-country-will-be-united-by-sun-moon-and-history/2017/08/15/fe9cbc5c-7ea2-11e7-83c7-5bd5460f0d7e_story.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJydcan5azOE__NZdYvGNKsqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjtSUCjC30XQwzqe5AQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2017 14:03:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/local/for-one-day-a-fractured-country-will-be-united-by-sun-moon-and-history/2017/08/15/fe9cbc5c-7ea2-11e7-83c7-5bd5460f0d7e_story.html" target="_blank"&gt;For one day, a fractured country will be united by sun, moon and history&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Washington Post&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A sign in Depoe Bay, Ore., lays out parking prices for visitors coming to experience the total solar eclipse on Monday. (Jane Ross/Reuters) The centerline of Monday’s total solar eclipse comes ashore about 10 a.m. Pacific Daylight Time on the rugged coast of Oregon near a place called Depoe Bay, where 40-ton gray whales spout and feed in the shallow water. At 2,000 mph the line, like one down the middle of a highway, streaks inland south of Salem. It goes over an extinct volcano in Idaho, a Stonehenge-like sculpture of junked cars in Nebraska, and crosses the Missouri River blocks from wher...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.washingtonpost.com">The Washington Post</source></item><item><title>UK Government Approves Plans To Build A Tunnel Under Stonehenge - The Huffington Post</title><link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/stonehenge-tunnel_us_587f2fbfe4b01cdc64c88140</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDRe7hjvkLsC6x4iaiviCd0qFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2017 13:24:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/stonehenge-tunnel_us_587f2fbfe4b01cdc64c88140" target="_blank"&gt;UK Government Approves Plans To Build A Tunnel Under Stonehenge&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Huffington Post&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stonehenge is one of the most famous sights in the world and like many popular tourist attractions, it has a traffic problem. The Neolithic monument attracts some 1.3 million visitors each year and whether tourists are traveling by planes, trains or automobiles, they must eventually take England’s A303 road to reach the UNESCO World Heritage Site. Stonehenge’s traffic jams are so notorious there’s even a website devoted to avoiding the painstakingly long line of cars. That’s why the British government approved a £2 billion (about $2.5 billion) plan to expand the road and build a tunnel that...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.huffingtonpost.com">The Huffington Post</source></item><item><title>Stonehenge tunnel given green light after nearly 30 years of delays - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/01/12/stonehenge-tunnel-given-green-light-nearly-30-years-delays/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELYNs7M_idFowPtVkqWi9gIqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 00:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/01/12/stonehenge-tunnel-given-green-light-nearly-30-years-delays/" target="_blank"&gt;Stonehenge tunnel given green light after nearly 30 years of delays&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A tunnel at Stonehenge has finally given the go-ahead after decades of delays despite fears that it could blight the historic landscape. The Government has confirmed that it intends to turn the whole length the A303, which passes within a few hundred metres of Stonehenge, into a dual carriageway with a 1.8 mile long tunnel. The plans will be put out to consultation after 30 years of delays amid bitter divides over the impact on the environment and the World Heritage site. While Unesco, the United Nations cultural body, has given its backing to the plans the Council for British Archaeology h...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Take the kids to … Stonehenge, Wiltshire - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/travel/2017/aug/28/take-the-kids-to-stonehenge-wiltshire-family-day-out</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELQGTGszFiwzxyqUYSq2yz4qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCw3Gc</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2017 08:00:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/travel/2017/aug/28/take-the-kids-to-stonehenge-wiltshire-family-day-out" target="_blank"&gt;Take the kids to … Stonehenge, Wiltshire&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a nutshell The world’s most famous prehistoric monument and one of the UK’s biggest tourist attractions, controversially roped off so visitors are not allowed within 10 metres of it – though it receives so many tourists (1,381,855 in 2016) that it would be virtually impossible to let them get closer. Fun fact It’s the greatest mystery in English history: why was it built here and how did they transport the 25-tonne sarsen stones from a quarry 25 miles away and, even more bafflingly, the two-tonne bluestones all the way from Wales … before the invention of the wheel? Best thing about it T...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>This 5,000-year-old stone carving may be the world's first drawing of an eclipse - The Washington Post</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/wonk/wp/2017/08/18/this-5000-year-old-stone-carving-may-be-the-worlds-first-drawing-of-an-eclipse/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENTW68Lf-RIjZ1-LOGLy8b0qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjtSUCjC30XQwjqi5AQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2017 16:14:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/wonk/wp/2017/08/18/this-5000-year-old-stone-carving-may-be-the-worlds-first-drawing-of-an-eclipse/" target="_blank"&gt;This 5,000-year-old stone carving may be the world's first drawing of an eclipse&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Washington Post&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This 5,000-year-old stone cairn in Ireland may contain the world's oldest visual representation of an eclipse. (Michael Fox/Boynevalleytours.com) An unassuming grass-covered stone mound outside Dublin may be home to the world's oldest visual representation of a solar eclipse. The Loughcrew Cairns in County Meath, Ireland, date to approximately 3,300 years B.C., predating the more well-known structures at Stonehenge, in southern England, by about 1,000 years. The 5,000-year-old Loughcrew structures appear to have served as burial sites for some of the region's inhabitants during the neolithi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.washingtonpost.com">The Washington Post</source></item><item><title>The total solar eclipse will occur over some of the nation's more unique landmarks - The Washington Post</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/capital-weather-gang/wp/2017/08/17/the-solar-eclipse-path-of-totality-includes-some-of-the-nations-more-unique-landmarks/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAszzX2Gzt7dezssotFcdgoqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjtSUCjC30XQwidHlAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2017 15:40:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/capital-weather-gang/wp/2017/08/17/the-solar-eclipse-path-of-totality-includes-some-of-the-nations-more-unique-landmarks/" target="_blank"&gt;The total solar eclipse will occur over some of the nation's more unique landmarks&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Washington Post&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(Carhenge.com) Only 4 percent of the population lives within the path of Monday’s total solar eclipse, but the slice of territory that will experience totality occupies a large plot of real estate. The moon’s shadow will carve a 70-mile-wide path encompassing some 173,000 square miles, or about 111 million acres. From coast to coast, it will travel 2,480 miles. The path spans purple mountains majesty to the amber waves of grain. And it will pass over some other curious sites as well… Carhenge If you can’t make it all the way over to England to see Stonehenge, you’re in luck — Alliance, Neb....&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.washingtonpost.com">The Washington Post</source></item><item><title>Stonehenge - Lintel 122 - 500px</title><link>https://500px.com/photo/195376909/stonehenge-lintel-122-by-brett-gasser</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDDiLCjbvp8BLP3Cssa_jWsqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow26UBMPBEMMD7CQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 17:02:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://500px.com/photo/195376909/stonehenge-lintel-122-by-brett-gasser" target="_blank"&gt;Stonehenge - Lintel 122&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;500px&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stonehenge winter sunrise. Centre frame, Sarsen Stones 21 and 22 supporting Lintel 122. The lintel stone fell and broke on New Years Eve 1900. This lead to public pressure to restore the site. You can see the crack where the repair was made.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://500px.com">500px</source></item><item><title>Stonehenge on a foggy day. - 500px</title><link>https://500px.com/photo/190587005/stonehenge-on-a-foggy-day-by-jeremy-tucker</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFm7qvienPRxsbLYLE-l0oYqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow26UBMPBEMMD7CQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2016 21:17:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://500px.com/photo/190587005/stonehenge-on-a-foggy-day-by-jeremy-tucker" target="_blank"&gt;Stonehenge on a foggy day.&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;500px&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have waiting for years for the perfect light to photograph Stonehenge and today I got it!&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://500px.com">500px</source></item><item><title>Stonehenge - Sunrise - 500px</title><link>https://500px.com/photo/217088337/stonehenge-sunrise-by-brett-gasser</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIn9wIGuV1BH_h5U76qsRxsqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow26UBMPBEMMD7CQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2017 16:04:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://500px.com/photo/217088337/stonehenge-sunrise-by-brett-gasser" target="_blank"&gt;Stonehenge - Sunrise&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;500px&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stonehenge at sunrise. We were part of a small group, but obviously I wanted photos with no one around the stones. I would have to be quick! Exiting the bus, I extended my tripod legs, fixed my camera and was ready to go. I ended up with just two people in frame, who scared off the sleeping birds. I removed the people in post and left the birds :)&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://500px.com">500px</source></item><item><title>The Stonehenge tunnel: ‘A monstrous act of desecration is brewing’ - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2017/apr/25/stonehenge-tunnel-desecration-prehistoric-traffic-jams</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEC0DeKtL0GCBh-rsJY6jeEqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2017 14:30:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2017/apr/25/stonehenge-tunnel-desecration-prehistoric-traffic-jams" target="_blank"&gt;The Stonehenge tunnel: ‘A monstrous act of desecration is brewing’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Solstice Park is “a strategically located development opportunity”. That’s what its promotional blurb says, anyway – but put more prosaically, it is a clump of offices, distribution centres and retail and hospitality businesses on the A303, just under 10 miles from Salisbury. It symbolises two things: government attempts to help the economy of south-west England, and the tourist industry centred on Stonehenge, a few minutes’ drive away. As if to somehow complement the monument’s antiquarian wonders, there is a faux-ancient statue outside the Holiday Inn, of a 22ft figure giving thanks to th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Tony Robinson attacks Government's approval of tunnel road near Stonehenge - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/home-news/tony-robinson-stonehenge-tunnel-approval-government-attack-criticism-a7941681.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEByAP14RHaDMye8U0szIOZ0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2017 22:57:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/home-news/tony-robinson-stonehenge-tunnel-approval-government-attack-criticism-a7941681.html" target="_blank"&gt;Tony Robinson attacks Government's approval of tunnel road near Stonehenge&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Time Team presenter and actor Tony Robinson has attacked the Government's decision to give the go-ahead for a 1.8-mile road tunnel near Stonehenge. He described the project as “the most brutal intrusion into the Stone Age landscape ever” and accused the Department for Transport (DfT) of paying “no attention at all” to the importance of the Wiltshire monument. But government heritage agency Historic England, and the National Trust and English Heritage, who manage the stone circle and its surrounding landscape, welcomed the announcement. - Read more Tunnel to be built under Stonehenge despite...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>The Week We Went Wild review – lazy, corrupt and shameful - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/tv-and-radio/2017/jan/10/the-week-we-went-wild-review-lazy-corrupt-and-shameful</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDSwH_9mAC9uyKyL-QCpQvYqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCOvRU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2017 07:20:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/tv-and-radio/2017/jan/10/the-week-we-went-wild-review-lazy-corrupt-and-shameful" target="_blank"&gt;The Week We Went Wild review – lazy, corrupt and shameful&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, the worst programme of the year is here. Good to get it out of the way early, I suppose. It’s The Week We Went Wild (Channel 5) and it’s like having a bucket of crap – I was going to say dashed at your television screen, but it’s more like having someone carefully spread it on with a spatula, side to side, corner to corner, so that not a single pixel is missed. The premise is as simple as it is stupid – send a troubled family on a five-day trek through the Panamanian jungle so that they can bond and mend themselves. The inaugural family are the Reeds. Dawn has eight children by six fath...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Avebury stone circle contains hidden square, archaeologists find - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/science/2017/jun/29/avebury-stone-circle-contains-hidden-square-archaeologists-find</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI4azRDFfyCvc00hUWhm9w0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCOvRU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2017 11:33:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/science/2017/jun/29/avebury-stone-circle-contains-hidden-square-archaeologists-find" target="_blank"&gt;Avebury stone circle contains hidden square, archaeologists find&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A mysterious square formation has been discovered within the Neolithic stone circle monument at Avebury, rewriting the narrative of one of the wonders of the prehistoric world. Archaeologists believe the hidden stones, discovered using radar technology, were one of the earliest structures at the site and may have commemorated a Neolithic building dating to around 3500 BC. Previously archaeologists had speculated that the vast stone outer circle, which at 330 metres in diameter is the largest in Europe, had been built from the outside inwards. The latest work suggests that a lowly wooden bui...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>A new road will make getting to Stonehenge easier. It may also ruin Stonehenge. - The Washington Post</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/worldviews/wp/2017/01/13/a-new-road-will-make-getting-to-stonehenge-easier-it-may-also-ruin-stonehenge/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK4aRfVfvErxh-GHMn0ycEEqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjtSUCjC30XQwzqe5AQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 15:32:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/worldviews/wp/2017/01/13/a-new-road-will-make-getting-to-stonehenge-easier-it-may-also-ruin-stonehenge/" target="_blank"&gt;A new road will make getting to Stonehenge easier. It may also ruin Stonehenge.&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Washington Post&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Visitors take photos among the prehistoric stones of Stonehenge at dawn on the winter solstice in southwest Britain. (Toby Melville/Reuters) Historians estimate that Stonehenge is at least 4,000 years old. It can take about as long to reach the site by car. The route to the ancient stone circles in Wiltshire, England, is frequently jammed with traffic. (Which makes sense. The World Heritage Site, among Britain's top tourist attractions, pulls in more than 1.3 million visitors annually.) Filming traffic jams beside the #A303 at #Stonehenge - lovely, my favourite..... pic.twitter.com/nhR23xk4...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.washingtonpost.com">The Washington Post</source></item><item><title>National Trust faces member rebellion over backing of Stonehenge tunnel - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/09/04/national-trust-faces-member-rebellion-backing-stonehenge-tunnel/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBLoAg0QEuTbxYPtsuAqYJcqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2017 18:53:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/09/04/national-trust-faces-member-rebellion-backing-stonehenge-tunnel/" target="_blank"&gt;National Trust faces member rebellion over backing of Stonehenge tunnel&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The National Trust is “compromising its reputation” with its support for a controversial tunnel cutting through the sacred Stonehenge site on a “brutal scale”, members have warned. The embattled charity is accused of giving its blessing to a plan that will “inject enormous amounts of concrete into the most significant prehistoric landscape if not in Britain, in the whole of Europe”. It is facing a rebellion from members, who are demanding that it rethink its position on the proposal to upgrade the clogged A303 and have accused it of prioritising Government criteria such as value-for-money a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>8 'tourist traps' that are truly worth a visit - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/travel/article/tourist-traps-worth-visiting/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPRyHP7jWeui9d8tgkbWw04qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 22:01:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/travel/article/tourist-traps-worth-visiting/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;8 'tourist traps' that are truly worth a visit&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A top attraction that lives up to its hype. You can avoid the crowds by going at sunrise or sunset. An alternative? Embrace the scrum, interact with the touts and talk to other tourists. The climb up is hot and crowded -- but at the top, you'll see why a million people do this every year. This is Athenian culture refined and placed on a pedestal 150 meters high. The most literal "tourist trap" on this list, London's tube system often turns commuters into prisoners, if only for a few minutes. But the complexity of the underground means shortcuts and alternate routes are available, if you do ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Vast 5,600-year-old religious centre discovered near Stonehenge - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/science/archaeology/stonehenge-prehistoric-religious-ceremonial-centre-discovered-archaeologists-a7425346.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELxpZkVHswFje2XM4wcS7T8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2016 19:59:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/science/archaeology/stonehenge-prehistoric-religious-ceremonial-centre-discovered-archaeologists-a7425346.html" target="_blank"&gt;Vast 5,600-year-old religious centre discovered near Stonehenge&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A huge, prehistoric religious and ceremonial complex has been discovered near Britain’s most famous prehistoric temple Stonehenge. Its discovery is likely to transform our understanding of the early development of Stonehenge’s ancient landscape. Built about 5,650 years ago – more than 1,000 years before the great stones of Stonehenge were erected – the 200m-diameter complex is the first major early Neolithic monument to be discovered in the Stonehenge area for more than a century. Read more - Remarkable ancient structure found just two miles from Stonehenge - Glaciers moved Stonehenge from ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Opportunity or threat? Stonehenge tunnel plan revives long-running debate - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2017/jan/13/opportunity-or-threat-stonehenge-tunnel-plan-revives-long-running-debate</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHzNu0fpYPsOx5-SvWnB2ikqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCOvRU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 16:52:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2017/jan/13/opportunity-or-threat-stonehenge-tunnel-plan-revives-long-running-debate" target="_blank"&gt;Opportunity or threat? Stonehenge tunnel plan revives long-running debate&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Peter Tunison, a retired architect from Minnesota, was in no doubt. “If this was a monument in the US, we wouldn’t have vehicles passing so close by. This is the place to visit in the UK. It’s windy today and you can still hear the traffic noise. A tunnel seems a very sensible option. I’d go for it.” A bitter wind was indeed blowing hard on Friday and yet visitors to Stonehenge could still clearly hear the rumble of cars, vans and lorries passing along the A303 a mere 165 metres from the one of the most important prehistoric monuments in the world. If the government’s plans come to fruition...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Forget sitting in traffic – the best way to see Stonehenge is on foot - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/destinations/europe/united-kingdom/england/wiltshire/articles/stonehenge-avebury-pilgrimage-without-the-crowds/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBjUmtX065QHKXETzMk8XPEqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCy8LkF</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 09:32:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/destinations/europe/united-kingdom/england/wiltshire/articles/stonehenge-avebury-pilgrimage-without-the-crowds/" target="_blank"&gt;Forget sitting in traffic – the best way to see Stonehenge is on foot&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sitting atop a 180-year-old stallion, just off Britain’s ancient Ridgeway, I watched a man meditating inside an extraterrestrial doodle. From my vantage, by the rump of a huge chalk figure – Hackpen Hill’s White Horse – I saw the man stroll amid a crop circle of alien (or prankster?) flattened wheat before pausing in the centre to commune, I presumed, with Martians or Mother Nature. This is the sort of thing that happens when you go walking in Wiltshire, a county whose maps are scrawled with more gothic font than you can wave a dowsing rod at. This month marks the 30th anniversary of the de...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Ancient Italian Stonehenge accidentally discovered by friends - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/europe/ancient-italian-stonehenge-accidentally-discovered-by-friends-a7515651.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJnE9HQogiUUCvyyRXjzOUUqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2017 10:58:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/europe/ancient-italian-stonehenge-accidentally-discovered-by-friends-a7515651.html" target="_blank"&gt;Ancient Italian Stonehenge accidentally discovered by friends&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A group of friends have accidentally discovered an ancient historical site dating thousands of years old thought to be the Italian equivalent of Stonehenge, it has been reported. The archaeological discovery has been confirmed by experts and hailed as a major find for understanding of prehistoric times. The friends, who are amateur archaeologists, were carrying out surveys of World War II bunkers when they stumbled across an usual arrangement of stones in Sicily, The Local reports. Professional verification by experts has since confirmed it is a sundial dating back to between 6000 and 3000 ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Stonehenge: Historians Furious Over Government Go-Ahead For Road Tunnel Under World Heritage Site - HuffPost UK</title><link>http://www.huffingtonpost.co.uk/entry/stonehenge-road-tunnel_uk_59b793f8e4b09be41657a310</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN3kbuOWrM5sQA64lY8ngSQqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowmdW_BzCbhUcwuqRp</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2017 10:00:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.huffingtonpost.co.uk/entry/stonehenge-road-tunnel_uk_59b793f8e4b09be41657a310" target="_blank"&gt;Stonehenge: Historians Furious Over Government Go-Ahead For Road Tunnel Under World Heritage Site&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost UK&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ministers have sparked outrage among historians and archaeologists by giving controversial plans to build a road tunnel near Stonehenge the go-ahead. After 30 years of heated debate over the issue, it was announced yesterday that a 1.8 mile tunnel will be built near the historic site as part of a £1.6 billion upgrade to the oft-congested A303. The government said that the move - which has received support from Historic England, the National Trust and English Heritage - will provide a “huge boost” for the area and enhance the famous landmark by removing the “sight and sound of traffic”. “Qui...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.huffingtonpost.co.uk">HuffPost UK</source></item><item><title>Stonehenge: Australia's Forgotten Farmers - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/stonehenge-australia-forgotten-farmers/4000154.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELozJlo6qskPNCWOsZZ6EnwqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwtOetBQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2017 01:08:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/stonehenge-australia-forgotten-farmers/4000154.html" target="_blank"&gt;Stonehenge: Australia's Forgotten Farmers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stonehenge is dry and has been for too long — seven years too long. You can taste the dust well before you cross the cattle grids that cut the only road into town. More than 1,700 kilometers (1,056 miles) northwest of Sydney, Australia's Stonehenge could not be more different from its famous namesake, the World Heritage prehistoric monument of Stonehenge in England. A stockman rides his horse as he leads another down a road toward the cattle yards in the outback town of Windorah, Queensland, located south of Stonehenge, in Australia, Aug. 11, 2017. Stonehenge in England averages 10 days a m...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Researchers give voice to historic sounds of Stonehenge - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-britain-tech-stonehenge-idUSKBN17D1RO</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMOORZRqO7l9iuIWgKbh2AkqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 16:43:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-britain-tech-stonehenge-idUSKBN17D1RO" target="_blank"&gt;Researchers give voice to historic sounds of Stonehenge&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Matthew J. Stock STONEHENGE (Reuters) - If you listen carefully - and with the right app - you can still hear the prehistoric acoustics that swirled around Britain's ancient monument Stonehenge over the last 5,000 years. A team of researchers spent eight years creating an app that allows you to hear the different noises the stones generated at various points over thousands of years, long before the traffic noise in the southwest English county of Wiltshire took over. While most modern archaeologists generally agree Stonehenge was some sort of prehistoric temple aligned to the movements o...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Now the Stonehenge tunnel has the green light, where are Britain's worst traffic bottlenecks? - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/09/13/now-stonehenge-tunnel-has-green-light-britains-worst-traffic/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO8TQ-09P59fWQwmCZpQVmoqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 07:48:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/09/13/now-stonehenge-tunnel-has-green-light-britains-worst-traffic/" target="_blank"&gt;Now the Stonehenge tunnel has the green light, where are Britain's worst traffic bottlenecks?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;After 30 years of controversy, there will finally be a tunnel at Stonehenge. Relief and anger in equal intensity will meet news that planned upgrades to the A303 – a major trunk road linking the M3 to the M5 and tying together much of South West England – have finally been given the go-ahead. The stretch running past Stonehenge to the A36 is one of the UK’s worst traffic bottlenecks, and the upgrades will, hopefully, reduce congestion for millions. Unfortunately for British motorists, this is just a single one of the tens of thousands of bottlenecks across the UK that eat up our time, pump ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>The Best Spot To View The Coming Solar Eclipse Is A Car Lover's Nirvana - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jimgorzelany/2017/08/10/the-best-spot-to-view-the-coming-solar-eclipse-is-a-car-lovers-nirvana/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDZzYP2QveQOLhjd_Zg4bEUqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2017 16:41:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/jimgorzelany/2017/08/10/the-best-spot-to-view-the-coming-solar-eclipse-is-a-car-lovers-nirvana/" target="_blank"&gt;The Best Spot To View The Coming Solar Eclipse Is A Car Lover's Nirvana&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rising from the Sandhills of Nebraska, the monolithic Carhenge affords a truly unique backdrop to a once-in-a-lifetime astronomical experience. (Shutterstock) If you love cars and are eager to view the coming full eclipse of the sun in all of its glory, plan to be on site at the famed Carhenge in Alliance, Nebraska at 11:49 am on August 21. Already one of the quirkiest roadside attractions in the U.S., it’s an assemblage of 39 vintage autos set in a circle and having the same proportions as England’s historic Stonehedge. Only instead of being built out of enormous rocks by ancient druids (o...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Druid To Take Charity To Court Over Stonehenge Parking Charges - Heat Street</title><link>http://heatst.com/life/druid-to-take-charity-to-court-over-stonehenge-parking-charges/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEjldoF4swXCOavfESd4QhYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowgd31CjC749wCMLq51QM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 11:26:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://heatst.com/life/druid-to-take-charity-to-court-over-stonehenge-parking-charges/" target="_blank"&gt;Druid To Take Charity To Court Over Stonehenge Parking Charges&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Heat Street&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Heat Street Staff | 6:26 am, January 12, 2017 A senior druid is taking one of the biggest charities in Britain to court after it introduced parking charges at Stonehenge for the Summer Solstice, forcing worshippers to “pay to pray”. King Arthur Pendragon – the 62-year-old self-proclaimed reincarnation of the mythical King Arthur – is taking legal action against English Heritage, arguing it is a breach of people's human rights to be charged a £15 ($18) fee before they can worship at the prehistoric monument. Mr Pendragon, whose real name is John Rothwell, appeared at Salisbury County Cour...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://heatst.com">Heat Street</source></item><item><title>Family Lodging for Part-Time Nature Seekers - The New York Times</title><link>http://www.nytimes.com/2017/03/22/travel/family-lodging-for-part-time-nature-seekers.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOu7zBe1OnidQ8FGqDo5wagqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzww54UY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2017 03:28:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.nytimes.com/2017/03/22/travel/family-lodging-for-part-time-nature-seekers.html" target="_blank"&gt;Family Lodging for Part-Time Nature Seekers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;New and improved family-friendly hotels and resorts in the United States and abroad offer access to adventures in wild places and milder alternatives, too.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>A 50-minute queue for the loo? Stonehenge should spend less money on tunnels and more on toilets - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/destinations/europe/united-kingdom/england/wiltshire/articles/stonehenge-queues-toilet-roll-problems-tunnel-investment/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFUYlls7OtDRCeWp6OotV0kqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCy8LkF</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 09:14:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/destinations/europe/united-kingdom/england/wiltshire/articles/stonehenge-queues-toilet-roll-problems-tunnel-investment/" target="_blank"&gt;A 50-minute queue for the loo? Stonehenge should spend less money on tunnels and more on toilets&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The go-ahead at Stonehenge for a controversial £1.6 million road tunnel should be met with scepticism not only because of the archaeological considerations that threaten its World Heritage Status, but also because the heritage attraction can’t seem to get the basic tourist experience right. Stonehenge was visited by 1.38m people last year, so you'd think they'd be used to crowds. Based on my experience this summer, don't even think about going unless you're prepared to queue for a long time. Chris Grayling, the Transport Secretary, would be wise to divert his attention and money to the visi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Stonehenge tunnel: heritage groups warn over ancient barrow - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2017/feb/08/stonehenge-tunnel-heritage-groups-warn-over-ancient-barrow</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKlQivCD1OK7vZzCOIqDY3QqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2017 06:00:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2017/feb/08/stonehenge-tunnel-heritage-groups-warn-over-ancient-barrow" target="_blank"&gt;Stonehenge tunnel: heritage groups warn over ancient barrow&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Stonehenge tunnel scheme has suffered a setback after three influential heritage organisations closely involved in the ancient site and the surrounding landscape raised concerns over a crucial aspect of the government’s preferred route. Historic England, English Heritage and the National Trust all said they backed the idea of a tunnel for the busy A303, which would remove the sight and sound of thousands of vehicles thundering close to the stone circle. However all three are worried that the proposed western portal – the tunnel entrance and exit – is too close to the Normanton Down Barr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>JMW Turner’s Stonehenge: ancient stones and bloodthirsty skies - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/artanddesign/2017/apr/07/jmw-turners-stonehenge-ancient-stones-and-bloodthirsty-skies</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHeVVcVD64KdqW1ZMElInhYqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCOvRU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2017 11:00:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/artanddesign/2017/apr/07/jmw-turners-stonehenge-ancient-stones-and-bloodthirsty-skies" target="_blank"&gt;JMW Turner’s Stonehenge: ancient stones and bloodthirsty skies&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A view to a kill In his famed image of Stonehenge, Turner’s celebrated skies have turned as bloodthirsty as the pagans supposedly were. Dominating clouds billow fiery amber against a wet, dark blue above the ancient stones, as a bolt of lightning is thrown from the heavens. The little shepherd on the ground is not dreaming of old Albion; he has been struck dead. Totally awesome This is an image that’s hardwired to Romanticism; it recalls William Wordsworth’s description of “night fire mounting to the clouds” and “a sacrificial altar” from his Salisbury Plain series: man is cowed by awesome ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Wiltshire’s A303: the route to a buyer’s art - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/038f594c-8333-11e7-94e2-c5b903247afd</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKq-KL9EF18B1lVUPpl4L98qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtt6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2017 04:00:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/038f594c-8333-11e7-94e2-c5b903247afd" target="_blank"&gt;Wiltshire’s A303: the route to a buyer’s art&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is a road that challenges Robert Louis Stevenson’s adage that to “travel hopefully is a better thing than to arrive”. The 92-mile-long A303, which follows an ancient route to the West Country, famously bottlenecks around Stonehenge, where it drops down to a single carriageway causing lengthy tailbacks — the only upside of which is the majestic view of the Neolithic stone circle. In recent years, however, the route has been garnering an altogether different reputation: with high-profile contemporary galleries springing up along its way, many are beginning to recognise it as something akin...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>A radioactive ghost town lures travelers - The Washington Post</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/lifestyle/travel/in-ukraine-a-radioactive-nuclear-ghost-town-near-chernobyl-is-a-hot-destination/2017/07/27/1f035b3e-5aa6-11e7-9b7d-14576dc0f39d_story.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC-ri8nzhCZLOv3vp5Ov6_0qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjtSUCjC30XQwzqe5AQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2017 19:20:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/lifestyle/travel/in-ukraine-a-radioactive-nuclear-ghost-town-near-chernobyl-is-a-hot-destination/2017/07/27/1f035b3e-5aa6-11e7-9b7d-14576dc0f39d_story.html" target="_blank"&gt;A radioactive ghost town lures travelers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Washington Post&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In Ukraine, an overhead look at the nuclear ghost town of Pripyat, which once was earmarked solely for Chernobyl workers. (Olivier Wullen /Alamy Stock Photo) The button that could have started a nuclear holocaust is gray — not red. I learned this after climbing into a nuclear rocket command silo, 12 floors below ground, and sitting in the same green chair at the same yellow, metal console at which former Soviet officers once presided. Here, they practiced entering secret codes into their gray keyboards, pushing the launch button and turning a key — all within seven seconds — to fire up to 1...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.washingtonpost.com">The Washington Post</source></item><item><title>Earth Day: A Look at the World's Most Beautiful Places - Newsweek</title><link>http://www.newsweek.com/earth-day-most-beautiful-photos-nuclear-world-war-three-north-korea-save-588118</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDrVE_2zDiiytoP10ylBQjsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow77zbCjDiq8wBMJiCsgU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2017 11:07:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.newsweek.com/earth-day-most-beautiful-photos-nuclear-world-war-three-north-korea-save-588118" target="_blank"&gt;Earth Day: A Look at the World's Most Beautiful Places&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Newsweek&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Earth Day: the nationwide tradition of basking in all that is beautiful in the world and celebrating the planet’s many bountiful resources. Some people plant trees. Others donate to wildlife conservation causes. But in 2017, progressive environmentalists and concerned citizens alike are embracing what could very well be the last celebration of its kind before the entire planet is destroyed forever. At least, that’s what countless people are fearing during a period of great uncertainty surrounding a bevy of existential crises. From the threat of nuclear missile attacks and the dissolve of th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.newsweek.com">Newsweek</source></item><item><title>The Great Wall of China tops British bucket lists (unless you vote Lib Dem) - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/news/great-wall-tops-british-bucket-lists/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMKLHvoW7BdjUfiUyDK0UAwqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCy8LkF</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2017 14:45:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/news/great-wall-tops-british-bucket-lists/" target="_blank"&gt;The Great Wall of China tops British bucket lists (unless you vote Lib Dem)&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Great Wall of China is the man-made wonder that most Britons would like to tick off their “bucket list”, new research has shown. A YouGov poll presented more than 5,000 people with 10 attractions, including the Great Pyramid of Giza and the Colosseum, before asking them to pick the three they most wanted to see. The vast Chinese construction topped the list, with 38 per cent of people choosing it. Machu Picchu took second spot, with 32 per cent, while the Taj Mahal came third, with 29 per cent. Which three world wonders would you most like to see? Bottom of the pile was Stonehenge, with...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>The Stonehenge tunnel will bring us closer to a mythic past - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/artanddesign/jonathanjonesblog/2017/jan/12/stonehenge-tunnel-bring-closer-mythic-past-hardy-constable</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFwrxpWWCI51EIKKSThNfW4qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 13:13:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/artanddesign/jonathanjonesblog/2017/jan/12/stonehenge-tunnel-bring-closer-mythic-past-hardy-constable" target="_blank"&gt;The Stonehenge tunnel will bring us closer to a mythic past&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Visiting Stonehenge becomes ever harder. You have to book ahead as if it were a swanky West End show, endure a visitor centre when what you really want to do is commune with the mysterious past – and when you do finally get your chance to walk around (not among) the stones, you need to assiduously ignore the hum of traffic from the heavily congested nearby A303. Related: Chris Grayling gives go-ahead to road tunnel under Stonehenge That, at least, is going to change. The government has decided to go ahead with a tunnel that will take this very busy road underground for 1.8 miles, removing t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Actually, Trump's Been Leaving Notes At Historic Sites All Over The World - HuffPost</title><link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/actually-trumps-been-leaving-notes-at-historic-sites-all-over-the-world_us_592460ece4b034684b104c5c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPgrMd81PrC4JQI_Kmag_7oqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2017 21:32:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/actually-trumps-been-leaving-notes-at-historic-sites-all-over-the-world_us_592460ece4b034684b104c5c" target="_blank"&gt;Actually, Trump's Been Leaving Notes At Historic Sites All Over The World&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;On Monday, President Trump visited the Western Wall in Jerusalem and, as is customary, placed a note of prayer inside. The internet did its internet thing and meme’d the event. But that isn’t the first time Donald Trump has left a note at significant landmarks around the world. Actually, it’s something he does quite often. Here are a few others! Great Pyramids of Giza - EgyptTerracotta Army - ChinaChrist The Redeemer - BrazilTaj Mahal - IndiaStonehenge - EnglandEaster Island - ChiléPompeii - ItalyMachu Picchu - Peru&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Summer Solstice 2016: Thousands travel to Stonehenge for the longest day of the year - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/home-news/summer-solstice-2016-strawberry-moon-stonehenge-thousands-travel-longest-day-year-a7092936.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELz9m3VMPNi89g5Fg6Ptl8kqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2016 15:31:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/home-news/summer-solstice-2016-strawberry-moon-stonehenge-thousands-travel-longest-day-year-a7092936.html" target="_blank"&gt;Summer Solstice 2016: Thousands travel to Stonehenge for the longest day of the year&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thousands of people have gathered at Stonehenge to celebrate the Summer Solstice. Approximately 12,000 people are attending the celebration at the historic Wiltshire monument throughout the day and night. The Summer Solstice is the longest day of the year, with daylight lasting around 17 hours in the UK - and this year it coincides with a Strawberry Moon. In pictures: Revellers celebrate the summer solstice at Stone Henge - 20 show all In pictures: Revellers celebrate the summer solstice at Stone Henge - 1/20 Rex Features - 2/20 REUTERS - 3/20 Rex Features - 4/20 Rex Features - 5/20 Rex Fea...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Ancient British stone circles were used for ‘Neolithic parties’, study finds - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/home-news/orkney-stone-circles-neolithic-parties-study-a7957846.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN_j0wKsI2t_AG6b0yPMWcEqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2017 16:16:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/home-news/orkney-stone-circles-neolithic-parties-study-a7957846.html" target="_blank"&gt;Ancient British stone circles were used for ‘Neolithic parties’, study finds&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Orkney is home to a host of Neolithic stone houses, stone circles and elaborate burial monuments, but a new study into the area has allowed experts to add a new purpose to the prehistoric communities’ use of some of these sites – partying. New research led by Professor Alex Bayliss at Historic England has challenged the previously understood narrative for prehistoric life on the islands and painted a clearer picture of how communities farmed, gathered together at festivals and buried their dead. The islands are home to renowned sites such as the Skara Brae settlement, Maeshowe passage grave...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>What is your favourite view in Britain? - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/travel/2017/apr/11/what-is-your-favourite-view-in-britain</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFllkZixGqRe-XxeNxBs6JMqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCw3Gc</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 09:44:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/travel/2017/apr/11/what-is-your-favourite-view-in-britain" target="_blank"&gt;What is your favourite view in Britain?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The view from the top of mount Snowdon on a clear day has been voted the best in Britain, according to a new poll. Coming in second was the Three Sisters mountains, in Scotland’s Glen Coe. Third was a view of Stonehenge, the famous and ancient ring of standing stones in the English county of Wiltshire. With the weather improving and even Theresa May embarking on a Snowdonia holiday, we would like to hear your own suggestions for the best views in Britain, so that we can put together our own, alternative list. You can share your suggestions by filling out the form below - please tell us in a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Chief druid wins right to take English Heritage to court over Stonehenge parking charges - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/01/10/chief-druid-wins-right-take-english-heritage-court-stonehenge/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEq9LPY5RJJacCJzHrADxXgqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2017 18:04:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/01/10/chief-druid-wins-right-take-english-heritage-court-stonehenge/" target="_blank"&gt;Chief druid wins right to take English Heritage to court over Stonehenge parking charges&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A senior druid has won the right to take a charity to court over "pay-to-pray" parking charges for the Summer Solstice at Stonehenge, claiming it should be free. King Arthur Pendragon argues that a £15 parking fee at the prehistoric monument near Amesbury, Wilts, breached his human rights. The 62-year-old has appeared at Salisbury Crown Court, Wilts, to present his case for the right to worship at the neolithic relic without unnecessary restriction or hindrance from English Heritage. People gather at the stonesCredit: Paul Grover Other druids and pagans gathered outside the court waving ban...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Was Stonehenge Used to Predict Astronomical Events? - Newsweek</title><link>http://www.newsweek.com/fall-equinox-stonehenge-lunar-eclipse-668730</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO641JMiypfXB9EeXdK791AqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow77zbCjDiq8wBMMiCsgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2017 08:03:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.newsweek.com/fall-equinox-stonehenge-lunar-eclipse-668730" target="_blank"&gt;Was Stonehenge Used to Predict Astronomical Events?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Newsweek&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This Friday night and Saturday morning, druids, pagans, hippies, and assorted hangers-on will gather at Britain’s world-famous neolithic “Stonehenge” site to mark the fall equinox, the point when summer ends and the days begin to shorten. But what will they be celebrating and what even is Stonehenge for, anyway? Here’s what you need to know. The fall equinox “This is the third of the four ‘sky points’ in our Wheel of the Year and it is when the sun does a perfect balancing act in the heavens,” says a piece on the Stonehenge blog. “After this celebration the descent into winter brings hours ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.newsweek.com">Newsweek</source></item><item><title>Romancing the Stones - The New Yorker</title><link>https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2014/04/21/romancing-the-stones</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBf5gfHrCEMpc4MhFUD-_RcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowjMqjCjCJhZwBMJHUywM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2014 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2014/04/21/romancing-the-stones" target="_blank"&gt;Romancing the Stones&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New Yorker&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;When we got off the bus, at around 6 A.M., it was pitch dark, and the fields of Salisbury Plain were sodden after a night of desultory rain. Most of the passengers—who included a retired physicist and his wife, and a pair of young lovers peering at their smartphones while audibly pining for hot chocolate—were dismayed to learn that the bus would go no farther. To our right, the new Stonehenge Visitor Center, an elegantly wispy structure with more than two hundred slender, tilted pillars and an undulating steel roof, was a blur in the murk. The standing stones were a mile and a half to the s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.newyorker.com">The New Yorker</source></item><item><title>Decoding the ancient astronomy of Stonehenge - Vox.com</title><link>https://www.vox.com/videos/2017/6/21/15843570/astronomy-stonehenge-solstice</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFtT3HQt5e_nGSYQp9lXXKkqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowlOzSATCaiDUwo9dy</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2017 14:20:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.vox.com/videos/2017/6/21/15843570/astronomy-stonehenge-solstice" target="_blank"&gt;Decoding the ancient astronomy of Stonehenge&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Vox.com&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;How the 5,000-year-old monument aligns with the sun. The Stonehenge monument in England is known for its alignment with the summer solstice sunrise, and a is popular destination for revelers welcoming the longest day of the year. The inner “horseshoe” of the monument opens toward the point on the horizon where the sun appears on the day in June when the sun’s path is furthest North. Joseph Lertola/Wikimedia Commons A rendering of the Stonehenge monument as it might have appeared 4,000 years ago. But on the same axis, in the opposite direction, is the point on the horizon where the sun sets ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.vox.com">Vox.com</source></item><item><title>Drone films breathtaking views of Whitby Abbey and Stonehenge - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2016/11/28/drone-films-breathtaking-views-whitby-abbey-stonehenge/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE6YQrX_FM_hIm1Tn97cJtoqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2016 17:55:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2016/11/28/drone-films-breathtaking-views-whitby-abbey-stonehenge/" target="_blank"&gt;Drone films breathtaking views of Whitby Abbey and Stonehenge&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;English Heritage released drone footage showing the breahtaking views from the skies around Whitby Abbey and Stonehenge. Video block text&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Revealed: The 20 most popular attractions in Britain - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/news/most-popular-attractions-in-britain-in-2016/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH9Va4YtloQNPH_WceYWLMgqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCy8LkF</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2017 08:21:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/news/most-popular-attractions-in-britain-in-2016/" target="_blank"&gt;Revealed: The 20 most popular attractions in Britain&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The British Museum has been confirmed as the most popular UK attraction for the 10th year running, with 6,420,395 people passing through its doors in 2016. Figures released today by the Association of Leading Visitor Attractions (ALVA) revealed that all of the 10 most popular spots are in London, with the National Gallery, the Tate Modern, the Natural History Museum and the Southbank Centre completing the top five. UK bucket list The most popular tourist attraction outside of London last year might come as a surprise, with Chester Zoo pipping the likes of Edinburgh Castle, Stonehenge and th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Stonehenge Landscape - 500px</title><link>https://500px.com/photo/204447471/stonehenge-landscape-by-brett-gasser</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHMfGowWGu7ZsxpmEXZjXokqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow26UBMPBEMMD7CQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2017 16:48:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://500px.com/photo/204447471/stonehenge-landscape-by-brett-gasser" target="_blank"&gt;Stonehenge Landscape&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;500px&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;I took this sunrise panorama at the Stonehenge visitors' centre, while waiting to be taken down to the stones.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://500px.com">500px</source></item><item><title>Stonehenge tunnel route moved by 50 metres after protests - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2017/sep/11/stonehenge-tunnel-route-moved-by-50-metres-after-protests</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMOv8r477-bjaHnt6SjMnG0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2017 21:30:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2017/sep/11/stonehenge-tunnel-route-moved-by-50-metres-after-protests" target="_blank"&gt;Stonehenge tunnel route moved by 50 metres after protests&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The government has changed the preferred route of a road tunnel designed to restore peace and tranquillity to Stonehenge after protests by druids, archaeologists and conservation experts. There was an outcry that the 1.8-mile tunnel would pass too close to precious barrows and ruin the view of the sun setting at the winter solstice, a crucial date in the pagan calendar. On Monday the government said it was now planning to shift the tunnel an extra 50 metres away from the prehistoric monument to try to ease the concerns of the scheme’s critics. Related: Opportunity or threat? Stonehenge tunn...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Stonehenge - 500px</title><link>https://500px.com/photo/216431379/stonehenge-by-iris-van-wolferen</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJQkvVnWr1HF6GfCWsaLpyMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow26UBMPBEMMD7CQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2017 14:02:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://500px.com/photo/216431379/stonehenge-by-iris-van-wolferen" target="_blank"&gt;Stonehenge&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;500px&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stonehenge is a prehistoric monument in Wiltshire, England, 2 miles (3 km) west of Amesbury and 8 miles (13 km) north of Salisbury. It consists of a ring of standing stones, with each standing stone around 4.1 metres (13 ft) high, 2.1 metres (6 ft 11 in) wide and weighing around 25 tons. The stones are set within earthworks in the middle of the most dense complex of Neolithic and Bronze Age monuments in England, including several hundred burial mounds.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://500px.com">500px</source></item><item><title>Stonehenge tunnel is a monumental error - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2017/jan/15/stonehenge-tunnel-is-a-monumental-error</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ5Hl4h-FNqsi1C1eh7u8KEqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCOvRU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2017 18:36:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2017/jan/15/stonehenge-tunnel-is-a-monumental-error" target="_blank"&gt;Stonehenge tunnel is a monumental error&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;On Friday, as usual, I drove westwards along the A303 on my way to Salisbury. A full moon in a clear sky was sinking behind Stonehenge. It was beautiful, and many of the travellers on that road will have enjoyed and perhaps been moved by the sight. The A303 is an ancient road and for hundreds of years the public have used it and been able to admire Stonehenge, some of us daily. When I was a child we were able to park nearby and walk among the stones. Now you can only get near it by paying the fee and becoming a tourist. Apart from the two solstices, the turning of this ancient monument into...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>The Stonehenge - 500px</title><link>https://500px.com/photo/214371319/the-stonehenge-by-souvik-dey</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEsx1SqNbuTueOGH-1NBDB4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAow26UBMPBEMMD7CQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 00:06:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://500px.com/photo/214371319/the-stonehenge-by-souvik-dey" target="_blank"&gt;The Stonehenge&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;500px&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;An attempt to capture the famous Stonehenge. The sky turned beautiful as you can see some flickering rays of the sun through the clouds.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://500px.com">500px</source></item><item><title>Stonehenge, Sunset - 500px</title><link>https://500px.com/photo/223941171/stonehenge-sunset-by-bill-resto</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIoo0WFMFf9y54Dq1mFHdt0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAow26UBMPBEMMD7CQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2017 17:06:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://500px.com/photo/223941171/stonehenge-sunset-by-bill-resto" target="_blank"&gt;Stonehenge, Sunset&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;500px&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Semi private tour at sunset. An incredibly difficult place to shoot without people in your photo. After a rainy dreary day the sun and sky were magnificent at the right time. The shooting window was very small and the guides were getting anxious with my delay.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://500px.com">500px</source></item></channel></rss>