<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Oxbridge - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIQgKIhtDQkFTRGdvSUwyMHZNRFZ0Y0Y4U0FtVnVLQUFQAQ?hl=en-GB&amp;gl=GB&amp;ceid=GB:en</link><language>en-GB</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 14:11:49 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Admissions to Oxbridge dominated by just eight schools, study shows - ITV News</title><link>https://www.itv.com/news/2018-12-07/eight-schools-dominate-admissions-to-oxbridge-study-shows/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">52780129133478</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 07:49:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.itv.com/news/2018-12-07/eight-schools-dominate-admissions-to-oxbridge-study-shows/" target="_blank"&gt;Admissions to Oxbridge dominated by just eight schools, study shows&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ITV News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/education-46470838" target="_blank"&gt;Oxbridge 'over-recruits from eight schools'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;BBC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.standard.co.uk/news/uk/eight-schools-send-more-pupils-to-oxbridge-than-nearly-3000-others-in-the-uk-a4010926.html" target="_blank"&gt;Eight schools send more pupils to Oxbridge than nearly 3,000 others in the UK, study shows&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Evening Standard&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/dec/07/oxbridge-guarantee-places-best-state-school-pupils-oxford-cambridge" target="_blank"&gt;Oxbridge needs to guarantee places for the best state school pupils&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.thetimes.co.uk/edition/news/eight-schools-send-more-to-oxbridge-than-2-800-rivals-psprjczdc" target="_blank"&gt;Eight schools send more to Oxbridge than 2800 rivals&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/stories/CAAqOQgKIjNDQklTSURvSmMzUnZjbmt0TXpZd1NoTUtFUWlteC1TbWpZQU1FVUF2c1hORmF5WXpLQUFQAQ?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;View full coverage on Google News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;</description><source url="https://www.itv.com">ITV News</source><media:content url="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/proxy/RxFZ1wplwkxkN8IFhTkNOpkFXM_0e5EEZt9IEIYjJi738DqKPpL5e0E1NCWe-VkL-uD1N7RU0zWQ5WG0Xg-nFX2kisRAOD3N9FUFU0h6LtE=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Elite Schools Send More Students To Oxbridge Than 2,900 Schools Combined - HuffPost UK</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.co.uk/entry/sutton-trust-oxbridge_uk_5c0990a6e4b0b6cdaf5d52ad</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELLBf8v0gco400-Nc1X0x94qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowmdW_BzCbhUcwuqRp</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 00:01:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.co.uk/entry/sutton-trust-oxbridge_uk_5c0990a6e4b0b6cdaf5d52ad" target="_blank"&gt;Elite Schools Send More Students To Oxbridge Than 2,900 Schools Combined&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost UK&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elite schools are dominating access to the UK's top universities, a study has found. A new analysis of UCAS data published by the Sutton Trust shows eight top ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.co.uk">HuffPost UK</source></item><item><title>Love Island is more lucrative than a degree from Oxbridge - The Week UK</title><link>http://www.theweek.co.uk/95363/love-island-is-more-lucrative-than-a-degree-from-oxbridge</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEISoXazRJPgKQoVA3lq4Sj0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowtuz8CjCfwokDML_70AU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 07:00:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.theweek.co.uk/95363/love-island-is-more-lucrative-than-a-degree-from-oxbridge" target="_blank"&gt;Love Island is more lucrative than a degree from Oxbridge&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Week UK&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Economists find that appearing on hit ITV show boosts your lifetime earnings more than attending Oxford or Cambridge.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.theweek.co.uk">The Week UK</source></item><item><title>50 years ago, my university days were tough – and the elitism is getting worse, not better - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/voices/oxbridge-university-elitist-schools-eton-social-class-students-philip-hammond-claudia-harris-a8672831.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMh7AXH_HZkOkNnmZmVugSYqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDMyxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 16:27:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/voices/oxbridge-university-elitist-schools-eton-social-class-students-philip-hammond-claudia-harris-a8672831.html" target="_blank"&gt;50 years ago, my university days were tough – and the elitism is getting worse, not better&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s no surprise that our top universities doggedly refuse to acknowledge their role in perpetuating the ugly truth about modern Britain: money and the right class still get you access and a seat at the top table. When it comes to choosing which pupils to accept for a highly prized place at Oxbridge, pedigree is everything. The Sutton Trust has discovered that just eight elite secondary schools send the same number of pupils to Oxford and Cambridge as three quarters of all the other schools in the UK. Pupils from independent schools make up 42 per cent of places at Oxbridge, and are seven t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Eight schools send more pupils to Oxbridge than three quarters of the rest of UK schools, report finds - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/education/oxbridge-admissions-acceptance-pupils-school-uk-fee-costs-students-a8671246.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAZtl33y-0qqCHQIoRBzZCEqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 23:58:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/education/oxbridge-admissions-acceptance-pupils-school-uk-fee-costs-students-a8671246.html" target="_blank"&gt;Eight schools send more pupils to Oxbridge than three quarters of the rest of UK schools, report finds&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eight schools and colleges had more students accepted to Oxbridge in the last three years than three quarters of all other schools, a report has revealed. The group, most of which are fee-paying independent schools, gained more than 1,300 admissions to courses at Oxford and Cambridge between 2015 and 2017. By contrast, some 2,900 schools and colleges, equating to three quarters of all further education centres in the UK, saw just 1,200 of their students accepted to Oxbridge in the same timeframe. The figures, collated from Ucas admissions data in a new report by education and social mobilit...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Eton and Westminster among eight schools dominating Oxbridge - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/education/2018/dec/07/eton-and-westminster-among-eight-schools-dominating-oxbridge</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOtp-wtRJErjsdg8YhW9tu0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 00:01:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/education/2018/dec/07/eton-and-westminster-among-eight-schools-dominating-oxbridge" target="_blank"&gt;Eton and Westminster among eight schools dominating Oxbridge&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eight top schools in the UK get as many pupils into the universities of Oxford and Cambridge as three-quarters of all schools and colleges together, according to new research. Over a three-year period the eight leading schools – which are mainly in the independent sector – sent 1,310 of their students to Oxbridge, while 2,900 schools, each with two or fewer acceptances, sent 1,220 pupils in total. The research showed that high-flying pupils from state schools were far less likely to apply to Oxbridge than their peers in the private sector, and were less likely to be successful when they did...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Oxbridge schemes to 'help' working class students adapt to university life are patronising and regressive - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/voices/oxford-cambridge-working-class-integration-diversity-a7929101.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMB0WyQd6a-D6JOVQorgJ_AqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDMyxU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2017 14:18:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/voices/oxford-cambridge-working-class-integration-diversity-a7929101.html" target="_blank"&gt;Oxbridge schemes to 'help' working class students adapt to university life are patronising and regressive&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bravo Oxford University. Last week the Student’s Union announced their new ‘Class Act’ scheme – where two working class students will be buddied up, allowing them a space to explore their anxieties such as “black tie and subfusc” on entering such an excruciatingly elitist environment. Well fusc that. I’m a Cambridge graduate, whose place at Queens’ College was certainly aided by the box my attendance at a state-comp and my low income household would allow the admissions office to tick. As a working class thorn, among legions of Etonian roses, my years at university were some of the most for...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>University Challenge and why everyone loves a clever-clogs - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/9d360886-1edc-11e7-b7d3-163f5a7f229c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMcOxl_TfwJXU3Y53OSQ4RkqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwgtt6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2017 04:00:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/9d360886-1edc-11e7-b7d3-163f5a7f229c" target="_blank"&gt;University Challenge and why everyone loves a clever-clogs&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;So that’s it, for another year. Eight clever young people return to their student lives to prepare for their exams in decent obscurity. After that will come nerve-racking applications for research funding, and the tedious business of making a living. Delighting millions with their lightly worn knowledge won’t count much then. But they will sally forth carrying in their minds the memory of how for a while their grimaces, their haircuts, their wardrobe, and their behaviour under stress were made plain for millions. Like GK Chesterton’s “The Donkey” (though they are self-evidently not donkeys)...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Oxford and Cambridge top world university rankings - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/education/2017/sep/05/oxford-cambridge-top-world-university-rankings</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPXFf-KYcVWhUi87L5KwtVIqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 14:53:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/education/2017/sep/05/oxford-cambridge-top-world-university-rankings" target="_blank"&gt;Oxford and Cambridge top world university rankings&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oxford and Cambridge have grabbed the top slots in the musical chairs of the international university league table, despite fears that British higher education is facing disruption over funding and student tuition fees. Related: UK universities fall down global league tables after budget cuts The latest rankings by Times Higher Education (THE) put Oxford on top for the second year in a row and rival Cambridge in second, displacing the California Institute of Technology. The sterling performance of Oxbridge and other British universities comes as a fillip to the sector after a summer of head...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Oxford University accused of failing to deal with admissions racism - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/education/2017/jan/14/oxford-university-accused-of-failing-to-deal-with-admissions-racism-david-lammy</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDy-rcOwUrQiMXx0BZ-_G2oqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2017 16:38:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/education/2017/jan/14/oxford-university-accused-of-failing-to-deal-with-admissions-racism-david-lammy" target="_blank"&gt;Oxford University accused of failing to deal with admissions racism&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A former higher education minister has accused the University of Oxford of failing to adequately tackle racism caused by an “unconscious bias” against black and disadvantaged applicants. The Labour MP for Tottenham, David Lammy provoked an indignant response from the senior representatives of Oxford colleges, with one interrupting him to call his comments absolute nonsense during a debate at the university. The event, a symposium on admissions held on Friday evening, had earlier heard the university’s vice-chancellor Louise Richardson suggest it might need to overhaul its admissions procedu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Bristol is right to lower entry requirements – elite institutions like Oxbridge should follow its lead - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/education/2017/01/11/bristol-right-lower-entry-requirements-elite-institutions/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI8-XVkaaS794D828PPuJPAqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCA8LkF</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2017 17:00:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/education/2017/01/11/bristol-right-lower-entry-requirements-elite-institutions/" target="_blank"&gt;Bristol is right to lower entry requirements – elite institutions like Oxbridge should follow its lead&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;My two-week stint as a fundraiser on a Cambridge telephone campaign last Easter was an illuminating – if not gruelling – experience. I spoke to women who were part of the first cohort allowed to study alongside men in 1972, old friends of my own tutors, and, inevitably, an infuriating number of voicemail messages. Almost every single person I spoke to remembered fondly the welcoming atmosphere at King’s College, with just as many asking whether the infamous hammer and sickle flag was still up in the college bar (it is, in case you were wondering). Bafflingly, however, another topic that aro...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Ucas decision time: 'I rejected a Russell Group university and never looked back' - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/women/life/ucas-decision-time-rejected-russell-group-university-never-looked/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELIpdh5IHDd3Xy6y2k2DeEsqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDqy7cF</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2017 13:50:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/women/life/ucas-decision-time-rejected-russell-group-university-never-looked/" target="_blank"&gt;Ucas decision time: 'I rejected a Russell Group university and never looked back'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Growing up in Durham, there was always an expectation that I would apply for the city’s university. Teachers at my sixth-form college urged me to go for it, given my predicted four A* grades. They said I would thrive there. Only I wasn’t convinced. I had known for a few years that I wanted to become a journalist, but there were few Russell Group universities that offered specific vocational courses. On top of that, I just wasn’t sure that I wanted to go to a highly academic university. Like many high-achievers, I like working at my own pace and often struggle under pressure, so I worried th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Britain’s Broken Ladder of Social Mobility - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2017/06/27/opinion/britains-broken-ladder-of-social-mobility.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIAedOD65fKarIgxaBNkBdsqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzwwqIQY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2017 08:46:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2017/06/27/opinion/britains-broken-ladder-of-social-mobility.html" target="_blank"&gt;Britain’s Broken Ladder of Social Mobility&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The barriers to entry to the middle class are now so high that even an elite university education is no guarantee of success.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>University Challenge rivals Eric Monkman and Bobby Seagull: ‘I think people like us … I don’t think they’re walking away laughing’ - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/tv-and-radio/2017/aug/11/university-challenge-rivals-eric-monkman-and-bobby-seagull-i-think-people-like-us-i-dont-think-theyre-walking-away-laughing</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECqyibyBWsD25EDUDiCc-IEqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2017 14:27:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/tv-and-radio/2017/aug/11/university-challenge-rivals-eric-monkman-and-bobby-seagull-i-think-people-like-us-i-dont-think-theyre-walking-away-laughing" target="_blank"&gt;University Challenge rivals Eric Monkman and Bobby Seagull: ‘I think people like us … I don’t think they’re walking away laughing’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;One Monday evening in January 2016, a Cambridge student came out of a meeting looking pale and shaken. He was Julian Sutcliffe, a history student at Peterhouse, and veteran quizzer (he had been on a University Challenge winning team). That night in Cambridge, he was acting in the Jeremy Paxman role at quiz practice, questioning teams from several of the university’s colleges who were about to appear on the TV show. “He said: ‘Oh, my God, there’s a miracle,’” remembers Bobby Seagull, who bumped into Sutcliffe afterwards. “He said, ‘There’s a Canadian man called Eric Monkman and he knows ever...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Sorry, Giles, that's not the Oxford I know - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/education/2016/12/19/sorry-giles-not-oxford-know/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN_odJr1jxb-E-nf4Bf1pb8qFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCA8LkF</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2016 07:09:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/education/2016/12/19/sorry-giles-not-oxford-know/" target="_blank"&gt;Sorry, Giles, that's not the Oxford I know&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Something was worryingly familiar about the tone of Giles Coren’s column for the Times this weekend, in which he wrote about the hopeless court case of Faiz Siddiqui, who is attempting to sue Oxford University for its substandard teaching and – by extension - his failure to get a first-class degree. It was the same refrain I hear from some college alumni, who come back to the dining hall for an overpriced reunion dinner and slur romantically about their ‘Oxford days’ over a pancetta-rolled pigeon breast and too many glasses of Pinot Noir. There seems to be something uniquely pompous about O...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>From Othello to Oxbridge - The Huffington Post UK</title><link>http://www.huffingtonpost.co.uk/andrew-law/from-othello-to-oxbridge_b_14632068.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJxo5qc2cmYdwxieiSqqyYAqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowmdW_BzCbhUcw2vd4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 09:42:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.huffingtonpost.co.uk/andrew-law/from-othello-to-oxbridge_b_14632068.html" target="_blank"&gt;From Othello to Oxbridge&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Huffington Post UK&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The British public schools, which educated many members of the present Westminster government, of course place great emphasis on developing the confident and effective use of spoken language. For the sake of social equality, state schools must also teach children the spoken language skills that they need for educational progress, and for life in general." (1) Those words, taken from the Bullock Report into language and education, were written all the way back in 1975. But do any of us truly believe that the problem with "social equality" in Britain identified over 40 years ago has really b...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.huffingtonpost.co.uk">The Huffington Post UK</source></item><item><title>Three-quarters of Britain’s prime ministers went to Oxford or Cambridge (but mostly Oxford) - Quartz</title><link>http://qz.com/811121/three-quarters-of-britains-prime-ministers-went-to-oxford-or-cambridge-but-mostly-oxford/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELcfYDqTar0NAhRR-x774HwqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowi4-MATDXsRUwlPieAw</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2016 07:00:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://qz.com/811121/three-quarters-of-britains-prime-ministers-went-to-oxford-or-cambridge-but-mostly-oxford/" target="_blank"&gt;Three-quarters of Britain’s prime ministers went to Oxford or Cambridge (but mostly Oxford)&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Quartz&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Britain formally started calling its top political leader “prime minister” in 1721, and for a long time graduates from Oxford and Cambridge, the country’s two premier universities, got the top job with roughly equal frequency. Then Oxford pulled ahead. Way ahead. Earlier this year, Theresa May became the 27th Oxford graduate to become prime minister. Cambridge, by contrast, has sent only 13 prime ministers to Westminster (or 14, if you count Charles Watson-Wentworth, whose educational history is the subject of some debate). The last Cambridge man to sit as prime minister was Stanley Baldwin...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://qz.com">Quartz</source></item><item><title>State school pupils have 'reduced chance' of winning Oxbridge places as they apply to oversubscribed courses - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/education/education-news/oxbridge-places-state-school-pupils-reduced-change-university-courses-oversubscribed-oxford-a7892101.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIog3z4-XZPj2jDDekTGXV0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2017 10:16:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/education/education-news/oxbridge-places-state-school-pupils-reduced-change-university-courses-oversubscribed-oxford-a7892101.html" target="_blank"&gt;State school pupils have 'reduced chance' of winning Oxbridge places as they apply to oversubscribed courses&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;State school pupils are lowering their chances of winning a place at Oxbridge because they are more likely to apply for over-subscribed subjects, latest analysis suggests. State-educated sixth-formers hoping to go on to the UK’s most prestigious institutions are more likely to apply for the most popular courses than those who attend fee-paying schools, according to figures obtained by the Press Association. Privately educated pupils are more likely to apply for the least over-subscribed, earning them a better chance of being accepted for an interview. - Read more Unis 'allow growing number ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Oxford, Cambridge Top World Rankings As U.S. Slips Again - Forbes Now</title><link>//www.forbes.com/sites/nickmorrison/2017/09/05/oxford-cambridge-top-world-rankings-as-u-s-slips-again/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGCPxod4fLpsBKD5uzEQVuIqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMKGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 13:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="//www.forbes.com/sites/nickmorrison/2017/09/05/oxford-cambridge-top-world-rankings-as-u-s-slips-again/" target="_blank"&gt;Oxford, Cambridge Top World Rankings As U.S. Slips Again&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just a year after losing the top spot in world university rankings for the first time, the U.S. slips again, with its top rated college falling behind both Oxford and Cambridge. But the U.K.’s success could be short-lived, as Brexit threatens to take a toll on the research income enjoyed by its leading higher education institutions, putting their future as world-leaders in jeopardy. Oxford this year held onto the top spot it gained for the first time last year, in global rankingspublished today by industry magazine Times Higher Education. Its triumph last time around was also the first time...&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Cambridge student hits back at trolls who claim she only got accepted because she's black - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/cambridge-student-black-racism-trolls-social-media-university-degree-acceptance-a7878336.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEELF6FI6LNrPnAEkcpPTmZwqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDdyhU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2017 12:25:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/cambridge-student-black-racism-trolls-social-media-university-degree-acceptance-a7878336.html" target="_blank"&gt;Cambridge student hits back at trolls who claim she only got accepted because she's black&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Cambridge student has hit back at Twitter trolls for their racist comments regarding her acceptance to the world-renowned university. Courtney Daniella, who runs a popular beauty and lifestyle YouTube channel, revealed the extent of prejudiced comments she receives in a thread last week. Having performed very well at school, achieving A*AA in her A Levels, she successfully enrolled in a degree in Human, Social and Political Sciences at the UK's top university. Do you know how many times I get comments on YT and even @'d about how 'lucky' I must feel to got to @Cambridge_Uni and how the 'q...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Oxford and Cambridge named best two universities in the world - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/education/2017/09/05/oxford-cambridge-named-best-two-universities-world/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJueHt7GCNxDwd_jwMbckyYqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCA8LkF</guid><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 19:33:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/education/2017/09/05/oxford-cambridge-named-best-two-universities-world/" target="_blank"&gt;Oxford and Cambridge named best two universities in the world&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The top two universities in the world are to be found in the UK, according to a new league table. Oxford held on to first place in the latest annual Times Higher Education World University Rankings, with Cambridge rising from fourth place to take second. It is the first time that the two prestigious institutions have taken the top two spots in the 13-year history of the rankings. Out of 31 UK universities to make the top 200, 16 have seen a fall in their position, compared to last year. Kings College, Cambridge Credit: Peter Barritt Phil Baty, editorial director of the THE global rankings,...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Ex-police commissioner adjusts to life as head of Oxford college - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/0baa2a34-680e-11e7-8526-7b38dcaef614</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEKhLUmTHuwyaApZL5khJG4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwktp6</guid><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2017 04:37:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/0baa2a34-680e-11e7-8526-7b38dcaef614" target="_blank"&gt;Ex-police commissioner adjusts to life as head of Oxford college&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Undergraduates called to the office of Helen King, the new principal of St Anne’s College at Oxford university, could be forgiven for feeling intimidated. Prominently displayed on a bookcase are the truncheon and handcuffs she was issued with when she entered the police force in 1986. Ms King exchanged her role as assistant commissioner at the Metropolitan Police to become the first police officer to head an Oxbridge college. She started at St Anne’s three months ago, but while she was lunching with academics and perusing the college accounts, Scotland Yard was trying to cope with two major...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Why Oxbridge's posh kids like to hide behind a 'working class' smokescreen - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/education/2017/02/21/oxbridges-posh-kids-like-hide-behind-working-class-smokescreen/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFhZ4XmEsHfUMjaIaHkyxHEqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCA8LkF</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 11:55:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/education/2017/02/21/oxbridges-posh-kids-like-hide-behind-working-class-smokescreen/" target="_blank"&gt;Why Oxbridge's posh kids like to hide behind a 'working class' smokescreen&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;When I look back to when I first started Cambridge, my conception of privilege was, admittedly, a sheltered one. I grew up in Northern Ireland in a little seaside village, where wealth was measured by what kind of school blazer students wore at the train station each morning. In many respects, I should have seen it coming from my school days, when the wealthier students stopped wearing Hollister clothing because it was becoming too common. It was only when I took a gap year then started university that I realised privilege comes in its most dangerous form when it is hidden in plain sight – ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>While the papers whine about Oxbridge debauchery, student altruism gets ignored - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/education/2017/03/01/papers-whine-oxbridge-debauchery-student-altruism-gets-ignored/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHZ5U_gl--Z1xNriPe2_SnoqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCA8LkF</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2017 13:55:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/education/2017/03/01/papers-whine-oxbridge-debauchery-student-altruism-gets-ignored/" target="_blank"&gt;While the papers whine about Oxbridge debauchery, student altruism gets ignored&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;There’s something quite odd about coming down to breakfast on a Sunday morning, often with a thick head, and glancing at the paper to see that someone else is having a go at the place where you live. I imagine it’s what it might have felt like to be a spy behind the lines during the war, when newspapers were full of news of your country’s terrible crimes, interspersed with op-eds about how we ought to fight them with all our strength. I’m not fighting a war, of course, and I might not do any more than have a little chuckle before going back to my fry-up. But there is something oddly obsessi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Our daughter did better than expected in her exams, can she still apply to Cambridge? - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/education/2016/07/14/our-daughter-did-better-than-expected-in-her-exams-can-she-still/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEARfO6G3aTpxUjT_WOkTUnIqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCA8LkF</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2017 09:44:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/education/2016/07/14/our-daughter-did-better-than-expected-in-her-exams-can-she-still/" target="_blank"&gt;Our daughter did better than expected in her exams, can she still apply to Cambridge?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;- Search for Clearing vacancies online - Download the Clearing app on iPhone or Android A-level Results Day is finally here. For International Baccalaureate (IB) students, however, the all-important day has been and gone. One July 6, students received their overall point score and found out if they had secured a place at the university of their choice. - Last week: Our son wants to switch degree courses at the last minute - is this possible at a top university? For those who missed out, Ucas Clearing opened to allow prospective undergraduates to find a place on a new course at a different ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>I went from care to Cambridge University. Let me show you where the barriers are - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2017/jul/12/leaving-care-cambridge-university-access-problems</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENCicwAGAKP2lXAKm_19OZwqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTC9vBU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2017 10:50:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2017/jul/12/leaving-care-cambridge-university-access-problems" target="_blank"&gt;I went from care to Cambridge University. Let me show you where the barriers are&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;I wore a miniskirt and fishnets to my registration at the University of Cambridge. Not for any particular reason: they were just items of clothing I had to hand. I woke up, got dressed, slipped on my tattered cherry-red Doc Martens and headed to the Old Library. There, I was greeted by a row of students all dressed in suits and ties, or demure black or navy dresses, and gowns. Related: Oxford and Cambridge 'need to improve access for disadvantaged students' I had no idea that registration at Cambridge, and the four-course meal that follows it, is a formal dress affair. That was my introduct...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Oxford and Cambridge still struggle with an elitist image - will this ever change? - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/education/2016/10/31/oxford-and-cambridge-still-struggle-with-an-elitist-image--will/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ4uOZf81UqhV2KyMEBEfrwqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCA8LkF</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2016 14:31:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/education/2016/10/31/oxford-and-cambridge-still-struggle-with-an-elitist-image--will/" target="_blank"&gt;Oxford and Cambridge still struggle with an elitist image - will this ever change?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A couple of weeks ago, in an attempt to demystify its application process, the University of Oxford released a batch of sample interview questions. It’s a step in the right direction (albeit, a well-trodden one); Oxbridge’s interviews, alongside the archaic, arcane traditions of dress code, hold a position of high cultural mystique. Yet in a survey by the Sutton Trust released this month, 13 per cent of state school teachers said they would not advise students to apply to Oxbridge because they were concerned they wouldn’t be happy, or felt they were unlikely to be accepted. Equally concerni...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Oxbridge Boat Race faces choppy waters amid fears flotilla could catch fire - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/education/2017/03/21/oxbridge-boat-race-faces-choppy-waters-amid-fears-flotilla-could/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF3lauEoJ1AHDG6fWr5ifCwqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCA8LkF</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2017 09:23:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/education/2017/03/21/oxbridge-boat-race-faces-choppy-waters-amid-fears-flotilla-could/" target="_blank"&gt;Oxbridge Boat Race faces choppy waters amid fears flotilla could catch fire&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The University Boat Race has hit choppy waters. The annual contest between the rowers of Cambridge and Oxford has found itself submerged in a rising tide of health and safety red tape. The problem is not the university rowing boats themselves but the colourful flotilla of river vessels that follows the crews up the Thames. For according to the Port of London Authority, the body responsible for safety on the river, many of the historic wooden support craft - including the Cambridge University launch Amaryllis - are in danger of being set on fire by their own petrol engines. Boat race guide T...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Oxbridge 'must do more to recognise potential in poorer applicants', says universities tsar - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/education/education-news/oxbridge-poor-applicants-universities-tsar-students-oxford-cambridge-les-ebdon-offa-a7812821.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBWFFP5l180aVAWRu9A1rTsqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2017 15:43:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/education/education-news/oxbridge-poor-applicants-universities-tsar-students-oxford-cambridge-les-ebdon-offa-a7812821.html" target="_blank"&gt;Oxbridge 'must do more to recognise potential in poorer applicants', says universities tsar&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oxford and Cambridge universities need to recognise potential in poorer applicants rather than rely too heavily on top grades, the Government's universities tsar has said. The two top-ranking institutions still have a "mountain to climb" in ensuring bright but disadvantaged teenagers have a chance of winning a place, said Professor Les Ebdon, director for the Office for Fair Access (Offa). Speaking at the University of Buckingham’s Festival of Higher Education, he said: "I wish Oxbridge would recognise potential more than they do.” - Read more Elite UK universities found to be second-rate i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>'Don't blame Cambridge for lack of black students,' says leading students’ society - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/05/03/dont-blame-cambridge-lack-black-students-saysleading-students/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO3Bo8QL0XAR-_29U9BFcEoqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2017 22:22:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/05/03/dont-blame-cambridge-lack-black-students-saysleading-students/" target="_blank"&gt;'Don't blame Cambridge for lack of black students,' says leading students’ society&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Britain's top universities should not be "attacked" for admitting low numbers of ethnic minority students as more black youngsters need to apply, a leading students’ society has said. Members of Cambridge University’s Afro-Caribbean Society (CUACS) who posed for a photograph outside St John's College have told how higher education institutions need to overcome negative messages and focus instead on empowerment. Daniel Oluboyede, 19, a first year medicine student and member of CUACS, told the Telegraph: “It is always encouraging to be positive on the matter instead of just looking at the neg...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>It's not shocking that an Oxford University graduate is suing because he didn't get a first class degree – it's inevitable - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/voices/oxford-university-oxbridge-graduate-sues-suing-first-class-honours-degree-tuition-fees-inevitable-a7456331.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOGv89haP4vnVAo5bYDSWXoqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDMyxU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2016 11:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/voices/oxford-university-oxbridge-graduate-sues-suing-first-class-honours-degree-tuition-fees-inevitable-a7456331.html" target="_blank"&gt;It's not shocking that an Oxford University graduate is suing because he didn't get a first class degree – it's inevitable&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A sweet city, replete with dreaming spires, not needful of June to heighten its beauty: Oxford, as E. M. Forster put it, would much rather have its inmates love it than their fellow inmates. My alma mater, and perhaps Forster too, might be disappointed to hear that that love is found wanting in the case of a former student who has brought a civil suit against the ancient seat of learning for its “negligent” teaching. Faiz Siddiqui argues that the poor standard of tuition he was subjected to led to him receiving a paltry 2:1 instead of a coveted first class degree. That result in turn, Siddi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Working class kids aren't getting a free pass into Oxbridge – they just finally have the chances they deserve - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/voices/james-delingpole-oxford-cambridge-oxford-durham-academic-standards-snowflakes-working-class-middle-a7658126.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA06HAAQaWu8mGYsY4cepA4qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDMyxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2017 13:20:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/voices/james-delingpole-oxford-cambridge-oxford-durham-academic-standards-snowflakes-working-class-middle-a7658126.html" target="_blank"&gt;Working class kids aren't getting a free pass into Oxbridge – they just finally have the chances they deserve&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The journalist and polemicist James Delingpole believes that to get a “real Oxbridge education” it’s now important to apply to another university altogether: Durham. Having spoken recently at both Oxford and Durham, and failing to garner sycophantic applause from his student audience at the former, the writer can apparently draw no other conclusion than that academic standards at Oxford are falling due to an influx of working class students creating a “PC monoculture”. Cambridge is, he says, suffering the same fate. As he puts it, Oxbridge is endangering itself “in its eagerness to purge it...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Oxbridge now recognises the importance of mental health - it's time for the rest to follow suit - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/education/2017/01/04/oxbridge-now-recognises-importance-mental-health-time-rest/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOp6XAd_sKYNcbDSvNSpS4MqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCA8LkF</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 11:29:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/education/2017/01/04/oxbridge-now-recognises-importance-mental-health-time-rest/" target="_blank"&gt;Oxbridge now recognises the importance of mental health - it's time for the rest to follow suit&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mental health: it’s something all of us have, and an issue one in four of us will fall foul of every single year. Awareness and understanding of these issues is only on the rise. Sadly though, it seems that awareness is yet to turn into any meaningful action. In terms of funding or improved treatment, only 55 percent of NHS mental health trusts have increased their budgets since 2012. In fact, mental health only accounts for 13 percent of the NHS total budget, despite the inescapable fact that 28 percent of burden placed on the health service is in some way related to mental illness. This i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Oxford’s Stormzy snub is not the only thing wrong with the university - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/nov/12/oxford-university-stormzy-ethnic-minority-students</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHY-yJp2_gPy1iT9cXk8T7EqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCOvRU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 16:37:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/nov/12/oxford-university-stormzy-ethnic-minority-students" target="_blank"&gt;Oxford’s Stormzy snub is not the only thing wrong with the university&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;It looks like someone, or a few people, within Oxford University didn’t know what to do with Stormzy, or get back to him, when he offered to fund a scholarship for black students in January. As the musician revealed last week, he went instead to Cambridge University, where his proposal was taken up. This was simply a mistake by Oxford, I am sure, and not necessarily evidence of malice; an error of this sort might be OK, generally, if it was unique. But it isn’t. In my experiences as a student, and now a student union leader on access, it has become clear to me that Oxford has a widespread p...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Stormzy: University Of Oxford Rejected My Scholarship Offer - HuffPost UK</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.co.uk/entry/stormzy-university-of-oxford-rejected-my-scholarship-offer_uk_5be40570e4b0769d24c98c0c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMxOCPrDUMfPnsQikBCzD1MqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowmdW_BzCbhUcwuqRp</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 10:05:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.co.uk/entry/stormzy-university-of-oxford-rejected-my-scholarship-offer_uk_5be40570e4b0769d24c98c0c" target="_blank"&gt;Stormzy: University Of Oxford Rejected My Scholarship Offer&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost UK&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stormzy has said Oxford University turned down his offer to fund scholarships for black students, leading him to take his proposal to Cambridge. The grime artist, 25, told an audience at London’s Barbican Centre on Wednesday that Oxford bosses rejected a fund for four places over two years. “We tried Oxford but they didn’t want to get involved,” Stormzy said, according to the Guardian. Stormzy reached an agreement with Cambridge to fund two undergraduate places a year for two years, including a fund for maintenance. The first set of scholarships was awarded last month. Oxford and Cambridge,...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.co.uk">HuffPost UK</source></item><item><title>Oxbridge failing disadvantaged students, critics claim - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/education/2017/04/05/oxbridge-failing-disadvantaged-students-critics-claim/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENc_6m8Hai420g15Hyb6G2MqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCA8LkF</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 16:04:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/education/2017/04/05/oxbridge-failing-disadvantaged-students-critics-claim/" target="_blank"&gt;Oxbridge failing disadvantaged students, critics claim&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Students from disadvantaged backgrounds are falling behind their peers at Britain’s top two universities, new figures show. Undergraduate degree results from Oxford and Cambridge universities, obtained through Freedom of Information requests, show that students identified by the university as financially or socially disadvantaged were less likely to achieve a First Class degree, and more likely to drop out before the end of their course. At Oxford disadvantaged students were, between 2013 and 2015, seven percent less likely to achieve a First and six percent less likely to complete their co...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Britain's highest paying degrees, according to graduate salary - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/education/0/uks-highest-paying-degrees-according-graduate-salary/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENiKDATzQVbUrjA0tt2N1lMqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCA8LkF</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 10:50:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/education/0/uks-highest-paying-degrees-according-graduate-salary/" target="_blank"&gt;Britain's highest paying degrees, according to graduate salary&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Asked which degree you should take for the highest graduate salary, you may well think of Oxbridge excellence in law or economics. With the Oxbridge deadline, as well as that for courses in medicine, veterinary science and dentistry, approaching on 15 October, such courses might be tempting to make the most money in later life. It is certainly true that some courses at top universities can give you some of the highest paying degrees, adding tens of thousands to the average starting salary. But some of the highest paying jobs actually come from some lesser known institutions, with engineerin...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Graduates of Imperial College beat Oxbridge on earnings - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/education/2018/sep/24/graduates-of-imperial-college-beat-oxbridge-on-earnings</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOyu7XOIeuLnWxaVWK7yPckqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDMwRU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2018 23:01:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/education/2018/sep/24/graduates-of-imperial-college-beat-oxbridge-on-earnings" target="_blank"&gt;Graduates of Imperial College beat Oxbridge on earnings&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Graduates from Imperial College London pick up the highest salaries in the first year after graduation, earning around a fifth more than students leaving Oxford and Cambridge, according to research by the job website Adzuna. The average Imperial graduate earns £37,931 in their first year post-graduation, £5,000 more than the typical Oxbridge graduate, the report found. Imperial has long jostled with Oxford and Cambridge at the top of the university academic league, with its specialisation in medical, engineering and technological subjects likely to explain its graduates’ higher earning powe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Britain surpassed for first time as second most-represented nation in university rankings - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/education/education-news/times-higher-education-world-university-rankings-britain-uk-global-reputation-league-tables-a8555736.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ6_8LO6S3mfGPhN3ofZ2u8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/education/education-news/times-higher-education-world-university-rankings-britain-uk-global-reputation-league-tables-a8555736.html" target="_blank"&gt;Britain surpassed for first time as second most-represented nation in university rankings&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Britain has been surpassed for the first time as the second most-represented nation in global university rankings – but Oxford and Cambridge have nonetheless retained the top two positions. The pair have once again topped the World University Rankings, with Oxford in first place and Cambridge in second. But the national picture shows stagnation and modest decline. Intensified global competition has seen the reputation of UK universities dip and experts are warning that Brexit could pose a further risk to Britain’s status and research capabilities. - Read more Oxbridge’s lack of diversity is...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Top graduate schemes dominated by private schools - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/09/23/top-graduate-schemes-dominated-private-schools/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIKEpbigGIffRzXFpbWq0w8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2018 23:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/09/23/top-graduate-schemes-dominated-private-schools/" target="_blank"&gt;Top graduate schemes dominated by private schools&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Britain's leading graduate schemes are dominated by privately educated young people, the Institute of Student Employers has found. Its survey found that 57 per cent of graduates hired by companies had been to a state school, compared to 91 per cent across the population. A poll of 38 employers, recruiting 32,202 young people and representing 17 sectors, found that privileged young people were over-represented. While almost all firms polled said that improving diversity was a priority, the data showed that many of them were struggling to reflect society in their graduate schemes. "People who...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Oxford 'spends £108,000' to recruit each extra low-income student - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/education/2018/sep/19/oxford-spends-108000-to-recruit-each-extra-low-income-student</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHmoBkkOLyVMdK7plHclkIQqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 06:00:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/education/2018/sep/19/oxford-spends-108000-to-recruit-each-extra-low-income-student" target="_blank"&gt;Oxford 'spends £108,000' to recruit each extra low-income student&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oxford University spends more than £100,000 for each additional student from a poor background it admits every year, according to a new analysis of its efforts to improve access. Figures published in Prospect show that Oxford’s “cost of acquisition” for every extra student from a low-income area admitted since 2009 is £108,000. The data is based on Oxford’s record of admitting about 10 extra students from low-income postcodes each year between 2009 and 2016, spending at least £14m a year on access and widening participation as required by higher education regulators. About 5,000 school-leav...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Prisoners will be offered bursaries to study at Cambridge University for first time - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/education/2018/09/13/prisoners-will-offered-bursaries-study-cambridge-university/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJzIcSSRWYCeBjmZUVVnTRIqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCA8LkF</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 16:46:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/education/2018/09/13/prisoners-will-offered-bursaries-study-cambridge-university/" target="_blank"&gt;Prisoners will be offered bursaries to study at Cambridge University for first time&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Prisoners will be offered bursaries to study at Cambridge University for the first time under a new scheme. Four bursaries, each worth £5,000, have been awarded to current and former prisoners, who will start their courses next month at Cambridge’s Institute of Continuing Education. The participants – who, if still serving time, would need to be in an open prison and qualify for a day release licence – will study towards an undergraduate higher education certificate. The bursaries are part of a broader research project on the role of education in rehabilitating prisoners into society after ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>The only way to end the class divide: the case for abolishing private schools - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/news/2018/aug/24/the-only-way-to-end-the-class-divide-the-case-for-abolishing-private-schools</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENG-H3dqyvMi1B8TjjATgy0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Aug 2018 05:00:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/news/2018/aug/24/the-only-way-to-end-the-class-divide-the-case-for-abolishing-private-schools" target="_blank"&gt;The only way to end the class divide: the case for abolishing private schools&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unlikely as it might sound, one of the most electric political meetings I have ever attended was a lecture on the Finnish educational system given by Pasi Sahlberg, the Finnish educator and author, in London in the spring of 2012. Sahlberg, who was speaking to a packed committee room 14 of the House of Commons – the most magnificent of a run of grand meeting rooms that directly overlook the Thames – has a rather laconic manner of delivery. However, in this particular instance, his flat speaking style proved the perfect vehicle for an unexpectedly radical message. Sahlberg described how Finn...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Stormzy to fund Cambridge scholarships for black students - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/education/2018/aug/16/stormzy-to-help-fund-cambridge-university-scholarships-for-black-students</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHBI-XIYGj7LmZtCt0v6CYYqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 10:21:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/education/2018/aug/16/stormzy-to-help-fund-cambridge-university-scholarships-for-black-students" target="_blank"&gt;Stormzy to fund Cambridge scholarships for black students&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stormzy has announced that he is funding two scholarships for black British students to go to Cambridge University. The grime artist will pay the students’ tuition fees as well as a maintenance grant for up to four years of an undergraduate course. Speaking on Thursday at his former school, the Harris City Academy in Croydon, south London, where A-level students were opening their results, Stormzy told BBC Breakfast: “If you’re academically brilliant don’t think because you come from a certain community that studying at one of the highest education institutions in the world isn’t possible.”...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>All credit to Stormzy. But Oxbridge must do more for black students - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/aug/16/stormzy-oxbridge-black-student-scholarships-bame</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP-u5UJaCREknkvgqgHNxGAqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 14:13:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/aug/16/stormzy-oxbridge-black-student-scholarships-bame" target="_blank"&gt;All credit to Stormzy. But Oxbridge must do more for black students&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stormzy is the people’s champion. In the past two years, he has proven himself to be one of the most committed public figures to furthering the interests of young black British people. He has made surprise appearances at youth sports days, access conferences and even singing at a funeral for a fan. From sponsoring Oxford University alumna Fiona Asiedu to take up a place at graduate school at Harvard, to launching the publishing imprint #MerkyBooks in partnership with Penguin, Stormzy has kept us on our toes, eagerly anticipating his next big move. So I was proud to participate in a photosho...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Privileged commentators are quick to tell working class kids they 'don't need uni' – but I'm glad to see Stormzy backing Oxbridge - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/voices/a-level-results-day-university-working-class-kids-stormzy-oxbridge-scholarship-a8494306.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELbjrJPSdzQEHGpUkMBihrYqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDMyxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 11:25:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/voices/a-level-results-day-university-working-class-kids-stormzy-oxbridge-scholarship-a8494306.html" target="_blank"&gt;Privileged commentators are quick to tell working class kids they 'don't need uni' – but I'm glad to see Stormzy backing Oxbridge&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are many reasons I shouldn’t be a Stormzy fan. He’s the only grime artist on my Spotify, my attempts to rap along to his rhymes are a disgrace and I spent much of his performance at this year’s Brit Awards worrying that the shower he was singing beneath would cause some kind of electric shock meltdown. Being cool isn’t really my thing, but that is precisely why I love Stormzy. He hangs out with oh-so-mainstream Ed Sheeran, talks about his former dream of studying political science at Oxford and lets his mum make his tour announcements. I suspect, secretly, he’s a bit of a geek just li...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>I thought getting into Oxford was a dream come true – I couldn't have been more wrong - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/voices/a-level-results-oxford-university-education-life-oxbridge-class-culture-a8492336.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECr7Vm1QFjEcUQV_yAVo9X4qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDMyxU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2018 09:36:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/voices/a-level-results-oxford-university-education-life-oxbridge-class-culture-a8492336.html" target="_blank"&gt;I thought getting into Oxford was a dream come true – I couldn't have been more wrong&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;When I got into Oxford, I envisaged debating with like-minded people, joining the Oxford Union, dining in the grand halls and learning to row. The reality was one big social, financial and intellectual struggle. I was intimidated by the cultural divide. During freshers’ week, one fellow student told me he’d spent his summer shooting on daddy’s estate, while another had been reading in their drawing room. Coming from a very different sort of estate myself (though thankfully with no shooting), I didn’t realise life like that existed outside of a Jane Austen novel. I was used to walking barefo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Government accused of 'total failure' to widen elite university access - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/education/2018/aug/15/government-accused-of-total-failure-to-widen-elite-university-access</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO5z01I3T330WyAPB8UOIJcqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2018 23:01:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/education/2018/aug/15/government-accused-of-total-failure-to-widen-elite-university-access" target="_blank"&gt;Government accused of 'total failure' to widen elite university access&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ministers have been accused of a “total and abject failure” to widen access to top universities for disadvantaged students, after analysis by the Labour party found the proportions attending Russell Group universities had increased by only one percentage point since 2010. Separately, research by a group of Labour MPs suggests pupils from towns are less likely to attend university than those from London, with a nine percentage point gap between pupils from London and the rest of the country, and a 20-point gap between those from low-income families in the capital and in towns. Labour said th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Restore maintenance grants for poorest students to boost diversity on campus, university boss says - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/education/education-news/maintenance-grants-university-students-russell-group-tim-bradshaw-diversity-a8471816.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEc8yRRo6_Ir7SjohhiT6LcqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Aug 2018 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/education/education-news/maintenance-grants-university-students-russell-group-tim-bradshaw-diversity-a8471816.html" target="_blank"&gt;Restore maintenance grants for poorest students to boost diversity on campus, university boss says&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The government must bring back maintenance grants for poor students in order to improve diversity in higher education, according to leading universities amid a major row over admissions policies. Tim Bradshaw, head of the Russell Group, which represents the most selective UK universities, called on ministers to make more money available to widen access, rather than “putting all the blame on universities”. His comments come as the group of 24 elite universities, which includes Oxford and Cambridge, are in the spotlight for failing to admit sufficient numbers of students from ethnic minoritie...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Grammar school superhead left students feeling suicidal with policy of exclusion for getting B grades - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/07/29/grammar-school-superhead-left-students-feeling-suicidal-policy/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJmE1-XrgytV31CzcREjrGsqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jul 2018 18:10:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/07/29/grammar-school-superhead-left-students-feeling-suicidal-policy/" target="_blank"&gt;Grammar school superhead left students feeling suicidal with policy of exclusion for getting B grades&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A “superhead” of an ultra-selective London grammar school left sixth-formers feeling suicidal and staff feeling bullied with a “constant emphasis” on perfect exam grades, a report has found. Aydin Önaç’s focus on his pupils at St Olave’ Grammar School in Orpington achieving A* grades and Oxbridge admissions left one student feeling he “might as well kill himself” after his offer of a place in Year 13 was withdrawn when he missed the three-Bs target in Year 12 exams. A report by Bromley Borough Council has concluded that 66-year-old Mr Önaç, who resigned from his £200,000-a-year post last ye...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>‘Love Island’ is more lucrative option than Oxbridge - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/17d9dd5c-90c3-11e8-bb8f-a6a2f7bca546</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBLd0GhtGVgTNwXYwHO0_swqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtt6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 13:44:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/17d9dd5c-90c3-11e8-bb8f-a6a2f7bca546" target="_blank"&gt;‘Love Island’ is more lucrative option than Oxbridge&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Forget the struggles of completing an Oxbridge degree — a group of economists have calculated that appearing as a contestant on TV show Love Island for eight weeks is likely to net you more money over the course of your life than three years at Oxford or Cambridge university. Analysis by Frontier Economics, an economic consultancy, estimated that someone who appears on the show could expect to earn £1.1m from subsequent sponsorship and appearance fees compared with a lifetime average return of £815,000 from completing an undergraduate degree at Oxbridge. With the hit ITV2 show, featuring su...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>DeepMind Is Giving Cambridge Money To Hire Staff - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/samshead/2018/07/25/deepmind-is-giving-cambridge-uni-money-to-hire-staff/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFdFFfGG5ANKhTrI5F188BAqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2018 09:58:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/samshead/2018/07/25/deepmind-is-giving-cambridge-uni-money-to-hire-staff/" target="_blank"&gt;DeepMind Is Giving Cambridge Money To Hire Staff&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cyclists and pedestrians move along Trinity Street past St Johns College, part of the University of Cambridge in Cambridge, U.K., on Sunday, Oct. 5, 2014. As the U.K. government cuts funding for universities, Cambridge’s colleges are becoming increasingly entrepreneurial about making money. Photographer: Peter Kindersley/Bloomberg DeepMind, a Google-owned lab that is at the front of the AI race, is gifting the University of Cambridge an undisclosed sum to appoint a “DeepMind Chair of Machine Learning”. The donation comes after DeepMind and other tech companies have been criticised for poach...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>University staff should go to mosques and working class youth clubs to improve campus diversity, says watchdog - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/education/education-news/university-mosques-diversity-uk-office-for-students-michael-barber-a8444461.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAQBWEPQRPGgK3RbqGbpxNcqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jul 2018 15:09:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/education/education-news/university-mosques-diversity-uk-office-for-students-michael-barber-a8444461.html" target="_blank"&gt;University staff should go to mosques and working class youth clubs to improve campus diversity, says watchdog&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;UK university staff should consider spending time in mosques and youth centres across the country to boost the number of students from minority groups, the higher education regulator has said. Sir Michael Barber, chair of the Office for Students (OfS), has accused UK universities of “passively waiting” for underrepresented students to apply, instead of seeking them out. Speaking to The Independent in an exclusive interview,Sir Michael said American universities were more active in their efforts to reach students from ethnic minorities and disadvantaged backgrounds than institutions in the U...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Oxbridge Shows The Folly Of Scrapping Affirmative Action - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/nickmorrison/2018/07/04/oxbridge-shows-the-folly-of-scrapping-affirmative-action/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF2VBcSG5Tir3YTs6y_Sr5oqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMKGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2018 17:20:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/nickmorrison/2018/07/04/oxbridge-shows-the-folly-of-scrapping-affirmative-action/" target="_blank"&gt;Oxbridge Shows The Folly Of Scrapping Affirmative Action&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A third of Oxford’s colleges admitted three or fewer black students over the last three years (Photo by: Loop Images/UIG via Getty Images) The Trump administration appears on the verge of rolling back affirmative action policies in U.S. higher education, but the lack of diversity at Oxford and Cambridge shows only too well what happens when universities are left to their own devices. Guidelines issued under President Obama aimed to promote diversity on campus through measures including admission preference for students from certain schools and including race as a factor in admissions proced...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>University league tables fuel a toxic undercurrent of snobbery - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/education/2018/07/04/university-league-tables-fuel-toxic-undercurrent-snobbery/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFuH45-yyyBreRLrR7kmkV4qFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCA8LkF</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2018 17:50:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/education/2018/07/04/university-league-tables-fuel-toxic-undercurrent-snobbery/" target="_blank"&gt;University league tables fuel a toxic undercurrent of snobbery&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;We hate them yet we find ourselves trusting them. League tables are arbitrary and divisive in broader debates about higher education reform. Why, then, do we give them so much credibility? What teachers don't talk about is the subtle undercurrent of toxic elitism that these meaningless tables fuel. This snobbery damaged me last summer as it will thousands of students and parents this August. League tables have reigned over our higher education sector for long enough. The process of choosing a university isn’t easy for us students and our families. That’s the point – government policy has fo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>How to write a great Ucas personal statement for university - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/education/0/how-to-write-a-great-ucas-personal-statement-for-university/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDT17Fr5uDi1uFoy2R4ScZsqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCA8LkF</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2018 14:04:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/education/0/how-to-write-a-great-ucas-personal-statement-for-university/" target="_blank"&gt;How to write a great Ucas personal statement for university&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The secret to getting ahead is getting started'. Whether, the American writer Mark Twain said this or not is up for debate. What is not up for debate, however, is the truth behind the expression, especially when it comes to personal statement writing. The Ucas deadline is Saturday June 30 at 6pm – this means students applying for a full-time degree at university or college starting this September must submit their applications before then. If you still haven't started, don't worry. To start with, it’s a good idea to get your head around the various aspects of the application that you will n...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Cambridge University has a problem with race. Now it must admit it - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/jun/26/cambridge-university-problem-race-priyamvada-gopal</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG-Qyg3U3bLd8FWWq8a0A7cqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 11:03:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/jun/26/cambridge-university-problem-race-priyamvada-gopal" target="_blank"&gt;Cambridge University has a problem with race. Now it must admit it&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Cambridge University academic has said she will no longer teach at one of its colleges because, she says, its porters have mistreated her. Dr Priyamvada Gopal said the King’s College porters treat her differently because of her race, and that ethnic minority students have also been discriminated against. Predictably, Gopal’s act of protest has been met with backlash. Virginia Blackburn, in the Daily Express, said: “What is really going on here is an almighty case of ego and self-importance, which is what usually lies behind the spurious claims of offence.” (Gopal had asked that the porter...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Where’s best for an ambitious young person: Love Island or Oxbridge? - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/tv-and-radio/shortcuts/2018/jun/06/wheres-best-for-an-ambitious-young-person-love-island-or-oxbridge</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJqzrfxcmW03jDxwo-lfKNkqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCOvRU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 15:32:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/tv-and-radio/shortcuts/2018/jun/06/wheres-best-for-an-ambitious-young-person-love-island-or-oxbridge" target="_blank"&gt;Where’s best for an ambitious young person: Love Island or Oxbridge?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is fierce debate doing the rounds online (when is there not?) about what it means that more people applied to appear on ITV2 reality show Love Island than to study at Oxbridge universities. The programme’s production team said that more than 85,000 people wanted to find love on an island this year (is Britain not good enough for these would-be Casanovas?), while 23,521 “domiciled” British citizens applied to Oxford or Cambridge in 2017. But which will stand you in better stead: Love Island or Oxbridge? Earning potential A 2015 study found that, over a lifetime, Oxbridge graduates earn...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>End-of-term ‘trashing’: where's the harm in Oxford students letting off a little steam? - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/education/2018/06/13/end-of-term-trashing-harm-oxford-students-letting-little-steam/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN7J5bna_RSN_X0mrcEAa10qFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCA8LkF</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/education/2018/06/13/end-of-term-trashing-harm-oxford-students-letting-little-steam/" target="_blank"&gt;End-of-term ‘trashing’: where's the harm in Oxford students letting off a little steam?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;When, in the summers of the 1970s, a small group of Oxford University students decided to celebrate the end of their exams by pouring champagne over their friends, they probably didn’t think their particular method of hijinks would catch on. But almost half a century later, hundreds of Oxford students emerged from their final exams this week to be doused in alcohol, whipped cream and confetti as part of the end-of-term tradition now known as ‘trashing’. Like many aspects of life at Britain’s ancient universities, graduates streaming out of 19th century exam halls in uniforms designed in 163...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Why the Love Island v Oxbridge statistic doesn't prove much - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/tv-and-radio/2018/jun/05/love-island-oxbridge-university-applications-misleading-statistic-twitter</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHo9K9vsWiGwiIsrLbDqp48qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCOvRU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2018 15:43:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/tv-and-radio/2018/jun/05/love-island-oxbridge-university-applications-misleading-statistic-twitter" target="_blank"&gt;Why the Love Island v Oxbridge statistic doesn't prove much&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;How does the number of people applying to be on Love Island compare with that of people applying for Britain’s elite universities, and what does the comparison tell us about the state of the nation? Well, quite a lot, if you listen to some Twitter pundits aghast at the widely shared statistic that far more of the country’s young people wanted to be on a reality TV show than get into Oxford or Cambridge. But are the numbers all they seem? Aside from attempting to compare very different things, the figures don’t actually show what some of the tweets seem to be aiming to prove: that young peop...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>The number of black students at Oxford is far from ideal - but it is making progress - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/education/2018/06/07/number-black-students-oxford-far-ideal-making-progress/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEDhzo3zZNGh7Emtx1tEqRsqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCA8LkF</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 18:14:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/education/2018/06/07/number-black-students-oxford-far-ideal-making-progress/" target="_blank"&gt;The number of black students at Oxford is far from ideal - but it is making progress&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lewis Iwu was the first black president of the Oxford University Students Union, the former director of the of the Fair Education Alliance and is a director at the consultancy Finsbury. It’s hard to look the data released by Oxford last month and conclude that the representation of black students at the university is anywhere near ideal. There are Oxbridge colleges that have failed to admit a single black British student in recent years. However, it’s wrong to suggest that change isn’t happening. The university has announced an increase to next year’s access programme by 50 percent. In 201...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Universities that fail to improve student diversity could have tuition fees cut, regulator warns - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/education/education-news/universities-student-diversity-tuition-fees-cut-michael-barber-ofs-regulator-a8387876.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIkJUT06JoHHZ9nJWx8GctcqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 18:51:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/education/education-news/universities-student-diversity-tuition-fees-cut-michael-barber-ofs-regulator-a8387876.html" target="_blank"&gt;Universities that fail to improve student diversity could have tuition fees cut, regulator warns&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Universities that fail to improve student diversity could have their tuition fees cut by a third, the new university regulator has warned after Oxford and Cambridge were in the spotlight over admissions. Sir Michael Barber, chair of the Office for Students, said he is “interested in results, not just plans” in boosting student diversity at the most selective institutions in the UK. His comments come after the two prestigious universities released admissions data showing that some Oxbridge colleges had admitted no black British students in recent years. - Read more Oxbridge’s lack of diversi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>'Love Island': Someone Pointed Out More People Apply For The Show Than Oxbridge And Twitter Had The Best Responses - HuffPost UK</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.co.uk/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOenqZqbl1fW3LXPwCMR4uoqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowmdW_BzCbhUcw-vd4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2018 16:46:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.co.uk/" target="_blank"&gt;'Love Island': Someone Pointed Out More People Apply For The Show Than Oxbridge And Twitter Had The Best Responses&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost UK&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;‘Love Island’ splits people into several camps - those who love it, those who hate it, and those who try to demean those who enjoy it or appear on it. And as the new series kicked off on Monday night, there were some in the latter camp who tried their best to hamper everyone’s enjoyment. Several people on Twitter were quick to point out that more people apply to be on ‘Love Island’ than apply to go to Oxford or Cambridge University. A reminder that more people applied for Love Island this year than Oxford/Cambridge University. — Tina Daheley (@TinaDaheley) June 4, 2018 While the stat is tru...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.co.uk">HuffPost UK</source></item><item><title>Oxbridge's Diversity Failure Is 'Staggering', Says Universities Minister - HuffPost UK</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.co.uk/entry/oxbridge-universities-minister_uk_5b177be6e4b0599bc6de2ea7</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM1aHm6SDiXoHr4NGVqmf2YqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowmdW_BzCbhUcwuqRp</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 06:26:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.co.uk/entry/oxbridge-universities-minister_uk_5b177be6e4b0599bc6de2ea7" target="_blank"&gt;Oxbridge's Diversity Failure Is 'Staggering', Says Universities Minister&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost UK&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Universities Minister has criticised Oxford and Cambridge for failing to enrol sufficient students who are black or from less privileged backgrounds, saying the situation is “staggering”. Sam Gyimah said the elite universities had not done enough, and they should “take into account a broad range of factors” rather than just academic results in order to get more diverse intakes. Gyimah, who is black and studied at Oxford, told The Daily Telegraph: “It is staggering that we have the best minds in our universities and we still do not know what the best way is when it comes to applications....&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.co.uk">HuffPost UK</source></item><item><title>Cambridge University says it cannot do more to admit black British students 'on its own' - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/education/education-news/cambridge-university-student-diversity-colleges-black-applicants-oxbridge-a8382136.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC6j7p2cJJZxQmMaOPKmIvkqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 16:10:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/education/education-news/cambridge-university-student-diversity-colleges-black-applicants-oxbridge-a8382136.html" target="_blank"&gt;Cambridge University says it cannot do more to admit black British students 'on its own'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The University of Cambridge has said it needs support from schools and parents to boost diversity after data showed some of its colleges admitted no black British students over five years. Six of Cambridge’s 29 undergraduate colleges admitted fewer than 10 British black or mixed white and black students between 2012 and 2016, a Freedom of Information (FoI) request by the Financial Times revealed. St Edmund's College failed to make any offers to more than 30 black applicants over the period, meanwhile Hughes Hall received 74 applications and only made between five and seven offers. - Read mo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Oxbridge owns a huge amount of land. But that's the tip of the iceberg - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/may/31/oxbridge-land-monopoly-universities-ownership-inequalities</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP529aWdj_O0c78bniwN21kqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTC9vBU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 11:00:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/may/31/oxbridge-land-monopoly-universities-ownership-inequalities" target="_blank"&gt;Oxbridge owns a huge amount of land. But that's the tip of the iceberg&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s often said that you can walk from Oxford to Cambridge without leaving land owned by the colleges. That’s almost certainly a myth. But as the Guardian’s recent investigation has revealed, they sure own one hell of a lot of land. England is owned by a tiny number of people and organisations – and the Oxbridge colleges, with their 126,000 acres of land and property portfolios worth some £3.5bn, are among the largest institutional landowners. The Guardian’s analysis is the most comprehensive since 1873. But why has it taken so long to find out? Land ownership remains one of England’s darke...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Oxford and Cambridge’s failure to take in more black and disadvantaged students is ‘staggering’, says universities minister - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/education/education-news/oxford-cambridge-university-black-disadvantaged-students-admissions-diversity-sam-gyimah-a8385456.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAE8fYRwzYGUIQApyzPjfHoqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 12:21:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/education/education-news/oxford-cambridge-university-black-disadvantaged-students-admissions-diversity-sam-gyimah-a8385456.html" target="_blank"&gt;Oxford and Cambridge’s failure to take in more black and disadvantaged students is ‘staggering’, says universities minister&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oxford and Cambridge's failure to take in more students who are black or from less privileged backgrounds is "staggering", the universities minister has said. Sam Gyimah criticised the elite institutions for not doing enough and warned that they could be fined by the new higher education regulator if they do not meet admissions targets. Mr Gyimah, an Oxford graduate himself, said the universities should not just focus on academic results during their admissions process to ensure they achieve more diverse intakes. - Read more Cambridge: We can't do more to admit black British students on our...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Six Cambridge colleges admitted fewer than ten black British students in five years - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/06/03/six-cambridge-colleges-admitted-fewer-ten-black-british-students/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMoHBOJ_owxxPBHrss2ZHKQqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2018 22:46:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/06/03/six-cambridge-colleges-admitted-fewer-ten-black-british-students/" target="_blank"&gt;Six Cambridge colleges admitted fewer than ten black British students in five years&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Six of Cambridge University’s colleges admitted fewer than ten black British students in five years, and some admitted none at all in some years, new data has shown. The data, obtained under the Freedom of Information Act by the Financial Times, comes after the revelation last month that one in four Oxford colleges did not admit a single black British student between 2015 and 2017. Cambridge University said that it cannot change diversity “on its own” and called for parents and schools to help boost the number of underrepresented minorities applying to its colleges. St Edmund’s College, Cam...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Elite universities improve teaching scores after requesting to be judged again in government rankings - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/education/education-news/university-teaching-scores-russell-group-improvements-government-rankings-tef-a8386321.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAaBqKcQD8SmUtdSy-1UfLEqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 15:58:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/education/education-news/university-teaching-scores-russell-group-improvements-government-rankings-tef-a8386321.html" target="_blank"&gt;Elite universities improve teaching scores after requesting to be judged again in government rankings&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some of the UK’s most prestigious universities have improved their scores for teaching standards after they requested to be judged again in official rankings. Four Russell Group institutions – the most selective in the UK - have seen a boost to their ratings in the Teaching Excellence Framework (TEF) after they resubmitted applications. It comes after more than half of the group of universities (13 out of 21) were not given a gold rating last year. Three were given a bronze award, which is the lowest rating for teaching. - Read more Oxbridge’s lack of diversity is ‘staggering', minister say...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item></channel></rss>