<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Freddie Scappaticci - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIggKIhxDQkFTRHdvSkwyMHZNRFl6Y21oekVnSmxiaWdBUAE?hl=en-GB&amp;gl=GB&amp;ceid=GB:en</link><language>en-GB</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 11:06:37 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>'British IRA informer Stakeknife' spared jail after extreme pornography conviction - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/12/05/man-widely-named-stakeknife-armys-ira-informer-guilty-extreme/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">52780126892838</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 10:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/12/05/man-widely-named-stakeknife-armys-ira-informer-guilty-extreme/" target="_blank"&gt;'British IRA informer Stakeknife' spared jail after extreme pornography conviction&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2018/dec/05/stakeknife-informant-freddie-scappaticci-pleads-guilty-to-pornography-charges" target="_blank"&gt;‘Stakeknife informant' pleads guilty to pornography charges&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/stories/CAAqOQgKIjNDQklTSURvSmMzUnZjbmt0TXpZd1NoTUtFUWltNXR1bGpZQU1FY0VPRXBlNTh3UmxLQUFQAQ?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;View full coverage on Google News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Police 'failed to investigate 18 murders in Northern Ireland to protect IRA mole' - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/crime/stakeknife-ira-mole-murders-not-investigated-by-northern-ireland-police-a7677361.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPRMObURKvV4ToBr9BRrfskqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2017 23:08:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/crime/stakeknife-ira-mole-murders-not-investigated-by-northern-ireland-police-a7677361.html" target="_blank"&gt;Police 'failed to investigate 18 murders in Northern Ireland to protect IRA mole'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Police failed to properly investigate the murders of more than a dozen people during the Troubles in Northern Ireland to prevent the identity of a key agent from being revealed, according to a report. Officers covered up a British spy’s alleged links to as many as 18 murders to prevent a mole known as StakeKnife being outed to the IRA, an investigation by the BBC claims to have found. An on-going criminal inquiry named Operation Kenova has been launched to probe whether StakeKnife’s fellow spies were sacrificed so that he could continue as a double agent. However, research by BBC Panorama s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Informant 'killed by IRA despite warning from British spy' - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/04/10/informant-killed-ira-despite-warning-british-spy/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP7hqIYjDTQFx29kme645l4qFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2017 23:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/04/10/informant-killed-ira-despite-warning-british-spy/" target="_blank"&gt;Informant 'killed by IRA despite warning from British spy'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A police informant working in Northern Ireland may have been "allowed to die" to avoid blowing the cover of another spy, investigators said. Joe Fenton was secretly providing information to the Royal Ulster Constabulary's special branch and was suspected by the armed group of being an informer. Bedfordshire Police Chief Constable Jon Boutcher is investigating the high-ranking Army mole, Stakeknife, who led the republican organisation's "nutting squad" internal security unit which interrogated and murdered suspected spies. His team is probing more than 50 murders and the BBC's Panorama links...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Stakeknife: double agent in IRA 'was given alibi by senior British officials' - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2017/apr/11/stakeknife-double-agent-in-ira-was-given-alibi-by-senior-british-officials</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBn8OKu_Loju_D37G99IVBwqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 05:02:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2017/apr/11/stakeknife-double-agent-in-ira-was-given-alibi-by-senior-british-officials" target="_blank"&gt;Stakeknife: double agent in IRA 'was given alibi by senior British officials'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of Britain’s most important agents inside the IRA has been linked to 18 murders and was provided with an alibi by a senior police officer to avoid getting him arrested during the Troubles, it has emerged. Related: Army whistleblower to testify on IRA double agent Stakeknife The Guardian can also reveal that the informer codenamed “Stakeknife” reported directly to the late Martin McGuinness in the 1980s and 90s when the man who would become Northern Ireland’s deputy first minister was the IRA’s northern commander and army council member. Stakeknife, whose real name is believed to be Fred...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Stakeknife could face perjury charges, says senior police officer - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2017/aug/21/stakeknife-could-face-perjury-charges-says-senior-police-officer</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFSrXc9knOzmtlgAn65ITyoqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2017 15:19:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2017/aug/21/stakeknife-could-face-perjury-charges-says-senior-police-officer" target="_blank"&gt;Stakeknife could face perjury charges, says senior police officer&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;An alleged British secret agent in the IRA who is accused of being linked to at least 20 murders while working for military intelligence could be charged with perjury for denying in court he was a spy, a senior UK police officer has told the Guardian. Stakeknife, whose real name is believed to be Freddie Scappaticci, was the IRA’s chief spy catcher and received £80,000 each year as one of Britain’s most important agents within the terror group. It is alleged that his army and police handlers turned a blind eye to murders in order to promote their agent inside the IRA’s ranks. Police are now...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Murdoch's UK paper arm admits computer hacking, fuelling criticism of Sky takeover - Reuters UK</title><link>https://uk.reuters.com/article/us-sky-m-a-fox-hack/murdochs-uk-paper-arm-admits-computer-hacking-fuelling-criticism-of-sky-takeover-idUKKBN1CB25F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDDxEXWUeMl9ECPaQqOvDMIqGAgEKg8IACoHCAow3MukCjD92Xcwy4jqAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 16:35:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://uk.reuters.com/article/us-sky-m-a-fox-hack/murdochs-uk-paper-arm-admits-computer-hacking-fuelling-criticism-of-sky-takeover-idUKKBN1CB25F" target="_blank"&gt;Murdoch's UK paper arm admits computer hacking, fuelling criticism of Sky takeover&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters UK&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;LONDON (Reuters) - Rupert Murdoch's British newspaper group said on Friday one of its titles had hacked the computer of a former intelligence officer, an admission which critics said showed why his takeover of European broadcaster Sky (SKYB.L: Quote, Profile, Research) should be blocked. In a hearing at London's High Court, Murdoch's News Group Newspapers (NWSA.O: Quote, Profile, Research) admitted "vicarious liability" for the hacking of computers belonging to Ian Hurst, who worked for British military intelligence. The case comes a month after Britain's media minister said regulators shou...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://uk.reuters.com">Reuters UK</source></item><item><title>Columba McVeigh: fresh search for remains of IRA victim - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2018/sep/17/columba-mcveigh-fresh-search-for-remains-ira-victim</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHR74EgWzu0wZCOQsYdCEz0qFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDJ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 17:49:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2018/sep/17/columba-mcveigh-fresh-search-for-remains-ira-victim" target="_blank"&gt;Columba McVeigh: fresh search for remains of IRA victim&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Forensic archaeologists have launched a fresh attempt to find the remains of a Northern Ireland teenager who was abducted, murdered and secretly buried by the IRA in 1975. A team of contractors on Monday started combing an acre of Braggan bog, near Emyvale in County Monaghan, in the Republic of Ireland. The bog is believed to hold the body of Columba McVeigh, who was 19 when the IRA killed him on suspicion of working as an informer for the security forces at the height of the Troubles. He was one of 16 people known as “the disappeared” who vanished after being abducted, mainly by IRA intern...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>RUC told to put intelligence before arrests, reveals secret MI5 report - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2018/jun/26/special-branch-ruc-put-evidence-before-arrest-walker-mi5-report-northern-ireland</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIjeLv0NZNC4FQ4BiSyJQoQqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDJ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 10:28:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2018/jun/26/special-branch-ruc-put-evidence-before-arrest-walker-mi5-report-northern-ireland" target="_blank"&gt;RUC told to put intelligence before arrests, reveals secret MI5 report&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A secret MI5 report that resulted in Northern Ireland’s police covertly prioritising intelligence-gathering over fighting crime has been made public after almost 40 years. The report resulted in detectives of the Royal Ulster Constabulary (RUC) – now the Police Service of Northern Ireland (PSNI) – being ordered never to arrest a suspected terrorist without consulting the force’s intelligence-gathering section. Detectives were also told that anyone who was arrested could be recruited as an agent rather than charged with a criminal offence. As a consequence, a number of British agents are now...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>How many murders can a police informer get away with? - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/news/2018/mar/08/how-many-murders-can-a-police-informer-get-away-with</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBsiDha8WotGeIm4TJHe7zUqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Mar 2018 06:00:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/news/2018/mar/08/how-many-murders-can-a-police-informer-get-away-with" target="_blank"&gt;How many murders can a police informer get away with?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;One day earlier this year, two prison officers led a portly, middle-aged man into court and instructed him to sit in the dock. He was wearing an ill-fitting grey suit and a grey tie; his hair was grey, and so too were his handcuffs. The only flash of colour came from his florid and slightly sagging face. In the public gallery, 10 feet behind the dock, a handful of people sat and stared at the back of the man’s red neck. Outside, 30 armed police officers were standing guard. In the dock, Gary Haggarty sat and listened for almost an hour and a half as the judge explained the sentence he was a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Army spy 'Stakeknife' who was head of IRA's internal security is arrested in investigation over murders - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/01/30/army-spy-stakeknife-head-iras-internal-security-arrested-investigation/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEARnT0qmXTVjzic0QhkLoWwqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2018 20:37:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/01/30/army-spy-stakeknife-head-iras-internal-security-arrested-investigation/" target="_blank"&gt;Army spy 'Stakeknife' who was head of IRA's internal security is arrested in investigation over murders&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A man accused of being the high-level Army mole inside the IRA codenamed Stakeknife has been arrested by police investigating dozens of Troubles-era murders. Fred Scappaticci, who has been widely identified as the notorious agent, was reportedly arrested by police “in connection with the investigation into allegations of murder, kidnap and torture”. Stakeknife reputedly led the republican organisation's "nutting squad", an internal security unit which brutally interrogated and murdered suspected spies during the Troubles. Scappaticci was outed as Stakeknife in 2003, following an investigati...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>IRA informer ‘Stakeknife’ arrested in murder investigation - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2018/jan/30/ira-informer-stakeknife-arrested-in-investigation</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEQbKEPuQ1HHOhE53ARZ1RsqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2018 17:12:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2018/jan/30/ira-informer-stakeknife-arrested-in-investigation" target="_blank"&gt;IRA informer ‘Stakeknife’ arrested in murder investigation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of Britain’s most important agents inside the IRA, “Stakeknife”, has been arrested by detectives investigating 18 murders during the Northern Ireland Troubles. Republican and security sources in Belfast confirmed on Tuesday that a 72-year-old man detained by police officers working on Operation Kenova was Freddie Scappaticci. Accused of being the IRA’s chief spycatcher, the Belfast man is accused of being a double agent who was working for the security forces while overseeing the murder of informers within the republican movement. A spokesperson for Operation Kenova said the 72-year-old...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Police question IRA informer 'Stakeknife' over UVF murder - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2018/jan/31/police-question-ira-informer-stakeknife-over-uvf</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELMpMVcpT5s1_3rbiMyGt74qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2018 14:35:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2018/jan/31/police-question-ira-informer-stakeknife-over-uvf" target="_blank"&gt;Police question IRA informer 'Stakeknife' over UVF murder&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Belfast man accused of being Britain’s most important agent inside the IRA is being questioned about the murder of a prominent Ulster loyalist terrorist, it has emerged. Detectives were questioning Freddie Scappaticci, 72, who is alleged to have been the British spy known as “Stakeknife” who operated within the IRA for 25 years. He was arrested on Tuesday by officers working on Operation Kenova – a multimillion-pound inquiry into the activities of “Stakeknife” – on suspicion of a number of offences. It is also investigating claims that his British handlers allowed the informer to be invol...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>StakeKnife: 'IRA informer' Fred Scappaticci arrested over dozens of murders - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/crime/stakeknife-ira-murder-arrest-troubles-northern-ireland-police-informer-a8186041.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENt_YLF1ZtIgUHxCWRc9J9sqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2018 18:41:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/crime/stakeknife-ira-murder-arrest-troubles-northern-ireland-police-informer-a8186041.html" target="_blank"&gt;StakeKnife: 'IRA informer' Fred Scappaticci arrested over dozens of murders&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The man who is said to have been the most successful British spy inside the IRA for more than a quarter of a century is believed to have been arrested over his alleged involvement in dozens of killings. Fred Scappaticci, codenamed Stakeknife, from Belfast, was detained in England following an investigation which has been going on for the last 18 months. Mr Scappaticci, 72, whose grandfather went to Ulster from Italy, is said to have infiltrated the highest echelons of the Provisionals and ended up running its feared internal security unit, known as the “Nutting Squad”. He was such a valuabl...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item></channel></rss>