<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Red Nose Day Actually - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqKAgKIiJDQkFTRXdvTkwyY3ZNVEZuT0Roa056RmpNQklDWlc0b0FBUAE?hl=en-GB&amp;gl=GB&amp;ceid=GB:en</link><language>en-GB</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 11:50:10 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Four Weddings and a Funeral star Hugh Grant returning for Red Nose Day sequel - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/films/news/four-weddings-and-a-funeral-2-sequel-red-nose-day-special-hugh-grant-richard-curtis-a8668661.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIi49m6BBE-X10zpx2oMhlwqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 14:31:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/films/news/four-weddings-and-a-funeral-2-sequel-red-nose-day-special-hugh-grant-richard-curtis-a8668661.html" target="_blank"&gt;Four Weddings and a Funeral star Hugh Grant returning for Red Nose Day sequel&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The cast of British classic Four Weddings and a Funeral are reuniting for a follow-up short film, set 25 years after the original. Hugh Grant, Andie McDowell and Kristin Scott Thomas are set to appear in the sequel which is being filmed by original director Mike Newell for Red Nose Day. John Hannah, Rowan Atkinson and Anna Chancellor will also return. Produced by Richard Curtis, it'll be titled One Red Nose Day and a Wedding. The project, which was announced on Twitter by producer and Curtis's wife Emma Freud, will be similar in vein to the 2017 short film Red Nose Day Actually which served...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>'Four Weddings And A Funeral' Gets A Sequel In Aid Of Comic Relief - HuffPost UK</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.co.uk/entry/four-weddings-and-a-funeral-comic-relief-sequel_uk_5c07ee1ce4b0680a7ecb5343</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMu5rJ0SYYdjo5JloVnecmAqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowmdW_BzCbhUcw-vd4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 16:21:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.co.uk/entry/four-weddings-and-a-funeral-comic-relief-sequel_uk_5c07ee1ce4b0680a7ecb5343" target="_blank"&gt;'Four Weddings And A Funeral' Gets A Sequel In Aid Of Comic Relief&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost UK&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;‘Four Weddings And A Funeral’ is set for a Comic Relief sequel, which will reunite the original film’s cast after 25 years. Hugh Grant, Andie MacDowell, Kristin Scott Thomas, John Hannah, Rowan Atkinson and Anna Chancellor will all come together in 2019 for ‘One Red Nose Day And A Wedding’. The script has been penned by ‘Four Weddings’ screenwriter Richard Curtis, the co-creator of Comic Relief, and will pick up 25 years on from where we last saw the characters. Richard said in a statement: “We’re all definitely older – I suspect no wiser. It’s been really enjoyable working out what’s happe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.co.uk">HuffPost UK</source></item><item><title>Four Weddings and a Funeral sequel set for Red Nose Day - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/film/2018/dec/05/four-weddings-and-a-funeral-sequel-set-for-red-nose-day</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBglFcJByCX6xunOjt-BTDkqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 14:58:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/film/2018/dec/05/four-weddings-and-a-funeral-sequel-set-for-red-nose-day" target="_blank"&gt;Four Weddings and a Funeral sequel set for Red Nose Day&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hugh Grant, Andie MacDowell, Kristin Scott Thomas and Rowan Atkinson are among the stars confirmed to take part in a short Four Weddings and a Funeral sequel, to be screened in the UK on Red Nose Day 2019. The film, which will be directed by the original’s Mike Newell, and scripted by original screenwriter Richard Curtis, takes place 25 years after the events of the original and features yet more nuptials. Says Curtis: “We’re all definitely older – I suspect no wiser. It’s been really enjoyable working out what’s happened to all the characters – and now they get back together for the fifth ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>'Four Weddings And A Funeral' Gets A Short Sequel For Red Nose Day - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/four-weddings-and-a-funeral-sequel-red-nose-day_us_5c08189ee4b0bf813ef3885b</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF-Py29jVQPusjgf_OG25HgqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 20:39:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/four-weddings-and-a-funeral-sequel-red-nose-day_us_5c08189ee4b0bf813ef3885b" target="_blank"&gt;'Four Weddings And A Funeral' Gets A Short Sequel For Red Nose Day&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ready for “Four Weddings and a Funeral” and another wedding? A minisequel to the 1994 hit movie will be walking down the aisle for 2019′s Red Nose Day ― and will feature a fifth wedding, The Hollywood Reporter reported on Wednesday. The original cast of Hugh Grant, Andie MacDowell, Kristin Scott Thomas, John Hannah, Rowan Atkinson and others appear in the short film, which is already in production, the trade daily said. The original involved five milestone occasions while centering on Grant’s confirmed bachelor character, Charles, who falls for MacDowell’s Carrie. “We’re all definitely olde...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Hugh Grant fans being offered chance to win picnic with actor in Notting Hill - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/films/news/hugh-grant-notting-hill-picnic-fans-competition-win-red-nose-day-richard-curtis-a8325136.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF3iEJg-DYQX7wuFBbONzVAqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 10:39:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/films/news/hugh-grant-notting-hill-picnic-fans-competition-win-red-nose-day-richard-curtis-a8325136.html" target="_blank"&gt;Hugh Grant fans being offered chance to win picnic with actor in Notting Hill&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Film fans are being offered the chance to have lunch with Hugh Grant in Notting Hill. Broadcaster Emma Freud - wife of writer-director Richard Curtis - announced the Omaze-sponsored competition on social media which is running in line with Red Nose Day USA. The winner will be flown to London to meet Curtis, who wrote the 1999 romantic comedy, with whom they'll tour the film's famous sites including Portobello Road Market and William Thacker's bookshop before lunching with Grant himself for a picnic in the film's titular location. To top it off, the lucky winner will stay at The Ritz the ver...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Richard Curtis to create a Four Weddings and a Funeral TV series - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/tv/2017/11/02/richard-curtis-brings-four-weddings-funeral-tv/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPSCD7EL40K6NSAofQSSj3MqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTD51N8D</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2017 10:27:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/tv/2017/11/02/richard-curtis-brings-four-weddings-funeral-tv/" target="_blank"&gt;Richard Curtis to create a Four Weddings and a Funeral TV series&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Richard Curtis has signed on as executive producer to a TV series inspired by his film Four Weddings and a Funeral, which The Mindy Project's Mindy Kaling will write, Deadline Hollywood reports. The 1994 romantic comedy following Hugh Grant's Charles as he tries to find love was an unexpected hit, grossing over $200 million (£150 m) at the box office, and winning Grant a Best Actor award at the Golden Globes. It co-starred Andie MacDowell as his love interest, Carrie. American streaming service Hulu, which also produces the Mindy Project, will finance the series. As yet, no plans for a UK b...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item></channel></rss>