<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Department of Labor and Employment - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIggKIhxDQkFTRHdvSkwyMHZNRGRyZW5FMUVnSmxiaWdBUAE?hl=en-PH&amp;gl=PH&amp;ceid=PH:en</link><language>en-PH</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 12:20:17 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Over 1000 jobs open for persons with disabilities: DOLE - ABS-CBN News</title><link>https://news.abs-cbn.com/business/12/02/18/over-1000-jobs-open-for-persons-with-disabilities-dole</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiYWh0dHBzOi8vbmV3cy5hYnMtY2JuLmNvbS9idXNpbmVzcy8xMi8wMi8xOC9vdmVyLTEwMDAtam9icy1vcGVuLWZvci1wZXJzb25zLXdpdGgtZGlzYWJpbGl0aWVzLWRvbGXSAQA</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 07:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://news.abs-cbn.com/business/12/02/18/over-1000-jobs-open-for-persons-with-disabilities-dole" target="_blank"&gt;Over 1000 jobs open for persons with disabilities: DOLE&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABS-CBN News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Department of Labor and Employment (DOLE) said over 1000 jobs will be available for persons with disabilities in a job fair on Wednesday Dec.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://news.abs-cbn.com">ABS-CBN News</source><media:content url="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/proxy/z9BTAm10-nNEvy4pAVBppbFgaJLHURO2VQa892yFA7r8VunYvUZM8qj2jeKwrYBxUdIibkWgyjsrZzCw-NtGmzpOjztk0YKwdAaMbKBpsgzQVK7lnZrNSNOsIgAc5egKiT310NFozL3EyiWC-KQP6LYtdS2vWeuHAA=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Dole offers incentive to firms hiring PWDs - INQUIRER.net</title><link>https://newsinfo.inquirer.net/1060452/dole-offers-incentive-to-firms-hiring-pwds</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiUGh0dHBzOi8vbmV3c2luZm8uaW5xdWlyZXIubmV0LzEwNjA0NTIvZG9sZS1vZmZlcnMtaW5jZW50aXZlLXRvLWZpcm1zLWhpcmluZy1wd2Rz0gGiAWh0dHBzOi8vbmV3c2luZm8taW5xdWlyZXItbmV0LmNkbi5hbXBwcm9qZWN0Lm9yZy92L3MvbmV3c2luZm8uaW5xdWlyZXIubmV0LzEwNjA0NTIvZG9sZS1vZmZlcnMtaW5jZW50aXZlLXRvLWZpcm1zLWhpcmluZy1wd2RzL2FtcD9hbXBfanNfdj0wLjEjd2Vidmlldz0xJmNhcD1zd2lwZQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 21:20:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://newsinfo.inquirer.net/1060452/dole-offers-incentive-to-firms-hiring-pwds" target="_blank"&gt;Dole offers incentive to firms hiring PWDs&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;INQUIRER.net&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Secretary Silvestre Bello III of the Department of the Labor and Employment (Dole) said such companies would be granted a yearlong “immunity from ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://newsinfo.inquirer.net">INQUIRER.net</source></item><item><title>Capitol, Dole award P22.3M to Spes, Tupad beneficiaries - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1777061</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJIfvOkPwFGu1n51q-2EiNoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJmtnQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 14:52:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1777061" target="_blank"&gt;Capitol, Dole award P22.3M to Spes, Tupad beneficiaries&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE Provincial Government of Pampanga and the Department of Labor and Employment (Dole) awarded on Monday, December 3, a total of P22.3 million to ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Workers get additional pay on Dec. 8 holiday - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1777613</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE_tE5RatYqgFxcDLmxSGTYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJeunQM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 16:23:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1777613" target="_blank"&gt;Workers get additional pay on Dec. 8 holiday&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WORKERS nationwide are expected to receive an additional 30 percent of their hourly rate this Saturday after Malacañang declared Dec. 8 a special non-working holiday. According to the Catholic Church, Dec. 8 is the Feast of the Immaculate Conception of the Blessed Virgin Mary. The Department of Labor and Employment (Dole) 7 reminded employers who plan to allow their employees to work on Saturday to pay the additional rate entitled to them. But Dole 7 Director Johnson Cañete also reminded employees that if they don’t work on the special non-working holiday, they are not entitled to the 30 pe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Pangan: The proposed Trabaho Centers - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1777554</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFINU-IMHBqgwrw3KbLWy80qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJmtnQM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 14:43:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1777554" target="_blank"&gt;Pangan: The proposed Trabaho Centers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;IF THE Senate Bill No. 1278 or the proposed Trabaho Center in Schools Act will pass into law as sponsored by Senator Paolo “Bam” Aquino, public high schools and state universities and colleges will have job placement offices. As reported, “The primary aim of the bill is to help and properly guide students in choosing the career tracks that they intend to pursue and to aid in matching senior high school students with industry employment opportunities”. For the record, Public Employment Service Offices (PESOs) have been conducting, with monitoring by Dole, career guidance counselling for Seni...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Biz leader: Upgrading of Filipino workers needed amid mobilization of manpower - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1777109</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENVBkHH6EGa4oYKK4ZZXi-sqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMPetnQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 05:10:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1777109" target="_blank"&gt;Biz leader: Upgrading of Filipino workers needed amid mobilization of manpower&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A LOCAL business leader said there is a need to upgrade the Filipino workforce amid the growing trend on the mobilization of manpower, particularly foreign nationals going to the Philippines as employees. Frank Carbon, chief executive officer of Metro Bacolod Chamber of Commerce and Industry (MBCCI), said migration of workers signals globalization or integration among countries. Carbon said the Philippines has to prepare for this through one, scaling up the knowledge and skills of Filipino workers as well as those of future labor force. "The world is becoming smaller, the Philippines is bec...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>PWD job fair to offer 1,000 jobs - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1776830/Manila/Local-News/PWD-job-fair-to-offer-1000-jobs?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO3_7qOjQvJMwYgh0XWa8pEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKmgnQM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 10:47:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1776830/Manila/Local-News/PWD-job-fair-to-offer-1000-jobs?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;PWD job fair to offer 1,000 jobs&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MORE than 1,000 jobs are set to be offered by the Department of Labor and Employment (Dole) to qualified applicants during the job fair exclusively set for persons with disability (PWD) on December 5 at the Quezon City Hall. Dole said the day-long event, set in time for the 85th founding anniversary of the department, will offer job openings from different sectors. Job openings include those in the business process outsourcing, electronics, advertising, hotel, health and wellness, travel, media, logistics, manpower and security services, sales, property management, pharmaceutical, and memor...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>'Exodus' of Chinese workers in PH alarms local labor group - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1776217</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOETlA_w5BRT7tRDMpNgiiYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMPetnQM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 05:08:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1776217" target="_blank"&gt;'Exodus' of Chinese workers in PH alarms local labor group&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;LOCAL labor group General Alliance of Workers Associations (Gawa) is alarmed over the alleged "exodus" of Chinese workers in the Philippines as it deprives Filipino workers of the employment opportunities, its top official said. Wennie Sancho, secretary-general of Gawa, said on November 27 that they are calling concerned government agencies to crackdown these foreign-workers not only in Metro Manila but also in Western Visayas. Sancho said there are over 119,000 Chinese workers who were given an alien working permit since 2015 based on the data of Department of Labor and Employment (Dole). ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Interns undergo DOLE assessment - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1775766</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPadi_lXIN-QMKVtM-HNfoAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJmtnQM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2018 12:19:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1775766" target="_blank"&gt;Interns undergo DOLE assessment&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ABUCAY, Bataan -- Some 56 interns from different parts of Bataan province recently underwent an assessment under the Department of Labor and Employment’s (DOLE)’s Government Internship Program (GIP). The event, held at the Las Marianas Café, is the culminating activity for the youth interns as they concluded their stint as interns in government service. In addition, the event coincided with the labor agency’s observance of the Children’s Month Celebration anchoring the theme “Isulong Tamang Pag-aaruga Para sa Lahat ng Bata.” DOLE Central Luzon Director Zenaida Angara-Campita reported to Lab...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Senator questions gov't estimate of Chinese workers in PH - ABS CBN News</title><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG48ccyafXfkoU4a0jRyEC8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow8IjwCjDw4s8CMLb_ngM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 02:40:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABS CBN News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA -- The senator leading an inquiry into the influx of Chinese workers on Monday questioned the government's accounting of foreign workers in the country. Sen. Joel Villanueva, chairman of the Senate committee on labor, employment and human resources said based on what he saw, the number of Chinese workers could be more than the estimate provided by the labor department. Chinese nationals accounted for over 50,000 of the 115,000 Alien Employment Permits issued from 2015 to 2017, Labor Usec. Ciriaco Lagunsad told senators. "Personal ko hong nakita parang may people power ang China doon,...&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>50 Mabalacat vendors get P1-M livelihood aid - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1775322</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKbsOors5AcqMGEzQha_Wb0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJmtnQM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 12:38:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1775322" target="_blank"&gt;50 Mabalacat vendors get P1-M livelihood aid&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SOME 50 ambulant vendors from Mabalacat City, Pampanga recently received livelihood assistance amounting to P1 million from the Department of Labor and Employment (DOLE). The assistance was initiated by the City Government of Mabalacat, through its Public Employment Service Office (PESO), and the DOLE Pampanga Field Office. DOLE Central Luzon Director Zenaida Angara-Campita reported to Labor Secretary Silvestre Bello III that the livelihood assistance was in the form of Negosyo sa Kariton (Nego Kart) projects. “We have been handing out DOLE Nego Karts since 2009. In Central Luzon, we have e...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>DOLE releases P4.7-million livelihood aid - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1774867</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOjOpAmkt7wsLzLVtJG31AoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKeunQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 14:20:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1774867" target="_blank"&gt;DOLE releases P4.7-million livelihood aid&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SOME 500 Dabawenyos will benefit from the P4.7-million fund released by the Department of Labor and Employment (DOLE) to the City Government of Davao. A total of 200 beneficiaries will be listed under the DOLE Kabuhayan Starter Kit Program and another 300 beneficiaries will be under the Tulong Panghanapbuhay sa Ating Disadvantaged or Displaced Workers (Tupad) Program. “This fund is intended for the DOLE Kabuhayan Starter Kits Project which includes hair dressing, bread and pastries, food processing and welding and weaving,” Dole Davao City field office chief Erlinda Mamitag said during the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>DOLE 7 to probe coke, labor - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1774893</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDpMX5r9S4KHTZ9qtq0dgWUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJeunQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 15:18:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1774893" target="_blank"&gt;DOLE 7 to probe coke, labor&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;LABOR inspectors of the Department of Labor and Employment (Dole) 7 are looking into the reported dispute at the Coca-Cola FEMSA plant in Mandaue City. Dole 7 Director Johnson Cañete said they sent labor inspectors to the beverage plant to ask about the labor situation there following the picket of some workers last Friday night, which ended in the arrest and detention of three workers. Cañete said the report of their labor inspectors will be evaluated by the Labor Relations/Labor Standard Division of Dole 7. The Coca-Cola FEMSA Philippines on Monday, Nov. 19, clarified that the picket last...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Duterte wants government offices' 'active role' in anti-narcotics drive - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1774749/Manila/Local-News/Rodrigo-Duterte-wants-government-offices-active-role-in-anti-narcotics-drive?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMiKvSavOT2IJUPg6uGhsJsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKmgnQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 05:22:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1774749/Manila/Local-News/Rodrigo-Duterte-wants-government-offices-active-role-in-anti-narcotics-drive?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;Duterte wants government offices' 'active role' in anti-narcotics drive&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PRESIDENT Rodrigo Duterte has ordered all government offices, including government-owned or -controlled corporations (GOCCs) and state universities and colleges (SUCs), to "take an active role" in his administration's campaign against illegal narcotics trade. Duterte gave the directive through Memorandum Circular 53 inked by Executive Secretary Salvador Medialdea by authority of the President on November 12. A copy of the memorandum was released to the media on Monday, November 19. Under the memorandum, all government offices, agencies and instrumentalities, including GOCCs and SUCs, are ma...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Dole 7 launches search for best HR practices in Bohol - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1773467</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB8AhKOr6lULwh7Yi2smXpUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJeunQM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Nov 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1773467" target="_blank"&gt;Dole 7 launches search for best HR practices in Bohol&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE Best Human Resources (HR) practices of companies done beyond what the labor laws require deserve not only applause but also due recognition, said Department of Labor and Employment (Dole) 7 Director Johnson G. Cañete in a statement. Cañete said that Dole 7 will start recognizing companies demonstrating the best HR practices in Bohol, in coordination with the Tripartite Industrial Peace Council of Bohol (TIPC-Bohol). For the first time in the region, the TIPC-Bohol launched the Search for Best HR Practices, which is expected to get involvement and participation from the council’s member-...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>OWWA launches OFW e-card for easier access to gov't benefits - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/216038-owwa-launches-ofw-e-card-easier-access-government-benefits</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEsWjftcuEsbsVMeohR8wzEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 06:31:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/216038-owwa-launches-ofw-e-card-easier-access-government-benefits" target="_blank"&gt;OWWA launches OFW e-card for easier access to gov't benefits&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines (UPDATED) – The Overseas Workers Welfare Administration (OWWA) launched on Tuesday, November 6, its overseas Filipino worker (OFW) e-card, a membership card that provides easier access to government benefits. The e-card can be used for OWWA services such as welfare programs, scholarship applications, training programs, and other social benefits. To apply for such programs, OFWs only have to show their card or the digital copy of the card, which has a QR code that can be easily scanned to verify authenticity. The e-card reduces the number of documents needed when applying...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Orola asks Dole for livelihood support for farmers - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1772496</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAg0MWPYXEjOpWqG2MbR42sqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMPetnQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 08:05:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1772496" target="_blank"&gt;Orola asks Dole for livelihood support for farmers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BACOLOD City Councilor Bartolome Orola has asked the Department of Labor and Employment (DOLE) in Western Visayas for livelihood support to the farmers of Bacolod through its capacity-building services for livelihood program. Orola said DOLE’s livelihood enhancement program assists self-employed and unpaid family workers and make their existing livelihood undertakings grow into viable and sustainable businesses that will provide income at par with minimum wage earners. He added the Dole, through its provincial offices, provides services such as the acquisition of productive resources in the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Karlo Nograles named new Cabinet Secretary - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1772488/Manila/Local-News/Karlo-Nograles-named-new-Cabinet-Secretary?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBH2ytPdpGKr6Xf4CnA_kvwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKmgnQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 05:08:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1772488/Manila/Local-News/Karlo-Nograles-named-new-Cabinet-Secretary?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;Karlo Nograles named new Cabinet Secretary&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(UPDATED) - President Rodrigo Duterte has appointed Davao City First District Representative Karlo Alexei Nograles as the new Cabinet secretary, Malacañang announced on Monday, November 5. Presidential Spokesperson Salvador Panelo, in a briefing with Palace reporters, said Duterte picked Nograles as the next Cabinet Secretary "as early as two weeks ago." Nograles will take his oath as the new Cabinet Secretary on Monday afternoon at the Malacañan Palace, Panelo said. "Former congressman Karlo Nograles will be taking his oath of office this afternoon as Cabinet Secretary. He enjoys the trust...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Labor chief clarifies: No wage hike in NCR yet - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1771996/Manila/Local-News/Labor-chief-clarifies-No-wage-hike-in-National-Capital-Region-yet?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMZcbpKJuvbxSxHyMBBxy9kqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKmgnQM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 08:52:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1771996/Manila/Local-News/Labor-chief-clarifies-No-wage-hike-in-National-Capital-Region-yet?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;Labor chief clarifies: No wage hike in NCR yet&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE Department of Labor and Employment (DOLE) on Wednesday, October 31, belied claims made by both employers and employees that the National Capital Region (NCR) wage board has already granted a P25 pay increase to minimum wage earners. In an interview, DOLE Secretary Silvestre Bello III said there is no truth to claims made by both the Employers Confederation of the Philippines (ECOP) and the Trade Union Congress of the Philippines (TUCP). “I don’t think TUCP has the authority to make the announcement. It is only the regional wage board that can make its recommendation to the commission. S...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>OFW saved from UAE death row reunites with family in PH - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/215773-ofw-jennifer-dalquez-reunites-with-family-philippines-november-2018</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIgA_p5RgA8K9-9Qx3SWKO0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 02:34:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/215773-ofw-jennifer-dalquez-reunites-with-family-philippines-november-2018" target="_blank"&gt;OFW saved from UAE death row reunites with family in PH&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – After nearly 4 years in an Abu Dhabi prison in the United Arab Emirates (UAE), overseas Filipino worker Jennifer Dalquez was finally reunited with her family in Manila on Friday morning, November 2. The Department of Foreign Affairs (DFA) released photos of Dalquez’s emotional homecoming shortly after her arrival in Manila, where she was welcomed by her family. She arrived in a Philippine Airlines flight that also carried 86 undocumented Filipinos who availed themselves of the 3-month UAE amnesty program, the DFA said in a statement. Dalquez was sentenced to death for ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Duterte creates Philippine Anti-Illegal Drugs Strategy - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1771835/Manila/Local-News/Rodrigo-Duterte-creates-Philippine-Anti-Illegal-Drugs-Strategy?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF_Y5OvpqQunUyHd3mZcdMYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKmgnQM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 04:48:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1771835/Manila/Local-News/Rodrigo-Duterte-creates-Philippine-Anti-Illegal-Drugs-Strategy?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;Duterte creates Philippine Anti-Illegal Drugs Strategy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;AMID the government's relentless drive against illegal drugs, President Rodrigo Duterte has institutionalized the Philippine Anti-Illegal Drugs Strategy (Pads). Duterte signed on October 29 Executive Order (EO) 66, directing all government offices, department bureaus, agencies, and offices, including government-owned or -controlled corporations (GOCCs) and state universities and colleges (SUCs), to implement the Pads, in accordance with their respective mandates. EO 66 also encouraged non-government organizations, civil society organizations, and private institutions to actively support the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Labor department gives aid to 1,465 Kapampangans - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1770508</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDZvZ9NB1hOwdG6druMYIcAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJmtnQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 15:39:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1770508" target="_blank"&gt;Labor department gives aid to 1,465 Kapampangans&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A TOTAL of 1,465 Kapampangans recently benefitted from the P6 million worth of livelihood assistance given by Department of Labor and Employment (Dole)-Central Luzon under its Tulong Panghanapbuhay sa Ating Disadvantaged Workers (Tupad) program. All beneficiaries were tasked to perform social community works like de-clogging of canals, clearing of road debris, and basic repair and maintenance of common public infrastructure. Dole-Central Luzon director Zenaida Angara-Campita said the Tupad beneficiaries all came from the province’s calamity-stricken communities. “We have partnered with the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>156 hired on the spot in 2-day job fair - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1770925</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPhZ60l-5v_KWbBOOypTROcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJiunQM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 12:12:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1770925" target="_blank"&gt;156 hired on the spot in 2-day job fair&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A TOTAL of 156 applicants were hired on the spot (Hots) while 751 qualified who are subject for final review and examination in the recently-held two-day Hermosa Job Fair in Zamboanga City. The job fair, which was part of the Zamboanga Hermosa Festival, was held from October 19 to 20 at the KCC Mall de Zamboanga. Maria Socorro Rojas, Public Employment Service Office (Peso), said that 103 of the 156 Hots were hired on the first day while the remaining 53 on the second day of the job fair. Rojas, who is also the City Social Welfare and Development Office (CSWDO) officer, said that 556 of the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Capitol’s Collective Negotiation Agreement inked - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1769950</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPVqc-36mwPe1fONSONSmMIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMOidnQM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 10:42:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1769950" target="_blank"&gt;Capitol’s Collective Negotiation Agreement inked&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE Iloilo Provincial Government represented by Governor Arthur Defensor, Sr. and Provincial Administrator Raul Banias and the Association of Provincial Government Employees (AIPGE) signed the Collective Negotiations Agreement (CNA) last Thursday, October 18. Joecil Mayor, AIPGE president, said the signing is “a historical milestone for the employees of the Iloilo provincial government.” It is the first time for the Iloilo Provincial Government to have a CNA which is a contract negotiated between an accredited employees’ organization and the management on the terms and conditions of employm...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Marginalized Tarlaqueños receive P5-M employment aid - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1768583</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL3p615RqdZA4IYH6aWzLfIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJmtnQM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 12:53:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1768583" target="_blank"&gt;Marginalized Tarlaqueños receive P5-M employment aid&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PANIQUI, Tarlac -- Some 1,357 marginalized Tarlaqueños from different towns of Tarlac province recently finished their employment stint under the Tulong Pangkabuhayan sa Ating Disadvantaged Workers (TUPAD). TUPAD is a community-based assistance program of the Department of Labor and Employment (Dole) that aims to provide emergency employment relief to displaced or marginalized workers. Dole Regional Director Zenaida Angara-Campita said that the emergency employment assistance was mobilized due to the recent calamity that struck some parts of the province. “As you know, the province of Tarla...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Gov't to streamline programs on OFW welfare - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/213588-philippine-government-to-streamline-ofw-welfare-programs</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPHXcBESQMDgDy9t-_NUTcIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 06:02:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/213588-philippine-government-to-streamline-ofw-welfare-programs" target="_blank"&gt;Gov't to streamline programs on OFW welfare&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – The Department of Foreign Affairs (DFA) and the Department of Labor and Employment (DOLE) met on Friday, October 5, to discuss and streamline government programs aimed to help overseas Filipino workers (OFWs). Foreign Affairs Secretary Alan Peter Cayetano said that a working group was created to identify existing programs across different government agencies geared to assist the OFWs. By identifying these, he said, the OFWs can easily find the programs that would suit their needs in a menu, especially for returning workers. (READ: The silent struggle of returning OFWs)...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Leftist undersecretary fired by Duterte was doing a good job, Bello says - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/10/05/Duterte-fires-left-labor-undersecretary-reactions.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIrFpDDY4R_Qwuwe6eek7NAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMJbthQM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 10:11:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/10/05/Duterte-fires-left-labor-undersecretary-reactions.html" target="_blank"&gt;Leftist undersecretary fired by Duterte was doing a good job, Bello says&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, October 5) — Labor Undersecretary Joel Maglunsod, the left-leaning official fired by President Rodrigo Duterte, was doing a good job. This was according to Department of Labor and Employment (DOLE) Secretary Silvestre Bello. He told reporters on Friday that he was "not officially informed of the action against" Maglunsod. He said all he knows was his undersecretary was put on "floating status." When asked if he thinks Maglunsod did his job well, Bello said yes. Labor groups criticized Duterte's move to sack Maglunsod. The President announced it last Tuesday as...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>Graduates receive P200,000 Dole welding machine starter kits - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1766787</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBiwERggod68Si-Ha9fMZZ4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJmtnQM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2018 12:53:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1766787" target="_blank"&gt;Graduates receive P200,000 Dole welding machine starter kits&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SOME 10 marginalized Bataeños from Pilar, Bataan are now budding entrepreneurs thanks to a P200,000 livelihood assistance from the Department of Labor and Employment (Dole). The livelihood provision was initiated by the Local Government of Pilar, through its Public Employment Service Office (Peso), in partnership with the Dole Bataan Field Office. Dole regional director Zenaida Angara-Campita reported to Silvestre Bello III that the beneficiaries are graduates of the Technical Education and Skills Development Authority’s (Tesda) Welder NC II training program. “We are glad to be part of this...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Labor department to track down illegal alien workers - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1766540</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJelY-12aUAh1xPTsMyP_tgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKmgnQM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 03:14:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1766540" target="_blank"&gt;Labor department to track down illegal alien workers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ON THE heels of reports that around 400,000 foreigners are currently working in Metro Manila, the Department of Labor and Employment (Dole) said it will track down those employed without the required Alien Employment Permit (AEP). Dole Secretary Silvestre Bello III assured that they will reinforce their inspections at workplaces in a bid to find illegal alien workers. “Maybe the other foreign nationals working might not have valid alien permits. Dole shall check on the illegals and further validate the issuance of AEPs to foreign workers,” Bello said. He said their move came as they have be...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Emergency jobs up for displaced Itogon residents - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1766122</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI7SVbdcSNASEkM6SYGCRBEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMLignQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2018 12:41:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1766122" target="_blank"&gt;Emergency jobs up for displaced Itogon residents&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WITH the impending closure of small-scale mining in Benguet Province, affected residents of Typhoon Ompong will be the recipients of labor-related jobs the government will offer. Displaced small-scale miners and residents of Itogon may avail of the Tulong Panghanapbuhay sa ating Disadvantaged/Displaced Workers (Tupad) Program or the Emergency Employment Program (EEP) of the Department of Labor and Employment (Dole) in the region. “The emergency employment program of DOLE will depend on the available work needed by the local government unit wherever they would be relocated. What we are doing...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Instead of more jobs, DOLE sees layoffs under Trabaho bill - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/business/212812-dole-warning-layoffs-trabaho-bill</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFHV3fgkL6TgX0D1z7Rix1EqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMP_mmQI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2018 09:21:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/business/212812-dole-warning-layoffs-trabaho-bill" target="_blank"&gt;Instead of more jobs, DOLE sees layoffs under Trabaho bill&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – An official of the Department of Labor and Employment (DOLE) warned that the Tax Reform for Attracting Better and Higher Quality Opportunities (Trabaho) bill would result in job losses if it becomes a law. During the first Senate hearing on the measure, DOLE Director Dominique Tutay said the agency expects job losses in the industry and services sector. "Ang tinitingnan natin ang technology-driven industries kapag hindi po sila naka-cope," Tutay said. (We're looking at technology-driven industries if they are not able to cope.) However, when senators asked for more det...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Drilon questions DOLE statistics on foreigners working in PH - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/212336-drilon-asks-dole-about-number-foreigners-with-working-permits-philippines</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOCnZbVCTr1x6ywLHoxWSHkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 08:21:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/212336-drilon-asks-dole-about-number-foreigners-with-working-permits-philippines" target="_blank"&gt;Drilon questions DOLE statistics on foreigners working in PH&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – Senate Minority Leader Franklin Drilon questioned the "official number" of foreigners working in the Philippines, based on Department of Labor and Employment (DOLE) data. During the budget deliberations for DOLE on Wednesday, September 19, Labor Secretary Silvestre Bello III said 40,000 foreigners – 25,000 of them Chinese – were given alien employment permits (AEPs) in the last 18 months. But Drilon said there must be more. "I do not believe that there are only 40,000 [with AEPs].... Industry people tell me that in Metro Manila alone, there are 400,000 [foreign workers...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Displaced radio station workers get P1.2-M money claims - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1764515</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMx0nr9c0z4PN_S6ECpfe50qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJmtnQM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2018 13:26:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1764515" target="_blank"&gt;Displaced radio station workers get P1.2-M money claims&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;TARLAC CITY -- Some 12 displaced radio station workers recently received their P1,232,900.99 small money claims with the help of the Department of Labor and Employment (Dole). DOLE Regional Director Zenaida Angara-Campita reported to Labor Secretary Silvestre Bello III that the settlement emanated from a response to a complaint letter received by the DOLE Tarlac Field Office. “Our field office, through routine inspection, responded to an anonymous complaint on various labor issues raised against a certain local radio station employing DJs, talent announcers, technicians, IT staff, drivers, ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>DOLE seeks higher budget to hire 2,000 labor inspectors - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/210732-dole-seeks-higher-budget-labor-inspectors-hiring</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOcLDNBtjmXLungIFCnAIK4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2018 05:44:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/210732-dole-seeks-higher-budget-labor-inspectors-hiring" target="_blank"&gt;DOLE seeks higher budget to hire 2,000 labor inspectors&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – Labor Secretary Silvestre Bello III on Thursday, August 30 appealed to lawmakers to increase their budget allocation to hire more labor inspectors across the country. During the budget hearing at the House of Representatives, Bello said that the department currently has around 800 labor inspectors tasked with examining the compliance to labor laws of 900,000 business establishments. "We badly need more budget to hire labor law compliance officers if we are expected to implement the labor standards and labor laws. We wanted to hire 2,000 [labor inspectors] but this was ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Bello: No misuse of P1.9-B DOLE funds - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/210829-bello-statement-allegations-misuse-dole-funds</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBsvGOgGzX_erNEBnUHZsDYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2018 07:29:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/210829-bello-statement-allegations-misuse-dole-funds" target="_blank"&gt;Bello: No misuse of P1.9-B DOLE funds&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – Labor Secretary Silvestre Bello on Friday, August 31, denied what he called a "wild accusation" that the Department of Labor and Employment (DLE) misused some P1.9 billion of its funds under his watch. In a press briefing, Bello clarified that unobligated funds under DOLE's Office of the Secretary were due to issues encountered in the implementation of financial assistance programs from 2016 to 2017. "We are dumbfounded by the wild accusation made by a member of the House of Representatives that we have misused a staggering P1.9 billion of our funds. That is the farthe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Tech-Voc Day to focus on infrastructure program - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1759125</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKxbv8P74MFLZS10LwioN_AqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJeunQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2018 14:55:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1759125" target="_blank"&gt;Tech-Voc Day to focus on infrastructure program&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE Technical Education and Skills Development Training Authority (Tesda) and the Department of Labor and Employment (Dole) urged employers and job seekers to join in the jobs fair to celebrate the National Tech-Voc (Technical-Vocational) Day on Aug. 25. In a press conference, Tesda Negros Oriental Provincial Director Floro Ringga said this is what they called World Cafe of Opportunity (WCO) in relation to Republic Act 10970 that created it. Ringga, the chairperson of WCO, said that WCO offers job linkaging and networking services and is one of the strategies of linking Tesda graduates/alum...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Gawa expects strict implementation of labor safety, health standards - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1759515</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMm296hVZTec3uf30z3E_GgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMPetnQM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2018 03:18:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1759515" target="_blank"&gt;Gawa expects strict implementation of labor safety, health standards&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NEGROS Occidental-based labor group General Alliance of Workers Associations (Gawa) is expecting that the government will strictly implement the newly signed law imposing stronger safety and health standards in the country's workplaces, its official said. Wennie Sancho, secretary general of Gawa, told SunStar Bacolod Wednesday, August 22, that they welcome the signing of the law hoped to strengthen the provisions provided by the Labor Code. Sancho said organized labor groups expect a stronger implementation of the measure by ensuring the provision of health, safety, and welfare program to t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Private sector urged to help dependents of fallen soldiers, cops - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1759974</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM7LStQyD2eMkA4591tAuEoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKmgnQM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 26 Aug 2018 09:24:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1759974" target="_blank"&gt;Private sector urged to help dependents of fallen soldiers, cops&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE Department of the Interior and Local Government (DILG) is encouraging the private sector to open their doors for the dependents of military and police personnel who were killed-in-action (KIA) and killed-in-police-operation (KIPO) for possible employment. DILG officer-in-charge Eduardo Ano said in Memorandum Circular 2018-116, local chief executives are encouraged to endorse and recommend dependents of military and police personnel who were killed or wounded in action (KIA/WIA) for employment in the private sector within their area of jurisdiction in order to help them provide for their...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Duterte strengthens occupational safety, healthy standards - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1758988</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGYffhJsPetfhPbZzUCS0qoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKmgnQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2018 10:12:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1758988" target="_blank"&gt;Duterte strengthens occupational safety, healthy standards&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;IN A BID to promote "safe and heathy workforce," President Rodrigo Duterte has signed into law a measure that would impose stronger safety and health standards in the country's work places. On August 17, Duterte inked Republic Act (RA) 11058, or An Act Strenghtening Compliance with Occupational, Safety and Health (OSH) Standards, that would slap fines for violations of safety and health standards. "The state shall ensure a safe and healthful workplace for all working people by affording them full protection against all hazards in their work environment," the newly-signed law read. RA 11058 ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>178 Clark workers receive P2.7-M labor claims thru SEnA - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1758744</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKHRiggKYnT6rczt4rWOj0QqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJmtnQM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Aug 2018 13:29:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1758744" target="_blank"&gt;178 Clark workers receive P2.7-M labor claims thru SEnA&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A TOTAL of 178 workers from Clark Freeport and nearby areas received P2,716,765 money claims from their respective companies through Department of Labor and Employment’s (Dole) Single Entry Approach (SEnA). Dole Regional Director Zenaida Angara-Campita said the presence of their Clark Satellite Office (CSO) makes it easier and more accessible for workers to seek assistance in resolving labor issues with their employers. “The SEnA has been around for nearly 10 years and we have found great success in preventing various labor disputes materialize into full blown labor standard cases. We are t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>New law aims to ensure safer workplaces - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/210014-duterte-signs-occupational-safety-health-standards-law</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOjdfe8e4tNvEZ3iULIkJOMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2018 09:02:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/210014-duterte-signs-occupational-safety-health-standards-law" target="_blank"&gt;New law aims to ensure safer workplaces&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – President Rodrigo Duterte has signed Republic Act No 11058, a law meant to ensure employers, contractors, and sub-contractors comply with occupational safety and health standards (OSHS). The new law requires employers, contractors, sub-contractors, or "any person who manages, controls, supervises" work to provide for workers a place of work that is safe from conditons that could cause death, illness, or physical harm. It also specifies various rights of workers – right to be informed about safety hazards in the workplace, right to refuse unsafe work, right to report ac...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>[OPINION] NutriAsia skirts the law to oppress workers, hide its greed - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/thought-leaders/209496-nutriasia-skirts-law-oppress-workers-hide-greed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDH9k4RM7HR_H3IRm4h0lj0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJDgmQI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2018 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/thought-leaders/209496-nutriasia-skirts-law-oppress-workers-hide-greed" target="_blank"&gt;[OPINION] NutriAsia skirts the law to oppress workers, hide its greed&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last week, the picketline at the NutriAsia, Inc factory in Marilao, Bulacan was violently dispersed and plant operations have resumed. But the labor dispute remains. The union is still officially on strike, demanding that the company regularize some 900 contractual workers, recognize the union and reinstate dismissed members. In support of the workers, activists and concerned citizens have called for a boycott of NutriAsia’s products, among them such iconic brands as Datu Puti, Silver Swan, Mang Tomas, UFC, Jufran, Mafran, and Papa catsup. NutriAsia, Inc maintains that the strikers are not ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>DOLE stands by cease and desist order vs PLDT contractors - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/209201-dole-stands-by-order-vs-pldt-contractors</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKTcS6TEFKFMJqy6xr3D2agqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2018 07:30:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/209201-dole-stands-by-order-vs-pldt-contractors" target="_blank"&gt;DOLE stands by cease and desist order vs PLDT contractors&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – The Department of Labor and Employment (DOLE) on Thursday, August 9, stood pat on its cease and desist order against customer service contractors of PLDT Incorporated, even if it would affect the services of the telecommunications company. Labor Undersecretary Joel Maglunsod stood firm on the DOLE order during the Senate hearing on regularization issues of employees of PLDT and NutriAsia on Thursday, August 9. Senator Nancy Binay asked Maglunsod if DOLE can allow PLDT customer service contractor SPI CRM Incorporated to continue its contract with the telco "just so the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Senators question 'core functions' of PLDT, NutriAsia amid labor dispute - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/209219-senators-question-pldt-nutriasia-core-functions</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEUlTZCJFgW1W1LzpNrdIIQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2018 10:21:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/209219-senators-question-pldt-nutriasia-core-functions" target="_blank"&gt;Senators question 'core functions' of PLDT, NutriAsia amid labor dispute&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – Senators on Thursday, August 9, questioned the core functions of telco giant PLDT Incorporated and condiments company NutriAsia amid ongoing labor disputes. At the Senate hearing on regularization issues, Senator Risa Hontiveros asked NutriAsia and PLDT about their core functions as its definition would delineate whether they engage in illegal contracting activities. In response, NutriAsia President Angie Flaminiano said only the employees hired by the condiments company would know the formula of their products – contrary to the claims of the workers hired by its contr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Bill wants free vocational training for teenagers - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/208969-house-representatives-adopt-bill-address-skills-mismatch</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI1MKAzb5Cldh7kwwsQ6K8EqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2018 11:10:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/208969-house-representatives-adopt-bill-address-skills-mismatch" target="_blank"&gt;Bill wants free vocational training for teenagers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – A joint committee in the House of Representatives adopted a bill on Monday, August 6, seeking to provide persons at least 15 years old free training to equip them better for in-demand jobs. Under the still unnumbered bill, to be known as “Tulong Trabaho Act,” select training programs of the Technical Education and Skills Development Authority (Tesda) will be available to them to address the mismatch between the skills possessed by applicants and requirements of employers. A fund will be established for the Philippine Labor Force Competency Competitiveness Program. The ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Palace saddened by CA decision vs PLDT workers: We are for their regularization - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/08/06/PLDT-workers-employee-regularization-endo-contractualization.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPeRhH0zH5uPt60DxugpXUkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMJbthQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2018 07:32:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/08/06/PLDT-workers-employee-regularization-endo-contractualization.html" target="_blank"&gt;Palace saddened by CA decision vs PLDT workers: We are for their regularization&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, August 6) — The Palace has sided with the workers of the Philippine Long Distance Telephone Company (PLDT) after the Court of Appeals (CA) blocked the regularization order issued by the Labor Department. "Ang desisyon ng DOLE ay desisyon ng executive. Siyempre nalulungkot kami na binaliktad ng CA ang desisyon. We are for the regularization of the workers of PLDT," Presidential Spokesperson Harry Roque said on Monday. The CA in its ruling said only workers of contractors performing installation, repairs, and maintenance services of PLDT lines should be consider...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>PLDT workers lose regularization case at Court of Appeals - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/208979-court-appeals-decision-pldt-workers-case</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED1-ypW-2rArpuiZxMwf8-4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2018 12:17:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/208979-court-appeals-decision-pldt-workers-case" target="_blank"&gt;PLDT workers lose regularization case at Court of Appeals&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – Workers of telecommunications giant PLDT Incorporated who previously secured regularization orders from the Department of Labor and Employment (DOLE) lost at the level of the Court of Appeals (CA). The CA voided DOLE’s regularization of the following workers of PLDT: - Janitorial services, messengerial and clerical services - Information technology (IT) firms and services - I.T support services, both hardware and software; and applications development - Back office support and office operations - Business process outsourcing or call centers - Sales - Medical, dental, e...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>TSU renews pact with DOLE as job placement office - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1755671?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEf7Xd2lDCBixNmN3wcDfxwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJmtnQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 13:28:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1755671?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;TSU renews pact with DOLE as job placement office&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE Tarlac State University (TSU) over the weekend renewed its ties with the Department of Labor and Employment (DOLE) as an institutionalized job placement office (JPO). DOLE regional director Zenaida Angara-Campita reported to Labor Secretary Silvestre Bello III that a memorandum of agreement (MOA) was signed between the DOLE and TSU for this joint endeavor. Under the MOA, the DOLE shall provide technical assistance on various employment services such as talent-mapping, career advocacy, employment coaching, labor market information (LMI), and livelihood programs. The labor department shal...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>P300-M OFW livelihood fund lauded - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1754863?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED48iMXCwP7oRYZ31s07uCkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKeunQM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1754863?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;P300-M OFW livelihood fund lauded&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE Overseas Workers Welfare Administration (Owwa 11) welcomed the P300-million budget allocated by the Department of Labor and Employment (Dole) for a livelihood program benefiting overseas workers who have returned home. Dole, spearheaded by Secretary Silvestre Bello III, has allocated earlier a P300 million to support the livelihood of the overseas Filipino worker (OFW) organization through the Overseas Workers Welfare Administration’s Tulong Pangkabuhayan sa Pag-unlad ng Samahang OFWs (Tulong Puso) program. Owwa Davao regional director Petrona Bergado said the program aims to provide OF...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>2,000 Tarlac students undergo career guidance seminar - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1754602?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENw1X7beWd0amiw3ckzTvlUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJmtnQM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2018 12:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1754602?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;2,000 Tarlac students undergo career guidance seminar&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BAMBAN, Tarlac -- Some 2,000 students from two Tarlac-based national high schools recently underwent a career guidance coaching Seminar facilitated by the Department of Labor and Employment (Dole). The seminar intended for graduating high school students was initiated by the Local Government of Bamban, through its Public Employment Service Office (Peso) and Dole Tarlac Field Office. Dole Regional Director Zenaida Cangara-Campita reported to Labor Secretary Silvestre Bello III that the participants was comprised of students from grades 10 and 12. “At the wake of our country’s K to 12 program...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>DOLE to displaced Boracay workers: Avail cash assistance - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1754193/Bacolod/Local-News/DOLE-to-displaced-Boracay-workers-Avail-cash-assistance</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKoQnP7fHJ-TLby-yYwIyfEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMPetnQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2018 04:23:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1754193/Bacolod/Local-News/DOLE-to-displaced-Boracay-workers-Avail-cash-assistance" target="_blank"&gt;DOLE to displaced Boracay workers: Avail cash assistance&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE Department of Labor and Employment (DOLE) urged the displaced employees of Boracay Island to avail the cash assistance program provided by the National Government amounting to P520 million. DOLE-Western Visayas director Raul Francia said there were about 20,000 formal sector workers who were displaced when Boracay closed down on May this year to make way for the rehabilitation upon the order of President Rodrigo Duterte. Half of the displaced employees have already availed of the cash assistance but there are those employees who have not applied for the said cash assistance. Francia sai...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>DOLE gives P3.2M worth of business kits to skilled workers in Albay - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/207877-dole-business-kits-skilled-workers-livelihood</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECNy3UEEtJPgXvB-zuGk8EoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2018 13:24:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/207877-dole-business-kits-skilled-workers-livelihood" target="_blank"&gt;DOLE gives P3.2M worth of business kits to skilled workers in Albay&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ALBAY, Philippines – Sixty skilled workers in Oas town were among the recipients of business kits from the Department of Labor and Employment (DOLE). DOLE distributed P3.2 million-worth of business kits or Kabuhayan Starter Kits to beneficiaries in 3 barangays in Albay, including Barangay San Agustin in Oas town. The beneficiaries are part of the informal economy or sectors with special concerns who do not qualify under the government's Pantawid Pamilyang Pilipino Program (4Ps). Among them are farmers, cooks, beauticians, bakers, and others. Acting DOLE Bicol Region Director Rovelinda dela...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>PLDT denies defying DOLE order to regularize 7,300 workers - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/business/208256-pldt-denial-defying-order-regularization-workers</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOeqiwF7rh5KfmhoqTG15ssqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMP_mmQI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 08:47:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/business/208256-pldt-denial-defying-order-regularization-workers" target="_blank"&gt;PLDT denies defying DOLE order to regularize 7,300 workers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – PLDT Incorporated denied defying the order of the Department of Labor and Employment (DOLE) for the telecommunications giant to regularize 7,300 employees. In a statement on Thursday, July 26, PLDT decried the issuance of a clarificatory order wherein DOLE somehow threatened PLDT with legal action should it fails to execute the regularization order. "If this is the conclusion of the clarificatory order or this Honorable Office, then, with due respect, it is wrong. PLDT has not taken any act to 'frustrate or tend to frustrate' this Honorable Office’s regularization orde...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Bello: Over 300,000 workers regularized during Duterte's term - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/07/21/silvestre-bello-contractualization-duterte.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGavs3U6RN3M2xLEa3ztwjYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMJbthQM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2018 15:02:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/07/21/silvestre-bello-contractualization-duterte.html" target="_blank"&gt;Bello: Over 300,000 workers regularized during Duterte's term&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, July 21) — Hundreds of thousands of contractual workers were regularized during the last two years, according to the labor department. Labor Secretary Silvestre Bello issued a statement Saturday, noting that 321,964 workers have been regularized since the start of the Duterte administration. "As President Rodrigo Roa Duterte renders his third State of the Nation Address, we at the Department of Labor and Employment reaffirm our commitment to the reforms initiated by his administration," Bello said. He added that among these initiatives is to end the practices ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>Bello says enemies want him out of DOLE, Ombudsman bid - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/207744-silvestre-bello-says-enemies-want-him-out-dole-ombudsman-bid</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHHmhAqaAjBj_1YEkTHvI3gqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2018 00:42:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/207744-silvestre-bello-says-enemies-want-him-out-dole-ombudsman-bid" target="_blank"&gt;Bello says enemies want him out of DOLE, Ombudsman bid&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – Labor Secretary Silvestre Bello III said that complaints against him are the work of his enemies who want to replace him as head of the Department of Labor and Employment (DOLE). In a phone interview with Rappler, Bello denied involvement in the extortion complaint filed before the Presidential Anti-Corruption Commission (PACC) by Alie Dizon of the Kilusang Pagbabago National Movement for Change. He said the complaint came at a time when he expressed interest in applying for the post of Ombudsman. "Nangyari 'yan noong nag-apply ako noon [sa Ombudsman], baka gusto akong...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Duterte urges Congress to pass law ending contractualization - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/208016-duterte-urges-congress-pass-law-ending-contractualization-sona-2018</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIz6oh4FwDbU-E4dCdPvH5gqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2018 11:01:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/208016-duterte-urges-congress-pass-law-ending-contractualization-sona-2018" target="_blank"&gt;Duterte urges Congress to pass law ending contractualization&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – President Rodrigo Duterte urged Congress during his 3rd State of the Nation Address (SONA) to pass a law ending contractualization "once and for all." On Monday, July 23, Duterte reiterated that lawmakers – not Malacañang – can end contractual employment schemes. "Much as I would like to do the impossible, that power is not vested upon me by the Constitution. And neither will I make both ends meet even if I violate the laws to achieve that purpose. Simply, it is not part of my territory," the President said. "That is why I add mine to their voices in asking Congress to...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>JobStart produces 237 graduates from Oro - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1754586?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGya0kypm4h0QmhKCLNvHLsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMIeunQM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2018 11:22:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1754586?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;JobStart produces 237 graduates from Oro&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SOME 237 Kagay-anon out-of-school youth graduated from the JobStart Philippines program this month, a city official said. Public Employment Services Office (Peso) manager Kathleen Kate Sorilla said the youth have undergone 3 cycles to complete the program, which includes the life skills training, technical training and internship within 3 months Of the 237 graduates, 159 jobstarters were successfully hired by their employers. "Others are working in hotels and our partner employers while others got the job from employers who are not even our partners," Sorilla said. In 2015, the Department o...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Factory worker's son thanks Dole for 'the happiest day of my life' - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1752988?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDD9tx2YpPcDFE2K97RdmMIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJeunQM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jul 2018 13:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1752988?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;Factory worker's son thanks Dole for 'the happiest day of my life'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ONCE, he doubted if he could go to college. Life was tough, he learned that early on. How he then used to envy his peers who seemingly had no problems at all of getting a degree! Others had the money while he had motivation. In the end, no difficulty could discourage a young heart, he mused. For Nelvin H. Calamba Jr. of Casili, Cosolacion, difficulties are but dares of fate–hurdles that tested his skills and attitude to survive and make his dreams come true. He is a Workers’ Organization Development Program (WODP) scholar of the Department of Labor and Employment (Dole). The eldest of three...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Probe sought on Jollibee labor practices - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1753348?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFeHxnwctUXR5xRrjE9yZTsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKmgnQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2018 14:21:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1753348?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;Probe sought on Jollibee labor practices&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE Makabayan bloc on Monday, July 16, filed a resolution urging the House of Representatives to investigate the alleged illegal labor practices committed by Jollibee Foods Corporation (JFC) and its service contractors. In the resolution, members of the Makabayan bloc said there is a need for the House of Representatives to revisit the labor code provision and the issuances on contractualization and labor-only contracting. This, after they have received reports that Jollibee has failed to regularize its employees amid a Department of Labor and Employment order to regularize less than 7,000 ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>PLDT defends its service contractors - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/business/2018/07/12/pldt-dole-service-contractors.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGI2zbnWwVShGvDq5GWnlaEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMOPjmAI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2018 12:10:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/business/2018/07/12/pldt-dole-service-contractors.html" target="_blank"&gt;PLDT defends its service contractors&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, July 12) — Telecommunications giant PLDT came to the defense of service contracting companies it has employed. In the continuing debacle between PLDT and the Department of Labor and Employment (DOLE) on the alleged illegal termination of 7,000 contractual workers by the company, the PLDT said that they have engaged with legal service contracting companies. This is contrary to Labor Secretary Silvestre Bello's recent statements that the workers at PLDT are employed by unqualified service providers. "The service contractors engaged by PLDT are bona fide corporat...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>Tell it to SunStar: PCOO Asec ‘distorted my remarks’ - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1752886?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELYAC6AGYLf7--fxYOpeSnMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJeunQM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jul 2018 16:12:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1752886?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;Tell it to SunStar: PCOO Asec ‘distorted my remarks’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PRESIDENTIAL Communications Operations Office (PCOO) Assistant Secretary Kristian Ablan should resign for peddling fake news and incompetence. In Wednesday’s second pre-Sona forum, Mr. Ablan maliciously if not ineptly distorted my previous remarks at the first pre-Sona forum. Mr. Ablan’s misrepresentation in the subsequent forum, which I did not attend, then gave Labor Secretary Silvestre Bello the excuse to attack me – to malign my name and character. The least Mr. Ablan can do is apologize for his irresponsible acts or better yet resign from his post. In the first pre-Sona forum,I merely ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Sibugay releases salary of student-workers - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1752801?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF-L4597voJYaPKJlxf-kVAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJiunQM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jul 2018 09:44:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1752801?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;Sibugay releases salary of student-workers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE Public Employment Service Office (Peso) of the province of Zamboanga Sibugay has started releasing the salaries of 162 students who are beneficiaries of the Special Program for Employment of Students (SPES). Nelsie Lazo, Zamboanga Sibugay’s Human Resource Management Office (HMRO) chief, said that each of the 162 student-beneficiaries received a daily wage of P453.86. Lazo said that 11 of the 162 student-beneficiaries will receive P13,615.80 each since they have worked for a period of 30 days. Laza, who is also the Peso acting manager, said the 151, who worked for a 20-day period, will r...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>DOLE orders PLDT to regularize workers 'without conditions' - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/207034-dole-order-pldt-regularize-workers-without-conditions</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELHvThJwnUjlRPveu4gTBBAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2018 06:42:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/207034-dole-order-pldt-regularize-workers-without-conditions" target="_blank"&gt;DOLE orders PLDT to regularize workers 'without conditions'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines (UPDATED) – The Department of Labor and Employment (DOLE) maintained that telecommunications giant PLDT Incorporated should regularize its service providers' employees. Contrary to PLDT's position that DOLE's order for contractors to cease and desist would displace workers, Labor Secretary Silvestre Bello III said PLDT should absorb the workers, as stipulated under labor laws. "[T]his office clarifies that pursuant to existing laws, the regularization of workers as a result of the finding of labor-only contracting takes effect by operation of law, and is not subject to a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>DOLE orders NutriAsia to regularize 80 workers - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/206374-dole-nutriasia-regularize-workers</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG7JbSjqwdWBXu2r5PJ26oIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2018 04:23:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/206374-dole-nutriasia-regularize-workers" target="_blank"&gt;DOLE orders NutriAsia to regularize 80 workers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines (UPDATED) – The Department of Labor and Employment (DOLE) ordered condiments giant NutriAsia Incorporated (NAI) to regularize 80 workers of one of its contractors. In a statement on Tuesday, July 3, DOLE said it found that contractor AsiaPro Multi-Purpose Cooperative (AMPC) was engaging in labor-only contracting schemes, and ordered NutriAsia to stop contracting activities with the firm. A June 25 order issued by DOLE Central Luzon Director Zenaida Angara Campita stated that AMPC "has no capacity to procure its own equipment and machinery because it leases the said tools...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>NutriAsia welcomes DOLE ruling on striking workers - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/06/27/NutriAsia-welcomes-DOLE-ruling-striking-workers.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEETZMHwUDm1YhWSjvXhhdGsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMJbthQM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 14:06:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/06/27/NutriAsia-welcomes-DOLE-ruling-striking-workers.html" target="_blank"&gt;NutriAsia welcomes DOLE ruling on striking workers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, June 27) — Food condiment giant NutriAsia welcomed the ruling of the Department of Labor and Employment (DOLE) on the status of workers on strike in its Bulacan plant. It said DOLE Region 3 has confirmed the workers are legitimate employees of NutriAsia's contractor, B-Mirk Enterprises Corporation. "In light of this ruling we choose to be compassionate and will work hard to bring this labor dispute to a peaceful resolution. It was unfortunate in the past that there were many negative reactions to this issue due to false information but we welcome the truth wit...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>Wage hike effective July 12 - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1750166?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENqC_2rzrEtnSY5VoY-3ZvEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMPetnQM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2018 05:29:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1750166?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;Wage hike effective July 12&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MINIMUM wage earners in Western Visayas will already be receiving an additional pay of P13.50 to P41.50 per day starting July 12. This, after the Regional Tripartite Wages and Productivity Board (RTWPB) in Western Visayas has published Wage Order No. 24 Wednesday, June 27, 16 days after it was signed by the members of the Board on June 11. Based on the guidelines, the new Wage Order should take effect 15 days after publication on a newspaper of general circulation. Lawyer Johnson Cañete, chairman of the RTWPB-Western Visayas, said yesterday, June 27, there is no major changes made by the Na...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Work stoppage - SunStar Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1748436?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKD0qNHA1WQPcK62e2EoEq4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMLignQM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jun 2018 09:42:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1748436?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;Work stoppage&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WORK STOPPAGE. Following the death of two workers who were buried alive, the Department of Labor and Employment (Dole)–Cordillera issued a work stoppage order against project developer FC Laranang Development Corporation. (Milo Brioso)&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>478 ‘near-hires’ in Kalayaan 2018 Job and Business Fair - SunStar Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1747868?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAjdHa71XhDAJNDmM5unxBgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJmtnQM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 12:11:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1747868?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;478 ‘near-hires’ in Kalayaan 2018 Job and Business Fair&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;TARLAC CITY -- The Department of Labor and Employment (Dole) tallied some 478 “near-hires” in Tuesday’s Kalayaan 2018 Trabaho, Negosyo, Kabuhayan (TNK) Job and Business Fair in Tarlac City. A preliminary report from the Dole Tarlac Field Office shows that around 573 jobseekers flocked the job and business fair held at the city’s Metro Town Mall. Dole Regional Director Zenaida Angara-Campita reported to Labor Secretary Silvestre Bello III that the near-hires only need to fulfill a few more requirements to get hired. “Our near-hires are considered hired but still need to submit additional or ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Independence Day jobs fair offers over 11K vacancies - SunStar Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1747536?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGpLzHTRAIWwM9JJ4rySvBwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJiunQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 12:36:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1747536?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;Independence Day jobs fair offers over 11K vacancies&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE Department of Labor and Employment (DOLE) is commemorating the 120th celebration of the Independence Day with the conduct of “Trabaho, Negosyo, and Kabuhayan (Job, Business and Livelihood)” fair in Zamboanga City. DOLE regional director Ofelia Domingo said the fair will be held from 9 a.m. to 5 p.m. at the East Wing Activity Center of KCC Mall de Zamboanga. Domingo said 21 employers will be offering 11,532 job vacancies, both for local and overseas placement. She said those who have already registered online during the Labor Day Job Fair need not register again since their data are alre...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>PLDT begins validating employees for regularization - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/06/02/PLDT-validating-employees-regularization.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM7vHRCiA_rNGzx9Xr_PkiQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMJbthQM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jun 2018 12:38:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/06/02/PLDT-validating-employees-regularization.html" target="_blank"&gt;PLDT begins validating employees for regularization&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, June 2) — Telecommunications company PLDT is moving to comply with the Labor Department's order against illegal contractualization. It began the process on Friday by validating its employees for regularization. PLDT employees gathered on Friday outside its office along Boni Avenue in Mandaluyong City, taking up half of the street as they awaited processing. "This is needed first of all to validate their identities and to fulfill other needs such as medical and physical examinations," PLDT spokesperson Ramon Isberto said in a statement. He added concerned indiv...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item></channel></rss>