<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Prosecutor of the International Criminal Court - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqJAgKIh5DQkFTRUFvS0wyMHZNR2h1WW5rd2VCSUNaVzRvQUFQAQ?hl=en-PH&amp;gl=PH&amp;ceid=PH:en</link><language>en-PH</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 12:34:34 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>ICC prosecutor continues preliminary probe on PH drug war - ABS-CBN News</title><link>https://news.abs-cbn.com/news/12/06/18/icc-prosecutor-continues-preliminary-probe-on-ph-drug-war</link><guid isPermaLink="false">52780128358649</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 08:45:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.abs-cbn.com/news/12/06/18/icc-prosecutor-continues-preliminary-probe-on-ph-drug-war" target="_blank"&gt;ICC prosecutor continues preliminary probe on PH drug war&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABS-CBN News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://newsinfo.inquirer.net/1060840/icc-ph-withdrawal-wont-stop-probe-of-drug-war" target="_blank"&gt;ICC: PH withdrawal won’t stop probe of drug war&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;INQUIRER.net&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.gmanetwork.com/news/news/nation/677362/palace-icc-s-probe-on-duterte-over-drug-war-killings-unfair-baseless/story/" target="_blank"&gt;Palace: ICC's probe on Duterte over drug war killings unfair, baseless&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;GMA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/218331-prosecutor-fatou-bensouda-says-icc-will-continue-examine-philippines-war-on-drugs" target="_blank"&gt;ICC Prosecutor: We will continue to examine PH war on drugs&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://newsinfo.inquirer.net/1060768/malacanang-seethes-over-icc-move-to-assess-drug-war" target="_blank"&gt;Malacañang seethes over ICC move to assess drug war&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;INQUIRER.net&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/stories/CAAqOQgKIjNDQklTSURvSmMzUnZjbmt0TXpZd1NoTUtFUWo1b2JXbWpZQU1FZGlOUENpUzBnSTdLQUFQAQ?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;View full coverage on Google News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;</description><source url="https://news.abs-cbn.com">ABS-CBN News</source><media:content url="https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/proxy/MxgJOpoweNK0e67tzsmLdO0OFSqiBQNcypViYBoupUwFS_XhyQuCcXpQCSwJH-2-cE7R3F7VJWWEXRcBwvlMSYUKSimTJ7dd86jeq6zTOlwGxT-49IWN0p-MfprpMDRaGZ2k-Q=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>ICC: Probe on PH drug war continues - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/12/06/icc-probe-duterte-drug-war-philippines.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOxliwpVqZ5X710y0nfUYTMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMJbthQM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 03:21:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/12/06/icc-probe-duterte-drug-war-philippines.html" target="_blank"&gt;ICC: Probe on PH drug war continues&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, December 6) — The International Criminal Court (ICC) prosecutor said the preliminary examination into alleged crimes against humanity committed during the Duterte administration's drug war would continue despite the Philippines' withdrawal from the Rome Statute. "The Office is continuing its assessment of the information available in order to reach a determination on whether there is a reasonable basis to believe that the alleged crimes fall within the subject-matter jurisdiction of the Court," ICC Prosecutor Fatou Bensouda said in her annual report on prelimi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>ICC prosecutor continues preliminary probe on PH drug war - ABS CBN News</title><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP6_iV7ARhvAlZgMIMCevqEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow8IjwCjDw4s8CMNj9mQI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 04:45:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABS CBN News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA - The prosecutor of the International Criminal Court (ICC) is continuing its “thorough factual and legal assessment” of available information on the Philippine drug war to determine if it has jurisdiction over alleged crimes under the Rome Statute. ICC Prosecutor Fatou Bensouda revealed this on Wednesday in her annual report on preliminary examination activities of her office. In her 4-page report on the Philippines, Bensouda disclosed that since the start of the preliminary examination on the country’s drug war on February 8, 2018, her office has received 52 communications. While th...&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Int'l court prosecutor reports progress in Palestinian probe - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/f420f3af67c9455e97cdf74317e2c8d8</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELo_DnEpXe-i8Vtlnt6yh5gqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 19:11:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/f420f3af67c9455e97cdf74317e2c8d8" target="_blank"&gt;Int'l court prosecutor reports progress in Palestinian probe&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE HAGUE, Netherlands (AP) — International Criminal Court prosecutors intend to complete "as early as possible" a long-running preliminary investigation into allegations of crimes in the Palestinian territories, according to a report issued Wednesday. The annual report by ICC prosecutors on progress in nine so-called preliminary examinations underway at the court, said that the Palestinian territories probe "has advanced and significantly progressed" analysis of whether legal conditions for opening a case have been met. Those legal conditions include whether alleged crimes were serious eno...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Conviction of Kian's killers won't weaken ICC examination of drug war – experts - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/217925-conviction-kian-delos-santos-killers-not-weaken-icc-examination-drug-war</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEANoSJohA0cCqc7rzYWzsFIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 09:39:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/217925-conviction-kian-delos-santos-killers-not-weaken-icc-examination-drug-war" target="_blank"&gt;Conviction of Kian's killers won't weaken ICC examination of drug war – experts&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – A conviction of policemen in one murder case under the administration’s war on drugs will not weaken the ongoing preliminary investigation by the International Criminal Court (ICC) into the high number of killings here, two international law experts told Rappler. ICC loses jurisdiction of the high crimes when it determines that Philippine courts are willing and able to investigate and prosecute perpetrators. After the conviction for murder of 3 local Caloocan cops for the killing of 17-year-old Kian delos Santos, Malacañang has come out to say the verdict just proves “...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>ICC confirms receipt of document alleging "mass murder" in PH drug war - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2017/04/25/ICC-confirms-receipt-of-communication.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKeVyH8_NH4OdSIgjrEBNaYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMJbthQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2017 17:39:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2017/04/25/ICC-confirms-receipt-of-communication.html" target="_blank"&gt;ICC confirms receipt of document alleging "mass murder" in PH drug war&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, April 25) — The International Criminal Court (ICC) on Monday said it received a document filed against President Rodrigo Duterte and his government by a lawyer. "We can confirm that we have received a communication," the ICC Office of the Prosecutor Fatou Bensouda told Reuters on Monday. "We will analyze it, as appropriate. As soon as we reach a decision, we will inform the sender and provide reasons for our decision," it added. Jude Sabio, lawyer of self-confessed hitman Edgar Matobato, on Monday submitted to the ICC in The Hague, his 77-page document, which ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>12 considerations on Duterte and the ICC - Rappler</title><link>http://www.rappler.com/thought-leaders/167894-12-considerations-duterte-icc</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH_FuIYgiEo_3uKwEFEWhmMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJDgmQI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2017 06:02:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.rappler.com/thought-leaders/167894-12-considerations-duterte-icc" target="_blank"&gt;12 considerations on Duterte and the ICC&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jude Sabio, a Mindanawon, UP Law graduate and lawyer of Edgar Matobato, has submitted to the Office of Prosecutor of the International Criminal Court (ICC) information that alleges that crimes against humanity have been committed by President Duterte and 11 other individuals. At this early stage, these considerations might help people understand what is happening and what could happen next. First, there is no case or complaint yet. What Jude Sabio has filed is a communication of information in the Office of the ICC Prosecutor that alleges Duterte and 11 others have committed crimes against ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>ICC prosecutor warns Philippines over drug war killings - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-warcrimes-philippines-idUSKCN12D2S5</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDFwEJRDtaOLb0AYRhkxl40qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2016 09:21:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-warcrimes-philippines-idUSKCN12D2S5" target="_blank"&gt;ICC prosecutor warns Philippines over drug war killings&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;AMSTERDAM (Reuters) - The International Criminal Court may have the jurisdiction to prosecute perpetrators of thousands of alleged extrajudicial killings in the Philippines' crackdown on drugs, a prosecutor at the Hague-based tribunal said. Nearly 2,300 people have died since Duterte started the campaign on June 30, according to police, of which 1,566 were drug suspects killed in police operations. "I am deeply concerned about these alleged killings and the fact that public statements of high officials of the republic of the Philippines seem to condone such killings," ICC Prosecutor Fatou B...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>ICC: new information delays decision on Afghan war crimes investigation - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-warcrimes-afghanistan-icct-idUSKBN19Q206</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHAKLDEvih5awNKcIE_BgEcqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2017 14:46:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-warcrimes-afghanistan-icct-idUSKBN19Q206" target="_blank"&gt;ICC: new information delays decision on Afghan war crimes investigation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Stephanie van den Berg The Hague (Reuters) - A decision on whether to open a formal investigation of potential war crimes committed in Afghanistan since 2003, including possible wrongdoing by U.S. personnel, has been delayed, International Criminal Court prosecutors told Reuters. The decision on an investigation, which ICC Prosecutor Fatou Bensouda had said was "imminent" in November, was pushed back after prosecutors received "substantial" new information from Kabul. In an email, Bensouda's office said it had received a large amount of new information from the government of Afghanistan ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Duterte willing to submit to ICC probe: Palace - ABS CBN News</title><link>http://news.abs-cbn.com/news/10/14/16/duterte-willing-to-submit-to-icc-probe-palace</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEg66AhbEi1QCjfn_lyKcqcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow8IjwCjDw4s8CMNj9mQI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2016 05:44:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://news.abs-cbn.com/news/10/14/16/duterte-willing-to-submit-to-icc-probe-palace" target="_blank"&gt;Duterte willing to submit to ICC probe: Palace&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABS CBN News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA – A Palace spokesman reiterated Friday President Rodrigo Duterte is willing to submit himself to any investigation after an International Criminal Court prosecutor expressed concern over thousands of alleged extrajudicial killings in the Philippines' crackdown on drugs. In a statement, Presidential Communications Office (PCO) chief Martin Andanar said "drug-related killings, including vigilante killings, are not State-sanctioned." "Many of those who died were killed during legitimate police operations which are currently undergoing investigation as directed by the President," he said...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://news.abs-cbn.com">ABS CBN News</source></item><item><title>US may have committed war crimes in Afghanistan: ICC prosecutor - ABS CBN News</title><link>http://news.abs-cbn.com/overseas/11/15/16/us-may-have-committed-war-crimes-in-afghanistan-icc-prosecutor</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIuO14a63vpjJ_LHFb-stQoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow8IjwCjDw4s8CMLf4ngM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2016 08:06:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://news.abs-cbn.com/overseas/11/15/16/us-may-have-committed-war-crimes-in-afghanistan-icc-prosecutor" target="_blank"&gt;US may have committed war crimes in Afghanistan: ICC prosecutor&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABS CBN News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;American soldiers wait to board helicopters at Kandahar airbase in Afghanistan in 2003. Kamal Kishore, AFP THE HAGUE - US military forces and the CIA may have committed war crimes in Afghanistan through the "cruel and violent" interrogation of detainees mostly between 2003-2004, the chief prosecutor of the International Criminal Court said Monday. There was a "reasonable basis to believe that, in the course of interrogating these detainees ... members of the US armed forces and the US Central Intelligence Agency resorted to techniques amounting to the commission of the war crimes of torture...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://news.abs-cbn.com">ABS CBN News</source></item><item><title>ICC Prosecutor Warns Philippines Over Drug War Killings - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/icc-prosecutor-warns-philippines-drug-war-killings/3549625.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDGEuQQOYy_5mKJxdDPKOIMqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2016 20:02:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/icc-prosecutor-warns-philippines-drug-war-killings/3549625.html" target="_blank"&gt;ICC Prosecutor Warns Philippines Over Drug War Killings&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The International Criminal Court may have the jurisdiction to prosecute perpetrators of thousands of alleged extrajudicial killings in the Philippines' crack down on drugs, a prosecutor at the Hague-based tribunal said. Earlier on Thursday, Philippine President Rodrigo Duterte called U.S. President Barack Obama, the European Union and United Nations "fools" and said he would humiliate them if they questioned his war on drugs. Nearly 2,300 people have died since Duterte started the campaign on June 30, according to police, of which 1,566 were drug suspects killed in police operations. "I am ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>War Crimes Suspect Called ‘Rambo’ Is Turned Over to International Court - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/18/world/africa/central-african-republic-colonel-rambo.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGw6AudEMsfYRp4vWc3V1xAqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzww5oEY</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 16:16:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/18/world/africa/central-african-republic-colonel-rambo.html" target="_blank"&gt;War Crimes Suspect Called ‘Rambo’ Is Turned Over to International Court&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;AMSTERDAM — A commander in a Central African Republic militia who is known as “Rambo” and is wanted on suspicion of war crimes, including murder, deportation and torture of Muslims, has been handed over to the International Criminal Court in The Hague, the tribunal said. Officials from the Central African Republic transferred the commander, Alfred Yekatom, on Saturday to officials from the court, which is looking into more than six years of violence that has destabilized a fragile region at the heart of the continent. Mr. Yekatom, a sitting member of Parliament, was flown out of the country...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>ICC prosecutor issues warning on Bedouin village demolition - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/24d3d2513b5241f0a7f704f1748ecedf</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK-Yzf8dpVchn3owHUo3LxUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwu4lR</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 12:07:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/24d3d2513b5241f0a7f704f1748ecedf" target="_blank"&gt;ICC prosecutor issues warning on Bedouin village demolition&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE HAGUE, Netherlands (AP) — The International Criminal Court's chief prosecutor issued a warning Wednesday that if Israel goes ahead and destroys a Palestinian Bedouin village on the West Bank that could constitute a war crime. Israel's Supreme Court recently rejected a final appeal against plans to demolish the village, Khan al-Ahmar. ICC Prosecutor Fatou Bensouda said in a written statement that "evacuation by force now appears imminent." She added: "It bears recalling, as a general matter, that extensive destruction of property without military necessity and population transfers in an ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Duterte: I will not submit to the ICC - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/10/18/duterte-icc-fatou-bensouda-not-submit.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENDFbUYoZfvospx2MlOT72YqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMJbthQM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 15:15:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/10/18/duterte-icc-fatou-bensouda-not-submit.html" target="_blank"&gt;Duterte: I will not submit to the ICC&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, October 18) — President Rodrigo Duterte said there was no way he would give in to the International Criminal Court (ICC). Speaking at an event in Manila Thursday, Duterte said, "Please do not drag me into that ICC. I will not submit to you. You idiots... Who's the prosecutor there? Who appointed her?" Duterte previously clashed with ICC Prosecutor Fatou Bensouda and threatened to have her arrested should she come to the Philippines. He questioned the ICC prosecutor's right to investigate him, saying, "Were you elected democratically? Are you the choice of the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>War crimes prosecutor begins examining alleged Rohingya deportations - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-myanmar-rohingya-icct/war-crimes-prosecutor-begins-examining-alleged-rohingya-deportations-idUSKCN1LY2QN</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFmYR67z6H5SHkHhX1LuEu4qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 19:42:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-myanmar-rohingya-icct/war-crimes-prosecutor-begins-examining-alleged-rohingya-deportations-idUSKCN1LY2QN" target="_blank"&gt;War crimes prosecutor begins examining alleged Rohingya deportations&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The prosecutor of the International Criminal Court on Tuesday said her office had begun a preliminary examination into whether alleged forced deportations of Rohingya from Myanmar into Bangladesh could constitute war crimes or crimes against humanity. The decision by Prosecutor Fatou Bensouda follows a ruling at the court earlier this month that it has jurisdiction over alleged forced deportations and related crimes because, while Myanmar is not a member of the court, Bangladesh is. (Reporting by Toby Sterling; Editing by Robin Pomeroy)&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>International Criminal Court Opens Probe Into Crimes Against Rohingya - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/international-criminal-court-opens-probe-into-crimes-against-rohingya</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAuxMwGNcFigfvlHGc1fCXQqFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMLXUiQY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 01:34:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/international-criminal-court-opens-probe-into-crimes-against-rohingya" target="_blank"&gt;International Criminal Court Opens Probe Into Crimes Against Rohingya&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Paula Bronstein/Getty, The International Criminal Court announced that it has opened a “preliminary examination” into the Myanmar military’s alleged crimes against the Rohingya Muslim minority, BBC reports. In a statement Tuesday, ICC prosecutor Fatou Bensouda said the examination may take into account “a number of alleged coercive acts” in the displacement of the Rohingya—including “deprivation of fundamental rights, killing, sexual violence, enforced disappearance, destruction and looting.” Bensouda also said the examination would consider whether persecution or “other inhumane acts” play...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>EXPLAINER: What is the value of Belgium tribunal’s guilty verdict on Duterte? - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/newsbreak/iq/212409-explanation-belgium-peoples-tribunal-guilty-verdict-duterte-crimes-against-humanity</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDFtczxLTmUyHplmGCKy_OIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJ_jmQI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2018 07:05:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/newsbreak/iq/212409-explanation-belgium-peoples-tribunal-guilty-verdict-duterte-crimes-against-humanity" target="_blank"&gt;EXPLAINER: What is the value of Belgium tribunal’s guilty verdict on Duterte?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – The International Peoples’ Tribunal in Brussels, Belgium, handed down on Thursday, September 20, a guilty verdict on President Rodrigo Duterte for crimes against humanity over the alleged “gross and systematic violations of human rights” in the Philippines. This is not a legally binding judgment, however. The Belgium tribunal is among a number of tribunals organized by civil society organizations and private individuals to highlight pressing issues in different countries. Presidential Spokesperson Harry Roque has called it a “sham proceeding” and “propaganda by the Lef...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>International court says it is undeterred after Bolton threatens U.S. sanctions - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-icc/international-court-says-it-is-undeterred-after-bolton-threatens-u-s-sanctions-idUSKCN1LR0OP</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDzL7tN68wKj7G1qKPH-uFYqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 16:14:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-icc/international-court-says-it-is-undeterred-after-bolton-threatens-u-s-sanctions-idUSKCN1LR0OP" target="_blank"&gt;International court says it is undeterred after Bolton threatens U.S. sanctions&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The International Criminal Court said on Tuesday it would "continue to do its work undeterred" a day after U.S. National Security Adviser John Bolton threatened sanctions if the tribunal investigated U.S. activities in Afghanistan. The Hague-based court said it was an independent and impartial institution with the backing of 123 countries. "The ICC, as a court of law, will continue to do its work undeterred, in accordance with those principles and the overarching idea of the rule of law," it said in a statement. ICC prosecutor Fatou Bensouda said last year there was a “reasonable basis to b...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>ICC 'Undeterred' by US Sanctions Threats - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/icc-says-undeterred-by-united-states-sanctions-threats/4566751.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK9O27QSe841LjDy5cO-Fs8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw-pwi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 14:19:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/icc-says-undeterred-by-united-states-sanctions-threats/4566751.html" target="_blank"&gt;ICC 'Undeterred' by US Sanctions Threats&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The International Criminal Court says it will continue to conduct its business as usual one day after the United States threatened to impose sanctions on ICC officials if the court investigated U.S. activities in Afghanistan A statement Tuesday from The Hague based court said, "The ICC, as a court of law, will continue to do its work undeterred, in accordance with those principles and the overarching idea of the rule of law." U.S. National Security Advisor John Bolton said Monday the U.S. would refuse to cooperate "in any way" with the tribunal if it carries out a prospective investigation ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Full text of John Bolton's speech to the Federalist Society - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/09/full-text-john-bolton-speech-federalist-society-180910172828633.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEClRaLIrsYX-MSv_NoctA78qFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 19:44:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/09/full-text-john-bolton-speech-federalist-society-180910172828633.html" target="_blank"&gt;Full text of John Bolton's speech to the Federalist Society&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Below is John Bolton's speech on Monday to the Federalist Society in Washington, DC: I am here to make a major announcement on US policy toward the International Criminal Court, or ICC. After years of effort by self-styled "global governance" advocates, the ICC, a supranational tribunal that could supersede national sovereignties and directly prosecute individuals for alleged war crimes, was agreed to in 1998. For ICC proponents, this supranational, independent institution has always been critical to their efforts to overcome the perceived failures of nation-states, even those with strong c...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Bolton Threatens International Criminal Court With Sanctions if They Continue Probe of Alleged U.S. War Crimes - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/bolton-threatens-international-criminal-court-with-sanctions-if-they-continue-probe-of-alleged-us-war-crimes</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAkersPrVAbc8wyw5iekomgqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMPGMAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 16:50:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/bolton-threatens-international-criminal-court-with-sanctions-if-they-continue-probe-of-alleged-us-war-crimes" target="_blank"&gt;Bolton Threatens International Criminal Court With Sanctions if They Continue Probe of Alleged U.S. War Crimes&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Denis Balibouse/Reuters In his first major speech since joining the White House, National Security Advisor John Bolton on Monday threatened sanctions against judges in the International Criminal Court if they continue attempting to probe alleged American war crimes in Afghanistan. Over the past decade, the prosecutor of the International Criminal Court has conducted a preliminary examination of allegations of war crimes and crimes against humanity in Afghanistan. But in November 2017, the the prosecutor moved a step further and requested authorization to investigate the alleged crimes carri...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Washington’s ICC hypocrisy 'without limits,’ US doesn’t care about human rights – analysts to RT - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/news/438204-us-icc-hypocrisy-afghanistan/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPBiy-EPuIZZkbXezzsgz00qFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww7oMo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 17:28:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/news/438204-us-icc-hypocrisy-afghanistan/" target="_blank"&gt;Washington’s ICC hypocrisy 'without limits,’ US doesn’t care about human rights – analysts to RT&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Washington’s threats against the International Criminal Court (ICC) are evidence of American hypocrisy, as the US is “continually calling for the heads of others” and doesn’t actually care about human rights, analysts told RT. As US National Security Advisor John Bolton said the ICC is “dead to us” in response to a probe into US war crimes in Afghanistan, international criminal lawyer Christopher Black told RT that American hypocrisy is clearly “without limits.” He believes the US is “continually calling for the heads of others, and their entire war against Syria is based on the pretext of ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>'Political, personal repercussions' may await gov't officials linked to drug war - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/newsbreak/rich-media/211560-political-personal-repercussions-government-officials-drug-war-ruben-carranza</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJjFmmgmXCiKsEwTfy4pXtIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJ_jmQI</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 09:43:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/newsbreak/rich-media/211560-political-personal-repercussions-government-officials-drug-war-ruben-carranza" target="_blank"&gt;'Political, personal repercussions' may await gov't officials linked to drug war&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – Government officials involved in the Duterte administration's violent anti-drug campaign may face repercussions which could affect not only them but also their families in the long run. "I think there are going to be political as well as personal repercussions for the people who might be subjected to charges at the International Criminal Court," international human rights lawyer Ruben Carranza said on Rappler Talk with Marites Vitug on Friday, September 7. The ICC's Office of the Prosecutor had begun a preliminary examination of the anti-drug campaign back in February....&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>International Criminal Court issue will mark Duterte presidency - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/210893-international-criminal-court-will-mark-duterte-presidency</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFkeZiEf7QYUq4nu-myYC_AqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2018 03:39:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/210893-international-criminal-court-will-mark-duterte-presidency" target="_blank"&gt;International Criminal Court issue will mark Duterte presidency&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;DUMAGUETE CITY, Philippines – Chief Presidential Counsel Salvador Panelo wants everyone to know that President Rodrigo Duterte is not afraid of anything, certainly not the International Criminal Court (ICC). “He doesn’t mind if you want him to be ousted or to be killed…. The character and history of this man demonstrate the falsity of the claim that he is afraid of the ICC,” Panelo said in a forum in Dumaguete City on Thursday, August 30. His audience included human rights lawyers and advocates who gathered to talk about the Philippine' withdrawal from the ICC. Now comes the dare: If Duter...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>EJK victims seek Duterte's arrest over crimes vs community - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1760296</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAGz8CfiEeL-D3_rN8rTI6cqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKmgnQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2018 05:48:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1760296" target="_blank"&gt;EJK victims seek Duterte's arrest over crimes vs community&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;FAMILIES of "victims" of extrajudicial killings have filed a communication before the International Criminal Court (ICC), accusing President Rodrigo Duterte of committing crimes against humanity in connection with his deadly drug war. The complainants, including rights advocacy group Rise Up for Life and for Rights, sought Duterte's arrest for the deaths of thousands of people killed amid his brutal anti-narcotics drive. They stressed that Duterte's inhumane acts caused "great suffering to the victims and their families." "It is our hope, that with the Court taking jurisdiction of herein co...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Myanmar to ICC: Rohingya jurisdiction request 'should be dismissed' - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-myanmar-rohingya/myanmar-to-icc-rohingya-jurisdiction-request-should-be-dismissed-idUSKBN1KU1NG</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN9B7a9HM1SbenIOIVCxPRkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2018 13:57:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-myanmar-rohingya/myanmar-to-icc-rohingya-jurisdiction-request-should-be-dismissed-idUSKBN1KU1NG" target="_blank"&gt;Myanmar to ICC: Rohingya jurisdiction request 'should be dismissed'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Myanmar said on Thursday a request by the International Criminal Court (ICC) prosecutor to seek jurisdiction over suspected deportations of Rohingya Muslims from Myanmar to Bangladesh was "meritless and should be dismissed". Judges at the court had asked Myanmar to respond to the request by July 27. The office of government leader Aung San Suu Kyi outlined reasons why Myanmar has declined to engage with the court on the matter and why it would not submit a response. "The request by the prosecutor may be interpreted as an indirect attempt to acquire jurisdiction over Myanmar which is not a S...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>The ICC is reaching out to victims of war crimes in Palestine - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/opinion/icc-reaching-victims-war-crimes-palestine-180720083114607.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENu_AXony6zIs6UikFAh_SQqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgwob0I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2018 14:37:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/opinion/icc-reaching-victims-war-crimes-palestine-180720083114607.html" target="_blank"&gt;The ICC is reaching out to victims of war crimes in Palestine&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In an extraordinary move, the Pre-Trial Chamber of the International Criminal Court recently issued a decision ordering its registry "to establish, as soon as practicable, a system of public information and outreach activities for the benefit of the victims and affected communities in the situation in Palestine". It is the first time the court issues an order for outreach at the earliest stages of the process, and before a decision has been reached by the ICC Prosecutor to open a formal investigation. The decision struck fear in the Israelis, who were yet again confronted with the long reac...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>The Latest: International court prosecutor won't be rushed - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/aa480b3b852f4c94933a7f89e425e530</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDawDXsEzAhktcbGND3Zz28qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 16:07:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/aa480b3b852f4c94933a7f89e425e530" target="_blank"&gt;The Latest: International court prosecutor won't be rushed&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE HAGUE, Netherlands (AP) — The Latest on the Palestinians' complaint against Israel before the International Criminal Court in The Hague, Netherlands (all times local): 6 p.m. The prosecutor of the International Criminal Court has signaled that she will not be rushed into making a decision on whether to launch an investigation into alleged crimes by Israel in the Palestinian territories. In a statement issued after the Palestinians called for an immediate investigation, Prosecutor Fatou Bensouda on Tuesday noted that she has been conducting a preliminary probe since January 2015 to estab...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>‘It’s illegal and I will arrest you’: Duterte threatens International Criminal Court prosecutor - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/news/424014-duterte-threatens-arrest-icc-prosecutor/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJzrkNvB-0XmyVMUrS8Xu9sqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww_oMo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2018 11:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/news/424014-duterte-threatens-arrest-icc-prosecutor/" target="_blank"&gt;‘It’s illegal and I will arrest you’: Duterte threatens International Criminal Court prosecutor&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Philippine President Rodrigo Duterte threatened to arrest an International Criminal Court (ICC) prosecutor, arguing she had no right conduct investigations as his country was no longer under ICC jurisdiction. Duterte argued the court had no right to conduct investigations as his country was no longer its member. ICC Prosecutor Fatou Bensouda was confronted after her announcement to start a preliminary examination into a complaint by a Philippine lawyer who had accused Duterte of crimes against humanity. Duterte challenged Bensouda and the ICC’s jurisdiction over him, telling reporters: “Wha...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>ICC prosecutor calls for end to Israeli violence in Gaza - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/04/icc-prosecutor-calls-israeli-violence-gaza-180408165010535.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKKv7nImdHbOpZgYvw1AUYUqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2018 19:32:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/04/icc-prosecutor-calls-israeli-violence-gaza-180408165010535.html" target="_blank"&gt;ICC prosecutor calls for end to Israeli violence in Gaza&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The prosecutor of the International Criminal Court on Sunday called for an end to violence in the Gaza Strip, adding the Palestinian territories were subject to a preliminary examination by her office and she was monitoring events there closely. Following the killing of at least 29 Palestinian protesters by Israeli forces in the past two weeks, Fatou Bensouda said in a statement "I remind all parties that the situation in Palestine is under preliminary examination by my Office. While a preliminary examination is not an investigation, any new alleged crime committed in the context of the sit...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Duterte threatens to arrest ICC prosecutor if she goes to PH - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/200150-duterte-arrest-international-criminal-court-prosecutor-fatou-bensouda</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBPD1n3T5VQSn433CF0dfAQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2018 02:53:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/200150-duterte-arrest-international-criminal-court-prosecutor-fatou-bensouda" target="_blank"&gt;Duterte threatens to arrest ICC prosecutor if she goes to PH&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – Still smarting from the decision of the International Criminal Court (ICC) to conduct preliminary examinations into his anti-drugs campaign, President Rodrigo Duterte threatened to have ICC chief prosecutor Fatou Bensouda arrested if she sets foot in the country to proceed with her probe. "You cannot exercise any proceedings here without basis. That is illegal and I will arrest you," he warned Bensouda during a press conference in Davao City upon his arrival from trips to China and Hong Kong on Friday, April 13. "Kaya ikaw, Ms Fatou, huwag kang pumunta dito kasi (So, M...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>'#DuwagDuterte!' says De Lima after PH withdrawal from ICC - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/198293-de-lima-duterte-duwag-international-criminal-court-withdrawal</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENoJYc9pEPlEB4EMo52pzoEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 03:35:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/198293-de-lima-duterte-duwag-international-criminal-court-withdrawal" target="_blank"&gt;'#DuwagDuterte!' says De Lima after PH withdrawal from ICC&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – Her police escorts have become stricter, but nothing could stop detained Senator Leila de Lima from shouting out a scathing tirade against President Rodrigo Duterte on Friday, March 16. “Akala ko ba hinamon niya ang ICC? #DuwagDuterte! (I thought he was challenging the ICC? #CowardDuterte)!” De Lima said as a dozen policemen towered over her, blocking her from camera view and rushing her to her mini bus before she could say more. {source} WATCH: Over her strict police escorts, De Lima shouts “Hashtag Duwag Duterte!” re ICC withdrawal pic.twitter.com/e3ysPZpbTC — Lian B...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Gary Alejano: Duterte can't do to ICC what he does to CHR, SC, Ombudsman - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/newsbreak/rich-media/196924-gary-alejano-magdalo-pressure-duterte-international-criminal-court</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKTCXiBQ5pJtY3sU-upRRF8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJ_jmQI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2018 05:33:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/newsbreak/rich-media/196924-gary-alejano-magdalo-pressure-duterte-international-criminal-court" target="_blank"&gt;Gary Alejano: Duterte can't do to ICC what he does to CHR, SC, Ombudsman&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – Magdalo Representative Gary Alejano believes that President Rodrigo Duterte and his administration are pressured by developments in the International Criminal Court (ICC) despite public pronouncements that show otherwise. This comes as the Office of the Prosecutor of the ICC on February 8 announced it was starting a preliminary examination into the high number of deaths under Duterte’s war on drugs"following a careful, independent, and impartial review of communications and reports.” “That is just his public image but in reality, it’s going to be a pressure and I don’t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Shoot me, don't jail me, Philippines' Duterte tells Hague court prosecutor - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-philippines-drugs-icct/shoot-me-dont-jail-me-philippines-duterte-tells-hague-court-prosecutor-idUSKBN1FT1XC</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGdv-gixXoURMQNJfLT6xXoqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 15:42:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-philippines-drugs-icct/shoot-me-dont-jail-me-philippines-duterte-tells-hague-court-prosecutor-idUSKBN1FT1XC" target="_blank"&gt;Shoot me, don't jail me, Philippines' Duterte tells Hague court prosecutor&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA (Reuters) - Philippine President Rodrigo Duterte on Friday told the International Criminal Court (ICC) to go ahead and investigate him for crimes against humanity, and said he would prefer to face a firing squad than be jailed. However, the firebrand leader notorious for his defiance of international pressure questioned whether the ICC had jurisdiction to indict him over the deaths of thousands of Filipinos in his war on drugs. He denied ever giving an order to police to kill drug suspects. ICC Prosecutor Fatou Bensouda said on Thursday the preliminary examination into Duterte's camp...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Duterte on dictatorship, ICC on war on drugs, Twitter records profits | Midday wRap - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/video/newscast/195626-thewrap-february-9-2018-midday-edition</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPBZqpCF5914tz7VllxU-ZoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMLDjmQI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 04:12:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/video/newscast/195626-thewrap-february-9-2018-midday-edition" target="_blank"&gt;Duterte on dictatorship, ICC on war on drugs, Twitter records profits | Midday wRap&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today on Rappler: President Rodrigo Duterte says he needs to be a dictator in order to effect change in the country. The Office of the Prosecutor of the International Criminal Court confirms it is starting a 'preliminary examination' into the high number of killings under President Rodrigo Duterte’s bloody war on drugs, adding it is 'closely following the situation' since 2016. Twitter reports its first-ever quarterly profit, delivering a boost to shares of the social network which has been lagging for years against fast-growing rivals. Executive Producer / Writer Lilibeth Frondoso Direct...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Duterte to ICC: 'If you find me guilty, go ahead' - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/195685-duterte-icc-find-me-guilty-go-ahead</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMyFwcsNhg18vTNSvA3EUoAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 15:09:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/195685-duterte-icc-find-me-guilty-go-ahead" target="_blank"&gt;Duterte to ICC: 'If you find me guilty, go ahead'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;DAVAO CITY, Philippines – President Rodrigo Duterte on Friday, February 9, welcomed an international tribunal’s first step to determining whether it could prosecute him for his alleged involvement in the killings done in the country’s war against drugs. "I welcome you. And if you find me guilty, go ahead. So be it," he said at a press conference at Matina Enclaves in Davao City. Duterte was taunting the Office of the Prosecutor of the International Criminal Court (ICC) which recently launched a preliminary examination to determine whether there is sufficient evidence to file a case under it...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Int'l Criminal Court to begin preliminary examination on PH killings - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/02/08/International-Criminal-Court-preliminary-examination-Duterte-drug-war.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHQaaYNMYyJKw0ykm8EobuIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMJbthQM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 04:05:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/02/08/International-Criminal-Court-preliminary-examination-Duterte-drug-war.html" target="_blank"&gt;Int'l Criminal Court to begin preliminary examination on PH killings&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, February 8) — The country's drug war gains global attention as the International Criminal Court (ICC) will begin a preliminary examination to determine if an investigation is needed. ICC Prosecutor Fatou Bensouda announced this through a statement Thursday. She said the international tribunal will look into the country’s situation following a “careful, independent, and impartial review of a number of communication and reports.” “It has been alleged that since July 2016, thousands of persons have been killed for reasons related to their alleged involvement in i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>Int'l Criminal Court closely following drug war killings since 2016 - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/195599-icc-the-hague-netherlands-duterte-drug-war-killings-2016</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELmv87nQx6In6RRnj0D5jKEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 12:36:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/195599-icc-the-hague-netherlands-duterte-drug-war-killings-2016" target="_blank"&gt;Int'l Criminal Court closely following drug war killings since 2016&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – The Office of the Prosecutor of the International Criminal Court (ICC) confirmed it is starting a "preliminary examination" into the high number of killings under President Rodrigo Duterte’s violent war on drugs – after “closely following the situation” since 2016. ICC Prosecutor Fatou Bensouda said that her office has decided to pursue a preliminary examination of the situation in the Philippines “following a careful, independent, and impartial review of communications and reports documenting alleged crimes.” “The preliminary exam in the Philippines will analyze crime...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Int'l Criminal Court takes 1st step in probe into Duterte drug war - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/195492-icc-the-hague-netherlands-duterte-drug-war-killings</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED5UNsXFeYPGaqRtwtTDUdgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 04:09:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/195492-icc-the-hague-netherlands-duterte-drug-war-killings" target="_blank"&gt;Int'l Criminal Court takes 1st step in probe into Duterte drug war&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – The International Criminal Court (ICC) is moving on the complaint filed against President Rodrigo Duterte in connection with the high number of killings under his violent war on drugs. The ICC is starting "preliminary examinations" to determine whether there is sufficient evidence to establish that the case falls under its jurisdiction. Malacañang confirmed this on Thursday, February 8. Presidential Spokesperson Harry Roque made the announcement in a press briefing on Thursday morning, and said that Duterte welcomed the move. "The President and I met about this extensi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Can the International Criminal Court Be Saved From Itself? - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2017/12/17/opinion/icc-symbolic-migrants-europe.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENqNZCyFnVQ2-miMwiNKyHYqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzwwt4QY</guid><pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2017 20:10:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2017/12/17/opinion/icc-symbolic-migrants-europe.html" target="_blank"&gt;Can the International Criminal Court Be Saved From Itself?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The I.C.C. is strictly symbolic. It might redeem itself by taking up the abuse migrants suffer on their way to Europe.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>The Observer view on the effectiveness of international law - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2017/dec/17/observer-view-international-law-criminal-court</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIPXcyTskYhULdrI5If5nNYqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTC9vBU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2017 00:05:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2017/dec/17/observer-view-international-law-criminal-court" target="_blank"&gt;The Observer view on the effectiveness of international law&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The recent conviction of Ratko Mladić, the former Bosnian Serb commander, on charges of genocide, war crimes and crimes against humanity committed in the 1990s may come to be viewed as a high-point for global justice. Mladić’s life sentence for his leading role in ethnic cleansing operations in Bosnia, the battle for Sarajevo, and the massacre of Muslims at Srebrenica was fully deserved. But this symbolic success cannot hide the fact that the international criminal justice system is under siege from within and without. In 2017, its problems grew worse. Mladić’s conviction followed the succe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Pentagon 'Deeply Committed' to Laws of War as ICC Considers Investigation - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/pentagon-international-criminal-court-investigation/4156012.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHgkRak2sWIk8bJPGVZDwK4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2017 00:25:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/pentagon-international-criminal-court-investigation/4156012.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pentagon 'Deeply Committed' to Laws of War as ICC Considers Investigation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Pentagon has reasserted its commitment to complying with the laws of war, after news emerged that the International Criminal Court is seeking an investigation into alleged war crimes by U.S. personnel in Afghanistan. Pentagon spokesman Mike Andrews, a lieutenant colonel in the Air Force, told VOA on Friday that the United States is "deeply committed to complying with the law of war, and we have a robust national system of investigation and accountability that more than meets international standards." Andrews was replying to a move by ICC Prosecutor Fatou Bensouda in November requesting ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>ICC Prosecutor Requests Probe for Alleged Misconduct in Afghanistan - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/icc-prosecutor-requests-probe-alleged-misconduct-afghanistan/4126942.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGGi7FEbzFj6jqBlscetWZAqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2017 19:11:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/icc-prosecutor-requests-probe-alleged-misconduct-afghanistan/4126942.html" target="_blank"&gt;ICC Prosecutor Requests Probe for Alleged Misconduct in Afghanistan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The prosecutor of the International Criminal Court on Monday asked judges to authorize an investigation in Afghanistan into allegations including rape and torture by the U.S. military and CIA, crimes against humanity by the Taliban and war crimes by Afghan security forces. The announcement marked the first time ICC Prosecutor Fatou Bensouda has gone after Americans for alleged war crimes and sets up a possible showdown with Washington. The United States is not a member state of the court, but its nationals can be charged with crimes committed in countries that are members. As well as allege...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Sudan's President Visits Russia, Asks for Protection From US - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/sudan-president-visits-russia-asks-for-protection-from-us/4131704.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEClZDtmsKfwrr3ad0D5u_AgqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2017 15:51:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/sudan-president-visits-russia-asks-for-protection-from-us/4131704.html" target="_blank"&gt;Sudan's President Visits Russia, Asks for Protection From US&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sudanese President Omar al-Bashir said on a visit to Russia Thursday that his country needs protection from the U.S. and could serve as a gateway to Africa for Moscow. Al-Bashir, speaking at the start of his meeting with Russian President Vladimir Putin in the Black Sea resort of Sochi, accused the U.S. of fomenting the conflict in Sudan. Al-Bashir added that "we need protection from the U.S. aggressive actions.'' The Darfur region has been the site of violent conflict since 2003, when rebels took up arms against the government in the capital, Khartoum, accusing it of discrimination and neg...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Burundi rejects International Criminal Court war crimes investigation - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-warcrimes-burundi/burundi-rejects-war-crimes-probe-but-opposition-welcomes-it-idUSKBN1DA1IH</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEpeM1WMhqpqjZcgworikQwqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 19:02:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-warcrimes-burundi/burundi-rejects-war-crimes-probe-but-opposition-welcomes-it-idUSKBN1DA1IH" target="_blank"&gt;Burundi rejects International Criminal Court war crimes investigation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Toby Sterling and Katharine Houreld AMSTERDAM/NAIROBI (Reuters) - Burundi said on Friday it will refuse to cooperate with an International Criminal Court (ICC) investigation into war crimes prosecutors suspect were committed by forces loyal to President Pierre Nkurunziza's government against their political opponents. The court ordered a formal investigation on Thursday into crimes committed between April 2015 to October 2017. But experts say it will be hard for ICC Prosecutor Fatou Bensouda to gather evidence without support from Burundi's government, which last month became the first t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>US and UK could face Afghanistan war crimes investigation - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/asia/us-uk-war-crimes-afghanistan-investigation-icc-criminal-court-hague-latest-a8035576.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGPnkU2dn1EZdCnNKqb2ILQqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/asia/us-uk-war-crimes-afghanistan-investigation-icc-criminal-court-hague-latest-a8035576.html" target="_blank"&gt;US and UK could face Afghanistan war crimes investigation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The prosecutor of the International Criminal Court has said she will seek approval to open a formal investigation into allegations of war crimes in Afghanistan, having concluded there was “reasonable basis to believe” such atrocities were committed there. More follows.... ]]&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item></channel></rss>