<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Expo 2020 - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqJAgKIh5DQkFTRUFvS0wyMHZNRFJxWm1aeWN4SUNaVzRvQUFQAQ?hl=en-PH&amp;gl=PH&amp;ceid=PH:en</link><language>en-PH</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 13:38:00 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Appeal to President Duterte for PH participation in Expo 2020 - The Manila Times</title><link>https://www.manilatimes.net/appeal-to-president-duterte-for-ph-participation-in-expo-2020/479078/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiYWh0dHBzOi8vd3d3Lm1hbmlsYXRpbWVzLm5ldC9hcHBlYWwtdG8tcHJlc2lkZW50LWR1dGVydGUtZm9yLXBoLXBhcnRpY2lwYXRpb24taW4tZXhwby0yMDIwLzQ3OTA3OC_SAQA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 16:07:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.manilatimes.net/appeal-to-president-duterte-for-ph-participation-in-expo-2020/479078/" target="_blank"&gt;Appeal to President Duterte for PH participation in Expo 2020&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Manila Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;FILIPINOS in the United Arab Emirates (UAE) just celebrated over the weekend our host country's 47th National Day. There were many festivities held across.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.manilatimes.net">The Manila Times</source><media:content url="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/proxy/ntR6YqRs3NEal6rYliRn88pKr8QET4ZwgI9I_ZcGYXC44KebsX82JwmCROxuxTSXp81pPeF6ocwS0jMitPVcWIqYfUqJbIRv5bCmacFuXYtiEPQPmQRDqWk3I1z87SZK0MQxBRCEA2aPsu4Q6NVz=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Yong Ju Lee and Atelier KJ Create Design for Korean Pavilion at Expo 2020 Dubai - ArchDaily</title><link>https://www.archdaily.com/907268/yong-ju-lee-and-atelier-kj-create-design-for-korean-pavilion-at-expo-2020-dubai</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHjbRzq4bmG9Sh40fpiT2FgqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowkLQGMJBaMK-8Ag</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.archdaily.com/907268/yong-ju-lee-and-atelier-kj-create-design-for-korean-pavilion-at-expo-2020-dubai" target="_blank"&gt;Yong Ju Lee and Atelier KJ Create Design for Korean Pavilion at Expo 2020 Dubai&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ArchDaily&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elusive Boundary Pavilion. Image Courtesy of Yong Ju Lee Architecture + Atelier KJ Yong Ju Lee Architecture and Atelier KJ have created "Elusive Boundary" for the Korean Pavilion at Expo 2020 Dubai. The project is designed as a place for radical encounters of different fields. The main theme of Korean Pavilion, Mobility, is defined as a new space of possibility created by movement between territories and escape/expansion to new territories. The movement defined by new mobility is not linear, but a simultaneous event between territories. Elusive Boundary Pavilion. Image Courtesy of Yong Ju L...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.archdaily.com">ArchDaily</source></item><item><title>A First Look at the US Pavilion for Expo 2020 Dubai, Designed by Fentress - ArchDaily</title><link>https://www.archdaily.com/906748/a-first-look-at-the-us-pavilion-for-expo-2020-dubai-designed-by-fentress</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGmGd77-UwUtyjYpVEUY8tEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowkLQGMJBaMK-8Ag</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 10:20:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.archdaily.com/906748/a-first-look-at-the-us-pavilion-for-expo-2020-dubai-designed-by-fentress" target="_blank"&gt;A First Look at the US Pavilion for Expo 2020 Dubai, Designed by Fentress&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ArchDaily&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Courtesy of Fentress Architects The design of the USA Pavilion for the Expo 2020 Dubai has been revealed, designed by Curtis W. Fentress and Fentress Architects. Destined to represent more than 325million Americans, the pavilion seeks to “provide a unique platform for [the United States] to come together to showcase the very best of [their] cultural and commercial achievements.” The pavilion is to be circular in form, with “slants fashioned to project a sensation of movement, making the viewer feel like the building itself is in motion.” The pavilion’s interior will showcase American innova...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.archdaily.com">ArchDaily</source></item><item><title>Kozlowski + Cardia Design Floating Tree Branch Pavilion for Expo 2020 - ArchDaily</title><link>https://www.archdaily.com/906669/kozlowski-plus-cardia-design-floating-tree-branch-pavilion-for-expo-2020</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN6QjQWCc1_WDmRPpqFJhBMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowkLQGMJBaMK-8Ag</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.archdaily.com/906669/kozlowski-plus-cardia-design-floating-tree-branch-pavilion-for-expo-2020" target="_blank"&gt;Kozlowski + Cardia Design Floating Tree Branch Pavilion for Expo 2020&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ArchDaily&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brazil Pavilion. Image Courtesy of Gabriel Kozlowski Architect Gabriel Kozlowski has partnered with Gringo Cardia, Bárbara Graeff, and Tripper Arquitetura to design a structure of floating tree branches for the Brazil pavilion at Expo 2020 Dubai. The pavilion is inspired by one of the greatest technological achievements of Brazil: the improvement of the Direct Planting System over straw. The design conceptually mimics this scheme through its layered arrangement - soil, an entanglement of protection, productivity - presenting itself as both a building and a symbolic image. Brazil Pavilion. I...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.archdaily.com">ArchDaily</source></item><item><title>Metaform and The Space Factory Win Competition for World Expo Luxembourg Pavilion - ArchDaily</title><link>http://www.archdaily.com/870303/metaform-and-the-space-factory-win-competition-for-world-expo-luxembourg-pavilion</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELqzPq-I3cckYTueqzT0Vt0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowkLQGMJBaMK-8Ag</guid><pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2017 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.archdaily.com/870303/metaform-and-the-space-factory-win-competition-for-world-expo-luxembourg-pavilion" target="_blank"&gt;Metaform and The Space Factory Win Competition for World Expo Luxembourg Pavilion&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ArchDaily&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;© Metaform - Vyonyx Metaform architects and The Space Factory scenographers have won the competition for the Luxembourg Pavilion at the World Expo 2020 in Dubai, which is centered on the theme of “opportunity.” Inspired by a Möbius strip, in which a twisted and folded ribbon has no beginning and no end, the winning pavilion proposal is modeled around the concept of “cradle to cradle” and the circular economy. © Metaform With a blurred distinction between the interior and exterior, the pavilion features a ramp entrance that leads into a central, multifunctional space on the first floor. © Me...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.archdaily.com">ArchDaily</source></item><item><title>After the expo: What happens when Dubai's global extravaganza is over? - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/style/article/dubai-expo-2020-legacy-plan/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPEYF1CBjflu84oGmBdQbbYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMIbnyQU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2017 15:21:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/style/article/dubai-expo-2020-legacy-plan/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;After the expo: What happens when Dubai's global extravaganza is over?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dubai is known for its maximalist tastes, and World Expo 2020 will be no different. The event will have a 438-hectare footprint when it lands -- one of the largest sites ever -- transforming the south west of the emirate. Since winning the bid in 2013, the huge construction project has created jobs and infrastructure, but what will be the legacy of the six-month bonanza? Previous expo hosts, along with the Olympic cities -- the only other event that can compare in scale -- offer valuable lessons for Dubai. So what are the do-s and don't-s of hosting the world's biggest parties? Expo 2020 Wh...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Hosting a global event: The good, the bad and the bankrupt - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/style/gallery/global-events-legacy/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMCjMpokcT4ZCYQ0r3snddUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMIbnyQU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2017 01:23:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/style/gallery/global-events-legacy/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Hosting a global event: The good, the bad and the bankrupt&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dubai is known for its maximalist tastes, and World Expo 2020 will be no different. The event will have a 438-hectare footprint when it lands -- one of the largest sites ever -- transforming the south west of the emirate. Since winning the bid in 2013, the huge construction project has created jobs and infrastructure, but what will be the legacy of the six-month bonanza? Previous expo hosts, along with the Olympic cities -- the only other event that can compare in scale -- offer valuable lessons for Dubai. So what are the do-s and don't-s of hosting the world's biggest parties? Expo 2020 Wh...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Dubai Plans $1.7 Billion Tourist Project on New Artificial Islands - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/3851767.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPw0QdkDhpILGnCvRjVg_7QqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwtOetBQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 15:08:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/3851767.html" target="_blank"&gt;Dubai Plans $1.7 Billion Tourist Project on New Artificial Islands&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dubai plans to develop a 6.3 billion dirham ($1.7 billion) tourist resort on two man-made islands it will build on either side of the Burj Al Arab, its luxury sail-shaped hotel. It is the latest development planned by the emirate as it aims to attract 20 million visitors a year by 2020 when Dubai will host the World Expo 2020 exhibition. Spanning 4 million square feet, Marsa Al Arab will be made up of two islands, one dedicated to entertainment and family tourism and the other featuring luxury villas and a private marina, state news agency WAM reported Monday. Dubai is already one of the wo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>LAVA Selected to Design German Pavilion for Expo 2020 Dubai - ArchDaily</title><link>https://www.archdaily.com/905514/lava-selected-to-design-german-pavilion-for-expo-2020-dubai</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELpuZF3dZZyyBfZxAQ40IJoqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowkLQGMJBaMK-8Ag</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.archdaily.com/905514/lava-selected-to-design-german-pavilion-for-expo-2020-dubai" target="_blank"&gt;LAVA Selected to Design German Pavilion for Expo 2020 Dubai&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ArchDaily&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;German Pavilion. Image Courtesy of facts and fiction | adunic | LAVA The Laboratory for Visionary Architecture (LAVA) has been selected to design the German Pavilion for Expo 2020 Dubai. Designed as a vertical campus that blends nature and technology, the pavilion takes cues from local architecture and Germany’s history of outstanding lightweight pavilion design. Formally, the design features a freeform roof that encloses interlinked floating cubes that house exhibition and event spaces. German Pavilion. Image Courtesy of facts and fiction | adunic | LAVA Demonstrating the Expo theme, every...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.archdaily.com">ArchDaily</source></item><item><title>Es Devlin to design UK Pavilion for Expo 2020 Dubai - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/style/article/es-devlin-uk-pavilion-dubai-expo-2020/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC28RYRHSBmwejWDuoHPUfMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 10:29:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/style/article/es-devlin-uk-pavilion-dubai-expo-2020/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Es Devlin to design UK Pavilion for Expo 2020 Dubai&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A rendering of "Poem Pavilion" by Es Devlin, the UK Pavilion for Expo 2020 Dubai. The British designer's space-inspired pavilion will be a giant interactive piece of public art, generating poetry using artificial intelligence. Scroll through to see more incredible works of public art from around the world. courtesy UK Department for International Trade Florentijn Hofman brought his eye-catching "Rubber Duck" to Hong Kong's busy harbor in 2013, but it's not the only time it's been shown. Hofman debuted the playpful piece in 2007, and has displayed it in Amsterdam, Osaka, Sydney and Sao Paulo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>WXCA's Polish Pavilion for Dubai Expo 2020 Features Kinetic Flocks of Birds - ArchDaily</title><link>https://www.archdaily.com/903469/wxcas-polish-pavilion-for-dubai-expo-2020-features-kinetic-flocks-of-birds</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGOjRrQB4EfECVMOs-ZNnWUqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowkLQGMJBaMK-8Ag</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2018 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.archdaily.com/903469/wxcas-polish-pavilion-for-dubai-expo-2020-features-kinetic-flocks-of-birds" target="_blank"&gt;WXCA's Polish Pavilion for Dubai Expo 2020 Features Kinetic Flocks of Birds&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ArchDaily&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;© Vivid Vision WXCA and Bellprat will design the Polish Pavilion for the 2020 World Expo in Dubai, having overcome more than 30 other proposals. The winning scheme seeks to create an “open, tree-like modular structure” inspired by Poland’s rich wildlife. The pavilion will feature an integrated exhibition with “kinetic flocks of birds floating over visitors’ heads,” referring to the many migratory birds which settle in Poland each year “inspiring legends, connecting minds, and creating the future.” © Vivid Vision The pavilion will adopt a sculptural form allowing the exhibition to unfold int...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.archdaily.com">ArchDaily</source></item><item><title>Jasmax Designs New Zealand's EXPO 2020 National Pavilion Inspired by Māori Culture - ArchDaily</title><link>https://www.archdaily.com/903069/jasmax-designs-new-zealands-expo-2020-national-pavilion-inspired-by-maori-culture</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELAR20Vbxlp5sDjCsDlydIwqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowkLQGMJBaMK-8Ag</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 16:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.archdaily.com/903069/jasmax-designs-new-zealands-expo-2020-national-pavilion-inspired-by-maori-culture" target="_blank"&gt;Jasmax Designs New Zealand's EXPO 2020 National Pavilion Inspired by Māori Culture&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ArchDaily&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;New Zealand Pavilion. Image Courtesy of Jasmax Architecture firm Jasmax has been selected to design New Zealand's National Pavilion for EXPO 2020 in Dubai. New Zealand will participate in Expo 2020 from October 2020 to April 2021. Expo 2020 Dubai will bring together 180 nations and 25 million international visitors. Over six months, the event will inspire collaboration on global challenges and opportunities. New Zealand’s theme for Expo 2020 is 'Care for People and Place'. The pavilion will feature an exhibition experience, corporate hosting facilities, a restaurant and design store. The Ne...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.archdaily.com">ArchDaily</source></item><item><title>Penda and Smartvoll Design Giant Watermill for Austria's EXPO 2020 Pavilion - ArchDaily</title><link>https://www.archdaily.com/903133/penda-and-smartvoll-design-giant-watermill-for-austrias-expo-2020-pavilion</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECFxrHG96ZzhAT7PiWbLHAYqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowkLQGMJBaMK-8Ag</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 03:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.archdaily.com/903133/penda-and-smartvoll-design-giant-watermill-for-austrias-expo-2020-pavilion" target="_blank"&gt;Penda and Smartvoll Design Giant Watermill for Austria's EXPO 2020 Pavilion&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ArchDaily&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Architecture and design practices Penda and Smartvoll have created a giant watermill for Austria's National Pavilion for EXPO 2020 in Dubai. ‘The Source of Everything’ was selected as a finalist in an international competition and marks the first collaboration between Penda Austria and Smartvoll. The project features a supersized mill that circulates water through the pavilion and brings an experience to the desert of Dubai that Austria is famous for: Refreshment. The Source of Everything. Image © Virgin Lemon “In my opinion, a pavilion at the Expo shouldn’t be a box that solely showcases p...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.archdaily.com">ArchDaily</source></item><item><title>Dubai 2020 Expo Pavilions and Architecture - ArchDaily</title><link>https://www.archdaily.com/902936/dubai-2020-expo-pavilions-and-architecture</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE8PL1oF-N0VoEQ3JFFljmIqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowkLQGMJBaMK-8Ag</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 15:05:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.archdaily.com/902936/dubai-2020-expo-pavilions-and-architecture" target="_blank"&gt;Dubai 2020 Expo Pavilions and Architecture&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ArchDaily&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;UK Pavilion. Image Courtesy of Es Devlin For the Dubai 2020 Expo, the United Arab Emirates and Sheikh Mohammed bin Rashid, Vice President and Ruler of Dubai, selected the theme Connecting Minds, Creating the Future. Organized around ideas of Sustainability, Mobility and Opportunity, the next world Expo will be the first to be held in the Middle East, North Africa and South Asia region. Organised every five years, the world expo lasts six months and is created as a global destination for millions of people to share ideas, showcase innovation, encourage collaboration and celebrate human ingen...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.archdaily.com">ArchDaily</source></item><item><title>Es Devlin to Design the UK’s “Poem Pavilion” for Dubai Expo 2020 - ArchDaily</title><link>https://www.archdaily.com/902853/es-devlin-to-design-the-uks-poem-pavilion-for-dubai-expo-2020</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOnz6CSflxu_1boM6wBEfA4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowkLQGMJBaMK-8Ag</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2018 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.archdaily.com/902853/es-devlin-to-design-the-uks-poem-pavilion-for-dubai-expo-2020" target="_blank"&gt;Es Devlin to Design the UK’s “Poem Pavilion” for Dubai Expo 2020&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ArchDaily&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Courtesy of Es Devlin Award-winning artist and designer Es Devlin OBE is set to design the UK Pavilion for Expo 2020 in Dubai. The scheme, titled “Poem Pavilion” will highlight “leading British expertise in Artificial Intelligence and Space,” and will be produced in collaboration with global brand agency Avantgarde. The Poem Pavilion will feature an illuminated “Message to Space,” with each of the Expo’s projected 25 million visitors invited to contribute. Courtesy of Es Devlin For the pavilion’s design, Devlin will draw on previous experience with artificial intelligence, such as her lumin...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.archdaily.com">ArchDaily</source></item><item><title>Selgascano + FRPO to Design Inflatable Canopy for Spain's EXPO 2020 National Pavilion - ArchDaily</title><link>https://www.archdaily.com/903067/selgascano-plus-frpo-to-design-inflatable-canopy-for-spains-expo-2020-national-pavilion</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC9tbJwoPA9lnNghaDthXPEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowkLQGMJBaMK-8Ag</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 03:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.archdaily.com/903067/selgascano-plus-frpo-to-design-inflatable-canopy-for-spains-expo-2020-national-pavilion" target="_blank"&gt;Selgascano + FRPO to Design Inflatable Canopy for Spain's EXPO 2020 National Pavilion&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ArchDaily&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Spanish Pavilion. Image Courtesy of Selgascano &amp; FRPO Architecture firms Selgascano and FRPO have been selected to design Spain's National Pavilion for EXPO 2020 in Dubai. The winning proposal includes an inflatable canopy of nine yellow ETFE cylinders set within a steel framework. Reinterpreting the Spanish plaza, the design creates a new take on the public square. The pavilion was made to be ultralight as a more sustainable structure that could be easily removed and transported. Formed as a 'breathing pavilion', the design allows two inflatables to move up and down to respond to views, li...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.archdaily.com">ArchDaily</source></item><item><title>Querkraft to Design Austria's National Pavilion for EXPO 2020 in Dubai - ArchDaily</title><link>https://www.archdaily.com/902220/querkraft-to-design-austrias-national-pavilion-for-expo-2020-in-dubai</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPt3hJmM9v1IPyC_03-qfnwqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowkLQGMJBaMK-8Ag</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.archdaily.com/902220/querkraft-to-design-austrias-national-pavilion-for-expo-2020-in-dubai" target="_blank"&gt;Querkraft to Design Austria's National Pavilion for EXPO 2020 in Dubai&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ArchDaily&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Austria Pavilion. Image Courtesy of Querkraft Architekten The Viennese architecture office Querkraft has been selected to design the Austrian Pavilion for the EXPO 2020 in Dubai. The design combines traditional building materials with modern techniques to present Austria as a center of innovation. Former Federal Minister Beatrix Karl was appointed honorary commissioner for the world expo and will represent Austria externally. The Expo in Dubai will be the first world exhibition in an Arab country in the 170-­year Expo history. The Austrian Pavilion will center on questions of how resources ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.archdaily.com">ArchDaily</source></item><item><title>Fentress Architects Chosen to Design USA Pavilion for World Expo 2020 in Dubai - ArchDaily</title><link>https://www.archdaily.com/898309/fentress-architects-chosen-to-design-usa-pavilion-for-world-expo-2020-in-dubai</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBGo2Kj-XxlMG4gZp5cwgxsqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowkLQGMJBaMK-8Ag</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.archdaily.com/898309/fentress-architects-chosen-to-design-usa-pavilion-for-world-expo-2020-in-dubai" target="_blank"&gt;Fentress Architects Chosen to Design USA Pavilion for World Expo 2020 in Dubai&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ArchDaily&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pictured here, the masterplan for the World Expo 2020 Dubai designed by HOK. Image via HOK Fentress Architects has been chosen to design the USA Pavilion for the World Expo 2020 in Dubai. The Pavilion USA 2020 will sit within the 438-hectare masterplan designed by HOK, pictured above. The U.S. Department of State selected the consortium containing Fentress Architects, led by Big Things Group, to deliver a pavilion based on the theme “What Moves You,” featuring highlights of American culture and technology. The team will seek to use the program as “a showcase of the innovation, creativity, a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.archdaily.com">ArchDaily</source></item><item><title>The world is coming to Dubai. Is it ready? - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/travel/2018/07/02/business-traveller-richard-quest-dubai-world-expo-2020-b.cnn</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPYogplJIUUXB_QI9RHkiRUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2018 16:27:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/travel/2018/07/02/business-traveller-richard-quest-dubai-world-expo-2020-b.cnn" target="_blank"&gt;The world is coming to Dubai. Is it ready?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The clock is ticking for Dubai to host the World Expo 2020. In true Emirati fashion, they're pulling out all the stops. ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A Time Warner Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Naples and Florence - art cities for Expo Dubai - Agenzia Ansa</title><link>http://www.ansamed.info/ansamed/en/news/sections/economics/2018/05/11/naples-and-florence-art-cities-for-expo-dubai_3faea3fe-1678-4009-ab10-75b05d75e5c7.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGAapzI63Xi445Wonk-q6lQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowsP-hCTCXv5cCMIWA0QU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 09:59:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.ansamed.info/ansamed/en/news/sections/economics/2018/05/11/naples-and-florence-art-cities-for-expo-dubai_3faea3fe-1678-4009-ab10-75b05d75e5c7.html" target="_blank"&gt;Naples and Florence - art cities for Expo Dubai&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Agenzia Ansa&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NAPLES - Italy will bring to Expo Dubai the creativity and beauty that can unite people by giving centrality to talent and professionalism, said Paolo Glisenti, the general commissioner for Italy at the 2020 Dubai Expo. Explaining the connection between Italian art cities ahead of the Universal Exposition, Glisenti said that ''territories will be the protagonists'', noting they are ''responding in an extraordinary and spontaneous way''. In Naples, the Festival delle Luci hosts a dialogue between the southern port city and Florence, two cities that will be protagonists of the Italian pavilio...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.ansamed.info">Agenzia Ansa</source></item><item><title>The city that grew up: What Dubai's ascent means for global architects - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/style/article/dubai-architects-industry-change/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENgC2B8DQrvsH6q9YM8ESI0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2018 06:16:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/style/article/dubai-architects-industry-change/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;The city that grew up: What Dubai's ascent means for global architects&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Skyscrapers in Dubai, topped with the Burj Khalifa. A building boom in the 21st century has seen the emirate become a hotspot for cutting-edge design. But what does that mean for architecture around the world? Nick Merrick for Hedrich Blessing/SOM At 2,716.5 feet (828m), the Burj Khalifa is nearly 60% taller than any building ever constructed. Engineers developed a method to pump concrete 2,000 feet in the air, practicing by laying pipes across the desert floor, says Skidmore Owings &amp; Merrill's (SOM) William Baker, structural engineering partner behind the build. Nick Merrick for Hedrich Bl...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title> - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/style/gallery/dubai-architecture-som-grimshaw-foster--partners/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKFw83VHKbhDeJZGwgYjDjwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMIbnyQU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 08:35:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/style/gallery/dubai-architecture-som-grimshaw-foster--partners/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Skyscrapers in Dubai, topped with the Burj Khalifa. A building boom in the 21st century has seen the emirate become a hotspot for cutting-edge design. But what does that mean for architecture around the world? Nick Merrick for Hedrich Blessing/SOM At 2,716.5 feet (828m), the Burj Khalifa is nearly 60% taller than any building ever constructed. Engineers developed a method to pump concrete 2,000 feet in the air, practicing by laying pipes across the desert floor, says Skidmore Owings &amp; Merrill's (SOM) William Baker, structural engineering partner behind the build. Nick Merrick for Hedrich Bl...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>The World's First Commercial Hyperloop is Coming to Abu Dhabi in 2020 - ArchDaily</title><link>https://www.archdaily.com/893006/the-worlds-first-commercial-hyperloop-is-coming-to-abu-dhabi-in-2020</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIgpn6HNX5DZOObxkIZmZkAqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowkLQGMJBaMK-8Ag</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.archdaily.com/893006/the-worlds-first-commercial-hyperloop-is-coming-to-abu-dhabi-in-2020" target="_blank"&gt;The World's First Commercial Hyperloop is Coming to Abu Dhabi in 2020&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ArchDaily&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Courtesy of HyperloopTT Hyperloop Transportation Technologies (HyperloopTT) has released details of their plan to create the world’s first commercial Hyperloop system in Abu Dhabi. Situated on the border between Abu Dhabi and Dubai, in close proximity to both the Al Maktoum International Airport and World Expo 2020 site, the HyperloopTT will begin with the construction of six miles (ten kilometers) of infrastructure, with future development potentially creating a commercial Hyperloop network across the United Arab Emirates and beyond. Courtesy of HyperloopTT Courtesy of HyperloopTT While th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.archdaily.com">ArchDaily</source></item><item><title>Expo 2020 to focus on creativity, says commissioner - Agenzia Ansa</title><link>http://www.ansamed.info/ansamed/en/news/sections/economics/2018/01/26/expo-2020-to-focus-on-creativity-says-commissioner_17c0b5c3-b2fe-47ba-81d6-c4e83408d444.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDnLAhwPVYdZL2GFC6TJL8sqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowsP-hCTCXv5cCMIWA0QU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 12:13:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.ansamed.info/ansamed/en/news/sections/economics/2018/01/26/expo-2020-to-focus-on-creativity-says-commissioner_17c0b5c3-b2fe-47ba-81d6-c4e83408d444.html" target="_blank"&gt;Expo 2020 to focus on creativity, says commissioner&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Agenzia Ansa&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(ANSAmed) - ROME, JANUARY 26 - Creativity, connection and knowledge will be the focus of Italy's participation in Expo 2020 in Dubai, General Commissioner Paolo Glisenti said during the Italian presentation of the event at the foreign ministry this week. He added that, in it, Italy will show its ''creativity as accessible, reproducible and spreadable''. Expo Dubai is expected to draw some 25 million visitors, 70% of whom from abroad, and in its participation Italy will be ''inspired by the values of partnership and sustainability'' and ''the Italian political agenda, conducting an operation...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.ansamed.info">Agenzia Ansa</source></item><item><title>Construction Breaks Ground on Calatrava's UAE Pavilion at Expo 2020 Dubai - ArchDaily</title><link>https://www.archdaily.com/885659/construction-breaks-ground-on-calatravas-uae-pavilion-at-expo-2020-dubai</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFYB-a6vhZtxwFDnzmkfV_8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowkLQGMJBaMK-8Ag</guid><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2017 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.archdaily.com/885659/construction-breaks-ground-on-calatravas-uae-pavilion-at-expo-2020-dubai" target="_blank"&gt;Construction Breaks Ground on Calatrava's UAE Pavilion at Expo 2020 Dubai&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ArchDaily&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Courtesy of Santiago Calatrava Construction has begun on one of the centerpiece structures at the upcoming 2020 Dubai Expo, the Santiago Calatrava-designed UAE Pavilion. Inspired by the shape of a flying falcon, the UAE Pavilion covers more than 15,000 square meters and four floors, including a 1,717-square-meter top story hospitality lounge. A 588-square-metre mezzanine will house support functions, with the remaining two floors containing 12,000 square meters will of exhibition space showcasing displays that respond to the Expo theme of “Connecting Minds, Creating the Future.” Courtesy of...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.archdaily.com">ArchDaily</source></item></channel></rss>