<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Abu Sayyaf - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIAgKIhpDQkFTRFFvSEwyMHZNSGh4WHhJQ1pXNG9BQVAB?hl=en-PH&amp;gl=PH&amp;ceid=PH:en</link><language>en-PH</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 12:52:16 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Indonesian abducted by Abu Sayyaf found in Sulu - ABS-CBN News</title><link>https://news.abs-cbn.com/news/12/06/18/indonesian-abducted-by-abu-sayyaf-found-in-sulu</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiVmh0dHBzOi8vbmV3cy5hYnMtY2JuLmNvbS9uZXdzLzEyLzA2LzE4L2luZG9uZXNpYW4tYWJkdWN0ZWQtYnktYWJ1LXNheXlhZi1mb3VuZC1pbi1zdWx10gEA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 08:41:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://news.abs-cbn.com/news/12/06/18/indonesian-abducted-by-abu-sayyaf-found-in-sulu" target="_blank"&gt;Indonesian abducted by Abu Sayyaf found in Sulu&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABS-CBN News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;LUUK, Sulu - An Indonesian national abducted by suspected Abu Sayyaf bandits was found by the Armed Forces in a remote village in this town Wednesday.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://news.abs-cbn.com">ABS-CBN News</source><media:content url="https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/proxy/LA9BldfoRirxXVlPjjJr5NiTGzoygtTnG2zk0F5Vy7mvi80vk3-27QKLi8ZP35pYxGJkOklHLcWFfePE6Xccs0pOvByNimpG71ou_WRjqPjbxmpHlNqX2Fn1Vg=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Military's 2022 plan: New army division vs Abu Sayyaf in Sulu - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/218280-military-create-infantry-divison-hunt-down-abu-sayyaf</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFVJDLZKNSBd9Obdj3-hS_UqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 10:46:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/218280-military-create-infantry-divison-hunt-down-abu-sayyaf" target="_blank"&gt;Military's 2022 plan: New army division vs Abu Sayyaf in Sulu&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The 11th Infantry Division will focus on the island province of Sulu, which has been a stronghold of the Abu Sayyaf and other terror groups.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Woman, child killed in Zamboanga encounter between troops, Abu Sayyaf - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/217361-woman-child-killed-clash-soldiers-abu-sayyaf-zamboanga-november-23-2018</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEuvvV4S0scSa3PBWszJGmEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 08:00:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/217361-woman-child-killed-clash-soldiers-abu-sayyaf-zamboanga-november-23-2018" target="_blank"&gt;Woman, child killed in Zamboanga encounter between troops, Abu Sayyaf&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Colonel Leonel Nicolas, commander of Taskforce Zamboanga, says an Abu Sayyaf member was also killed during the clash in Limaong Island.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>AFP hopes new infantry division will address Abu Sayyaf problem in Sulu - INQUIRER.net</title><link>https://newsinfo.inquirer.net/1060410/afp-hopes-new-infantry-division-will-address-abu-sayyaf-problem-in-sulu</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMibWh0dHBzOi8vbmV3c2luZm8uaW5xdWlyZXIubmV0LzEwNjA0MTAvYWZwLWhvcGVzLW5ldy1pbmZhbnRyeS1kaXZpc2lvbi13aWxsLWFkZHJlc3MtYWJ1LXNheXlhZi1wcm9ibGVtLWluLXN1bHXSAQA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 13:42:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://newsinfo.inquirer.net/1060410/afp-hopes-new-infantry-division-will-address-abu-sayyaf-problem-in-sulu" target="_blank"&gt;AFP hopes new infantry division will address Abu Sayyaf problem in Sulu&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;INQUIRER.net&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The AFP will create a new infantry division to be permanently stationed in Sulu to address the persisting problem of Abu Sayyaf.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://newsinfo.inquirer.net">INQUIRER.net</source><media:content url="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/proxy/SlgAO-T4iz2Ho6jeMRh4hmz5YjYy8wME4oJr2rX9ajK2yqUc48f7qgcHoNZaO4IYhhQ0eLZrdvM19FK9druCwK0wLKbeqJk7JntRURCBaQUVFg=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Funeral honors given to 5 soldiers killed in firefight vs Abu Sayyaf - ABS-CBN News</title><link>https://news.abs-cbn.com/news/11/19/18/funeral-honors-given-to-5-soldiers-killed-in-firefight-vs-abu-sayyaf</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMia2h0dHBzOi8vbmV3cy5hYnMtY2JuLmNvbS9uZXdzLzExLzE5LzE4L2Z1bmVyYWwtaG9ub3JzLWdpdmVuLXRvLTUtc29sZGllcnMta2lsbGVkLWluLWZpcmVmaWdodC12cy1hYnUtc2F5eWFm0gEA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 08:00:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://news.abs-cbn.com/news/11/19/18/funeral-honors-given-to-5-soldiers-killed-in-firefight-vs-abu-sayyaf" target="_blank"&gt;Funeral honors given to 5 soldiers killed in firefight vs Abu Sayyaf&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABS-CBN News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ZAMBOANGA CITY—Funeral honors were given to 5 soldiers of the Philippine Army who were killed in a gun battle with members of the Abu Sayyaf Group last ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://news.abs-cbn.com">ABS-CBN News</source><media:content url="https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/proxy/7yPLwkd47kAnIgHDudxeTwCY5TwkkKXpMdhxVuRnw5pQtipefYVyDgodcA_6bA-Px-Ll58J1SDWIRz-l4_AwWm2RKfL20lh_v63nfyoMyNbFhwhXbPPfo-fkPXkvDc7qhGDZB5712TCVPPUreM1UKNp4YFk=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>5 soldiers killed in Sulu while rescuing hostages from Abu Sayyaf - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/216906-5-soldiers-killed-jolo-abu-sayyaf-november-2018</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEANVeG_GHkU1kxzw7nyOxm4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 08:00:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/216906-5-soldiers-killed-jolo-abu-sayyaf-november-2018" target="_blank"&gt;5 soldiers killed in Sulu while rescuing hostages from Abu Sayyaf&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – The Armed Forces of the Philippines (AFP) said on Saturday, November 17, that 5 soldiers were killed and 23 others were injured while ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Malaysia police detain 7 Abu Sayyaf fighters in raids - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/malaysia-police-detain-8-abu-sayyaf-fighters-raids-181116034401267.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIUS1afwq2H5UaX1qHaFQDEqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 08:00:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/malaysia-police-detain-8-abu-sayyaf-fighters-raids-181116034401267.html" target="_blank"&gt;Malaysia police detain 7 Abu Sayyaf fighters in raids&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Malaysian police say they've arrested eight suspects including a number of alleged members of Abu Sayyaf, after reports the group was planning to carry out a ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Duterte eyes revamp of military personnel in Jolo after recent deadly clashes - ABS CBN News</title><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG_oaOtQdnP-zviqrfhbshkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow8IjwCjDw4s8CMNj9mQI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 08:45:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABS CBN News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA—President Rodrigo Duterte on Friday said he will order a revamp of the military’s composition in Jolo, Sulu, following the deaths of several soldiers in recent clashes there. “In a few days I’m transferring one division sa Jolo. Nagsawa na ako. A fortnight ago, nag-usap kami ni Del (Defense Secretary Delfin Lorenzana) and I communicated to them my disappointment kung bakit gano’n, sige na lang tayo mamatayan,” Duterte said in a speech in Davao City. “It’s an attrition thing at tatapusin na natin iyan.” (In a few days I’m transferring one division in Jolo. I’ve grown tired of it. A fo...&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Military chief off to Opapp upon retirement - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1777294/Manila/Local-News/Military-chief-off-to-Opapp-upon-retirement?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIDljl7dgG5GE_hWpDg4KYsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKmgnQM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 05:39:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1777294/Manila/Local-News/Military-chief-off-to-Opapp-upon-retirement?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;Military chief off to Opapp upon retirement&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PRESIDENT Rodrigo Duterte wants retiring Armed Forces of the Philippines (AFP) Chief-of-Staff Carlito Galvez Jr. to be the next presidential peace adviser, Malacañang announced on Wednesday. Duterte announced his plan during the 32nd Cabinet meeting held at the Malacañan Palace, Presidential Spokesperson Salvador Panelo said in a statement. "The President announced his intention to appoint General Carlito Galvez, Jr. to the Office of the Presidential Adviser on the Peace Process (Opapp)," the Palace official said. Galvez, a member of the Philippine Military Academy "Sandiwa" Class of 1985, ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Duterte honors wounded soldiers in Zamboanga - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/11/25/dutyerte-sulu-wounded-soldiers-zamboanga-abu-sayyaf.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBhb3FlNVJIrw_nuOw10l4kqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMJbthQM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2018 07:57:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/11/25/dutyerte-sulu-wounded-soldiers-zamboanga-abu-sayyaf.html" target="_blank"&gt;Duterte honors wounded soldiers in Zamboanga&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, November 25) — President Rodrigo Duterte visited on Saturday 23 soldiers wounded in clashes in Sulu. Duterte visited Camp Navarro General Hospital in Zamboanga City where the soldiers were recovering. In a report from the Presidential Communications Operations Office (PCOO), the soldiers, who were hurt in separate clashes with the Abu Sayyaf Group in the province, were conferred the Order of Lapu-Lapu with the Rank of Kampilan. According to the PCOO, "The Order of Lapu-Lapu with the Rank of Kampilan is awarded to personnel of the government and private individ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>3 killed, 3 wounded in clash - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1775439</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFnk_WTtZGasX-GzXrd8_l8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJiunQM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 08:05:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1775439" target="_blank"&gt;3 killed, 3 wounded in clash&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;AN ALLEGED Abu Sayyaf bandit and two civilians, including a seven-year-old child, were killed in a clash with troops early Friday, November 23, on Limaong Island. Three other children caught in the crossfire were wounded, according to Colonel Leonel Nicolas of Joint Task Force Zamboanga. Nicolas said the clash occurred shortly after 5 a.m. Friday while the Marine Battalion Landing Team-11 troops were checking the reported presence of a group of armed men in Sitio Logpond. Nicolas said the firefight lasted for about 10 minutes. An alleged Abu Sayyaf bandit identified as a certain Abu Nibra, ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Military, MILF prepare to secure Bangsamoro vote vs violence - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/217430-philippine-military-milf-security-preparations-bangsamoro-organic-law-plebiscite</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJLSwNqo7EhROTVPoy4eBIMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2018 02:01:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/217430-philippine-military-milf-security-preparations-bangsamoro-organic-law-plebiscite" target="_blank"&gt;Military, MILF prepare to secure Bangsamoro vote vs violence&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – The Moro Islamic Liberation Front (MILF) said the plebiscite on the creation of a new Bangsamoro region on January 21, 2019, will not be marred by the usual violence seen in regular elections in Mindanao. “While we see that there’s a possibility of some violence during the plebiscite, for me, the plebiscite is not like regular elections,” MILF chairman Al Haj Murad Ebrahim said. The military and the MILF discussed security preparations for the plebiscite during Murad’s historic Camp Aguinaldo visit on November 21, two months before the crucial plebiscite. “Napag-usapan...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>6 Sayyafs surrender amid military offensive - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1774965</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPwAYlnXzXVkeOh7-u2BgqAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJiunQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1774965" target="_blank"&gt;6 Sayyafs surrender amid military offensive&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SIX Abu Sayyaf Group (ASG) members have surrendered to authorities due to pressures of continuous military offensive in Sulu, officials said Tuesday, November 20. Lieutenant Colonel Gerry Besana, Western Mindanao Command (Westmincom) information officer, said the group surrendered around 8 a.m. Monday to the 2nd Special Forces Battalion headed by Lieutenant Colonel Jessie Montoya in Talipao, Sulu. Besana identified them as follows: Annuar Sumlahani Dalawis alias Urban; Arsi Kalam Akili; Nassal Asaral; Alvarez Sadjan alias Tundok; Aysal Ajaral alais Taki; and Medzmar Mursin alias Choy. He sa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>5 soldiers killed in clash vs. Abu Sayyaf - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/regional/2018/11/17/soldiers-killed-abu-sayyaf-sulu-clash.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIyB2Q0OyzDjRN-O70D2x3AqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMPHhmQI</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 06:26:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/regional/2018/11/17/soldiers-killed-abu-sayyaf-sulu-clash.html" target="_blank"&gt;5 soldiers killed in clash vs. Abu Sayyaf&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, November 17) — Five soldiers were killed while 23 others were wounded when they fought members of the Abu Sayyaf group in Patikul, Sulu Friday, the military said Saturday. According to the military's Western Mindanao Command, the firefight lasted for more than an hour at Barangay Liang at around 4 p.m. An initial report said the soldiers encountered around 50 Abu Sayyaf fighters under leader Almuder Yadah. The Abu Sayyaf group is one of the foreign terrorist organizations listed by the United States Department of State. Duterte in July reached out to the bandi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>5 killed, 23 wounded in Sulu clash - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1774603</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELezO6EFqXdsbeo07-Bzn_MqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJiunQM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 03:22:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1774603" target="_blank"&gt;5 killed, 23 wounded in Sulu clash&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ZAMBOANGA CITY -- Five soldiers were killed and 23 others, including an officer, were wounded in a clash with a group of Abu Sayyaf bandits in the hinterlands of Sulu. Lieutenant Colonel Gerry Besana, Western Mindanao Command (Westmincom) information officer, said the clash took place around 4:10 p.m. Friday, November 16, in the village of Liang, Patikul, Sulu. Besana said the troops from the Joint Task Force Sulu were conducting intensified military operation when they encountered 50 Abu Sayyaf bandits led by sub-leader Almujer Yadah. Besana said the firefight lasted for about one hour and...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>AFP chief Galvez seeks OPAPP post after retirement - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/217040-military-chief-carlito-galvez-jr-seeks-opapp-post-after-retirement</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBBDgDo833R4LWWC2oImpREqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 07:38:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/217040-military-chief-carlito-galvez-jr-seeks-opapp-post-after-retirement" target="_blank"&gt;AFP chief Galvez seeks OPAPP post after retirement&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – Armed Forces of the Philippines (AFP) chief General Carlito Galvez Jr said he wants to serve as consultant at the Office of the Presidential Adviser on the Peace Process (OPAPP) after his retirement on December 12. "I already conveyed my interest [to] OPAPP. I told Secretary Jesus Dureza, 'Can I be some sort of consultant?' He accepted my request," Galvez said in a press conference in Camp Aguinaldo on Monday, November 19. "We have trust and confidence [in the] MILF (Moro Islamic Liberation Front) and MNLF (Moro National Liberation Front). Maybe we can also reach out t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Maute recruiter sentenced to 40 years in prison - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/217163-maute-recruiter-gets-40-years-in-prison</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFC96qugpxs7HOQEloekrVcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 11:35:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/217163-maute-recruiter-gets-40-years-in-prison" target="_blank"&gt;Maute recruiter sentenced to 40 years in prison&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – A Maute recruiter was sentenced to 40 years in prison after he was found guilty of rebellion in connection to the war in Marawi City in 2017. Taguig Regional Trial Court (RTC) Branch 70 Judge Felix Reyes convicted Nur Supian of terrorism under Republic Act 9732 or the Human Security Act. Marine Sergeant Johnson Malavega infiltrated a suspected Maute group n July 2017, or two months after war broke out in Marawi, where he met Supian who introduced himself as a leader of the Moro National Liberation Front (MNLF). Malavega was a key witness for the prosecution, who testif...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Economic, political gains will be lost if martial law in Mindanao is stopped — AFP - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/11/16/AFP-martial-law-mindanao-extension-gains.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPdwFk61sS9zS4e3phwX94cqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMJbthQM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 11:25:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/11/16/AFP-martial-law-mindanao-extension-gains.html" target="_blank"&gt;Economic, political gains will be lost if martial law in Mindanao is stopped — AFP&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, November 16) — The Armed Forces of the Philippines (AFP) on Friday said allowing martial law in Mindanao to lapse would pose a disadvantage because it will give the government's armed enemies "breathing space" to reconstitute their forces. In a media briefing, AFP Chief Carlito Galvez said that several economic and political gains will also be lost if there won't be any extension of martial rule. The gains include a decrease in the crime index as well as gains in governance, he added. "Martial law has led to increased tourist and economic activity in Mindanao,...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>Philippines: scores of Islamic State fighters on Mindanao island - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/11/philippines-scores-of-islamic-state-fighters-on-mindanao-island</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKY2S_di7R23XvAFayQWVNwqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Nov 2018 15:51:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/11/philippines-scores-of-islamic-state-fighters-on-mindanao-island" target="_blank"&gt;Philippines: scores of Islamic State fighters on Mindanao island&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The threat of Islamic State is mounting again in the Philippines, with estimates there could be between 40 to 100 foreign fighters, and a growing momentum among local pro-Islamic State militant groups. In May last year, the Mindanao city of Marawi was overrun by Isis fighters and a caliphate declared. It took a bloody, five-month siege by the army, in which 1,200 lives were lost, for the government to regain control. But one year on from Marawi’s liberation, Prof Rommel Banlaoi, chairman of the Philippine Institute for Peace, Violence and Terrorism Research, told the Guardian that he had se...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Navy personnel awarded for rescue of kidnap victim - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1773812</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELvWZxhQEgNlLddfz_DPcJEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJiunQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 11:31:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1773812" target="_blank"&gt;Navy personnel awarded for rescue of kidnap victim&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE Naval Forces Western Mindanao (NFWM) has awarded Bronze Cross Medal to gallant sailors and marines for the successful rescue of a kidnap victim from the hands of the Abu Sayyaf bandits in Sulu province. Rear Admiral Rene Medina, NFWM commander, and Captain Richard Gonzaga, deputy for fleet operations, led the awarding during the flag raising ceremony Monday, November 12, at the Naval Station Romulo Espaldon in Zamboanga City. The awardees are the following: Colonel Armel Tolato, Philippine Marine Ready Force-Sulu commander; Major Junnibert Tubo, Marine Battalion Landing Team-3 (MBLT-3) ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>AFP chief says martial law extension ‘highly possible’ - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1773899</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH99BqBtZQM9KT0KI9115WcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKeunQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 15:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1773899" target="_blank"&gt;AFP chief says martial law extension ‘highly possible’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;EXTENDING the declaration of martial law in Mindanao for the third time is highly possible with the Armed Forces of the Philippines (AFP) likely recommending it. AFP Chief of Staff Carlito Galvez Jr., said based on their consultations, the people are supportive of extending military rule in Mindanao. “Based on the recommendation of the Eastmincom (Eastern Mindanao Command) and based on the recommendation of the LGU (local government units), there is a positive possibility that we will extend martial law,” Galvez told media Tuesday, November 23, after a command conference at the Eastmincom h...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Officer, 3 soldiers injured in Sulu clash - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1772705</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBSOgjj2G1mj25Ebcdw9WSYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJiunQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 10:42:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1772705" target="_blank"&gt;Officer, 3 soldiers injured in Sulu clash&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOUR soldiers, including an officer, were wounded in a clash as the government offensive continue against the Abu Sayyaf Group (ASG) in Sulu province, a top military official said Tuesday. The firefight took place at 1:40 p.m. Monday at Sitio kan Apo Aluk in Panglayahan village, Patikul, Sulu, according to Lieutenant General Arnel Dela Vega, Western Mindanao Command (Westmincom) commander. Dela Vega said the troops were conducting focused military operation when they clashed with some 50 Abu Sayyaf bandits led by one-armed and senior bandit leader Radullan Sahiron. He did not identify the i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Kidnap victim 'Duterte' rescued in Sulu - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/215770-kidnap-victim-with-surname-duterte-rescued-sulu-november-2018</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC-7mQnFOLr2Ls-5WETBQBMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 01:53:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/215770-kidnap-victim-with-surname-duterte-rescued-sulu-november-2018" target="_blank"&gt;Kidnap victim 'Duterte' rescued in Sulu&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ZAMBOANGA CITY, Philippines – Government troops have rescued a kidnap victim who had been held by the Abu Sayyaf group for over a year in Sulu, the military said. Continued military operations against the Abu Sayyaf in Panamao, Sulu, paved the way for the rescue of Jose Duterte, 66, on Thursday, November 1. The kidnap victim is not related to President Rodrigo Duterte. The Philippine Navy in Sulu, with Marine Battalion Landing Team 3, rescued Duterte early Thursday afternoon, a few days after troops neutralized and captured a number of ASG members in the area. Duterte and wife Jessica were ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>2 Abu Sayyaf bandits killed in Sulu clash, 2 captured - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1771671</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECR5yU3xA4vuNYgAF86oM44qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJiunQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 08:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1771671" target="_blank"&gt;2 Abu Sayyaf bandits killed in Sulu clash, 2 captured&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MARINE forces have killed two Abu Sayyaf members and captured two wounded bandits following a firefight early Tuesday, October 30, in Sulu. Lieutenant General Arnel Dela Vega, Western Mindanao Command (Westmincom) chief, said the Marines were on combat operations when they encountered around 100 Abu Sayyaf bandits at 5:08 a.m. Tuesday, October 30, in the village of Lihbug Kabaw, Panglima Estino, Sulu. The bandits were led by Radullan Sahiron and sub-leaders Idang Susukan and Almujer Yadah. Dela Vega said two Abu Sayyaf members were killed in the clash, while two others were wounded and capt...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>3 soldiers, 1 Abu Sayyaf killed in encounter - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1771088/Manila/Local-News/3-soldiers-1-Abu-Sayyaf-killed-in-encounter?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELLzIGSGgROM4pc1PSYxlh8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKmgnQM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 06:59:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1771088/Manila/Local-News/3-soldiers-1-Abu-Sayyaf-killed-in-encounter?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;3 soldiers, 1 Abu Sayyaf killed in encounter&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THREE marine soldiers and one Abu Sayyaf Group (ASG) terrorist were killed in an encounter in Patikul, Sulu on Friday morning, October 26. Three other soldiers were wounded and brought to the KHTB station hospital for treatment, said Western Mindanao Command spokesperson Lieutenant Colonel Gerry Besana. He said soldiers of the Joint Task Force Sulu under Brigadier General Divino Rey Pabayo encountered an undetermined number of ASG members under sub-leaders Alnijar Ekit and Aldi Alun in Barangay Timpook. Besana said the body of a suspected ASG terrorist was recovered from the battle area. He...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>3 Marines, 1 Abu Sayyaf killed in Sulu clash - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/215225-marines-killed-sulu-clash-abu-sayyaf-october-26-2018</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBgR49y0y6hI2pusUz12qNcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 05:30:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/215225-marines-killed-sulu-clash-abu-sayyaf-october-26-2018" target="_blank"&gt;3 Marines, 1 Abu Sayyaf killed in Sulu clash&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ZAMBOANGA CITY, Philippines – At least 3 marines and an Abu Sayyaf member were killed in an encounter between government troops and the terrorist group in Patikul, Sulu, on Friday, October 26. Troops from the 61st, 62nd, and 64th Marine Companies clashed with Abu Sayyaf members under subleaders Alnijar Ekit and Aldi Alun in Barangay Timpook, Patikul, the military said. Three other soldiers sustained minor injuries and were brought to the KHTB Station Hospital for immediate medical attention. The military said the ongoing firefight also dealt casualties on the Abu Sayyaf side. Troops recover...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>3 soldiers killed in clash with Abu Sayyaf members in Sulu - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/10/26/marines-soldiers-killed-sulu-encounter.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEFNgnfeMdfKDmjcRHij4zEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMJbthQM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 05:55:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/10/26/marines-soldiers-killed-sulu-encounter.html" target="_blank"&gt;3 soldiers killed in clash with Abu Sayyaf members in Sulu&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, October 26) — Three soldiers were killed and three others injured in a clash with suspected Abu Sayyaf members Friday morning in Sulu. A report from the Armed Forces of the Philippines-Western Mindanao Command confirmed three marines were gunned down in an encounter with an undetermined number of bandits in Patikul town. The soldiers were members of the Joint Task Sulu under Brig. Gen. Rey Pabayo. No further details from the Abu Sayyaf side, but initial investigation showed a number of bandits were "severely wounded." The injured soldiers are now at the KHTB ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>6 Abu Sayyaf bandits surrender in Sulu - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1770570</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECcxuiLHNaMn-epIb_pCZQIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJiunQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 11:47:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1770570" target="_blank"&gt;6 Abu Sayyaf bandits surrender in Sulu&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SIX members of the Abu Sayyaf Group (ASG) have surrendered in the province of Sulu, the military said Tuesday, October 23. Lieutenant General Arnel Dela Vega, Western Mindanao Command (Westmincom) chief, identified them as follows: Mohammad Boyhe, Rojimar Dahim, Abdu Amidol, Kandang Abduhalim Jumadil, Tader Odong Asdure, and Matar Hajarani Saliling. Dela Vega said they have surrendered to the troops of the Joint Task Force Sulu last Friday in Maimbung, Sulu. He said the group surrendered through the efforts of Maimbung Mayor Samier Tan of Maimbung and Captain Rico Tagure of the Army’s 2nd S...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>2 Sayyafs killed, 4 others captured in Sulu - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1768708/Zamboanga/Local-News/2-Sayyafs-killed-4-others-captured-in-Sulu</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMX6du9DcYTk1_nkQn0TePcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJiunQM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 11:14:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1768708/Zamboanga/Local-News/2-Sayyafs-killed-4-others-captured-in-Sulu" target="_blank"&gt;2 Sayyafs killed, 4 others captured in Sulu&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;TWO Abu Sayyaf bandits were killed while four others were captured following a brief firefight in the province of Sulu, the military said Thursday, October 11. Lieutenant General Arnel Dela Vega, commander of the Western Mindanao Command (Westmincom), said the firefight broke out when the joint team of soldiers and policemen launched an operation around 1:30 a.m. Wednesday in Kajatian village, Indanan, Sulu. Dela Vega said the firefight resulted in the death of two Abu Sayyaf bandits, Jade Hassan alias Radjik and Kemar Jade. The Westmincom commander said captured were: Lino Tantung, 42; Ham...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>PRO-Zamboanga awards ‘Merit Medal’ to 14 policemen - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1768355</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENS070asU58UdIw31N2u4woqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJiunQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2018 09:32:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1768355" target="_blank"&gt;PRO-Zamboanga awards ‘Merit Medal’ to 14 policemen&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOURTEEN policemen, including four officers, were awarded the “Medalya ng Kagalingan (PNP Merit Medal)” for their accomplishments in the campaign against the Abu Sayyaf Group (ASG) and other lawless elements in Zamboanga Peninsula. Chief Inspector Helen Galvez, Police Regional Office (PRO)-Zamboanga Peninsula information officer, said Chief Superintendent Emmanuel Luis Licup, director, led the awarding ceremony which was held Monday, October 8, in Camp Colonel Romeo Abendan. Camp Abendan houses the headquarters of the PRO-Zamboanga Peninsula in Mercedes village, this city. The awardees of t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>FAST FACTS: Who is incoming DSWD Secretary Rolando Bautista? - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/newsbreak/iq/213579-things-to-know-rolando-bautista</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGmFCgvLvBIqCVzTVSg4U3gqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJ_jmQI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 04:44:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/newsbreak/iq/213579-things-to-know-rolando-bautista" target="_blank"&gt;FAST FACTS: Who is incoming DSWD Secretary Rolando Bautista?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – Army Chief Lieutenant General Rolando Bautista is set to take on a civilian post after he reaches his mandatory retirement age of 56 on October 15. President Rodrigo Duterte announced on Thursday, October 4, that Bautista will become the next Department of Social Welfare and Development secretary. Duterte first toyed with the idea of Bautista as head of the National Food Authority to replace Jason Aquino, but he changed his mind. Once appointed as department secretary, the army chief would be joining retired military officers in the Cabinet, such as National Security A...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Martial law helped lessen violence in ARMM – report - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/213348-martial-law-helped-lessen-violence-armm-conflict-alert-2018</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKu_Q5fkM-p86Fs4IQq2RhQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 10:15:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/213348-martial-law-helped-lessen-violence-armm-conflict-alert-2018" target="_blank"&gt;Martial law helped lessen violence in ARMM – report&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – President Rodrigo Duterte’s martial law in Mindanao helped lessen violence in the Autonomous Region in Muslim Mindanao (ARMM) by discouraging armed groups from bringing out their weapons. This was one of the findings of the 2018 Conflict Alert report, launched on Tuesday, October 2. “It disabled the ability of armed groups to take out their weapons….The biggest effect we saw of martial law is control of the weapons,” said Francisco Lara Jr, Senior Peace and Conflict Adviser in Asia for International Alert Philippines. Lara was among those who presented the report to m...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Duterte awards medals to wounded soldiers - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1766127</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKXcv5co3ryp6v6HUtJOcRwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJiunQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2018 12:55:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1766127" target="_blank"&gt;Duterte awards medals to wounded soldiers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOURTEEN soldiers who were recently wounded in a clash against the Abu Sayyaf bandits received medals with the Order of Lapu-Lapu level of Kampilan in an awarding ceremony led by no less than President Rodrigo Duterte, a military official said on Tuesday, September 25. Lieutenant Colonel Gerry Besana, Western Mindanao Command (Wesmincom) information officer, said the awarding ceremony was held on Monday when President Duterte visited the Joint Task Force-Sulu headquarters in Camp General Teodulfo Bautista in Jolo, Sulu. Besana said the 14 awardees were the following: Second Lieutenant Manny...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Militants Free 3 Indonesian Hostages in Southern Philippines - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/militants-free-3-indonesian-hostages-in-southern-philippines/4573604.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBjztFqhLD6Z5CSLkdfGlmoqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2018 08:54:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/militants-free-3-indonesian-hostages-in-southern-philippines/4573604.html" target="_blank"&gt;Militants Free 3 Indonesian Hostages in Southern Philippines&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Muslim militants have freed three Indonesian men they kidnapped at sea early last year off Malaysia then brought them to their jungle hideouts in the southern Philippines, officials said Sunday. The Indonesians were freed Friday with the help of the Moro National Liberation Front, a rebel group that signed a peace deal with the Philippine government, in Indanan town in Sulu province, police said. The released hostages, Hamdam Salim, Subandi Sattuh and Sudarlan Samansung, were to be handed to the Indonesian ambassador in southern Zamboanga city later Sunday, the military said. Taken off Born...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Military denies claims of Sulu massacre - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1764727</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGOarvZ6qFpjjzK7vmAUjBQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKmgnQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 09:36:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1764727" target="_blank"&gt;Military denies claims of Sulu massacre&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE Armed Forces of the Philippines (AFP) on Monday, September 17, insisted that the September 14 encounter in Patikul, Sulu was legitimate, not a massacre as claimed by some sectors. “We stand firm in our report that this was a legitimate encounter contrary to enemy propaganda that it was a “massacre,” AFP spokesperson Colonel Edgard Arevalo said. “The site of the encounter is a notorious ASG territory. That is a fact established by military and human intelligence. The folks of Patikul knows it very well such that no civilians dared to go or pass by the place,” he added. The military claim...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Davao Region placed under threat level 3 - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1765348</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHQ6gN-ZuATMU2Nu6bDjI7sqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKeunQM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 12:34:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1765348" target="_blank"&gt;Davao Region placed under threat level 3&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;DAVAO Region has been placed under terrorism threat level 3 due to the prevailing security situation in neighboring region. Philippine Army 1003rd Brigade commander Brigadier General Ernesto Torres told reporters on Wednesday, September 19, that Davao region’s threat level was raised to Level 3, citing a strong possibility of terror attacks within a short period of time due to reports of bombings, plans of the Abu Sayyaf Group (ASG), remnants of the Maute Group and the Bangsamoro Islamic Freedom Fighters (BIFF) and the kidnap for ransom groups. Based on the legend of terrorism threat level,...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>7 Abu Sayaf killed, 17 soldiers wounded in Sulu clash - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1764557</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMVzOaOAzX0xFln_nQhj8DAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJiunQM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2018 14:32:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1764557" target="_blank"&gt;7 Abu Sayaf killed, 17 soldiers wounded in Sulu clash&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SEVEN Abu Sayyaf Group (ASG) members were killed while 23 others wounded, including 17 soldiers, in a firefight in the province of Sulu, a top military official said Saturday, September 15. Lieutenant General Arnel Dela Vega, Western Mindanao Command (Wesmincom) chief, said the firefight broke out around 1:30 p.m. Friday in the village of Bakong, Patikul, Sulu. Dela Vega said the troops were on combat operations when they chanced some 100 Abu Sayyaf bandits led by ASG one-armed leader Radullan Sahiron and sub-leaders Hatib Hajan Sawadjaan and Idang Susukan in the village of Bakong. Sahiron ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Were 7 killed in Sulu encounter Abu Sayyaf or not? - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/212088-killed-in-sulu-encounter-abu-sayyaf-or-not</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBe0EBQ6KLWfN0pd1WHlgYkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2018 13:06:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/212088-killed-in-sulu-encounter-abu-sayyaf-or-not" target="_blank"&gt;Were 7 killed in Sulu encounter Abu Sayyaf or not?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – Seven alleged members of the terrorist group Abu Sayyaf were killed in an encounter on Friday, September 14, according to a report of Joint Task Force Sulu headed by Brigadier General Divino Rey Pabayo. The number of dead was based on a body count, according to a press statement from Lieutenant Colonel Gerry Besana, public affairs officer of the Western Mindanao Command. Six others were reported injured, including ASG Senior Leader Hatib Hajan Sawadjaan, who was said to be seriously hit in his stomach and lower extremities. Miliary says they're terrorists: The same rep...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>3 Indonesian hostages freed by Abu Sayyaf - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1764573</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOmEl7hBOU9EP4n-cuaG-QIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKmgnQM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2018 09:51:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1764573" target="_blank"&gt;3 Indonesian hostages freed by Abu Sayyaf&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ABU Sayyaf group freed three Indonesians who they abducted on January in 2017, a military official said on Sunday, September 16. Western Mindanao Command spokesperson Lieutenant Colonel Gerry Besana said Hamdam Salim,34; Subandi Sattuh,27 and Sudarlan Samansung,41 were released to Brigadier General Divino Rey Pabayo Jr., commander of the Joint Task Force Sulu, former Governor Abdusakur Tan and Provincial Director of the Sulu Provincial Police Office Police Senior Superintendent Labra in Barangay Buanza, Indanan, Sulu around 4 p.m. on Saturday, September 15. The said hostages were forcibly t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Troops, Abu Sayyaf bandits clash in Sulu - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1763787</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBApUYxmrG1YqjIo5CAgxj4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJiunQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 10:58:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1763787" target="_blank"&gt;Troops, Abu Sayyaf bandits clash in Sulu&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;AN ABU Sayyaf Group (ASG) member was killed in a clash with military troops as offensive continues in a bid to rescue the kidnap victims in the island province of Sulu, the military said. Lieutenant General Arnel Dela Vega, Western Mindanao Command (Westmincom) chief, said the clash happened around 9 a.m. Monday, September 10, when Army’s 21st Infantry Battalion troops chanced upon 60 ASG bandits in Bungkaong village, Patikul, Sulu. Dela Vega said the troops were on security operation when they clashed with the bandit group led by ASG sub-leaders Almujer Yadah and Idang Suskan in Barangay B...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Murder charges filed vs. suspects in Basilan bombing - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/09/10/basilan-suspect-murder-charges.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENJcILL4GQMGOA36gmVf_DwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMJbthQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 06:34:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/09/10/basilan-suspect-murder-charges.html" target="_blank"&gt;Murder charges filed vs. suspects in Basilan bombing&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, September 10) — The Philippine National Police (PNP) said murder cases were filed against suspects in the car bomb blast in Lamitan, Basilan that killed 10 people in July. PNP Chief Oscar Albayalde said Monday 18 suspects behind the attack were charged with two separate cases of murder and multiple frustrated murder in the Regional Trial Court Branch Two of Isabela City. Eight of the suspects are now in police custody while ten remain at large and are the subject of manhunt operations, Albayalde added. Police also said the group behind the attack was led by Fu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>8 suspects in Lamitan City bombing arrested - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1763557</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMDpovuhDPAZCkYBcAN_NPEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKmgnQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 03:39:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1763557" target="_blank"&gt;8 suspects in Lamitan City bombing arrested&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE Philippine National Police (PNP) has arrested at least eight persons for their alleged involvement in the Lamitan City bombing that killed 10 people, including soldiers, government militiamen and their families. The eight arrested suspects and their role in the said incident are as follows: 1. Musa Jallaha -- Middleman for the purchase of the van, helped in loading the IED components and painted the van color white using spray paint 2. Hadji Hurang, alias Nura Narimin -- Kept the detached van seats and white gallons containing traces of IED components 3. Nsir Nuruddin, alias Battuh Mura...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Treasury sanctions target Islamic State recruiters - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/27203cd90c1e474bb1149b3fb5490fbe</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPNgC1-stgt90cioSKeWiD4qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Aug 2018 18:31:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/27203cd90c1e474bb1149b3fb5490fbe" target="_blank"&gt;Treasury sanctions target Islamic State recruiters&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The United States on Friday sanctioned three members of the Islamic State who were featured in a beheading video distributed by the group and accused of luring recruits in Southeast Asia. The Treasury Department sanctions target Mohamad Rafi Udin, Mohammed Karim Yusop Faiz and Mohammad Reza Lahaman Kiram. The action freezes any interest they have in property within U.S. jurisdiction and blocks Americans from engaging in transactions with them. The U.N. Security Council sanctioned the same three on Thursday. As of late last year, Udin was believed to be the most senior Mala...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>1 Abu Sayyaf member dead, 20 soldiers wounded in Sulu clash - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/regional/2018/08/23/Abu-Sayyaf-Sulu-clash.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBMiwQxIZ7k6316oipn1K7wqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMPHhmQI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2018 10:49:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/regional/2018/08/23/Abu-Sayyaf-Sulu-clash.html" target="_blank"&gt;1 Abu Sayyaf member dead, 20 soldiers wounded in Sulu clash&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, August 23) — An Abu Sayyaf member was killed while 20 soldiers were wounded in a clash in Sulu on Thursday, the military said. Government troops fought at least 40 bandits in Barangay Langhub in Patikul town at around 9:30 a.m., the Western Mindanao Command said. It said a certain Alpata Abdurasa was killed in the 45-minute firefight, while a number of Abu Sayyaf fighters were hurt. On the government side, 18 had shrapnel injuries while two had gunshot wounds, the military said. They were rushed to the Camp Teodulfo Bautista Station Hospital for treatment. The...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>Briones: Travel advisory - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1759493</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBm7MbgGule0I9khBWhy6wcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMMu4nAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2018 15:45:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1759493" target="_blank"&gt;Briones: Travel advisory&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;I UNDERSTAND why the British government would issue an advisory to its nationals urging them not to travel to western and central Mindanao and the Sulu archipelago. After all, some of these areas are affected by the ongoing conflict between Muslim separatists and the Philippine government. This region is also home to members of the Abu Sayyaf, who use religion as a shield to hide their true intent. You know, kidnappings, extortion and what-not. So yes, it would be prudent for British people and any other foreigner not to include this part of the country in their itinerary because they’d mak...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Briones: A ‘terrorist’ in our midst - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1758803</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEg8jabhYZjl6mzjfJ5nSVkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJeunQM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Aug 2018 16:03:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1758803" target="_blank"&gt;Briones: A ‘terrorist’ in our midst&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THEY come in all shapes and sizes. Ages, too. And terrorists don’t care what method or soldiers they use or deploy on the field as long as they achieve the desired effect. According to Peter W. Singer, a former expert, strategist and senior fellow at the Brookings Institution, an American research group, 300,000 boys and girls under 18 serve as combatants in almost 75 percent of the world’s conflicts. Some 18 percent of the fighters are younger than 12 years old. They offer terrorist group leaders “cheap and easy recruits who provide new options to strike at their foes.” Here in the Philipp...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Suspected Abu Sayyaf member falls in Carcar - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1758486</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFPoBlBaGrEoPWvXxQpZVhUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJeunQM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 14:58:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1758486" target="_blank"&gt;Suspected Abu Sayyaf member falls in Carcar&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;LESS than 24 hours after the local enforcement units said they have not received threats in southern Cebu, a suspected Abu Sayyaf member was caught in a raid in Barangay Ocaña, Carcar City past 3 a.m. yesterday. The arrest of Oger Roma Pelonio, also known as Juncal and Aktoy, came after Malacañang ordered a surveillance on him. The directive was based on intelligence reports from the military, dyLA radio reported. Pelonio, 69, denied being an Abu Sayyaf member and disowned the evidence seized from him. “I even served in the army before and now I was accused of being part of the Abu Sayyaf? ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Abu Sayyaf leader killed in Sulu clash - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1758183</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAlBkFfVhCHe2-xoz3lN7owqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJiunQM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2018 14:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1758183" target="_blank"&gt;Abu Sayyaf leader killed in Sulu clash&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;AN ABU Sayyaf Group (ASG) leader was killed in a clash with government troops in the hinterlands of Sulu, the military said Wednesday, August 15, 2018. Rear Admiral Rene Medina, Naval Forces Western Mindanao (NFWM) commander, said slain was Abdul Ajim Abdulgani alais Suraka Ingog, a sub-leader of the ASG and an explosive expert. Medina said the clash ensued when joint marine and police troopers in an operation spotted a group of Abu Sayyaf bandits in Latih village, Patikul, Sulu. Medina said Abdulgani to the group of the late Muamar Askali alias Abu Rami, who was killed in a clash with gove...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Neighbors say suspected abu kept to himself - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1758650</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELBUJYTX5waIjgEzc0YswNcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJeunQM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2018 16:26:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1758650" target="_blank"&gt;Neighbors say suspected abu kept to himself&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;OGER Pelonio and his wife lived a peaceful and private life during his five-year stay in Barangay Ocaña, Carcar City, so it came as a huge shock to his neighbors in Sitio Bonbon when intelligence officers from the military and the police served a search warrant on his doorstep last Thursday dawn. “Sulod, gawas ra gud na siya sa ila. Di na makighalobilo namo diri sa mga tambay, private gud na siya (He didn’t mingle with us and was private),” a resident, who requested anonymity, told SunStar Cebu. Pelonio, who told reporters that he was Roman Catholic, rented a room in an all-blue house besid...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Basilan blast victim dies - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/209110-gerry-inso-basilan-bombing-dies</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAa98LOH10uucaEv3wFv9-0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 07:41:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/209110-gerry-inso-basilan-bombing-dies" target="_blank"&gt;Basilan blast victim dies&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ZAMBOANGA CITY, Philippines – The death toll in the Basilan bombing climbed to 11 after a blast victim died while undergoing treatment in this city. Gerry Inso, a militia man, died after nearly a week in the hospital Tuesday night, August 7. He died of irreversible brain damage due to severe blood loss caused by blast injuries. Inso was among the 9 who were injured in the van explosion in Lamitan City on July 31, which claimed 10 lives that day. Authorities earlier said the van carried soldiers, militiamen, their relatives, and the driver who detonated the improvised explosive device in the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Abu Sayyaf ‘spotter’ arrested - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1757180</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMuuoKGnaRMxV68AuzWJMpcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJiunQM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2018 12:28:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1757180" target="_blank"&gt;Abu Sayyaf ‘spotter’ arrested&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;JOINT police and military operatives have arrested an alleged Abu Sayyaf bandit and seized bomb-making components in this southern port city, an official announced Thursday. Majid Isnilon, 25, was arrested around 2:30 a.m. Tuesday, August 7 in Barangay Pasilmanta, according to Chief Inspector Helen Galvez, Police Regional Office-Zamboanga Peninsula information officer. Isnilon has standing warrants of arrest for murder and multiple attempted murder issued by two courts in Zamboanga City. Galvez said the suspect is also the “spotter” and messenger of Sulu-based Abu Sayyaf sub-leader Hatib Sa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Military foils bombing attempt in North Cotabato - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/08/08/North-Cotabato-bombing-BIFF.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFjKT5vmGIyg4wdaIRTSCAAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMJbthQM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 05:38:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/08/08/North-Cotabato-bombing-BIFF.html" target="_blank"&gt;Military foils bombing attempt in North Cotabato&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, August 8) — The military on Wednesday killed two suspected Bangsamoro Islamic Freedom Fighters (BIFF) members allegedly planning to deploy bombs in North Cotabato. Western Mindanao Command (Wesmincom) spokesperson Lieutenant Colonel Gerry Besana said the two unidentified suspects were crossing a checkpoint in Barangay Sangat in M'lang early Wednesday morning. When military officials approached them, the suspects started acting suspiciously and attempted to escape. Besana said the suspects fired at the soldiers, prompting the troops to return fire, which led to...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>Bangsamoro law to be 'vaccine' vs terrorism - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/208966-bangsamoro-organic-law-vaccine-vs-terrorism</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDDq7cvWupXTXGxO28eXnXgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2018 10:38:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/208966-bangsamoro-organic-law-vaccine-vs-terrorism" target="_blank"&gt;Bangsamoro law to be 'vaccine' vs terrorism&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – President Rodrigo Duterte formally handed the Bangsamoro Organic Law (BOL) to Moro Islamic Liberation Front (MILF) chairman Al Haj Murad Ebrahim on Monday, August 6, marking a milestone in the group's efforts to bring peace to Mindanao. The landmark law was presented by Duterte to Murad during a ceremony in Malacañang, in the presence of Congress leaders and Cabinet members. The BOL is a significant step to stopping the spread of terrorism and extremist beliefs in Mindanao, a region that has been besieged with conflict, said Deputy Presidential Peace Process Adviser Na...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Philippine Bombing Kills 10, Showing Insurgents Remain a Problem - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/07/30/world/asia/philippines-bombing-abu-sayyaf.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFZp-MPj-3B33k6l1G7QupoqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzwwt4QY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 03:56:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/07/30/world/asia/philippines-bombing-abu-sayyaf.html" target="_blank"&gt;Philippine Bombing Kills 10, Showing Insurgents Remain a Problem&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Officials say the blast was carried out by Abu Sayyaf, a militant group that besieged the southern city of Marawi for five months.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>Abu Sayyaf behind Basilan van blast - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/208536-abu-sayyaf-behind-basilan-blast-july-31-2018</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM_ua8b9ElgUEohKcIrf6SkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 04:57:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/208536-abu-sayyaf-behind-basilan-blast-july-31-2018" target="_blank"&gt;Abu Sayyaf behind Basilan van blast&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – The Abu Sayyaf group was behind the deadly van explosion in Lamitan City, Basilan, the Armed Forces of the Philippines (AFP) said on Tuesday, July 31. In a Camp Aguinaldo press briefing, AFP Spokesperson Edgard Arevalo said Abu Sayyaf Basilan commander Furuji Indama had a hand in the blast. Indama, Arevalo said, is a "hardline member" of the Abu Sayyaf, refusing to surrender despite intensified community relations efforts of the AFP. In a phone interview with Rappler, Western Mindanao Command chief Lieutenant General Arnel dela Vega said Indama's group may be "trying t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Islamic State claims southern Philippine blast that killed 11 - Reuters</title><link>https://internal.www.reuters.com/article/us-philippines-militants/islamic-state-claims-southern-philippine-blast-that-killed-11-idUSKBN1KL07P?feedType=RSS&amp;feedName=worldNews</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMwzCcj09VparInyctV7QOoqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 12:05:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://internal.www.reuters.com/article/us-philippines-militants/islamic-state-claims-southern-philippine-blast-that-killed-11-idUSKBN1KL07P?feedType=RSS&amp;feedName=worldNews" target="_blank"&gt;Islamic State claims southern Philippine blast that killed 11&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A bomb exploded in a van in the restive southern Philippines on Tuesday, killing 11 people at a military checkpoint in what militant group Islamic State called a suicide attack for which it claimed responsibility. The blast took place on Basilan, the island stronghold of the Abu Sayyaf group notorious for kidnapping and banditry, which was the home of the former "emir" of Islamic State in Southeast Asia, killed last year by Philippine troops. A suspected bomber, a soldier, five paramilitary troopers and four civilians, including a mother and her child, were killed and seven people were woun...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://internal.www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Basilan blast 'looks like a suicide bombing' – Lorenzana - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/208599-basilan-blast-looks-like-suicide-bombing</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFFmNnwQLLX_kze87m1IZBIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 23:26:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/208599-basilan-blast-looks-like-suicide-bombing" target="_blank"&gt;Basilan blast 'looks like a suicide bombing' – Lorenzana&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – Defense Secretary Delfin Lorenzana said the blast in Basilan that killed at least 11 people, including the driver of the van that exploded, appeared to have been a "suicide bombing." In a text message to Rappler on Tuesday, July 31, hours after the blast, Lorenzana said, "It looks like a suicide bombing as the driver of the van with explosives was the one who detonated it, killing himself in the process." If true, it would be the first known case of suicide bombing in the Philippines, right at the birthplace of the Abu Sayyaf, which the militay said was behind the expl...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Military: ISIS claim in deadly Basilan blast a 'terrorist propaganda' - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/08/01/Basilan-blast-car-bomb-explosion-ISIS.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAornD_zMVumAfyG3A6dlmUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMJbthQM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2018 04:58:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/08/01/Basilan-blast-car-bomb-explosion-ISIS.html" target="_blank"&gt;Military: ISIS claim in deadly Basilan blast a 'terrorist propaganda'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, August 1) — The military on Wednesday refused to acknowledge the claim of the Islamic State group or ISIS that it was responsible for the car bomb attack in Lamitan, Basilan that killed 10 people. "Any terrorist group or organization can conveniently claim responsibility and ride on the incident for their own glorification. Jumping into it will be like aiding their narrative and lending themselves (the people) as instruments of terrorists' propaganda," the Armed Forces of the Philippines said in a statement. ISIS, through a statement carried by its news agency...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>Palace to public: Stop speculating about Basilan bombing - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1756141?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHqFrfRLXPzV8vhzWUbwYXEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKmgnQM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 08:17:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1756141?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;Palace to public: Stop speculating about Basilan bombing&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MALACAÑANG called on the public on Friday, August 3, to refrain from speculating about the July 31 explosion in Basilan that killed 10 people. Speaking to reporters in Bukidnon, Presidential Spokesperson Harry Roque Jr. said it would be best to await the conclusion of the ongoing investigation into the reported suicide bombing in the restive southern Philippines. "It's very easy to claim credit for an attack but we're not concluding anything yet because investigation has just started," Roque said. "For now, I ask the public to cease and desist from making any speculation and let's await for...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Duterte OKs bill creating Muslim autonomous region in south - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/a24ca6e1a9224a9c96e46d343ebeb69a</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENEQouBsrVeBhe7LGlxzumEqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2018 00:38:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/a24ca6e1a9224a9c96e46d343ebeb69a" target="_blank"&gt;Duterte OKs bill creating Muslim autonomous region in south&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines (AP) — Philippine President Rodrigo Duterte has signed legislation creating a new Muslim autonomous region aimed at settling nearly half a century of Muslim unrest in the south, where troops crushed an attempt last year by Islamic State group-linked militants to turn a city into a stronghold. Presidential spokesman Harry Roque and another key aide, Bong Go, told reporters without elaborating late Thursday that Duterte signed the bill creating the region, to be called Bangsamoro. The autonomy deal, which has been negotiated for more than two decades under four presidents,...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>50 soldiers get meritorious promotion - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1755389?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDc9hObGpqr-bsWlQYlqURoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJiunQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 01:52:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1755389?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;50 soldiers get meritorious promotion&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;FIFTY gallant soldiers, who helped liberate Marawi City from the Islamic State for Iraq and Syria (ISIS)-inspired Maute group, have received meritorious promotion. Lieutenant Colonel Gerry Besana, Western Mindanao Command (Wesmincom) information officer, said 48 of the 50 promoted soldiers belong to the Army’s 1st and 5th Scout Ranger Battalions. Besana said that one of the remaining two is from the Army’s 101st Infantry Brigade and other one is from the 12th Light Reaction Company. He said National Defense Secretary Delfin Lorenza led the simple donning of ranks ceremony held on at Kuta He...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Duterte to Abu Sayyaf: 'Let's talk' - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/208358-duterte-abu-sayyaf-lets-talk</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB2EeFbIk2ZW47uAUzpHUa8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2018 01:24:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/208358-duterte-abu-sayyaf-lets-talk" target="_blank"&gt;Duterte to Abu Sayyaf: 'Let's talk'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – President Rodrigo Duterte said on Friday, July 27, that he wants to dialogue with terrorist group Abu Sayyaf to bring an end to bloodshed in Mindanao. "Mag-usap na lang. Iyong Abu Sayyaf, mag-usap na lang tayo. Ano bang gawain natin? Magpatayan tayong lahat (Let's talk. The Abu Sayyaf, let's just talk. What do we do? Just kill each other)?" Duterte said in a speech in Jolo, Sulu, where the Abu Sayyaf operates from. It was not the first time for the President to express his openness to a dialogue with the Abu Sayyaf. Days before he formally assumed the presidency in 201...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Zamboanga tightens security after Basilan blast - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1755640?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEECqpZs9y8Hgo_G4KzQEqBMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJiunQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 11:09:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1755640?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;Zamboanga tightens security after Basilan blast&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ZAMBOANGA City Mayor Maria Isabelle Climaco-Salazar on Tuesday, July 31, advised the public to remain vigilant even as she alerted the security forces to tighten security measures following the car explosion in Basilan province. Salazar convened a meeting in her office to discuss security measures in the city on the same day that an improvised explosive device went off inside a van in Lamitan City, Basilan. The explosion, which authorities blamed on the Abu Sayyaf Group, killed a soldier, a 10-year-old child, the driver of the van and eight others. Those who attended the meeting in Salazar’...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Lidasan: Thoughts and actions for the Bangsamoro - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1754506?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKQeeBPEa2qwas17UY7tkWIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKeunQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 15:10:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1754506?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;Lidasan: Thoughts and actions for the Bangsamoro&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MAHATMA Gandhi once said, “A man is but the product of his thoughts; What he thinks, he becomes”. I believe these words are powerful in addressing the problems of violent extremism in Mindanao. In our fight against violent extremism, we need to learn how the violent extremists think and act to advance their political agenda. The current Bangsamoro peace process tells us that the drivers for insurgency are almost always the same as the drivers of violent extremism. These drivers include feelings of being oppressed, a sense of victimhood, and the government not doing enough for their welfare....&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>6 killed in 2 clashes in Sulu - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1753776/Zamboanga/Local-News/6-killed-in-2-clashes-in-Sulu</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENaoLUrFrWOK_14o-Q6ZDRcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJiunQM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2018 06:12:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1753776/Zamboanga/Local-News/6-killed-in-2-clashes-in-Sulu" target="_blank"&gt;6 killed in 2 clashes in Sulu&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SIX people, including five Abu Sayyaf bandits, were killed while two others wounded in separate clashes as government offensive continue against the bandits in Sulu province, the military said Friday, July 20, 2018. The first clash happened at midnight of Wednesday in the boundary of the villages of Tanum and Liang, Patikul and the second around 9:30 a.m. Thursday in Tabu-Bato village, Maimbung. Brigadier General Divino Rey Pabayo, Joint Task Force Sulu commander, said the troops from the Army’s 45th Infantry Battalion were conducting focused military operation when they clashed at midnight...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>3 Abu Sayyaf members killed in Sulu clash - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1752445/Manila/Local-News/3-Abu-Sayyaf-members-killed-in-Sulu-clash</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP6j-i1pEK7uHRKnB8LU_OcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKmgnQM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2018 07:22:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1752445/Manila/Local-News/3-Abu-Sayyaf-members-killed-in-Sulu-clash" target="_blank"&gt;3 Abu Sayyaf members killed in Sulu clash&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(UPDATED) - Three suspected members of the Abu Sayyaf Group (ASG) and a soldier were killed in separate clashes between the terrorist group and government troops in Sulu, the military said Thursday, July 12. Brigadier General Divino Rey Pabayo, Joint Task Force Sulu commander, said the three ASG members were killed in a clash at around 4:30 a.m. Thursday in Kuppong village, Indanan town. The soldier was killed in a clash that took place at 1:55 p.m. Wednesday in Sitio Kan Apo Aluk in Panglayahan village, Patikul town. Ten other soldiers were wounded. Pabayo said the clash in Indanan ensued ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Westmincom honors 10 wounded soldiers - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1752803?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPah-Eq_djCfHNjIjy2UOvIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJiunQM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jul 2018 09:55:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1752803?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;Westmincom honors 10 wounded soldiers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE Western Mindanao Command (Westmincom) has awarded Wounded Personnel Medal (WPM) for gallantry in action to the soldiers who were wounded in a recent clash against the Abu Sayyaf bandits in Sulu province. Lieutenant General Arnel Dela Vega, Westmincom chief, awarded WPM during his visit on Friday to the soldiers at Camp Teodulfo Bautista Station Hospital in Jolo, Sulu. The recipients of WPM are the 10 soldiers from the Army’s 32nd Infantry Battalion who were wounded in a two-hour sporadic firefight with around 60 Abu Sayyaf bandits on Wednesday at Sitio Kan Apo Alu in Panglayahan village...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Duterte, Mahathir discuss violent extremism, sea piracy in meeting - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/207444-duterte-mahathir-discuss-extremism-sea-piracy-july-2018-meeting</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELk7LvkvMVz5vO6H_f7rsKgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 09:09:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/207444-duterte-mahathir-discuss-extremism-sea-piracy-july-2018-meeting" target="_blank"&gt;Duterte, Mahathir discuss violent extremism, sea piracy in meeting&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – Security concerns dominated the meeting between Philippine President Rodrigo Duterte and Malaysian Prime Minister Mahathir Mohamad on Monday, July 16. The meeting was held around 3 pm at the Prime Minister's Office in Putrajaya, federal administrative center of Malaysia. Malacañang said the two leaders discussed terrorism and transnational crimes. The issues were brought up by Duterte. (READ: Where Duterte, Mahathir stand on pressing ASEAN issues) "President Duterte pointed out the need to address terrorism and violent extremism in the region, as well as transnational ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Suspected Abu Sayyaf member arrested - SunStar Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1750336?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEQjtzmaqhYT_PgH7y6Z_CEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJiunQM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2018 10:06:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1750336?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;Suspected Abu Sayyaf member arrested&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;AUTHORITIES have arrested a suspected Abu Sayyaf member who was allegedly involved in the raid of a plantation 17 years ago in Basilan province, a police official announced Friday, June 29. Wahab Salapuddin, alias Abu Damdam, was served a warrant of arrest at 5:45 p.m. Thursday in the village of Sangali in Zamboanga City. Chief Inspector Shellamie Chang, Zamboanga City Police Office (ZCPO) information officer, said Salapuddin was wanted for seven counts of kidnapping with serious illegal detention. Chang said Salapuddin was allegedly involved in the raid of the Golden Harvest Plantation in ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Abu Sayyaf bandits seize child in Tawi-Tawi - SunStar Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1750035?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAcFuK38qFCU4FwAzpq6QWQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJiunQM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 10:38:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1750035?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;Abu Sayyaf bandits seize child in Tawi-Tawi&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;GUNMEN believed to be Abu Sayyaf bandits have seized a child following a brief shootout late Monday in an island town in Tawi-Tawi. The shootout resulted to the injury of the child’s mother identified as Rahsa Malyn Asta. Inspector Albert Carillo, Tandubas town police chief, identified the victim as Radzmalyn Asta, 7, who was taken around 9:30 p.m. Monday, June 27, at Sitio Polao Pinang in Himba village, Tandubas. Carillo said investigation showed that the Abu Sayyaf bandits aboard a motorboat arrived and docked at the establishment of Rahim Asta, the victim’s father, to buy gasoline. He sa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item></channel></rss>