<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Mikey Arroyo - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqJAgKIh5DQkFTRUFvS0wyMHZNRE4zYUdKeE9CSUNaVzRvQUFQAQ?hl=en-PH&amp;gl=PH&amp;ceid=PH:en</link><language>en-PH</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 11:48:51 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Supreme Court affirms junking of Mikey Arroyo tax case - INQUIRER.net</title><link>https://newsinfo.inquirer.net/1060144/supreme-court-affirms-junking-of-mikey-arroyo-tax-case</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiXGh0dHBzOi8vbmV3c2luZm8uaW5xdWlyZXIubmV0LzEwNjAxNDQvc3VwcmVtZS1jb3VydC1hZmZpcm1zLWp1bmtpbmctb2YtbWlrZXktYXJyb3lvLXRheC1jYXNl0gGuAWh0dHBzOi8vbmV3c2luZm8taW5xdWlyZXItbmV0LmNkbi5hbXBwcm9qZWN0Lm9yZy92L3MvbmV3c2luZm8uaW5xdWlyZXIubmV0LzEwNjAxNDQvc3VwcmVtZS1jb3VydC1hZmZpcm1zLWp1bmtpbmctb2YtbWlrZXktYXJyb3lvLXRheC1jYXNlL2FtcD9hbXBfanNfdj0wLjEjd2Vidmlldz0xJmNhcD1zd2lwZQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 04:58:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://newsinfo.inquirer.net/1060144/supreme-court-affirms-junking-of-mikey-arroyo-tax-case" target="_blank"&gt;Supreme Court affirms junking of Mikey Arroyo tax case&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;INQUIRER.net&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Supreme Court has affirmed the dismissal of the tax evasion case of former party-list Rep. Juan Miguel "Mikey" Arroyo.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://newsinfo.inquirer.net">INQUIRER.net</source></item><item><title>Because of OSG lapse, SC upholds Mikey Arroyo's acquittal in tax case - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/218236-supreme-court-upholds-mikey-arroyo-acquittal-tax-evasion-case</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHvv7W2HahpgnJ66hGr7AZQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 03:32:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/218236-supreme-court-upholds-mikey-arroyo-acquittal-tax-evasion-case" target="_blank"&gt;Because of OSG lapse, SC upholds Mikey Arroyo's acquittal in tax case&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The appeal is junked because the Office of the Solicitor General committed procedural lapses.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>SC upholds acquittal of Mikey Arroyo in ₱27-M tax evasion case - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/12/05/supreme-court-acquittal-Mikey-Arroyo-court-of-tax-appeals.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG45DqRE5zay_0bCkV3TZ8IqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMJbthQM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 06:05:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/12/05/supreme-court-acquittal-Mikey-Arroyo-court-of-tax-appeals.html" target="_blank"&gt;SC upholds acquittal of Mikey Arroyo in ₱27-M tax evasion case&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, December 5) — The Supreme Court (SC) has affirmed the acquittal of former Pampanga 2nd District Representative Juan Miguel "Mikey" Arroyo in his P27-million tax evasion case. In an extended resolution dated September 12, 2018, the high court said it junked the government's appeal assailing the Court of Tax Appeals' (CTA) decision to clear Arroyo "for its procedural defects and substantive deficiencies." SC upholds Arroyo "The CTA in Division, noting that the BIR (Bureau of Internal Revenue) did not discover the sources of Arroyo's vaunted income, fully disclos...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>Officials distribute educational aid to Porac residents - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1777407</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMa7BAIqQbEDd7SSn7pMGTMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJmtnQM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 14:53:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1777407" target="_blank"&gt;Officials distribute educational aid to Porac residents&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PAMPANGA. Former 2nd District congressman Mikey Arroyo and Porac mayoralty candidate Vice-Mayor Dexter Albert David and Team Dad led the recent distribution of educational assistance under the Ched Tulong Dunong Program at the Porac Gym. (Chris Navarro)&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Utzurrum: Amigos welcome a congresswoman - Sun.Star Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/cebu/lifestyle/2016/12/28/utzurrum-amigos-welcome-congresswoman-517281</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBu4SP3TLIM28Gl-qgUl0ykqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJeunQM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2016 13:56:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/cebu/lifestyle/2016/12/28/utzurrum-amigos-welcome-congresswoman-517281" target="_blank"&gt;Utzurrum: Amigos welcome a congresswoman&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Sun.Star Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;“YOU'RE looking great!” was the unanimous cry of the members of the Amigos de España as soon as former Philippine President and now Congresswoman Gloria Macapagal-Arroyo (GMA) set foot at the function room of Casino Español de Cebu. She was accompanied by dashing husband, lawyer Mike Arroyo and welcomed by Amigos president Amparito Lhuillier and club founder Don Jaime Picornell. The Amigos de España is very efficient secretary Myra Gonzalez reported that the members were in almost perfect attendance, when they learned that their guest would be Rep. GMA. As the lunch meeting progressed, Rep....&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">Sun.Star Philippines</source></item><item><title>LOOK: Duterte graces CGMA's 70th birthday - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2017/04/06/duterte-gma-birthday.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDAChl9XZa4b69-8IUuGqBEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMJbthQM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2017 08:54:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2017/04/06/duterte-gma-birthday.html" target="_blank"&gt;LOOK: Duterte graces CGMA's 70th birthday&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, April 6) — President Rodrigo Duterte joined former President and now Pampanga Representative Gloria Macapagal Arroyo on her 70th birthday celebration Wednesday night. The President was joined by his partner Honeylet Avanceña, and their daughter, Veronica, at Arroyo's house in La Vista Subdivision, Quezon City. Duterte gave a short message to the former President, who was accompanied by former First Gentleman Mike Arroyo. Arroyo, an ally of Duterte, was ousted as deputy house speaker after opposing the death penalty bill. Read more: House leaders remove Arroyo,...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>Dacawi: How do we? How can they? - Sun.Star Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/baguio/opinion/2017/10/06/dacawi-how-do-we-how-can-they-568118</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPCCcwHae_eB63vuP4jCVH4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMMu4nAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 14:21:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/baguio/opinion/2017/10/06/dacawi-how-do-we-how-can-they-568118" target="_blank"&gt;Dacawi: How do we? How can they?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Sun.Star Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;HOW do you bring attention to and action on issues of national and even international significance but which are glossed over and ignored by national decision-makers who, despite their pronouncements to the contrary, deem them insignificant and of local application? Of issue here is the Cordillera, this mountainous region that, time and again, is proclaimed – because it really is – as the watershed cradle of Northern Luzon and the nation’s resource base, its water harnessed and its gold extracted to spur national development. Of issue here is a historical injustice, yet an irony deemed insi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">Sun.Star Philippines</source></item><item><title>Speaker, Mike Arroyo twit De Lima: Is she mad? - ABS CBN News</title><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELFrOYLRIeA0cnIP5h8pbJwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow8IjwCjDw4s8CMNj9mQI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 01:13:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABS CBN News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Senator Leila de Lima is seen at the Plenary Hall of the Senate in Pasay City Monday. Voltaire Domingo, NPPA MANILA - House Speaker Pantaleon Alvarez and former first gentleman Mike Arroyo threw shade Tuesday at the mental fitness of Senator Leila de Lima after her latest tirades against the administration. This, after De Lima slammed the Duterte government for allowing a "reunion of criminals," allegedly including the Marcoses, former president Gloria Macapagal-Arroyo and alleged pork barrel scam mastermind Janet Lim Napoles. De Lima also urged the Cabinet to declare Duterte unfit to lead....&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Fisherfolks get P7-M assistance from BFAR - Sun.Star Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/pampanga/business/2017/05/10/fisherfolks-get-p7-m-assistance-bfar-541147</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHRvX8jH2QG88hNqdxtQl0MqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMMuPnAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2017 12:20:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/pampanga/business/2017/05/10/fisherfolks-get-p7-m-assistance-bfar-541147" target="_blank"&gt;Fisherfolks get P7-M assistance from BFAR&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Sun.Star Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;LUBAO -- Fisherfolks from the second district of Pampanga and other parts of the province received P7-million worth of assistance and programs from the Bureau of Fisheries and Aquatic Recourses (BFAR) at the Lubao Bamboo Hub, Wednesday, May 10. The assistance included 135 units of 20-footer motorized fibreglass boats, fishing paraphernalia and community fishing landing center (CFLC) projects and a recently inaugurated monitoring and control station. Leading the distribution were BFAR Regional Director Willy Cruz, Governor Lilia Pineda, Provincial Government Environment and Natural Resources...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">Sun.Star Philippines</source></item><item><title>Ombudsman charges 25 individuals for P900 million Malampaya Fund scam - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2016/12/27/ombudsman-25-officials-malampaya-fund-scam.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDRs-reW1irqPvz1re-CjAMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMJbthQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2016 13:07:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2016/12/27/ombudsman-25-officials-malampaya-fund-scam.html" target="_blank"&gt;Ombudsman charges 25 individuals for P900 million Malampaya Fund scam&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines) — A number of officials during the Arroyo administration have a lot of explaining to do at the anti-graft court. The Office of the Ombudsman on Tuesday finds probable cause to file charges against them over the P900-million Malampaya fund scam. Former officials at the Department of Budget and Management (DBM) and Department of Agrarian Reform (DAR), and representatives of non-government organizations (NGOs) are facing plunder, graft and fund malversation charges. Former President now Pampanga Representative Gloria Macapagal-Arroyo is not in the charge list. Th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>Police charge ex-lawmaker's driver over car crash - Sun.Star Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/pampanga/local-news/2017/01/26/police-charge-ex-lawmakers-driver-over-car-crash-522178</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDI8cgk-uQhkOFViEvKHFiMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJmtnQM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2017 16:38:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/pampanga/local-news/2017/01/26/police-charge-ex-lawmakers-driver-over-car-crash-522178" target="_blank"&gt;Police charge ex-lawmaker's driver over car crash&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Sun.Star Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BACOLOR - The driver of former Second District Representative Juan Miguel "Mikey" Arroyo is now facing charges over the head-on car collision involving him, the ex-lawmaker and another passenger onboard a Toyota Hilux which killed a policeman who was driving a Honda Civic in the mishap that transpired at the portion of the FVR Megadike in Bacolor town. On Monday, Arroyo and his two companions, driver John Michael Macaraeg and Edward Mendoza Montevergin figured in a car crash with Police Officer 3 Alexander Villamin of the Central Luzon Regional Public Safety Battalion in Barangay Maliwalu i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">Sun.Star Philippines</source></item><item><title>Rep. Mikey Arroyo hurt in vehicle collision; policeman in other car dead on the spot - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2017/01/24/mikey-arroyo-road-accident-pampanga.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJcQ0GL6E3qhNH_xg4lc1WMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMJbthQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2017 11:46:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2017/01/24/mikey-arroyo-road-accident-pampanga.html" target="_blank"&gt;Rep. Mikey Arroyo hurt in vehicle collision; policeman in other car dead on the spot&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines) — The driver of former Party-list Representative Juan Miguel "Mikey" Arroyo is facing charges related to the death of a policeman in a road accident on Monday. According to the spot report from the National Operations Center, the accident happened around 3:30 p.m. along the Mega Dike road in Bacolor, Pampanga. Arroyo; his driver, John Frederick Macaraeg; and another companion, Edward Mendoza, were aboard a Toyota Hi-Lux pick-up when they collided with a Honda Civic driven by PO2 Alexander VIllamin. Villamin was part of the Police Regional Public Safety Battali...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>Porac micro-entrepreneurs get loan assistance - Sun.Star Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/pampanga/local-news/2017/06/29/porac-micro-entrepreneurs-get-loan-assistance-550274</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMr8oG3mgcL7RGL9sMi8upkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKetnQM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2017 15:50:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/pampanga/local-news/2017/06/29/porac-micro-entrepreneurs-get-loan-assistance-550274" target="_blank"&gt;Porac micro-entrepreneurs get loan assistance&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Sun.Star Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PORAC -- Some 50 micro-entrepreneurs here received loan assistances from the Lourdes Tuason Arroyo Foundation Inc. through the facilitation of Mayor Condralito dela Cruz and Vice Mayor Dexter David. Dela Cruz and David led the distribution of P5,000 loan assistance each to 50 residents engaged in micro businesses in the town. The loans were presented at the Mayor’s Office the other day. The loans are payable within six months at zero percent interest. The loans, according to David, will provide start-up capital for the beneficiaries to improve and expand their businesses. He added that smal...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">Sun.Star Philippines</source></item><item><title>Aguilar: Be joyful and give thanks - Sun.Star Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/pampanga/opinion/2017/01/18/aguilar-be-joyful-and-give-thanks-520833</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC1eIEfkhx4OJYnKyldccLgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMMu4nAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2017 13:17:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/pampanga/opinion/2017/01/18/aguilar-be-joyful-and-give-thanks-520833" target="_blank"&gt;Aguilar: Be joyful and give thanks&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Sun.Star Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;“BE JOYFUL always and give thanks for this is God’s will for you in Christ Jesus” (2 Thessalonians: 16, 18). People from all walks of life are naturally happy on some occasions like Christmas and New Year, the happiness of Christian is not dependent on circumstances. It comes from what Christ has done, and it’s constant. Indeed, Christians are differentiated from the natural man in taking joy and giving thanks. Because of what God has done, they are continually thankful whatever the circumstances. And they are always joyful because they knew full that God causes all things to work for the g...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">Sun.Star Philippines</source></item><item><title>Cop dies, Mikey Arroyo injured after Pampanga car crash - Rappler</title><link>http://www.rappler.com/nation/159280-mikey-arroyo-pampanga-car-accident</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEId-eUz1caC4-eGk0hyyqxoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2017 14:33:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.rappler.com/nation/159280-mikey-arroyo-pampanga-car-accident" target="_blank"&gt;Cop dies, Mikey Arroyo injured after Pampanga car crash&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – Former Pampanga 2nd District and Ang Galing Pinoy Representative Juan Miguel Arroyo and his two companions were hurt, while a Central Luzon policeman was killed in a vehicular accident in Bacolor town in Pampanga on Monday afternoon, January 23. Police Officer 2 Alexander Villamin died after his Honda Civic crashed into the Toyota Hilux carrying Arroyo, Edward Mendoza Montervergin, and their driver John Macaraeg at around 3:30 pm along Maliwalu village on the megadike's eastern side. {source} LOOK: Sedan and pick-up truck in the aftermath of vehicular accident involvin...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Ex-lawmaker, 2 companions injured; policeman killed in car crash - Sun.Star Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/pampanga/local-news/2017/01/24/ex-lawmaker-2-companions-injured-policeman-killed-car-crash-521947</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH0xuRD4aScNo4eePt0hUTQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJmtnQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2017 15:07:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/pampanga/local-news/2017/01/24/ex-lawmaker-2-companions-injured-policeman-killed-car-crash-521947" target="_blank"&gt;Ex-lawmaker, 2 companions injured; policeman killed in car crash&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Sun.Star Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BACOLOR - Former Second District Representative Juan Miguel "Mikey" Arroyo and his two companions were injured while a Central Luzon policeman was killed in a car collision that transpired at the portion of FVR Megadike in Bacolor town on Monday at about 3:30 pm. According to Police Officer 2 Melchizedek Asuncion, investigator of the case, a metallic gray Toyota Hilux bearing conduction sticker VH-7847 driven by John Frederick Macaraeg and carrying Arroyo and Edward Mendoza Montevergin were headed to Porac town while a Honda Civic with plate number WFP-604 driven by Police Officer 2 Alexand...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">Sun.Star Philippines</source></item><item><title>Seeking DOF post in 2019? ‘It's so hypothetical,’ says Arroyo - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/216570-gloria-arroyo-bid-for-department-finance-post-2019-hypothetical</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPD0-lKfrYhYpaP3XZbgnwMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 04:50:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/216570-gloria-arroyo-bid-for-department-finance-post-2019-hypothetical" target="_blank"&gt;Seeking DOF post in 2019? ‘It's so hypothetical,’ says Arroyo&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – Speaker Gloria Macapagal Arroyo dispelled rumors she is thinking of joining President Rodrigo Duterte’s Cabinet next year as Department of Finance (DOF) secretary. The former president turned Pampanga 2nd District congresswoman was asked by reporters on Tuesday, November 13, about talks in the banking community that she would become the next DOF chief. “Ay, it's so hypothetical,” said Arroyo, who was smiling as she repeatedly shook her head. Arroyo, an economist who saw the passage on 3rd reading of Duterte’s second batch of tax reforms during her term as Speaker, is a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Mikey Arroyo eyes comeback in congressional bid - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1769032</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGJprR1RyrUguByZfTsoCYEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJmtnQM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2018 12:22:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1769032" target="_blank"&gt;Mikey Arroyo eyes comeback in congressional bid&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;FORMER Second District Representative Juan Miguel “Mikey” Arroyo is staging a comeback into politics as he filed his certificate of candidacy Friday, October 12, at the Commission on Elections (Comelec) office in the City of San Fernando. Former President and incumbent Pampanga Second District Representative Gloria Macapagal Arroyo is set to end her last term as congressional representative, a post which the younger Arroyo held in 2004 to 2010. At present, Mrs. Arroyo is the speaker of the House of Representatives. The younger Arroyo, running under the Lakas-Christian Muslims Democrats (CMD...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Sangil: Gloria, Baby and Vilma - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1763673</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMh47EPswhU_mTDtvh6QyboqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJmtnQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1763673" target="_blank"&gt;Sangil: Gloria, Baby and Vilma&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MORE than a year ago, I said in this space that it is only barber shop talks that former President and now House of Representatives Speaker Gloria Macapagal Arroyo and Governor Lilia “Nanay Baby” Pineda are preparing for the 2019 hustings and running for public office. Running as candidates, not sure. But getting involved in the coming elections? Yes they are. GMA for her favorite son former Congressman Mikey Arroyo who wants to succeed her in the second congressional district. And Nanay Baby for her favorite son Vice Governor Dennis “Delta” Pineda who is gunning for the top capitol post. L...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Manalansan, Arroyo visit Fighter Town - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1759432</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPyZz6_P-Lvm_o0XM32JqK0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJmtnQM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2018 14:07:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1759432" target="_blank"&gt;Manalansan, Arroyo visit Fighter Town&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PAMPANGA. Floridablanca Mayor Darwin Manalansan and former Pampanga Second District congressman Mikey Arroyo receive a warm welcome from officers of the Philippine Air Force Defense Command 5th Fighter Town in Basa Air Base during a recent visit. (Photo by Chris Navarro)&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>More CHEd scholarships available for Poraquenos - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1753301?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO86lZIXB766ViG540qfaQUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJmtnQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2018 13:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1753301?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;More CHEd scholarships available for Poraquenos&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PORAC Vice-Mayor Dexter David on Tuesday, July 17, announced the availability of 36 slots for P6,000 worth of educational assistance from the Commission on Higher Education (CHEd) through the effort of Second District Representative Gloria Macapagal Arroyo. The slots are part of the 50 secured by David with the help of Arroyo's son, Mikey Arroyo. David said that interested parties, who are not enrolled in state colleges and universities, may avail of the slots through application at the vice-mayor's office. David said that the financial assistance program aims to help indigents with their t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Sangil: The people of Lubao - Sun.Star Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1632681?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAWyU0uVxdysE5c5cjAgj8sqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJmtnQM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 12:35:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1632681?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;Sangil: The people of Lubao&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Sun.Star Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MOST people coming from Lubao town don't just give up a fight. Lubao is the town of the Macapagals, Pinedas, Dimsons, Danans, Paules, De la Rosas, Arrastias, Lingads, Bernals, Beltrans and many other illustrious surnames. They represented the true grit of a Kapampangan. They never gave up. Remember how then former President Gloria Macapagal Arroyo (GMA) was bedeviled by ex-President B.S. Noynoy Aquino?B.S. Aquino attacked with relentless passion the person of GMA, and only was too happy to see her clipped. Aside from sending her to a hospital arrest, he heaped all the blame to his predecess...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">Sun.Star Philippines</source></item><item><title>Tax court acquits Mikey Arroyo in P27-M tax evasion case - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/199146-mikey-arroyo-acquitted-cta-tax-evasion</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED8KgcxYE605NUAyLc1HFQoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 08:20:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/199146-mikey-arroyo-acquitted-cta-tax-evasion" target="_blank"&gt;Tax court acquits Mikey Arroyo in P27-M tax evasion case&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – The Court of Tax Appeals (CTA) has acquitted former Pampanga 2nd District representative Juan Miguel “Mikey” Arroyo in his P27 million tax evasion case. The court said it found insufficient the investigators' dependence on a computation method to charge the son of former president now Pampanga 2nd District Representative Gloria Macapagal-Arroyo. “Juan Miguel Arroyo is acquitted of the offenses charged in CTA Criminal Case Nos. O-247, O-248 and O-249 for failure of the prosecution to prove his guilt beyond reasonable doubt,” the CTA First Division said in a decision pro...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Guagua town honors Nicdao patriarch - Sun.Star Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/pampanga/local-news/2018/02/25/guagua-town-honors-nicdao-patriarch-590745</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELKXC2dPHdePoDgRltNTG0cqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKetnQM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2018 14:07:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/pampanga/local-news/2018/02/25/guagua-town-honors-nicdao-patriarch-590745" target="_blank"&gt;Guagua town honors Nicdao patriarch&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Sun.Star Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;GUAGUA--The municipal government has honored the late Ruperto Nicdao by erecting a commemorative marker and naming a boulevard after him. Ruperto Nicdao was a public school teacher who rose to the position of supervisor. Despite being a middle income earner, Nicdao and his wife were able to send 250 scholars from poor families to school during their lifetime. The Nicdao patriarch was an active member of non-government and civic organizations and tirelessly worked to improve the lives of the people in his town. Nicdao was the father of well known businessman Jesus "Jess" Nicdao. The commemor...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">Sun.Star Philippines</source></item><item><title>Politicos Make Good Actors - Sun.Star Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/pampanga/opinion/2017/12/17/politicos-make-good-actors-580214</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHq83OyUoK4rtZbBGXHVZBUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJmtnQM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2017 11:49:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/pampanga/opinion/2017/12/17/politicos-make-good-actors-580214" target="_blank"&gt;Politicos Make Good Actors&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Sun.Star Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;There’s a concept in literary criticism that art imitates life. Another school of thought asserts that life imitates art. When an actor acts the role of a madman that’s art depicting reality. There is an abundance of crazy people around. The closest example of this duality is the actor-politician. There are politicians who were actors first and became successful in the art of make believe in public office. Marquee names in a bygone period were Rogelio dela Rosa and Diosdado Macapagal. Their experience in zarzuela honed and developed their acting skills and the ability to manipulate people’s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">Sun.Star Philippines</source></item><item><title>Bondoc likely bet for guv in 2019 - Sun.Star Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/pampanga/local-news/2017/11/15/bondoc-likely-bet-guv-2019-574929</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO2kSq0Yq_7HQ8INjtm3mPgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKetnQM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2017 14:03:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/pampanga/local-news/2017/11/15/bondoc-likely-bet-guv-2019-574929" target="_blank"&gt;Bondoc likely bet for guv in 2019&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Sun.Star Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;CLARK FREEPORT -- What has long been rumored might, in fact, be reality. This, as PDP-Laban Central Luzon Chairman Tito Mendiola said last Friday during the forum of the Capampangan in Media Inc., (CAMI) here, that Pampanga Fourth District Representative Juan Pablo Bondoc will most probably be the party's official candidate in the 2019 gubernatorial race. "At this point, that appears to be the likely scenario," he said, noting that Bondoc has already been sworn in as member of the party. Bondoc used to be under the Nationalist Party Coalition (NPC). Mendiola, former mayor of Floridablanca t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">Sun.Star Philippines</source></item></channel></rss>