<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Sulu - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIggKIhxDQkFTRHdvSkwyMHZNREZ5WkdNMkVnSmxiaWdBUAE?hl=en-PH&amp;gl=PH&amp;ceid=PH:en</link><language>en-PH</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 11:04:05 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Indonesian abducted by Abu Sayyaf found in Sulu - ABS-CBN News</title><link>https://news.abs-cbn.com/news/12/06/18/indonesian-abducted-by-abu-sayyaf-found-in-sulu</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiVmh0dHBzOi8vbmV3cy5hYnMtY2JuLmNvbS9uZXdzLzEyLzA2LzE4L2luZG9uZXNpYW4tYWJkdWN0ZWQtYnktYWJ1LXNheXlhZi1mb3VuZC1pbi1zdWx10gEA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 08:41:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://news.abs-cbn.com/news/12/06/18/indonesian-abducted-by-abu-sayyaf-found-in-sulu" target="_blank"&gt;Indonesian abducted by Abu Sayyaf found in Sulu&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABS-CBN News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;LUUK, Sulu - An Indonesian national abducted by suspected Abu Sayyaf bandits was found by the Armed Forces in a remote village in this town Wednesday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/stories/CAAqOQgKIjNDQklTSURvSmMzUnZjbmt0TXpZd1NoTUtFUWk0bXFpbWpZQU1FUk1NbHJ2NGxNTzFLQUFQAQ?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;View full coverage on Google News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;</description><source url="https://news.abs-cbn.com">ABS-CBN News</source><media:content url="https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/proxy/LA9BldfoRirxXVlPjjJr5NiTGzoygtTnG2zk0F5Vy7mvi80vk3-27QKLi8ZP35pYxGJkOklHLcWFfePE6Xccs0pOvByNimpG71ou_WRjqPjbxmpHlNqX2Fn1Vg=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Military's 2022 plan: New army division vs Abu Sayyaf in Sulu - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/218280-military-create-infantry-divison-hunt-down-abu-sayyaf</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFVJDLZKNSBd9Obdj3-hS_UqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 10:46:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/218280-military-create-infantry-divison-hunt-down-abu-sayyaf" target="_blank"&gt;Military's 2022 plan: New army division vs Abu Sayyaf in Sulu&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The 11th Infantry Division will focus on the island province of Sulu, which has been a stronghold of the Abu Sayyaf and other terror groups.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>AFP hopes new infantry division will address Abu Sayyaf problem in Sulu - INQUIRER.net</title><link>https://newsinfo.inquirer.net/1060410/afp-hopes-new-infantry-division-will-address-abu-sayyaf-problem-in-sulu</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMibWh0dHBzOi8vbmV3c2luZm8uaW5xdWlyZXIubmV0LzEwNjA0MTAvYWZwLWhvcGVzLW5ldy1pbmZhbnRyeS1kaXZpc2lvbi13aWxsLWFkZHJlc3MtYWJ1LXNheXlhZi1wcm9ibGVtLWluLXN1bHXSAQA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 13:42:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://newsinfo.inquirer.net/1060410/afp-hopes-new-infantry-division-will-address-abu-sayyaf-problem-in-sulu" target="_blank"&gt;AFP hopes new infantry division will address Abu Sayyaf problem in Sulu&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;INQUIRER.net&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The AFP will create a new infantry division to be permanently stationed in Sulu to address the persisting problem of Abu Sayyaf.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://newsinfo.inquirer.net">INQUIRER.net</source><media:content url="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/proxy/SlgAO-T4iz2Ho6jeMRh4hmz5YjYy8wME4oJr2rX9ajK2yqUc48f7qgcHoNZaO4IYhhQ0eLZrdvM19FK9druCwK0wLKbeqJk7JntRURCBaQUVFg=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>5 soldiers killed in Sulu while rescuing hostages from Abu Sayyaf - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/216906-5-soldiers-killed-jolo-abu-sayyaf-november-2018</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEANVeG_GHkU1kxzw7nyOxm4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 08:00:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/216906-5-soldiers-killed-jolo-abu-sayyaf-november-2018" target="_blank"&gt;5 soldiers killed in Sulu while rescuing hostages from Abu Sayyaf&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – The Armed Forces of the Philippines (AFP) said on Saturday, November 17, that 5 soldiers were killed and 23 others were injured while ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>5 soldiers slain in Sulu going home as heroes - INQUIRER.net</title><link>https://newsinfo.inquirer.net/1054862/5-soldiers-slain-in-sulu-going-home-as-heroes</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiU2h0dHBzOi8vbmV3c2luZm8uaW5xdWlyZXIubmV0LzEwNTQ4NjIvNS1zb2xkaWVycy1zbGFpbi1pbi1zdWx1LWdvaW5nLWhvbWUtYXMtaGVyb2Vz0gGlAWh0dHBzOi8vbmV3c2luZm8taW5xdWlyZXItbmV0LmNkbi5hbXBwcm9qZWN0Lm9yZy92L3MvbmV3c2luZm8uaW5xdWlyZXIubmV0LzEwNTQ4NjIvNS1zb2xkaWVycy1zbGFpbi1pbi1zdWx1LWdvaW5nLWhvbWUtYXMtaGVyb2VzL2FtcD9hbXBfanNfdj0wLjEjd2Vidmlldz0xJmNhcD1zd2lwZQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 08:00:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://newsinfo.inquirer.net/1054862/5-soldiers-slain-in-sulu-going-home-as-heroes" target="_blank"&gt;5 soldiers slain in Sulu going home as heroes&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;INQUIRER.net&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Five soldiers are going home to their respective families as heroes.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://newsinfo.inquirer.net">INQUIRER.net</source></item><item><title>Duterte eyes revamp of military personnel in Jolo after recent deadly clashes - ABS CBN News</title><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG_oaOtQdnP-zviqrfhbshkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow8IjwCjDw4s8CMNj9mQI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 08:45:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABS CBN News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA—President Rodrigo Duterte on Friday said he will order a revamp of the military’s composition in Jolo, Sulu, following the deaths of several soldiers in recent clashes there. “In a few days I’m transferring one division sa Jolo. Nagsawa na ako. A fortnight ago, nag-usap kami ni Del (Defense Secretary Delfin Lorenzana) and I communicated to them my disappointment kung bakit gano’n, sige na lang tayo mamatayan,” Duterte said in a speech in Davao City. “It’s an attrition thing at tatapusin na natin iyan.” (In a few days I’m transferring one division in Jolo. I’ve grown tired of it. A fo...&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Comelec to hold two-day Bangsamoro plebiscite in January, February 2019 - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/12/07/comelec-bangsamoro-plebiscite.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELxkWn3Q21Tcd69bE6gVvFYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMJbthQM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 13:44:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/12/07/comelec-bangsamoro-plebiscite.html" target="_blank"&gt;Comelec to hold two-day Bangsamoro plebiscite in January, February 2019&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, December 7) — The plebiscite for the ratification of the Bangsamoro law will be split into two dates, the Commission on Elections (Comelec) announced Friday. The poll body said the initial plebiscite date of January 21, 2019 will still push through. However, another day was added for local government units which petitioned for voluntary inclusion in the region. The second day of the referendum is set on February 6, 2019. comelec bangsamoro In its press release, Comelec said the geographical areas comprising the Autonomous Region of Muslim Mindanao (ARMM)-- Su...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>Gov't, MILF kick off campaign for Bangsamoro plebiscite - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/218380-government-milf-plebiscite-campaign-period-kick-off</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELjJ4FqcSZrCfXEAx6B9GWsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 17:40:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/218380-government-milf-plebiscite-campaign-period-kick-off" target="_blank"&gt;Gov't, MILF kick off campaign for Bangsamoro plebiscite&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – Government officials and leaders of the Moro Islamic Liberation Front (MILF) urged the public to unite and take part in the plebiscite to ratify the landmark Bangsmaro Organic Law (BOL) in January 2019. “The BOL is for the welfare not only of the Bangsamoro people but (also of) non-Muslims residing in the Bangsamoro areas…. The BOL is a formula for peace, development, and progress,” MILF peace panel chair Mohagher Iqbal said in a statement Thursday night, December 6. The campaign period for the plebiscite started Friday, December 7, and will end on January 19, 2019. Th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Bangsamoro youth showcase innovative community projects - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1777036</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDUhxKcXXk0OnBpqQfdkzewqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMIeunQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 14:09:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1777036" target="_blank"&gt;Bangsamoro youth showcase innovative community projects&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;COTABATO CITY -- Young leaders from the Autonomous Region in Muslim Mindanao gathered in Cotabato City on November 22 to showcase various innovative projects implemented in their respective communities. The event served as a culminating activity for the successful first run of the Bangsamoro Young Leaders Program–Leadership Communities (BYLP–LeadCom), a partnership program implemented by Ayala Foundation, the Office of the Regional Governor–Autonomous Region in Muslim Mindanao (ORG–Armm), and the Eisenhower Fellows Association of the Philippines (Efap). A total of 35 fellows from the five A...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Sultan calls for unity among Muslim leaders ahead of BOL plebiscite - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1776799</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBrsmCgJRgGWxtiw87KyWicqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMIeunQM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 09:32:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1776799" target="_blank"&gt;Sultan calls for unity among Muslim leaders ahead of BOL plebiscite&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MADALUM, Lanao Del Sur -- A Maranao sultan has gathered some 500 traditional leaders from all over the two provinces of Lanao to put up a united front in supporting for the ratification of the Bangsamoro Organic Law (BOL) ahead of the plebiscite on January 21, 2019. Sultan Usman Sarangani Sr., the sultan of Uya-an and reigning paramount sultan of Mindanao, said he has gathered the datus and baes of Lanao del Sur and Lanao del Norte to explain to them that the BOL ratification needs their support. The BOL is a mechanism that will create the Bangsamoro Autonomous Region in Muslim Mindanao (BA...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>TWG against violent extremism created in Lanao Sur - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1776624</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE6uzhzoMHmp7auhCUxeYzUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMIeunQM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 12:59:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1776624" target="_blank"&gt;TWG against violent extremism created in Lanao Sur&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A TECHNICAL working group (TWG) composed of local government officials, religious leaders, as well as traditional leaders in Lanao del Sur was launched on Wednesday, November 21, in an aim to prevent and transform violent extremism. Assemblyman Zia Alonto Adiong (Lanao del Sur) said the TWG will be a policy-making body that will guide officials to combat violent extremism in their province. He said it is a collective effort of the provincial government of Lanao del Sur, Royal Sultanates of Lanao and the Ulamas to create programs that will address the threat of violent extremism and answer t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>5 killed, 23 wounded in Sulu clash - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1774603</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELezO6EFqXdsbeo07-Bzn_MqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJiunQM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 03:22:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1774603" target="_blank"&gt;5 killed, 23 wounded in Sulu clash&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ZAMBOANGA CITY -- Five soldiers were killed and 23 others, including an officer, were wounded in a clash with a group of Abu Sayyaf bandits in the hinterlands of Sulu. Lieutenant Colonel Gerry Besana, Western Mindanao Command (Westmincom) information officer, said the clash took place around 4:10 p.m. Friday, November 16, in the village of Liang, Patikul, Sulu. Besana said the troops from the Joint Task Force Sulu were conducting intensified military operation when they encountered 50 Abu Sayyaf bandits led by sub-leader Almujer Yadah. Besana said the firefight lasted for about one hour and...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>MILF chair confident in constitutionality of Bangsamoro law - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/11/19/milf-bangsamoro-law-constitutional.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJdWT5VzrkkNprOYr42TBtsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMJbthQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 08:13:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/11/19/milf-bangsamoro-law-constitutional.html" target="_blank"&gt;MILF chair confident in constitutionality of Bangsamoro law&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, November 19) — Moro Islamic Liberation Front (MILF) Chairman Al Haj Murad Ebrahim said his group remains confident of the constitutionality of the Bangsamoro law amid calls of a local government unit to stop its implementation. Murad on Monday addressed the Sulu government's petition to nullify the measure, and reiterated that it will not stop the peace process in Mindanao. "As far as the petition is concerned… we're very confident that the issue of constitutionality is well-addressed," Murad said during a joint media briefing with the Armed Forces of the Phi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>6 Sayyafs surrender amid military offensive - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1774965</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPwAYlnXzXVkeOh7-u2BgqAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJiunQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1774965" target="_blank"&gt;6 Sayyafs surrender amid military offensive&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SIX Abu Sayyaf Group (ASG) members have surrendered to authorities due to pressures of continuous military offensive in Sulu, officials said Tuesday, November 20. Lieutenant Colonel Gerry Besana, Western Mindanao Command (Westmincom) information officer, said the group surrendered around 8 a.m. Monday to the 2nd Special Forces Battalion headed by Lieutenant Colonel Jessie Montoya in Talipao, Sulu. Besana identified them as follows: Annuar Sumlahani Dalawis alias Urban; Arsi Kalam Akili; Nassal Asaral; Alvarez Sadjan alias Tundok; Aysal Ajaral alais Taki; and Medzmar Mursin alias Choy. He sa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>5 soldiers killed in clash vs. Abu Sayyaf - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/regional/2018/11/17/soldiers-killed-abu-sayyaf-sulu-clash.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIyB2Q0OyzDjRN-O70D2x3AqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMPHhmQI</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 06:26:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/regional/2018/11/17/soldiers-killed-abu-sayyaf-sulu-clash.html" target="_blank"&gt;5 soldiers killed in clash vs. Abu Sayyaf&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, November 17) — Five soldiers were killed while 23 others were wounded when they fought members of the Abu Sayyaf group in Patikul, Sulu Friday, the military said Saturday. According to the military's Western Mindanao Command, the firefight lasted for more than an hour at Barangay Liang at around 4 p.m. An initial report said the soldiers encountered around 50 Abu Sayyaf fighters under leader Almuder Yadah. The Abu Sayyaf group is one of the foreign terrorist organizations listed by the United States Department of State. Duterte in July reached out to the bandi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>Coast Guard intercepts P50-M smuggled rice shipment - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1774514</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENtnasAS5QW4yrd0_LppbAIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJiunQM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 10:44:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1774514" target="_blank"&gt;Coast Guard intercepts P50-M smuggled rice shipment&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;AN ESTIMATED P50 million worth of smuggled rice shipment was intercepted by the Philippine Coast Guard (PCG) while on maritime patrol in the Sulu sea, an official said Saturday, November 17. Lieutenant Commander Noriel Ramos, Zamboanga Coast Guard Station commander, said the vessel, M/V Hulk loaded with some 50,000 bags of rice of 25 kilos each, was intercepted by the BRP-Cape San Agustin (MRRV-4408) around 8 a.m. Thursday, November 15, anchored south of Buland Island, Sulu. Ramos said the PCG personnel spotted M/V Hulk while verifying reports of the Customs Intelligence Zamboanga and other...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Navy personnel awarded for rescue of kidnap victim - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1773812</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELvWZxhQEgNlLddfz_DPcJEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJiunQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 11:31:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1773812" target="_blank"&gt;Navy personnel awarded for rescue of kidnap victim&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE Naval Forces Western Mindanao (NFWM) has awarded Bronze Cross Medal to gallant sailors and marines for the successful rescue of a kidnap victim from the hands of the Abu Sayyaf bandits in Sulu province. Rear Admiral Rene Medina, NFWM commander, and Captain Richard Gonzaga, deputy for fleet operations, led the awarding during the flag raising ceremony Monday, November 12, at the Naval Station Romulo Espaldon in Zamboanga City. The awardees are the following: Colonel Armel Tolato, Philippine Marine Ready Force-Sulu commander; Major Junnibert Tubo, Marine Battalion Landing Team-3 (MBLT-3) ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Abrigo: Barter ports in the south - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1773078</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEBpbj50BGenLSF9eQQODhcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKeunQM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 13:03:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1773078" target="_blank"&gt;Abrigo: Barter ports in the south&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BARTER is the oldest system of commerce that can be traced back to 6000 B.C. in Mesopotamia (now Iraq). It is a swapping of goods or services with another person, usually a neighbor, for other goods and services in return, without money involved. In ancient barter, the goods include foods, tea, spices, and weapons. But the most valuable good in barter is salt that Roman soldiers’ salaries were paid with it. One of the most notable advantages in bartering is that the value of the good is widely flexible as our forefather’s favorite anecdote -a hectare of land swap to a cigar pipe (hunsoy). E...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Officer, 3 soldiers injured in Sulu clash - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1772705</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBSOgjj2G1mj25Ebcdw9WSYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJiunQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 10:42:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1772705" target="_blank"&gt;Officer, 3 soldiers injured in Sulu clash&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOUR soldiers, including an officer, were wounded in a clash as the government offensive continue against the Abu Sayyaf Group (ASG) in Sulu province, a top military official said Tuesday. The firefight took place at 1:40 p.m. Monday at Sitio kan Apo Aluk in Panglayahan village, Patikul, Sulu, according to Lieutenant General Arnel Dela Vega, Western Mindanao Command (Westmincom) commander. Dela Vega said the troops were conducting focused military operation when they clashed with some 50 Abu Sayyaf bandits led by one-armed and senior bandit leader Radullan Sahiron. He did not identify the i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Kidnap victim 'Duterte' rescued in Sulu - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/215770-kidnap-victim-with-surname-duterte-rescued-sulu-november-2018</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC-7mQnFOLr2Ls-5WETBQBMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 01:53:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/215770-kidnap-victim-with-surname-duterte-rescued-sulu-november-2018" target="_blank"&gt;Kidnap victim 'Duterte' rescued in Sulu&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ZAMBOANGA CITY, Philippines – Government troops have rescued a kidnap victim who had been held by the Abu Sayyaf group for over a year in Sulu, the military said. Continued military operations against the Abu Sayyaf in Panamao, Sulu, paved the way for the rescue of Jose Duterte, 66, on Thursday, November 1. The kidnap victim is not related to President Rodrigo Duterte. The Philippine Navy in Sulu, with Marine Battalion Landing Team 3, rescued Duterte early Thursday afternoon, a few days after troops neutralized and captured a number of ASG members in the area. Duterte and wife Jessica were ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>MNLF faction reiterates support for Bangsamoro Organic Law - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/215826-mnlf-faction-supports-bangsamoro-organic-law</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOFzzV3zuOcrCH9SkzLbUmEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2018 01:10:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/215826-mnlf-faction-supports-bangsamoro-organic-law" target="_blank"&gt;MNLF faction reiterates support for Bangsamoro Organic Law&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;DAVAO CITY, Philippines – A faction of the Moro National Liberation Front (MNLF) led by fomer Sulu governor Yusop Jikiri renewed its support for the Bangsamoro Organic Law (BOL) amid moves to question the legality of the measure. The Office of the Presidential Adviser on the Peace Process (OPAPP) said in a press statement on Saturday, November 3, that Jikiri relayed his group's support for the BOL in a meeting with Chief Peace Adviser Jesus Dureza earlier this week on Monday, October 29. The meeting was held a day before it was reported that incumbent Sulu Governor Abdusakur Tan II filed a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>2 Abu Sayyaf bandits killed in Sulu clash, 2 captured - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1771671</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECR5yU3xA4vuNYgAF86oM44qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJiunQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 08:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1771671" target="_blank"&gt;2 Abu Sayyaf bandits killed in Sulu clash, 2 captured&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MARINE forces have killed two Abu Sayyaf members and captured two wounded bandits following a firefight early Tuesday, October 30, in Sulu. Lieutenant General Arnel Dela Vega, Western Mindanao Command (Westmincom) chief, said the Marines were on combat operations when they encountered around 100 Abu Sayyaf bandits at 5:08 a.m. Tuesday, October 30, in the village of Lihbug Kabaw, Panglima Estino, Sulu. The bandits were led by Radullan Sahiron and sub-leaders Idang Susukan and Almujer Yadah. Dela Vega said two Abu Sayyaf members were killed in the clash, while two others were wounded and capt...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Sulu gov't to SC: Nullify Bangsamoro law - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/10/30/sulu-province-petition-supreme-court-nullify-bangsamoro-law.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOT4cvMW51OFj-BMajbxVyAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMJbthQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 06:42:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/10/30/sulu-province-petition-supreme-court-nullify-bangsamoro-law.html" target="_blank"&gt;Sulu gov't to SC: Nullify Bangsamoro law&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, October 30) — The Sulu provincial government has asked the Supreme Court (SC) to nullify the Bangsamoro law, saying the enactment of the monumental measure is unconstitutional. The province, through its governor Abdusakur A. Tan II, filed a petition for certiorari and prohibition asking the high court to review the constitutionality of the said law. In the document dated October 11, Tan criticized not only the constitutionality of some provisions-- but the entire law itself. Tan noted the province is "being coerced" to be part of the soon-to-be-established Ban...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>Governor Tan of Sulu runs to Supreme Court to block Bangsamoro law - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/215554-sulu-abdusakur-tan-ii-supreme-court-petition-block-bangsamoro-organic-law</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFFEbOMXf5T1yMLB-M0Yfa8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 06:00:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/215554-sulu-abdusakur-tan-ii-supreme-court-petition-block-bangsamoro-organic-law" target="_blank"&gt;Governor Tan of Sulu runs to Supreme Court to block Bangsamoro law&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – Governor Abdusakur Tan II of Sulu filed the first Supreme Court (SC) petition to block the landmark Bangsamoro Organic Law (BOL), citing questions on constitutionality. Tan filed a petition for certiorari and prohibition with a request for temporary restraining order (TRO) before the SC. Lawmakers who crafted the BOL expected this petition, and welcomed the move as it would settle questions on legality and allow them to move forward without constraints. “I truly believe though that the Organic Law that we passed can stand the test of constitutionality after careful scr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>3 Marines, 1 Abu Sayyaf killed in Sulu clash - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/215225-marines-killed-sulu-clash-abu-sayyaf-october-26-2018</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBgR49y0y6hI2pusUz12qNcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 05:30:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/215225-marines-killed-sulu-clash-abu-sayyaf-october-26-2018" target="_blank"&gt;3 Marines, 1 Abu Sayyaf killed in Sulu clash&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ZAMBOANGA CITY, Philippines – At least 3 marines and an Abu Sayyaf member were killed in an encounter between government troops and the terrorist group in Patikul, Sulu, on Friday, October 26. Troops from the 61st, 62nd, and 64th Marine Companies clashed with Abu Sayyaf members under subleaders Alnijar Ekit and Aldi Alun in Barangay Timpook, Patikul, the military said. Three other soldiers sustained minor injuries and were brought to the KHTB Station Hospital for immediate medical attention. The military said the ongoing firefight also dealt casualties on the Abu Sayyaf side. Troops recover...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Minda: Empower sea trade routes - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1771184</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPt3V5rC8gClWjxCLKscrgYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKeunQM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 13:12:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1771184" target="_blank"&gt;Minda: Empower sea trade routes&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SEA trade routes in Mindanao must be empowered to entice more economic profit especially in the Autonomous Region in Muslim Mindanao (ARMM), an official said. Mindanao Development Authority (Minda) Development Management Officer Raymond Peter Esperat emphasized that regulation in these trading routes must be done in order to secure trade activities. He was one of the speakers of last Thursday’s Mindanao Energy Plan 2018 public consultations at The Royal Mandaya Hotel, Davao City. Esperat said Minda has been forwarding the creations of economic zones along Maguindanao, and Basilan, Sulu, Taw...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>3 soldiers, 1 Abu Sayyaf killed in encounter - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1771088/Manila/Local-News/3-soldiers-1-Abu-Sayyaf-killed-in-encounter?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELLzIGSGgROM4pc1PSYxlh8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKmgnQM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 06:59:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1771088/Manila/Local-News/3-soldiers-1-Abu-Sayyaf-killed-in-encounter?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;3 soldiers, 1 Abu Sayyaf killed in encounter&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THREE marine soldiers and one Abu Sayyaf Group (ASG) terrorist were killed in an encounter in Patikul, Sulu on Friday morning, October 26. Three other soldiers were wounded and brought to the KHTB station hospital for treatment, said Western Mindanao Command spokesperson Lieutenant Colonel Gerry Besana. He said soldiers of the Joint Task Force Sulu under Brigadier General Divino Rey Pabayo encountered an undetermined number of ASG members under sub-leaders Alnijar Ekit and Aldi Alun in Barangay Timpook. Besana said the body of a suspected ASG terrorist was recovered from the battle area. He...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>6 Abu Sayyaf bandits surrender in Sulu - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1770570</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECcxuiLHNaMn-epIb_pCZQIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJiunQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 11:47:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1770570" target="_blank"&gt;6 Abu Sayyaf bandits surrender in Sulu&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SIX members of the Abu Sayyaf Group (ASG) have surrendered in the province of Sulu, the military said Tuesday, October 23. Lieutenant General Arnel Dela Vega, Western Mindanao Command (Westmincom) chief, identified them as follows: Mohammad Boyhe, Rojimar Dahim, Abdu Amidol, Kandang Abduhalim Jumadil, Tader Odong Asdure, and Matar Hajarani Saliling. Dela Vega said they have surrendered to the troops of the Joint Task Force Sulu last Friday in Maimbung, Sulu. He said the group surrendered through the efforts of Maimbung Mayor Samier Tan of Maimbung and Captain Rico Tagure of the Army’s 2nd S...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>3 soldiers killed in clash with Abu Sayyaf members in Sulu - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/10/26/marines-soldiers-killed-sulu-encounter.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEFNgnfeMdfKDmjcRHij4zEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMJbthQM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 05:55:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/10/26/marines-soldiers-killed-sulu-encounter.html" target="_blank"&gt;3 soldiers killed in clash with Abu Sayyaf members in Sulu&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, October 26) — Three soldiers were killed and three others injured in a clash with suspected Abu Sayyaf members Friday morning in Sulu. A report from the Armed Forces of the Philippines-Western Mindanao Command confirmed three marines were gunned down in an encounter with an undetermined number of bandits in Patikul town. The soldiers were members of the Joint Task Sulu under Brig. Gen. Rey Pabayo. No further details from the Abu Sayyaf side, but initial investigation showed a number of bandits were "severely wounded." The injured soldiers are now at the KHTB ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>2 Sayyafs killed, 4 others captured in Sulu - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1768708/Zamboanga/Local-News/2-Sayyafs-killed-4-others-captured-in-Sulu</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMX6du9DcYTk1_nkQn0TePcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJiunQM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 11:14:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1768708/Zamboanga/Local-News/2-Sayyafs-killed-4-others-captured-in-Sulu" target="_blank"&gt;2 Sayyafs killed, 4 others captured in Sulu&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;TWO Abu Sayyaf bandits were killed while four others were captured following a brief firefight in the province of Sulu, the military said Thursday, October 11. Lieutenant General Arnel Dela Vega, commander of the Western Mindanao Command (Westmincom), said the firefight broke out when the joint team of soldiers and policemen launched an operation around 1:30 a.m. Wednesday in Kajatian village, Indanan, Sulu. Dela Vega said the firefight resulted in the death of two Abu Sayyaf bandits, Jade Hassan alias Radjik and Kemar Jade. The Westmincom commander said captured were: Lino Tantung, 42; Ham...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Sea marshal hurt in knife attack on board ship - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1768185</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGkWE9kd_ffMg9Glpbjphc8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJiunQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2018 10:34:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1768185" target="_blank"&gt;Sea marshal hurt in knife attack on board ship&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A MEMBER of the Philippine Coast Guard assigned as sea marshal was wounded in a knife attack on board a ship off Sulu, a PCG official said Monday, October 8. Lieutenant Commander Noriel Ramos, Zamboanga Coast Guard Station commander, identified the injured PCG personnel as Seaman Second Class (SN2) Michael Ladja, the marshal head of M/V Ever Queen. Ramos said the knife attack happened aboard the passenger vessel on Friday afternoon near the town of Siasi, Sulu. He said the suspect, who was shot and killed by the other sea marshals, was identified as Juldi Mahbud, a resident of Siasi. Ramos ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Special voters’ listing in Marawi completed - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1768671</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMNlw7ruqrO8enJR4ZEaIYUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMIeunQM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 03:53:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1768671" target="_blank"&gt;Special voters’ listing in Marawi completed&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MARAWI CITY -- The special voters’ registration in Marawi City and Lanao del Sur province was successfully concluded despite the scheduled hearings of the Election Registration Board (ERB) on Tuesday, Oct. 9, for the approval or disapproval of voters’ applications. Lawyer Joyce E. Moran, Commission on Election’s regional lawyer for the Autonomous Region in Muslim Mindanao (ARMM) and acting election officer of Bayang, Lanao del Sur, said the ERB hearings on Tuesday was simultaneously conducted nationwide pursuant to Section 2 of Comelec Resolution 10392 where thousands of voter applicants fa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>PRO-Zamboanga awards ‘Merit Medal’ to 14 policemen - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1768355</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENS070asU58UdIw31N2u4woqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJiunQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2018 09:32:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1768355" target="_blank"&gt;PRO-Zamboanga awards ‘Merit Medal’ to 14 policemen&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOURTEEN policemen, including four officers, were awarded the “Medalya ng Kagalingan (PNP Merit Medal)” for their accomplishments in the campaign against the Abu Sayyaf Group (ASG) and other lawless elements in Zamboanga Peninsula. Chief Inspector Helen Galvez, Police Regional Office (PRO)-Zamboanga Peninsula information officer, said Chief Superintendent Emmanuel Luis Licup, director, led the awarding ceremony which was held Monday, October 8, in Camp Colonel Romeo Abendan. Camp Abendan houses the headquarters of the PRO-Zamboanga Peninsula in Mercedes village, this city. The awardees of t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Duterte awards medals to wounded soldiers - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1766127</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKXcv5co3ryp6v6HUtJOcRwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJiunQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2018 12:55:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1766127" target="_blank"&gt;Duterte awards medals to wounded soldiers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOURTEEN soldiers who were recently wounded in a clash against the Abu Sayyaf bandits received medals with the Order of Lapu-Lapu level of Kampilan in an awarding ceremony led by no less than President Rodrigo Duterte, a military official said on Tuesday, September 25. Lieutenant Colonel Gerry Besana, Western Mindanao Command (Wesmincom) information officer, said the awarding ceremony was held on Monday when President Duterte visited the Joint Task Force-Sulu headquarters in Camp General Teodulfo Bautista in Jolo, Sulu. Besana said the 14 awardees were the following: Second Lieutenant Manny...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Military denies claims of Sulu massacre - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1764727</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGOarvZ6qFpjjzK7vmAUjBQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKmgnQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 09:36:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1764727" target="_blank"&gt;Military denies claims of Sulu massacre&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE Armed Forces of the Philippines (AFP) on Monday, September 17, insisted that the September 14 encounter in Patikul, Sulu was legitimate, not a massacre as claimed by some sectors. “We stand firm in our report that this was a legitimate encounter contrary to enemy propaganda that it was a “massacre,” AFP spokesperson Colonel Edgard Arevalo said. “The site of the encounter is a notorious ASG territory. That is a fact established by military and human intelligence. The folks of Patikul knows it very well such that no civilians dared to go or pass by the place,” he added. The military claim...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Were 7 killed in Sulu encounter Abu Sayyaf or not? - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/212088-killed-in-sulu-encounter-abu-sayyaf-or-not</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBe0EBQ6KLWfN0pd1WHlgYkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2018 13:06:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/212088-killed-in-sulu-encounter-abu-sayyaf-or-not" target="_blank"&gt;Were 7 killed in Sulu encounter Abu Sayyaf or not?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – Seven alleged members of the terrorist group Abu Sayyaf were killed in an encounter on Friday, September 14, according to a report of Joint Task Force Sulu headed by Brigadier General Divino Rey Pabayo. The number of dead was based on a body count, according to a press statement from Lieutenant Colonel Gerry Besana, public affairs officer of the Western Mindanao Command. Six others were reported injured, including ASG Senior Leader Hatib Hajan Sawadjaan, who was said to be seriously hit in his stomach and lower extremities. Miliary says they're terrorists: The same rep...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>3 Indonesian hostages freed by Abu Sayyaf - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1764573</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOmEl7hBOU9EP4n-cuaG-QIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKmgnQM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2018 09:51:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1764573" target="_blank"&gt;3 Indonesian hostages freed by Abu Sayyaf&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ABU Sayyaf group freed three Indonesians who they abducted on January in 2017, a military official said on Sunday, September 16. Western Mindanao Command spokesperson Lieutenant Colonel Gerry Besana said Hamdam Salim,34; Subandi Sattuh,27 and Sudarlan Samansung,41 were released to Brigadier General Divino Rey Pabayo Jr., commander of the Joint Task Force Sulu, former Governor Abdusakur Tan and Provincial Director of the Sulu Provincial Police Office Police Senior Superintendent Labra in Barangay Buanza, Indanan, Sulu around 4 p.m. on Saturday, September 15. The said hostages were forcibly t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>7 Abu Sayaf killed, 17 soldiers wounded in Sulu clash - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1764557</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMVzOaOAzX0xFln_nQhj8DAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJiunQM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2018 14:32:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1764557" target="_blank"&gt;7 Abu Sayaf killed, 17 soldiers wounded in Sulu clash&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SEVEN Abu Sayyaf Group (ASG) members were killed while 23 others wounded, including 17 soldiers, in a firefight in the province of Sulu, a top military official said Saturday, September 15. Lieutenant General Arnel Dela Vega, Western Mindanao Command (Wesmincom) chief, said the firefight broke out around 1:30 p.m. Friday in the village of Bakong, Patikul, Sulu. Dela Vega said the troops were on combat operations when they chanced some 100 Abu Sayyaf bandits led by ASG one-armed leader Radullan Sahiron and sub-leaders Hatib Hajan Sawadjaan and Idang Susukan in the village of Bakong. Sahiron ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Troops, Abu Sayyaf bandits clash in Sulu - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1763787</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBApUYxmrG1YqjIo5CAgxj4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJiunQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 10:58:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1763787" target="_blank"&gt;Troops, Abu Sayyaf bandits clash in Sulu&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;AN ABU Sayyaf Group (ASG) member was killed in a clash with military troops as offensive continues in a bid to rescue the kidnap victims in the island province of Sulu, the military said. Lieutenant General Arnel Dela Vega, Western Mindanao Command (Westmincom) chief, said the clash happened around 9 a.m. Monday, September 10, when Army’s 21st Infantry Battalion troops chanced upon 60 ASG bandits in Bungkaong village, Patikul, Sulu. Dela Vega said the troops were on security operation when they clashed with the bandit group led by ASG sub-leaders Almujer Yadah and Idang Suskan in Barangay B...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Piñol wants to legalize smuggled rice in Zamboanga-Basilan area - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/business/210619-pinol-wants-smuggled-rice-legalized-zamboanga-basilan-sulu-tawi-tawi</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENQbvuFh7O_R4F0RQ2ZcIhcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMP_mmQI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2018 16:29:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/business/210619-pinol-wants-smuggled-rice-legalized-zamboanga-basilan-sulu-tawi-tawi" target="_blank"&gt;Piñol wants to legalize smuggled rice in Zamboanga-Basilan area&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – After saying it was smuggled rice that caused sky-high prices in Zamboanga-Basilan-Sulu-Tawi-Tawi (Zambasulta), Agriculture Secretary Emmanuel Piñol is considering to legalize their entry. Piñol earlier floated the idea in a Facebook post, and only expounded on it on Tuesday, August 28. “So my proposal is to establish a rice trading center, where you bring in rice, wherever that came from, and pay a little tariff,” Piñol said. “This is a peculiar problem because Zambasulta relied on smuggled rice,” he added. Smuggled rice supply was suddenly cut off after President Rod...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Piñol wants special rice imports for Zambasulta area - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/business/210484-special-rice-imports-zamboanga-basilan-sulu-tawi-tawi</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFa3I6HVQBBj4laognYodKAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMP_mmQI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 04:57:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/business/210484-special-rice-imports-zamboanga-basilan-sulu-tawi-tawi" target="_blank"&gt;Piñol wants special rice imports for Zambasulta area&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – Agriculture Secretary Emmanuel Piñol proposed additional rice imports for the Zamboanga-Basilan-Sulu-Tawi-Tawi (Zambasulta) area due to sky-high prices. Zamboanga City and Basilan earlier declared a state of calamity due to rice woes. Rice prices in these two areas reached as high as P70 per kilo. Piñol also said a kilo of rice in some areas in Tawi-Tawi reached as high as P100 after Eid'l Fitr. In a Facebook post, the agriculture chief said he submitted a memorandum to President Rodrigo Duterte to allow the special importation of 132,000 metric tons of rice from the p...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>1 Abu Sayyaf member dead, 20 soldiers wounded in Sulu clash - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/regional/2018/08/23/Abu-Sayyaf-Sulu-clash.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBMiwQxIZ7k6316oipn1K7wqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMPHhmQI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2018 10:49:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/regional/2018/08/23/Abu-Sayyaf-Sulu-clash.html" target="_blank"&gt;1 Abu Sayyaf member dead, 20 soldiers wounded in Sulu clash&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, August 23) — An Abu Sayyaf member was killed while 20 soldiers were wounded in a clash in Sulu on Thursday, the military said. Government troops fought at least 40 bandits in Barangay Langhub in Patikul town at around 9:30 a.m., the Western Mindanao Command said. It said a certain Alpata Abdurasa was killed in the 45-minute firefight, while a number of Abu Sayyaf fighters were hurt. On the government side, 18 had shrapnel injuries while two had gunshot wounds, the military said. They were rushed to the Camp Teodulfo Bautista Station Hospital for treatment. The...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>Gunmen seize Grade 5 pupil in Jolo - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1758348/Zamboanga/Local-News/Gunmen-seize-Grade-5-pupil-in-Jolo</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKraEsFTirgI7SVIHUOvBnQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJiunQM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 11:04:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1758348/Zamboanga/Local-News/Gunmen-seize-Grade-5-pupil-in-Jolo" target="_blank"&gt;Gunmen seize Grade 5 pupil in Jolo&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A 10-YEAR-OLD boy was seized by gunmen in the province of Sulu, the military reported Thursday, August 16. Lieutenant Colonel Gerry Besana, Western Mindanao Command (Westmincom) information officer, said the incident happened around 7:20 a.m. Thursday near a snack house in the village of San Raymundo, Jolo, Sulu. Besana identified the victim as Zaire Khan Pasil, 10, a Grade 5 pupil of the Notre Dame of Jolo Elementary School. Besana said Pasil was with his elder sister, Fatima Zaima, 13, aboard a family-owned jeep driven by Aldasir Tallow when accosted and seized by six gunmen who were aboa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Reviving of sea route to spur Tawi-Tawi - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1756652?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBw4UmlEZwNR3fi_qfRAYzIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKeunQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2018 14:34:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1756652?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;Reviving of sea route to spur Tawi-Tawi&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE reviving the Zamboanga-Sandakan-Tawi-Tawi trading sea route, it will help boost the formation of Tawi-Tawi free economic zone. “We must invest in Tawi-Tawi because Tawi-Tawi is a part of Mindanao, a part of our home,” Mindanao Development Authority (Minda) Secretary Datu Abdul Khayr Dangcal Alonto said during the third Mindanao Shipping Conference 2018 at Waterfront Insular Hotel, Davao City. Alonto said Tawi-Tawi with its geographical setting is a strategic avenue to conduct and even empower trading routes in the island region of Tawi-Tawi and even neighboring Asean countries like Mala...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Abu Sayyaf ‘spotter’ arrested - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1757180</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMuuoKGnaRMxV68AuzWJMpcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJiunQM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2018 12:28:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1757180" target="_blank"&gt;Abu Sayyaf ‘spotter’ arrested&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;JOINT police and military operatives have arrested an alleged Abu Sayyaf bandit and seized bomb-making components in this southern port city, an official announced Thursday. Majid Isnilon, 25, was arrested around 2:30 a.m. Tuesday, August 7 in Barangay Pasilmanta, according to Chief Inspector Helen Galvez, Police Regional Office-Zamboanga Peninsula information officer. Isnilon has standing warrants of arrest for murder and multiple attempted murder issued by two courts in Zamboanga City. Galvez said the suspect is also the “spotter” and messenger of Sulu-based Abu Sayyaf sub-leader Hatib Sa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Basilan under state of calamity after military ops - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/208930-basilan-under-state-of-calamity-after-military-ops</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB7ZMay96o6IFVpn5jvzdcoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2018 04:44:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/208930-basilan-under-state-of-calamity-after-military-ops" target="_blank"&gt;Basilan under state of calamity after military ops&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BASILAN, Philippines – The provincial board of Basilan declared a state of calamity in the province Monday, August 6, upon the recommendation of the peace and order council. This was after the Armed Forces of the Philippines launched massive operations in the municipality of Mohammad Ajul Municipality. Authorities said 705 families were evacuated. Also cited as reason for the state-of-calamity declaration was the rice shortage in the province due to the "cocolisap" (coconut scale insects) infestation. This is a developing story. Refresh the page for updates. – Rappler.com&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>30,000 flee huge fire in Sulu - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/208176-30,000-flee-huge-fire-in-sulu</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPV02V91NykJ_Iu2DRqq0EsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2018 08:42:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/208176-30,000-flee-huge-fire-in-sulu" target="_blank"&gt;30,000 flee huge fire in Sulu&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BASILAN, Philippines – About 2,600 homes were burned to the ground in Jolo, Sulu, in an overnight fire that was put out Wednesday morning, July 25. According to initial reports from the Sulu Provincial Police Office, the fire started in the Sitio Port area of Barangay Walled City, on Tuesday. The fire spread to Barangay Bus-Bus of the same municipality. More than 30,000 residents have fled the area. Relief goods were delivered Wednesday to those affected by the fire. For the relief operations, Governor Mujiv Hataman of the Autonomous Region in Muslim Mindanao led the ARMM Humanitarian Emerg...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Armm police in full alert after Basilan blast - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1755769?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECxWtaivL-gHeOGhFEcYkZwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKmgnQM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2018 03:55:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1755769?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;Armm police in full alert after Basilan blast&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE Police Regional Office (PRO) in the Autonomous Region in Muslim Mindanao (Armm) went on full alert status following the bombing incident in Lamitan City, Basilan, that killed 11 people on Tuesday, July 31. PRO-Armm Director Graciano Mijares said policemen in the region were ordered to beef up checkpoints and foot and mobile patrolling, especially in highly populated areas. He said they will also intensify coordination with other security forces to strengthen intelligence monitoring and sharing. Among those killed in the Basilan explosion were a soldier, five Citizens Armed Forces Geogra...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>6 killed in 2 clashes in Sulu - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1753776/Zamboanga/Local-News/6-killed-in-2-clashes-in-Sulu</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENaoLUrFrWOK_14o-Q6ZDRcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJiunQM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2018 06:12:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1753776/Zamboanga/Local-News/6-killed-in-2-clashes-in-Sulu" target="_blank"&gt;6 killed in 2 clashes in Sulu&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SIX people, including five Abu Sayyaf bandits, were killed while two others wounded in separate clashes as government offensive continue against the bandits in Sulu province, the military said Friday, July 20, 2018. The first clash happened at midnight of Wednesday in the boundary of the villages of Tanum and Liang, Patikul and the second around 9:30 a.m. Thursday in Tabu-Bato village, Maimbung. Brigadier General Divino Rey Pabayo, Joint Task Force Sulu commander, said the troops from the Army’s 45th Infantry Battalion were conducting focused military operation when they clashed at midnight...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Duterte signs Bangsamoro law - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1754771?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFG1CkLTUnOROUPhm3oNTpsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKmgnQM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 10:55:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1754771?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;Duterte signs Bangsamoro law&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PRESIDENT Rodrigo Duterte has signed into law the Bangsamoro Organic Law, which seeks to create a new Bangsamoro region to replace the Autonomous Region in Muslim Mindanao (ARMM). "Signed na ang BBL," Duterte said Thursday, July 26, in a speech delivered in Ipil, Zamboanga Sibugay. (The BBL - Bangsamoro Basic Law - has been signed into law.) The bill was first known as BBL and later renamed to Bangsamoro Organic Law. But the President said he still needed to consult Nur Misuari, Moro National Liberation Front (MNLF) founder, to make sure the law is implemented by the end of the year. Presid...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Editorial: Now the work begins - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1754998?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGG4GPDKmcYqUiETXB2Vo7EqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKeunQM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2018 11:56:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1754998?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;Editorial: Now the work begins&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE Bangsamoro Organic Law has finally been signed as announced by Malacañang and the President himself last Thursday, July 26, in a speech he delivered in Ipil, Zamboanga Sibugay. Now, the real work begins. The President said he still needed to consult Nur Misuari, Moro National Liberation Front (MNLF) founder, to make sure the law is implemented by the end of the year. Meaning, that the leader will see that BOL does not run counter to the previous peace agreement signed even as it replaces the five-province Autonomous Region for Muslim Mindanao (Armm), which will become the Bangsamoro Aut...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>House ratifies Bangsamoro bill - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1754406?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELMnsyLnDOZ13OKpa8hlgg8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKmgnQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 08:53:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1754406?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;House ratifies Bangsamoro bill&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE House of Representatives on Tuesday, July 24 ratified the bicameral conference committee report on the proposed Bangsamoro Oganic Law, a bill which seeks the abolition of the Autonomous Region in Muslim Mindanao and the creation of the Bangsamoro Autonomous Region in Muslim Mindanao. The Senate ratified the bicameral conference committee report on the BOL on Monday. This means the final bill now only awaits the signing of President Rodrigo Duterte. The said bill was expected to be signed into law by the President before his State of the Nation Address on Monday. The House, however, fail...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Senate ratifies bill on Bangsamoro Organic Law - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/07/23/bangsamoro-organic-law-bbl-olbarmm-armm-duterte-congress-milf-senate-house-of-representatives.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI-7ybWlZImc8S3EBVDwmCEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMJbthQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2018 02:55:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/07/23/bangsamoro-organic-law-bbl-olbarmm-armm-duterte-congress-milf-senate-house-of-representatives.html" target="_blank"&gt;Senate ratifies bill on Bangsamoro Organic Law&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, July 23) — Hours before President Rodrigo Duterte's third State of the Nation Address on Monday, the Senate ratified the proposed Bangsamoro Organic Law, which creates the Bangsamoro Autonomous Region in Muslim Mindanao. The House of Representatives has yet to do the same. Duterte, the first President who hails from Mindanao, earlier certified the bill as urgent, prompting Congress to fast-track its passage. The bicameral conference committee approved the final version of the bill on July 18. Officials said the President may sign the Organic Law for the Bangsa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>Troops rescue kidnapped family of six in Sulu - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1753436?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJxP3FRrejdATg7_8RYbG5QqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJiunQM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 11:05:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1753436?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;Troops rescue kidnapped family of six in Sulu&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A FAMILY of six seized by a kidnap-for-ransom-group (KFRG) on June 28 in Zamboanga del Norte was rescued by the troops in the hinterlands of Sulu, the military said Wednesday, July 18, 2018. The Joint Task Force Sulu reported to the Western Mindanao Command (Westmincom) that the victims were rescued around 11 p.m. Tuesday in Gata village, Talipao, Sulu. Rescued were couple Feliciano and Elsa Javier, both 28 years old; with son Vincent, five months old; and couple Junior and Rica Javier, both 22 years old with son Val Javier, five. The victims were seized by a KFRG led by Jamilon Tukalan ali...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Westmincom honors 10 wounded soldiers - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1752803?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPah-Eq_djCfHNjIjy2UOvIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJiunQM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jul 2018 09:55:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1752803?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;Westmincom honors 10 wounded soldiers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE Western Mindanao Command (Westmincom) has awarded Wounded Personnel Medal (WPM) for gallantry in action to the soldiers who were wounded in a recent clash against the Abu Sayyaf bandits in Sulu province. Lieutenant General Arnel Dela Vega, Westmincom chief, awarded WPM during his visit on Friday to the soldiers at Camp Teodulfo Bautista Station Hospital in Jolo, Sulu. The recipients of WPM are the 10 soldiers from the Army’s 32nd Infantry Battalion who were wounded in a two-hour sporadic firefight with around 60 Abu Sayyaf bandits on Wednesday at Sitio Kan Apo Alu in Panglayahan village...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Marawi folks less convinced Duterte has concern for Muslims – SWS - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/207670-marawi-residents-duterte-muslims-sws-survey-april-2018</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBZGgwiN8qBMQ4m9eeMkYBsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2018 04:30:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/207670-marawi-residents-duterte-muslims-sws-survey-april-2018" target="_blank"&gt;Marawi folks less convinced Duterte has concern for Muslims – SWS&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – A newly released Social Weather Stations (SWS) survey showed only 30% to 50% of Marawi residents are convinced President Rodrigo Duterte “has concern for Muslims” – much lower than the provincial average of 83% both in the entire Lanao del Sur and neighboring Maguindanao. “Marawi respondents were less convinced Duterte has concern for Muslims,” said SWS fellow-in-residence and Mindanao expert Steve Rood, who presented the survey results on Wednesday, July 18. Marawi residents living in IDP camps or evacuation centers are feeling more neglected, with 30% saying they thi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Bicam OKs final Bangsamoro bill for Duterte signature - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/207524-bangsamoro-bill-final-version-approved-for-duterte-signature</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPwLJS2cgWdfpNeKbxG5j8YqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 12:45:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/207524-bangsamoro-bill-final-version-approved-for-duterte-signature" target="_blank"&gt;Bicam OKs final Bangsamoro bill for Duterte signature&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines (3rd UPDATE) – The bicameral conference committee finalized on Wednesday, July 18, the bill that would establish and grant greater autonomy to a new Bangsamoro region. It took the bicam more than a week to reconcile the differing provisions of the House and Senate versions of the measure, with heated exchanges between members. The House and the Senate would now have to ratify the bicameral conference committee report. They are set to do it on Monday, July 23, during the opening of the 3rd session of the 17th Congress and ahead of President Rodrigo Duterte's 3rd State of ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>3 Abu Sayyaf members killed in Sulu clash - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1752445/Manila/Local-News/3-Abu-Sayyaf-members-killed-in-Sulu-clash</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP6j-i1pEK7uHRKnB8LU_OcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKmgnQM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2018 07:22:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1752445/Manila/Local-News/3-Abu-Sayyaf-members-killed-in-Sulu-clash" target="_blank"&gt;3 Abu Sayyaf members killed in Sulu clash&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(UPDATED) - Three suspected members of the Abu Sayyaf Group (ASG) and a soldier were killed in separate clashes between the terrorist group and government troops in Sulu, the military said Thursday, July 12. Brigadier General Divino Rey Pabayo, Joint Task Force Sulu commander, said the three ASG members were killed in a clash at around 4:30 a.m. Thursday in Kuppong village, Indanan town. The soldier was killed in a clash that took place at 1:55 p.m. Wednesday in Sitio Kan Apo Aluk in Panglayahan village, Patikul town. Ten other soldiers were wounded. Pabayo said the clash in Indanan ensued ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Former mayor's ex-wife, daughter rescued - SunStar Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1749238?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN2YSiQ2gGNdGzutN29_BcoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJiunQM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2018 03:41:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1749238?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;Former mayor's ex-wife, daughter rescued&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;TROOPS have rescued the ex-wife and daughter of the former mayor seized by Abu Sayyaf Group (ASG) members in the province of Sulu, the military reported Thursday, June 21. Rescued around 6 p.m. Wednesday, June 20, in the boundary of Sinumaan and Kagay villages in Talipao town were Addang Tulawie, 57, and her daughter, Edelyn, 27. Addang is the ex-wife, while Edelyn is the daughter of former Talipao mayor Tambrin Tulawie, whose son Nebukadnezar is the town's incumbent mayor. Lieutenant Colonel Gerry Besana, Western Mindanao Command (Westmincom) information officer, said the rescue came as th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>LOOK: Learn about Bangsamoro heritage through this village - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/life-and-style/arts-and-culture/205602-armm-villages-expo-cotabato-city-bangsamoro</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB8YMcDbo8dHqZSlvNb-rQQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMODhmQI</guid><pubDate>Sat, 23 Jun 2018 07:40:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/life-and-style/arts-and-culture/205602-armm-villages-expo-cotabato-city-bangsamoro" target="_blank"&gt;LOOK: Learn about Bangsamoro heritage through this village&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you’re visiting the Autonomous Region in Muslim Mindanao (ARMM) anytime soon, then you really should see its tribal village exhibits. The ARMM is showcasing and promoting the region’s grandest mock tribal villages that showcase the variety of cultures, traditions, history and oneness of the Bangsamoro people. There are many other aspects of life in the Bangsamoro that complete the picture of these people: Their arts and culture; their craftsmanship and entrepreneurial spirit; the cuisine they enjoy and the hospitality they offer to those who come to their communities in peace and with si...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>DavOcc breaks ground for P3-B capitol building - SunStar Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1747157?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAijCyklGtPrYGHruBTxanwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKeunQM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 13:12:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1747157?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;DavOcc breaks ground for P3-B capitol building&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE groundbreaking ceremony for the P3 billion worth Davao Occidental Provincial Capitol Building and Government Business Center was held yesterday in Barangay Lais, Malita, Davao Occidental. Davao Occidental Governor Claude Bautista told reporters Friday, June 8, that target date of completion of the construction of the Capitol building is within two years, while the whole complex will be from three to four years. The 30-hectare lot for the facility was donated by Eduardo Danding Cojuanco of San Miguel Corporation. “The whole complex will have the Capitol building, Sangguniang Panlalawigan...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Sweet tradition: A peek at Tausug treats - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/life-and-style/best-eats/203473-tausug-treats-sweet-tradition-ramadan</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO57-ducnwIQQK4qzvZ0hroqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMODhmQI</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 May 2018 09:25:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/life-and-style/best-eats/203473-tausug-treats-sweet-tradition-ramadan" target="_blank"&gt;Sweet tradition: A peek at Tausug treats&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;From a coconut shell pierced with holes, white batter trickles in tiny waterfalls down the wok, with skillful hands slowly swirling them into a web of delicate threads. This web is then carefully folded, rolled, pressed, and fried. The result is a golden, three-dimensional filigree called jaa among Tausugs in Sulu, lokot-lokot among neighboring Zamboangueño Muslims, and also known by other names among Muslims in other parts of Mindanao. Tausug delicacies, as well as other cuisine in Muslim Mindanao, come with rich traditions, and sometimes, as with the jaa, much attention and detail in the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Release of 96 MNLF men saddens Zamboanga mayor - Sun.Star Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1745273?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM72CNc6eU4b5MnmvszH6D8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJiunQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2018 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1745273?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;Release of 96 MNLF men saddens Zamboanga mayor&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Sun.Star Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MAYOR Maria Isabelle Climaco-Salazar on Monday, May 28, was saddened by the release of 96 accused members of the Moro National Liberation Front (MNLF) who were involved in the 21-day 2013 Zamboanga siege. Salazar issued the statement after the Regional Trial Court (RTC) Branch 158 recently ordered the release of 96 MNLF members involved in the siege. She said though that the City Government will continue to fight for justice for the victims of the siege, which left more than 200 people dead and over a 100,000 residents displaced. "The City Government is saddened by the release of the accuse...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">Sun.Star Philippines</source></item><item><title>Two freed cops meet Duterte - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/05/20/Abu-Sayyaf-Duterte-Sulu-cops.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELw8xP9CrqOMLFog3S7KO00qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMJbthQM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2018 03:36:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/05/20/Abu-Sayyaf-Duterte-Sulu-cops.html" target="_blank"&gt;Two freed cops meet Duterte&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, May 20) — President Rodrigo Duterte met on Saturday the two police officers who were abducted by suspected Abu Sayyaf members in Sulu. Moro National Liberation Front (MNLF) Chair Nur Misuari and Presidential Peace Adviser Jesus Dureza personally fetched Police Officer 1 Dinah Gumahad and Police Officer 2 Benierose Alvarez from Jolo and presented them to the Presdient in Davao City. The President thanked the combined efforts of the Philippine National Police (PNP), the Armed Forces of the Philippines (AFP), the MNLF, and local leaders for the release of the off...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>Abu Sayyaf frees another captive - Sun.Star Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1744170?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAwWi8LOkKMpIcuvluziPX4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJiunQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 06:21:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1744170?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;Abu Sayyaf frees another captive&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Sun.Star Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE Abu Sayyaf Group released one of its captives on Monday morning, May 21, a military official said. Joint Task Force Sulu commander Brigadier General Cirilito Sobejana said the male victim, who he is yet to be identified, was released by the bandit group around 8 a.m. He said the victim was placed under the custody of the Joint Task Force Sulu where he will undergo medical examination and debriefing before he will be turned over to his family. Sobejana said the Abu Sayyaf is still holding nine kidnap victims including a Dutch, Indonesians, Vietnamese and Filipinos. Earlier, the Abu Sayya...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">Sun.Star Philippines</source></item><item><title>Abu Sayyaf bandits release 2 policewomen - Sun.Star Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1743437?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP-lJo9CRxXAgzSm-FAHfYAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJiunQM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 10:46:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1743437?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;Abu Sayyaf bandits release 2 policewomen&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Sun.Star Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE Abu Sayyaf bandits have released the two policewomen they seized last April 29 in Sulu province after an alleged payment of P2.5-million ransom, an official said Wednesday, May 16. Senior Superintendent Pablo Labra II, Sulu police director, said that Police Officer (PO) 3 Benierose Alvarez and PO1 Dinah Gumahad were released at 10:15 a.m. and 6:45 p.m., respectively, on Tuesday “somewhere in Talipao” municipality. Alvarez, who is from Isabela City, Basilan, is assigned with the Engineer Service Division under the Regional Logistics Office of the Police Regional Office-Zamboanga Peninsul...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">Sun.Star Philippines</source></item><item><title>10 injured in Jolo bomb explosion - Sun.Star Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1742859?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENLJkmiCIu-RI2EGD2J9qiwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJiunQM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 12 May 2018 13:13:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1742859?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;10 injured in Jolo bomb explosion&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Sun.Star Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;TEN people were injured when an improvised explosive device (IED) exploded in Sulu province, a top military official said Saturday, May 12. Brigadier General Cirilito Sobejana, Joint Task Force Sulu commander, said the explosion happened at 7:10 p.m. Friday at the JNB Sari-Sari store and videoke bar at Sitio Martirez in San Raymundo village, Jolo. Sobejana said the victims were also customers of the videoke bar who were having a drinking spree at the time of explosion. The victims, who were slightly injured, were rushed to the hospital of the Sulu Integrated Provincial Health Office. The mi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">Sun.Star Philippines</source></item><item><title>Sulu Sultanate, Bangsa Sug push revision of BBL - Sun.Star Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1742513?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHCwOWByhiOAFLe5ahScYLoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJiunQM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 11:07:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1742513?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;Sulu Sultanate, Bangsa Sug push revision of BBL&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Sun.Star Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE Sultanate of Sulu and the multi-sectoral groups of the Bangsa Sug has agreed in a consensus on Wednesday to push for the revision of certain provisions on the proposed Bangsamoro Basic Law (BBL). The Bangsa Sug refers to the inhabitants of the provinces of Basilan, Sulu and Tawi-Tawi as well as certain areas in Zamboanga Peninsula. The consensus, which was held at a local hotel on Wednesday afternoon, May 9, was initiated by Datu Shahbandar Abdusakur Tan, the special envoy of the Royal Council of the Sulu Sultanate. The consensus was attended by more than 2,000 people coming from the di...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">Sun.Star Philippines</source></item><item><title>Troops rescue companion of abducted policewomen - Sun.Star Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1742330?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ9xyjhmzkY6hLVFDyQe4QQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKmgnQM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 04:13:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1742330?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;Troops rescue companion of abducted policewomen&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Sun.Star Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;GOVERNMENT forces rescued on Tuesday, May 8, one of the two companions of the two policewomen who were abducted by the Abu Sayyaf last week in Patikul, Sulu. Joint Task Force (JTF) Sulu commander Brigadier General Cirilito Sobejana said Wednesday, May 9, that troops of the Marine Battalion Landing Team rescued Blas Jackosalim Ahamad around 2 p.m. Tuesday in Sitio Budjang, Barangay Libog Kabao, Panglima Estino, Sulu. He said Ahamad underwent a medical examination and was later on brought to the JTF Sulu headquarters where he underwent custodial debriefing before he was turned over to his fam...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">Sun.Star Philippines</source></item><item><title>Military checking reported killing of Abu Sayyaf leader - Sun.Star Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1741820?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMnLB6KINMamaqUDMvEHbVYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKmgnQM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 06 May 2018 07:34:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1741820?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;Military checking reported killing of Abu Sayyaf leader&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Sun.Star Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE Armed Forces of the Philippines said Saturday, May 5, it is checking intelligence reports that a Middle East-educated commander of the Abu Sayyaf extremist group has died after being wounded in an artillery strike in the south.Brig Gen. Cirilito Sobejana said that if the reported killing of Yassir Igasan in southern Sulu province turns out to be true, it would add to a leadership crisis within the Abu Sayyaf. The brutal group has lost many commanders to combat and surrenders in recent years.The military received intelligence that Igasan was seriously wounded in the leg by artillery fire...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">Sun.Star Philippines</source></item></channel></rss>