<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Arnel Pineda - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqJAgKIh5DQkFTRUFvS0wyMHZNRE5qYzJSa1p4SUNaVzRvQUFQAQ?hl=en-PH&amp;gl=PH&amp;ceid=PH:en</link><language>en-PH</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 12:38:50 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>'Crazy, Rich Asians' director eyes movie about Arnel Pineda: report - ABS-CBN News</title><link>https://news.abs-cbn.com/entertainment/12/06/18/crazy-rich-asians-director-eyes-movie-about-arnel-pineda</link><guid isPermaLink="false">52780127638298</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 05:06:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.abs-cbn.com/entertainment/12/06/18/crazy-rich-asians-director-eyes-movie-about-arnel-pineda" target="_blank"&gt;'Crazy, Rich Asians' director eyes movie about Arnel Pineda: report&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABS-CBN News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.comingsoon.net/movies/news/1015807-crazy-rich-asians-director-to-helm-arnel-pineda-biopic" target="_blank"&gt;Crazy Rich Asians Director to Helm Arnel Pineda Biopic&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ComingSoon.net&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://nextshark.com/crazy-rich-asians-director-arnel-pineda/" target="_blank"&gt;‘Crazy Rich Asians’ Director to Make Movie About Filipino Legend Arnel Pineda&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;NextShark&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.spin.com/2018/12/jon-m-chu-biopic-journey-singer-arnel-pineda/" target="_blank"&gt;Jon M. Chu to Direct Biopic on Journey Frontman Arnel Pineda&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SPIN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.stereogum.com/2025168/journey-movie-arnel-pineda-jon-m-chu/news/" target="_blank"&gt;'Crazy Rich Asians' Director Turning Journey Singer's Life Into A Movie&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Stereogum&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/stories/CAAqOQgKIjNDQklTSURvSmMzUnZjbmt0TXpZd1NoTUtFUWlhcG9tbWpZQU1FWjZFdW96UDk4c2lLQUFQAQ?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;View full coverage on Google News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;</description><source url="https://news.abs-cbn.com">ABS-CBN News</source><media:content url="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/proxy/zzXCzZwIZfDiDdZuJc3vlL6x89hpRE-8pv_9cjc2y8p94SzKgrTCNs6gUQzbvcwbVc1toG54gGrHkesyxHUkvufbDdnyyUnmuRTOliorPe396lv9EZinQGX9Z_JNym5MiftM1Wk=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>'Crazy Rich Asians' director to helm Arnel Pineda's journey in biopic – report - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/12/06/Journey-Arnel-Pineda-biopic-movie-Crazy-Rich-Asians-director.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECrNsxHDgIrfVkTc_3qX3EAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMJbthQM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 07:52:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/12/06/Journey-Arnel-Pineda-biopic-movie-Crazy-Rich-Asians-director.html" target="_blank"&gt;'Crazy Rich Asians' director to helm Arnel Pineda's journey in biopic – report&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, December 6) — The man behind the box-office hit film 'Crazy Rich Asians' is set to direct the film chronicling the rise to fame of Journey's Filipino frontman Arnel Pineda. Director Jon M. Chu confirmed to online magazine Deadline on Wednesday that he is working with Warner Bros to create the Arnel Pineda biopic based on the "Don't Stop Believin': Everyman's Journey" documentary. He said "Maze Runner" producer Marty Bowen will also join the team. Chu said he wants to highlight the rags-to-riches story of Manila-born and -raised Pineda, who was discovered by th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>'Crazy Rich Asians' director working on movie about Journey's Ariel Pineda – report - Rappler</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fiP1NBDzX8M</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAqv5DpOZPy921FivwOBNeQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMMCTnwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 20:05:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fiP1NBDzX8M" target="_blank"&gt;'Crazy Rich Asians' director working on movie about Journey's Ariel Pineda – report&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jon M. Chu and Warner Bros are reportedly working on a feature about the life of Filipino singer Arnel Pineda, who shot to fame as lead singer of American rock band Journey. Story: https://www.rappler.com/entertainment/news/218324-crazy-rich-asians-director-working-movie-about-arnel-pineda&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.youtube.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Arnel Pineda reacts to Rock and Roll Hall of Fame snub - ABS CBN News</title><link>http://news.abs-cbn.com/entertainment/11/21/16/arnel-pineda-reacts-to-rock-and-roll-hall-of-fame-snub</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKHprMEESr9qfa39bh15L2kqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow8IjwCjDw4s8CMNf9mQI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2016 12:37:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://news.abs-cbn.com/entertainment/11/21/16/arnel-pineda-reacts-to-rock-and-roll-hall-of-fame-snub" target="_blank"&gt;Arnel Pineda reacts to Rock and Roll Hall of Fame snub&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABS CBN News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A photo posted by Journey (@journeymusicofficial) on Nov 19, 2016 at 9:17am PST MANILA -- American rock band Journey frontman Arnel Pineda has no ill-feelings that he was not included in the list of artists nominated for induction to the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame for 2017. This, amid reports that the band will petition for Pineda to be included should Journey get inducted. In an earlier interview with Billboard, keyboardist-guitarist Jonathan Cain said he does not think it is fair that Pineda wasn’t on the list of Journey members given the nod. - READ: Journey backs Arnel Pineda over Rock...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://news.abs-cbn.com">ABS CBN News</source></item><item><title>Journey to hold Manila concert in 2017 - Rappler</title><link>http://www.rappler.com/entertainment/news/156367-journey-band-manila-concert-2017</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBdETp6YeTbL2UukmJTRVeAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMI7omQI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2016 01:48:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.rappler.com/entertainment/news/156367-journey-band-manila-concert-2017" target="_blank"&gt;Journey to hold Manila concert in 2017&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – Journey is coming back to Manila to hold a concert on February 17, 2017! The band, led by Pinoy Arnel Pineda since 2007, will perform at the Mall of Asia Concert Grounds next year. Arnel himself announced the concert on social media with a poster. On Instagram, he simply captioned the photo, "Hey friends and folks!! It's Feb 17 at MOA." {source} hey Friends &amp; Folks!! its Feb 17 at MOA @journeymusicofficial @nealschon @jonathancainmusic #stevesmithdrums #rossvaloryjourney #dontstopbelieving #faithfully #openarms #separateways A photo posted by arnel c. pineda (@arnelpin...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Pearl Jam and Tupac Shakur Will Join Rock and Roll Hall of Fame - The New York Times</title><link>http://www.nytimes.com/2016/12/20/arts/music/rock-roll-hall-fame-inductees-2017.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECU1Z-LwQL6U9Aqi4sRKXIwqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzwwt4QY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2016 13:00:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.nytimes.com/2016/12/20/arts/music/rock-roll-hall-fame-inductees-2017.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pearl Jam and Tupac Shakur Will Join Rock and Roll Hall of Fame&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pearl Jam, Journey and Tupac Shakur will join the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame’s class of 2017, along with Joan Baez, Electric Light Orchestra and Yes. The six acts will enter the pantheon at the Rock Hall’s 32nd annual induction ceremony at Barclays Center in Brooklyn on April 7, with excerpts from the event to be broadcast later in the year by HBO. The hall’s latest batch of honorees continues its trends of nabbing 1990s rock icons the instant they become eligible, and finally opening the door to older stars who have been shut out for years. Pearl Jam’s acceptance, in the band’s first year ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>Sinulog weekend kicks off with concert - Sun.Star Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/cebu/entertainment/2017/01/12/sinulog-weekend-kicks-concert-519684</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELIxzbM0xVW8mZ_T2aS1A1UqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJeunQM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2017 16:27:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/cebu/entertainment/2017/01/12/sinulog-weekend-kicks-concert-519684" target="_blank"&gt;Sinulog weekend kicks off with concert&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Sun.Star Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MERRIMENT around the metro goes full swing this weekend with the staging of Unlimited Voices, a musical concert featuring Jonalyn Viray, Johanne Morissette D. Amon, Jolianne Salvado and Arnel Pineda at 8 p.m. on Saturday at the Pacific Grand Ballroom of Waterfront Cebu City Hotel and Casino. Coined the country’s Soul Princess, Viray is known for her belting technique and ability to sing operatic arias. Cebu-born Amon, or simply Morissette, rose to prominence at 14 when she emerged as runner-up on TV5’s Star Factor. Another Cebuana taking center stage is Salvado. The 13-year-old vocalist and...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">Sun.Star Philippines</source></item><item><title>IN PHOTOS: Arnel Pineda’s 50th birthday concert - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/entertainment/music/181918-arnel-pineda-50th-birthday-concert-manila</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOByYSwjJwdnxT0aDM4z71YqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMI7omQI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2017 07:43:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/entertainment/music/181918-arnel-pineda-50th-birthday-concert-manila" target="_blank"&gt;IN PHOTOS: Arnel Pineda’s 50th birthday concert&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – One of the premier vocalists of the Philippines celebrated a milestone with a one-of-a-kind concert at the newly opened Grand Ballroom of Okada Manila. Arnel’s vocal prowess is something to behold, he could sing the phonebook and still move mountains. He addressed the audience in a comfortable and genuine fashion explaining how fortunate and thankful he is to be where he is today. After a handful of songs, there was a video presentation that documented Arnel’s inspirational story, from humble beginnings to his rise to fame as lead singer of the legendary band Journey. ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>LOOK: Arnel Pineda meets former Journey singer Steve Perry - Rappler</title><link>http://www.rappler.com/entertainment/news/166467-arnel-pineda-meets-journey-singer-steve-perry</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGeOxRRvpYuIdFK4Maw6sLcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMI7omQI</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2017 02:28:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.rappler.com/entertainment/news/166467-arnel-pineda-meets-journey-singer-steve-perry" target="_blank"&gt;LOOK: Arnel Pineda meets former Journey singer Steve Perry&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – Arnel Pineda has met former Journey lead singer Steve Perry. The two met at the Rock &amp; Hall of Fame induction ceremony, where Journey was one of the groups honored. It was held at Brooklyn's Barclays Center on Friday, April 7. On Instagram, Arnel, who is the current frontman of the group, expressed his joy upon meeting one of the singers he admires. "One of the sweetest hugs you can ever get from one of my heroes and silent mentors... it means the world to me. Waited 35 years for this moment. Thank you almighty God! "Thank you so much Mister Steve Perry for your pricel...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Donald Trump Is Now Causing Drama With The Members Of Journey - HuffPost</title><link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/journey-neal-schon-drama-donald-trump_us_5988cf19e4b0a66b8badb9f2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPZTRD7vJAZf1_cMe9f9dYIqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMKOXAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2017 21:49:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/journey-neal-schon-drama-donald-trump_us_5988cf19e4b0a66b8badb9f2" target="_blank"&gt;Donald Trump Is Now Causing Drama With The Members Of Journey&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Journey’s Neal Schon won’t be running toward Donald Trump with open arms anytime soon. However, some of his bandmates already have, and he’s not happy about it. Last week, Schon shared a post on Facebook in which he called out three of his bandmates ― keyboardist Jonathan Cain, bassist Ross Valory, and frontman Arnel Pineda ― who visited the White House last Thursday. Schon, a founding member of the band, seems to believe the publicized meeting was done with the intention of exploiting the Journey brand, and it doesn’t sit well with him. He also claims it was arranged without his knowledge....&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>WATCH: Arnel, Morissette cover 'I Finally Found Someone' - ABS CBN News</title><link>http://news.abs-cbn.com/entertainment/10/28/16/watch-arnel-morissette-cover-i-finally-found-someone</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECuioAwO2ohPH90_ZCYe86oqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow8IjwCjDw4s8CMNf9mQI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2016 02:45:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://news.abs-cbn.com/entertainment/10/28/16/watch-arnel-morissette-cover-i-finally-found-someone" target="_blank"&gt;WATCH: Arnel, Morissette cover 'I Finally Found Someone'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABS CBN News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA -- Journey frontman Arnel Pineda and "ASAP" regular Morissette Amon teamed up for an special duet of the ballad "I Finally Found Someone" by Barbra Streisand and Bryan Adams. A video of their duet was uploaded on YouTube by radio station Wish 107.5 and has been making the rounds online since Wednesday. As of writing, the video has been viewed for over 156,000 times. Pineda and Amon are part of the upcoming concert "Powerhouse" on October 28 at The Theater at Solaire. Joining them in the special concert are Michael Pangilinan, 4th Impact, and Mayumi &amp; Toms.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://news.abs-cbn.com">ABS CBN News</source></item><item><title>Journey performs in Manila after 8 years - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/lifestyle/2017/02/17/Journey-performs-in-Manila-after-8-years.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENKcyOou0p3LP3I3VBMeJIoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMLXvpAM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2017 04:18:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/lifestyle/2017/02/17/Journey-performs-in-Manila-after-8-years.html" target="_blank"&gt;Journey performs in Manila after 8 years&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines) — Avid rock fans should not miss the "one night only concert" of American rock band Journey. The band's lead singer, Arnel Pineda, will also be performing with the band. The rock band, famous for the hits "Don't Stop Believin'," "Open Arms," and "Faithfully," among others, last performed in Manila in 2009. Four original members, Neal Schon on lead guitar, Jonathan Cain on keyboards, Ross Valory on bass and returning drummer Steve Smith, will perform tonight. Arnel Pineda even said he will perform with 110 percent of his ability so he could keep up with the gro...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>LOOK: Arnel Pineda meets Journey's Steve Perry for first time - ABS CBN News</title><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFRWk9MErrxd8KcMKM7wzIUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow8IjwCjDw4s8CMNf9mQI</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2017 06:45:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABS CBN News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A post shared by arnel c. pineda (@arnelpineda2007) on Apr 7, 2017 at 5:25pm PDT For nearly four decades, Arnel Pineda has always wanted to meet Journey's original frontman Steve Perry. On Friday, the Filipino singer finally got his wish — and then some. The touching moment happened after Journey was inducted into the Rock &amp; Roll Hall of Fame in a ceremony held in Brooklyn, New York. "One of the sweetest hug you can ever get from one of my heroes and silent mentors," said Pineda as he shared on Instagram a photo of him embracing the music legend. "It means the world to me. Waited 35 years f...&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>From The Archives: The Rise Of Monster Vocalist Arnel Pineda - FHM Philippines</title><link>http://www.fhm.com.ph/lifestyle/entertainment/the-rise-of-journey-vocalist-arnel-pineda-a381-20170411-lfrm2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHhVFrjRA1mlZIZ9tABRUYkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowvKfeCjCB1NUBMK7nmQI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 10:45:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.fhm.com.ph/lifestyle/entertainment/the-rise-of-journey-vocalist-arnel-pineda-a381-20170411-lfrm2" target="_blank"&gt;From The Archives: The Rise Of Monster Vocalist Arnel Pineda&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;FHM Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(Journey, the legendary American rock band formed in 1973, was inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame last April 7, at Barclays Center in Brooklyn, New York, along with the equally prodigious Pearl Jam, Yes, Tupac Shakur, Elo, and Joan Baez. It marked the first time that ex-Journey lead vocalist, Steve Perry, has ever been on stage with his former bandmates. In his speech, Perry made special mention of the band's current vocalist, our very own Arnel Pineda, exclaiming: "I must give a complete shout out to someone who sings his heart out every night, and it's Arnel Pineda. Where are yo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.fhm.com.ph">FHM Philippines</source></item><item><title>A fake band goes on tour: Threatin provides a perfect tale for our times - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/nov/13/threatin-fake-band-rock-pop</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPSjGUg8tQDVzpPRQthwChIqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTC9vBU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 07:00:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/nov/13/threatin-fake-band-rock-pop" target="_blank"&gt;A fake band goes on tour: Threatin provides a perfect tale for our times&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;As great rock’n’roll swindles go, the story of Threatin is rather impressive. The LA-based metal act – essentially just Jered Threatin – had apparently been enjoying a successful tour of the UK, with shows secured on the strength of an online following and advance ticket sales promising a fine night and healthy bar sales. In the event, however, this is not quite how it rolled. Related: Threatin: band creates fake fanbase for tour attended by no one At the Underworld in Camden (capacity: 500) Threatin’s agent claimed 29 advance tickets had been confirmed at the north London venue. In reality...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Filipino singer Marcelito Pomoy to guest on Ellen Show - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/entertainment/2018/10/29/marcelito-pomo-ellen-degeneres.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMb2FLgyySjRb1bg8iJdDoUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMJXupAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 00:56:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/entertainment/2018/10/29/marcelito-pomo-ellen-degeneres.html" target="_blank"&gt;Filipino singer Marcelito Pomoy to guest on Ellen Show&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, October 29) — Pilipinas Got Talent Season 2 winner Marcelito Pomoy is on the spotlight again for his unique singing voice, this time on the international stage. Known for his ability to sing low and high notes in one performance, Pomoy was recognized by U.S. television show host Ellen DeGeneres for his rendition of "The Prayer," originally performed by Andrea Bocelli and Celine Dion. DeGeneres posted a preview of Pomoy's performance on Monday, showing the singer singing both female and male parts of the piece. "Marcelito Pomoy's voice is incredible. Both of th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>Steve Perry Walked Away From Journey. A Promise Finally Ended His Silence. - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/09/05/arts/music/steve-perry-journey-traces-interview.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEnQTaItURAjAb9gK-KnsY4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzwwqIQY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2018 14:00:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/09/05/arts/music/steve-perry-journey-traces-interview.html" target="_blank"&gt;Steve Perry Walked Away From Journey. A Promise Finally Ended His Silence.&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;He was the singer in the enormously popular band until he burned out. Finding and losing the love of his life led him back to music after two decades.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>Morissette sets ‘Made in Cebu’ concert - SunStar Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1747154?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELXsHr0bejiUPIByZi41Ma0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMIm1nAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 14:52:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1747154?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;Morissette sets ‘Made in Cebu’ concert&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;CEBUANA Morissette Amon sets her homecoming concert this July 14. This is her first homecoming concert since making a name for herself in the national scene following appearances in TV5’s “Star Factor” (2010) and ABS-CBN’s “The Voice of the Philippines” Season 1 (2013). She is also a mainstay on “ASAP.” “I am both excited and nervous kay it’s my very first homecoming concert—ever since ‘The Voice,’ ever since sa TV5,” Asia’s Phoenix said in a press conference last Thursday. “Very excited ko nga i-share akong journey again sa akong mga kapwa Cebuanos and excited pud mi sa tanan surprises na ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Here’s The Story Behind 'Don’t Stop Believin,’' The Song That Keeps On Giving - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/journey-dont-stop-believin_us_5ae9b94de4b022f71a03cef1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOcvckWLvYo57aw5tjhS6TkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMKOXAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2018 15:46:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/journey-dont-stop-believin_us_5ae9b94de4b022f71a03cef1" target="_blank"&gt;Here’s The Story Behind 'Don’t Stop Believin,’' The Song That Keeps On Giving&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;There’s no denying it: Rarely a wedding or party goes by without Journey’s “Don’t Stop Believin’” being played. Released in June 1981, the song appeared on the rock band’s seventh album, “Escape.” Although it never made it to No. 1 on the charts, “Don’t Stop Believin’” has seeped into our culture in countless ways. The “Sopranos” series finale. That memorable “Glee” pilot episode. Broadway’s “Rock of Ages” musical. Your karaoke night. You probably know the words by heart, but you may not know the details behind the making of the song. Journey keyboardist Jonathan Cain tells the story of the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item></channel></rss>