<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Carlos Dominguez III - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqKAgKIiJDQkFTRXdvTkwyY3ZNVEZqTUhCNWVUZGpOQklDWlc0b0FBUAE?hl=en-PH&amp;gl=PH&amp;ceid=PH:en</link><language>en-PH</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 12:57:19 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Dominguez hits Arroyo over 'scandalous' China deals - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/218343-dominguez-hits-arroyo-scandalous-china-deals</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH6SQHkm2nWzVZ6WO6J4qVEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 07:55:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/218343-dominguez-hits-arroyo-scandalous-china-deals" target="_blank"&gt;Dominguez hits Arroyo over 'scandalous' China deals&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;'I don't have to mention the names, I'll just mention some initials. ZTE, for instance,' says Finance Secretary Carlos Dominguez III.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Dominguez: PH shuns 'debt trap' with 'great prudence' in borrowings - ABS-CBN News</title><link>https://news.abs-cbn.com/business/11/28/18/dominguez-ph-shuns-debt-trap-with-great-prudence-in-borrowings</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiaWh0dHBzOi8vbmV3cy5hYnMtY2JuLmNvbS9idXNpbmVzcy8xMS8yOC8xOC9kb21pbmd1ZXotcGgtc2h1bnMtZGVidC10cmFwLXdpdGgtZ3JlYXQtcHJ1ZGVuY2UtaW4tYm9ycm93aW5nc9IBAA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://news.abs-cbn.com/business/11/28/18/dominguez-ph-shuns-debt-trap-with-great-prudence-in-borrowings" target="_blank"&gt;Dominguez: PH shuns 'debt trap' with 'great prudence' in borrowings&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABS-CBN News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA -- President Rodrigo Duterte's government "borrows with great prudence," the head of his economic team said Wednesday, as he dismissed as "totally ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://news.abs-cbn.com">ABS-CBN News</source><media:content url="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/proxy/Ft7vR9NkJ2DKY5smUMrlcQgteb_dUFbrWjRdbrGbX_y9WfCSyaIz_7RDy1ADtnuHtN8nz8ewXv9QvFBquz3D4L8sRtCp5iZIXW0sBZuSOBiPbQlWBAaFLMnztVWqh_-rPig=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>DOF's Carlos Dominguez announces tax increase to push through - Top Gear Philippines</title><link>https://www.topgear.com.ph/news/motoring-news/dof-suspend-oil-tax-hike-a962-20181129</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiVGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LnRvcGdlYXIuY29tLnBoL25ld3MvbW90b3JpbmctbmV3cy9kb2Ytc3VzcGVuZC1vaWwtdGF4LWhpa2UtYTk2Mi0yMDE4MTEyOdIBAA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 08:38:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.topgear.com.ph/news/motoring-news/dof-suspend-oil-tax-hike-a962-20181129" target="_blank"&gt;DOF's Carlos Dominguez announces tax increase to push through&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Top Gear Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;DOF secretary Carlos Dominguez has announced that managers have taken back their recommendation to suspend 2019's oil tax increase.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.topgear.com.ph">Top Gear Philippines</source><media:content url="https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/proxy/E7fOK2ya05yRdHxGrY96EBJznvPhRKmMx2oylCX3W1LpD1L2FPiVQ4I1R83jAg65bLrisQm7H76kmOkrbGzA5cUWvtwvEhZZvdJVNEIutB0fyhJR7fxmJvxANgpBlJtbit6_zkeXu2k0QiuaI5gl_9T2=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>The ANC Brief: Day of reckoning for Revilla - ABS CBN News</title><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEBSvkOkc3kAqCDeVz0O0mYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow8IjwCjDw4s8CMNj9mQI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 04:01:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABS CBN News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s the day of reckoning for former Sen. Bong Revilla in his plunder case. Meanwhile, President Duterte continues to take potshots at a favorite target: the Catholic Church. Here are the stories ANC will be covering today: Ruling on Revilla The promulgation of the plunder case against former Senator Bong Revilla is scheduled today at the Sandiganbayan. ANC will make sure to report on the latest updates on the decision on Revilla and stay in touch with both the prosecution and Revilla’s side. What will the decision mean for the other PDAF cases? Former Ombudsman Conchita Morales said if she...&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Governor Imee Marcos calls for 1-year VAT suspension - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1776696</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEID2K8RyRh7z1CrkgcFOSzsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMIeunQM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 07:22:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1776696" target="_blank"&gt;Governor Imee Marcos calls for 1-year VAT suspension&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ILOCOS Norte Governor Imee Marcos has called for the immediate one-year suspension of the value-added tax (VAT) on basic food commodities, fuel, and electricity to address the record-high inflation that has burdened Filipinos for several months now. Marcos, who is running for senator in the 2019 midterm polls, said a combination of substitute measures can offset the expected revenue loss from her proposed VAT suspension. “The temporary lifting of the VAT on basic commodities will provide urgent much-needed relief to Filipinos as inflation hit the hardest in the countryside. The poor Filipin...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Impossible for PH to fall into debt trap — China - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/11/28/china-foreign-minister-geng-shuang-philippines-philippines-debt-trap.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEs_8idPRVvW346QEketTBEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMJbthQM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 13:36:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/11/28/china-foreign-minister-geng-shuang-philippines-philippines-debt-trap.html" target="_blank"&gt;Impossible for PH to fall into debt trap — China&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, November 28) — It is impossible for the Philippines to fall into the debt trap of China, according to the Chinese Foreign Ministry. "China's loans only account for a very limited share of the Philippines' foreign debts. It's impossible for the Philippines to fall into the so-called "debt trap" due to these loans," Foreign Ministry Spokesperson Geng Shuang said Tuesday in a press briefing in Beijing. He also said China has since financed relevant infrastructure projects at the Philippines' request, in line with the Duterte administration's "Build, Build, Build"...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>Critics of Chinese-funded projects ‘uninformed’ - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1776245</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOHwQK06OXiBcMET0FFJaG0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMMuPnAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 10:56:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1776245" target="_blank"&gt;Critics of Chinese-funded projects ‘uninformed’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aside from tax reform, the “Build, Build, Build” infrastructure program is benefitting from the generous funding support from Japan and China, two of the Philippines’ closest development partners in the region, Finance Secretary Carlos Dominguez III said on Wednesday, November 28. Dominguez, speaking at the Sulong Pilipinas Forum in Davao City, noted that some “uninformed critics have made unfounded claims” about the country falling into a debt trap, as a result of the financing extended by China and Japan, even though the government had secured these at the lowest interest rates and longes...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Government needs P72.5B to rehab Marawi - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1776277</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB--AFBayKqoYBwH1qsCDF0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKeunQM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 12:31:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1776277" target="_blank"&gt;Government needs P72.5B to rehab Marawi&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;FINANCE Secretary Carlos G. Dominguez III said P72.5 billion is needed to rehabilitate Marawi City over the next five years. “Of this amount, P42.7 billion is needed for the Bangon Marawi Comprehensive Rehabilitation and Recovery Program. The financing requirement will also include P17.2 billion that will be spent to rehabilitate the most affected areas and a P1.25 billion for livelihood assistance,” Dominguez said in a press conference during the Sulong Pilipinas Philippine Development Forum at SMX Convention Center in SM Lanang Premier on Wednesday, November 28. Dominguez said the funds w...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Slow China loans a blessing in disguise? - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/business/217330-slow-china-loans-philippines-blessing-in-disguise</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKRTb9J2uJwO5xRqeLaRZUUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMP_mmQI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 10:05:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/business/217330-slow-china-loans-philippines-blessing-in-disguise" target="_blank"&gt;Slow China loans a blessing in disguise?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – President Rodrigo Duterte and Chinese President Xi Jinping signed a total of 29 deals during Xi's state visit to Manila. But a closer look at the list shows that most are still in various stages of talks and are not yet for actual implementation. (LIST: Deals signed during Xi Jinping's trip to Philippines) China pledged some $24 billion worth of loans for projects, but most have yet to materialize. Looking at data from the National Economic and Development Authority (NEDA), traditional partners like Japan have provided the most official development assistance (ODA) gra...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Bzzzzz: What inspired the Hitlerish Effigy - Sun.Star Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/cebu/local-news/2017/07/25/bzzzzz-what-inspired-hitlerish-effigy-554936</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIbZJfMXG_uy7dTR4x176a8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJeunQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2017 14:13:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/cebu/local-news/2017/07/25/bzzzzz-what-inspired-hitlerish-effigy-554936" target="_blank"&gt;Bzzzzz: What inspired the Hitlerish Effigy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Sun.Star Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WHATEVER and whoever gave the idea of comparing President Duterte to Hitler, which was how Sona protesters last Monday (July 24) depicted him in effigy? The “what” is disputable but the “who” gets an easy, non-contentious answer. It was Duterte himself who did. While at one time he argued he couldn’t be a Hitler, he said he’d “happy to slaughter” three million Filipino drug addicts. He fumed that he was “portrayed or pictured as a cousin of Hitler.” Hitler massacred “three million Jews,” but Hitler-like he’d kill all those Pinoy drug addicts. Well, the Sona protesters got the idea and creat...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">Sun.Star Philippines</source></item><item><title>Tax reform package 1 to be implemented before year end - Sun.Star Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/davao/business/2017/07/25/tax-reform-package-1-be-implemented-year-end-554812</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENo5MOc2gX9UUsOMYbCfIiAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKeunQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2017 18:59:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/davao/business/2017/07/25/tax-reform-package-1-be-implemented-year-end-554812" target="_blank"&gt;Tax reform package 1 to be implemented before year end&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Sun.Star Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PACKAGE 1 of the Tax Reform and Acceleration and Inclusion of Department of Finance (DOF) is to be implemented by the third or fourth quarter of 2017. The comprehensive tax reform program is a series of five reform packages which, according to Finance secretary Carlos Dominguez III, is aimed at making the tax system in the Philippines fairer and more efficient. First package includes simplification of the tax system which allows entry-level workers with annual income of P250,000 and below to be exempted from the income tax. It also includes value added tax (VAT) base expansion while liming ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">Sun.Star Philippines</source></item><item><title>DOF gets P19.73-billion budget for 2018 - Sun.Star Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/cebu/business/2017/09/06/dof-gets-p1973-billion-budget-2018-562652</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJCADo6Q3Q706M8gOBKDfDgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMMuPnAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2017 13:49:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/cebu/business/2017/09/06/dof-gets-p1973-billion-budget-2018-562652" target="_blank"&gt;DOF gets P19.73-billion budget for 2018&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Sun.Star Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A SMALLER budget looms for the Department of Finance (DOF) in 2018 after the Committee on Appropriations of the House of Representatives endorsed P19.73 billion for congressional approval. Next year’s budget is 16 percent lower or a P3.5-billion decrease from 2017. Finance Secretary Carlos Dominguez explained that 2017 saw most of the agency’s investment outlays, property, plant and equipment, and so the department purposely requested for a lower budget next year. “The DOF voluntarily submitted a lower budget for 2018 compared to the preceding year to set an example for other departments to...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">Sun.Star Philippines</source></item><item><title>Ledesma: Rallies fizzle for who can quarrel with success? (2nd of 2 parts) - Sun.Star Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/davao/opinion/2017/09/25/ledesma-rallies-fizzle-who-can-quarrel-success-2nd-2-parts-565874</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBna51o8TsIG-ld0-fH3A8cqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMMu4nAM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2017 16:46:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/davao/opinion/2017/09/25/ledesma-rallies-fizzle-who-can-quarrel-success-2nd-2-parts-565874" target="_blank"&gt;Ledesma: Rallies fizzle for who can quarrel with success? (2nd of 2 parts)&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Sun.Star Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BACK in Manila, the usual coterie of the now moribund Liberal Party huddled in a chapel in University of the Philippines (UP)-Diliman in what they bannered as “Mass for Justice.” They had shed off the usual yellow attire and they came all dressed in immaculate white the sheen was like that of a sheep’s clothing. Former President Noynoy Aquino had lost so much weight. Senators Frank Drilon, Kiko Pangilinan, Bam Aquino, loser Mar Roxas and VP Leni Robredo were all there wearing glum faces. Noynoy managed to say a brief statement saying “dapat magkaisa para pigilan ang pagpapatay.” He forgot t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">Sun.Star Philippines</source></item><item><title>Sangil: Pagcor wearing two crowns - Sun.Star Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/pampanga/opinion/2017/09/13/sangil-pagcor-wearing-two-crowns-563921</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELymueIjohs9v_pPVoMxtj4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMMu4nAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 13:35:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/pampanga/opinion/2017/09/13/sangil-pagcor-wearing-two-crowns-563921" target="_blank"&gt;Sangil: Pagcor wearing two crowns&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Sun.Star Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE latest news coming out from the Department of Finance is that starting next year the 17 casinos operated by the state run Philippine Amusement and Gaming Corporation (Pagcor) will be privatized, meaning it will no longer an operator but merely a regulatory agency. The agency in the first place shouldn't be wearing two crowns - hat of an operator and a regulator at the same time. Based on What DOF Secretary Carlos Dominguez' statements, the casinos in the provinces will go first. I was in my mid-twenties when I worked in the casinos. High life. Big stakes. Top entertainment. The danger l...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">Sun.Star Philippines</source></item><item><title>All systems go for 26th Minbizcom - Sun.Star Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/cagayan-de-oro/business/2017/09/06/all-systems-go-26th-minbizcom-562507</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGDI2eDlSmZ5_SACA9-lZOoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMMuPnAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 19:46:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/cagayan-de-oro/business/2017/09/06/all-systems-go-26th-minbizcom-562507" target="_blank"&gt;All systems go for 26th Minbizcom&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Sun.Star Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;IT'S all systems go for host Cagayan de Oro Chamber of Commerce and Industry Foundation (Oro Chamber) as it prepares to host the biggest annual gathering of businessmen and policymakers not just from Mindanao but from the whole country. Over 1,000 businessmen are expected to attend the 26th Mindanao Business Conference (Minbizcon) which will begin on Thursday, September 7, at the Xavier Sports and Country Club. Finance Secretary Carlos Dominguez is expected to grace the first day of the three-day gathering to deliver the opening keynote. President Rodrigo Duterte is scheduled to deliver the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">Sun.Star Philippines</source></item><item><title>AirAsia eyes more int'l flights from Davao - Sun.Star Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/davao/business/2017/08/28/airasia-eyes-more-intl-flights-davao-560934</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAaAIIcz5ZTySP_d1_R4NSQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMMuPnAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2017 13:29:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/davao/business/2017/08/28/airasia-eyes-more-intl-flights-davao-560934" target="_blank"&gt;AirAsia eyes more int'l flights from Davao&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Sun.Star Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MALAYSIA-BASED low-cost airline, AirAsia, is looking into the possibility of opening more international flights from Davao City to other key destinations in Asia. In a press statement, the Department of Finance said Asia's leading low-cost airline has expressed interest in expanding its services in the Philippines to include flights from Davao City to key cities in China, Korea and Malaysia. “There’s a big population here. There’s a good business here. We met some farmers who wish to send their cargos directly to these places,” Tony Fernandes, CEO of AirAsia Group, said. Fernandes also said...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">Sun.Star Philippines</source></item><item><title>Gov’t posts budget deficit at P154.5B - Sun.Star Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/manila/local-news/2017/07/24/govt-posts-budget-deficit-p1545b-554655</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDA3GR638UMaXt9Hh4BVJicqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKmgnQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2017 06:59:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/manila/local-news/2017/07/24/govt-posts-budget-deficit-p1545b-554655" target="_blank"&gt;Gov’t posts budget deficit at P154.5B&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Sun.Star Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA -- The Philippine Government posted a P154.5 billion budget gap in the first half of 2017, higher than the P143.8 billion target for the period. Data released by the Bureau of the Treasury (BTr) Monday, July 24, showed a 28 percent rise in the budget deficit from 2016’s P120.3 billion. This, after expenditures rose by nine percent to P1.33 trillion, hitting the target, from 2016’s P1.22 trillion. Revenues during the same period posted a lower growth of seven percent to P1.176 trillion against the P1.101 trillion in end-June 2016. Compared to the program, collections in the first half...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">Sun.Star Philippines</source></item><item><title>Procurement, rightsizing bills tackled at 2nd Ledac meeting - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/180545-ledac-meeting-procurement-rightsizing-bills</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB0u4xHExnUqbqpU6IK9GDkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 00:37:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/180545-ledac-meeting-procurement-rightsizing-bills" target="_blank"&gt;Procurement, rightsizing bills tackled at 2nd Ledac meeting&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – Top government officials led by President Rodrigo Duterte discussed with Congress leaders the proposed bills seeking to modify the procurement process and streamline the government bureaucracy during the second Legislative-Executive Development Advisory Council (Ledac) meeting on Tuesday, August 29. The President, who convened the Ledac 7 months after the first meeting on January 30, had mentioned amendments to the procurement process and bills for the rightsizing of government among his 6 priority bills in his second State of the Nation Address. The current procuremen...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>DOF chief asks police to run after killers of his consultant - Sun.Star Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/iloilo/local-news/2017/08/04/dof-chief-asks-police-run-after-killers-his-consultant-556655</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF3HVFO7KhcvbbNjks9jzbYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKetnQM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2017 05:06:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/iloilo/local-news/2017/08/04/dof-chief-asks-police-run-after-killers-his-consultant-556655" target="_blank"&gt;DOF chief asks police to run after killers of his consultant&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Sun.Star Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;FINANCE Secretary Carlos Dominguez III called Friday on the law enforcement authorities to find and prosecute the killers of Michael Marasigan, his communications consultant. Dominguez has expressed shock and deep sadness over the death of Marasigan, along with his brother, Christopher, who was with him inside the vehicle when unidentified gunmen fired at them in San Juan City Thursday night. "I am both saddened and shocked," Dominguez said, stressing that the authorities should "find and prosecute to the fullest extent of the law the perpetrators behind the killing. "My deepest condolences...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">Sun.Star Philippines</source></item><item><title>Finance chief: Duterte won't fire Faeldon amid drug shipment probe - Sun.Star Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/manila/local-news/2017/08/01/finance-chief-duterte-wont-fire-faeldon-amid-drug-shipment-probe-556134</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAMEx8qAIbPTHRH1D1li9goqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKetnQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2017 12:17:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/manila/local-news/2017/08/01/finance-chief-duterte-wont-fire-faeldon-amid-drug-shipment-probe-556134" target="_blank"&gt;Finance chief: Duterte won't fire Faeldon amid drug shipment probe&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Sun.Star Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PRESIDENT Rodrigo Duterte will not fire Customs chief Nicanor Faeldon despite the controversial shipment of P6.25 billion worth of shabu contraband that entered through the Bureau of Customs (BOC), Finance Secretary Carlos Dominguez III on Tuesday. Dominguez, who was present when Duterte called Faeldon in Palace around 4 p.m. for a meeting, said the Customs chief would stay in his post. Dominguez said the President told Faeldon to continue fulfilling his mandate, even after some lawmakers sought his resignation following the multi-billion peso shipment of smuggled illegal drugs. "The Presid...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">Sun.Star Philippines</source></item><item><title>Legislators grill Faeldon, Customs on 3rd consecutive day - Rappler</title><link>http://www.rappler.com/nation/177526-ways-and-means-probe-faeldon-customs</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG1MPvhDRQnE-4QC69cDzYcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2017 13:42:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.rappler.com/nation/177526-ways-and-means-probe-faeldon-customs" target="_blank"&gt;Legislators grill Faeldon, Customs on 3rd consecutive day&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – A day after being summoned by no less than President Rodrigo Duterte, Customs Commissioner Nicanor Faeldon and his agency were again the subject of scrutiny by lawmakers on Wednesday, August 2. For the third consecutive day, Faeldon and his subordinates faced lawmakers, this time members of the House of Representatives’ ways and means committee, still over how billions of shabu were able to get past the express lane of the bureau. The illegal drugs were later seized by bureau agents from a Valenzuela warehouse on May 26. On August 1, Duterte called Faeldon to Malacañan...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>AirAsia exec urges gov't to scrap outbound travel tax for Pinoys - Sun.Star Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/davao/business/2017/07/26/airasia-exec-urges-govt-scrap-outbound-travel-tax-pinoys-555014</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBWkNAaDDIdr784eW6tS75QqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMMuPnAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2017 17:28:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/davao/business/2017/07/26/airasia-exec-urges-govt-scrap-outbound-travel-tax-pinoys-555014" target="_blank"&gt;AirAsia exec urges gov't to scrap outbound travel tax for Pinoys&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Sun.Star Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;AIRASIA Group chief executive officer Anthony Francis Fernandes urged the Philippine Government to consider removing the travel tax on outbound Filipino tourists to stir up more international flights in the country particularly outside Metro Manila like Davao City. Fernandes pointed out that the government will not lose much by removing the taxes as not much is being earned in airports that do not have international flights. “The travel tax is the deterrent, I think we have to show the government that actually you earn more through connectivity. This will encourage travelers to visit the in...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">Sun.Star Philippines</source></item><item><title>SC lifts TRO on Aquino's EO 179, 180 - Sun.Star Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/cebu/business/2017/09/25/sc-lifts-tro-aquinos-eo-179-180-566055</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDvVT7ilH6McJZo0G33TVe8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMMuPnAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2017 14:01:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/cebu/business/2017/09/25/sc-lifts-tro-aquinos-eo-179-180-566055" target="_blank"&gt;SC lifts TRO on Aquino's EO 179, 180&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Sun.Star Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;UCPB welcomes the lifting of the Supreme Court’s temporary restraining order on former Pres. Benigno S. Aquino III’s Executive Orders Nos. 179 &amp; 180, the company said in a statement. As announced by DOF Secretary Carlos G. Dominguez III, the government will soon resume the bank’s privatization through a recapitalization program and sale of the government’s majority stake in UCPB. (PR)&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">Sun.Star Philippines</source></item><item><title>Finance department targets $1.8-B loan for dev't - Sun.Star Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/davao/business/2017/07/27/finance-department-targets-18-b-loan-devt-555375</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOsoA3SeY4pYIqPNNJPPuTMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMMuPnAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2017 15:40:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/davao/business/2017/07/27/finance-department-targets-18-b-loan-devt-555375" target="_blank"&gt;Finance department targets $1.8-B loan for dev't&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Sun.Star Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE Department of Finance (DOF) targets to incur a total of $1.8 billion official development assistance (ODA) loans for 2018. During the 4th Davao Investment Conference (Icon) held at SMX Convention Center, SM Lanang, Saturday, July 23, Finance Secretary Carlos Dominguez said the amount will be used to implement key big ticket infrastructure projects of the country. He said the country is currently targeting a financing mix of 80 percent domestic borrowing and 20 percent foreign. “The preference for peso-denominated financing has altered the country’s debt portfolio. At present 67.1 percen...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">Sun.Star Philippines</source></item><item><title>Aguirre orders NBI to probe slay of ex-journalist, brother - Sun.Star Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/manila/local-news/2017/08/04/aguirre-orders-nbi-probe-slay-ex-journalist-brother-556682</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHshUMZVMlzbHiYxBu8KUawqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKmgnQM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2017 10:30:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/manila/local-news/2017/08/04/aguirre-orders-nbi-probe-slay-ex-journalist-brother-556682" target="_blank"&gt;Aguirre orders NBI to probe slay of ex-journalist, brother&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Sun.Star Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA -- Justice Secretary Vitaliano Aguirre II ordered the National Bureau of Investigation (NBI) on Friday to investigate the killing of Michael D. Marasigan, a former journalist who was shot dead in San Juan City Thursday night. Aguirre issued Department Order No. 515 directing NBI Director Dante Gierran to conduct a probe and case build-up on the killing of Marasigan and his brother, Christopher, who was with him inside the vehicle when the gunmen riding a motorcycle fired at them. Read: Former journalist shot dead in San Juan City "I have signed a Department Order instructing the NBI ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">Sun.Star Philippines</source></item><item><title>TradeNet to go live by yearend - Sun.Star Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/cebu/business/2017/09/11/tradenet-go-live-yearend-563570</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDY6KG9UYO8ndr6hLI7pL0IqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJeunQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2017 14:39:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/cebu/business/2017/09/11/tradenet-go-live-yearend-563570" target="_blank"&gt;TradeNet to go live by yearend&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Sun.Star Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;TO cut red tape for business, the Department of Finance (DOF) said it is finalizing a new, faster, and online-based import permit application. Called TradeNet, the platform aims to connect 66 agencies and 10 economic zones involved in the approval of import and export permits. At this point, DOF said the government is consolidating all requirements involving applications for imports to drastically shorten the process and make TradeNet available online. In a statement, Finance Secretary Carlos Dominguez acknowledged the tedious process of obtaining import permits, which currently involves mo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">Sun.Star Philippines</source></item><item><title>Tell it to SunStar: Delay jeopardizes bigger gov’t bonuses - Sun.Star Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/cebu/opinion/2017/09/04/tell-it-sunstar-delay-jeopardizes-bigger-govt-bonuses-562096</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENuzh3l9ksXyEfIio_p9n6QqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMMu4nAM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2017 22:17:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/cebu/opinion/2017/09/04/tell-it-sunstar-delay-jeopardizes-bigger-govt-bonuses-562096" target="_blank"&gt;Tell it to SunStar: Delay jeopardizes bigger gov’t bonuses&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Sun.Star Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE bigger Christmas bonuses of salaried employees, including government personnel, are now at risk owing to the delay in the passage of the first tax reform package in the Senate. The Senate should just put in whatever modifications they want and pass the tax reform bill. After all, President Duterte has certified the measure. Once the Senate approves the bill, we can leave it all up to the bicameral conference committee to thresh out the final version of the measure for ratification. Besides slashing individual income tax rates and freeing all personal income up to P250,000 from taxes, th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">Sun.Star Philippines</source></item><item><title>Former journalist shot dead in San Juan City - Sun.Star Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/manila/local-news/2017/08/04/former-journalist-shot-dead-san-juan-city-556657</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDGlTkk7GwQkcATMK4mFbBIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKetnQM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2017 05:58:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/manila/local-news/2017/08/04/former-journalist-shot-dead-san-juan-city-556657" target="_blank"&gt;Former journalist shot dead in San Juan City&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Sun.Star Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ARMED men on a motorcycle shot dead a former journalist and his brother Thursday night, August 3, in San Juan City, Metro Manila. Michael D. Marasigan, a former editor of BusinessWorld, died on the spot from multiple gunshots to his chest and neck while his brother Christopher was declared dead on arrival at a hospital. The attack on Marasigan shocked colleagues in the media. Finance Secretary Carlos Dominguez III, for whom Marasigan worked as communications consultant, called on law enforcers to find and prosecute to the fullest extent of the law the perpetrators behind the killing. "I hav...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">Sun.Star Philippines</source></item><item><title>Villar is only billionaire among Duterte Cabinet members - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2017/07/20/Villar-is-only-billionaire-among-Duterte-Cabinet-members.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGghm-OuHLDKaz2NgO_rGsoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMJbthQM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2017 15:50:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2017/07/20/Villar-is-only-billionaire-among-Duterte-Cabinet-members.html" target="_blank"&gt;Villar is only billionaire among Duterte Cabinet members&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, July 20) — Public Works Secretary Mark Villar is the only Cabinet member whose net worth has gone over a billion pesos, according to his latest Statements of Assets, Liabilities and Net Worth (SALNs). Malacañang released the summary of SALNs of the Cabinet members Thursday afternoon. Villar, whose net worth is P1,409,149,497 is the son of incumbent Senator Cynthia Villar, and former senator and real estate tycoon Manny Villar. He is followed Finance Secretary Carlos Dominguez, whose net worth only reached hundreds of millions: P351,859,283. On the other hand...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>Duterte to consider other expenses when deciding on free tuition bill - Rappler</title><link>http://www.rappler.com/nation/177592-duterte-free-tuition-sucs-bill-considerations</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDG8hZktTmKNciZWOlg3RHsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 06:42:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.rappler.com/nation/177592-duterte-free-tuition-sucs-bill-considerations" target="_blank"&gt;Duterte to consider other expenses when deciding on free tuition bill&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – Malacañang said the government's big expenses in other programs will be a major consideration for President Rodrigo Duterte when he decides whether or not to veto the Universal Access to Quality Tertiary Education Act. The bill, now up for Duterte's signature, aims to provide full tuition subsidy for students in 112 state universities and colleges (SUCs), local universities and colleges, and government-run technical-vocational schools. "We've got lots of problems, especially with the rehabilitation of Marawi and our OFWs (overseas Filipino workers) who need to be broug...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Chinese President Xi Jinping arrives in Philippines - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/217105-chinese-president-xi-jinping-arrival-philippines</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHPlGvvwYbYgNpGaJ0Iq2SYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 03:36:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/217105-chinese-president-xi-jinping-arrival-philippines" target="_blank"&gt;Chinese President Xi Jinping arrives in Philippines&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines (UPDATED) – Chinese President Xi Jinping arrived in the Philippines before noon on Tuesday, November 20, for a two-day state visit that is expected to include the signing of a controversial framework for the joint exploration of the South China Sea. Xi's plane landed at the Ninoy Aquino International Airport (NAIA) Terminal 1 at 11:27 am on Tuesday, and Xi exited his aircraft at 11:54 am. Xi was welcomed by Philippine Finance Secretary Carlos Dominguez III, Philippine Ambassador to China Chito Santa Romana, and Chinese Ambassador to the Philippines Zhao Jianhua. Xi is th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Seeking DOF post in 2019? ‘It's so hypothetical,’ says Arroyo - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/216570-gloria-arroyo-bid-for-department-finance-post-2019-hypothetical</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPD0-lKfrYhYpaP3XZbgnwMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 04:50:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/216570-gloria-arroyo-bid-for-department-finance-post-2019-hypothetical" target="_blank"&gt;Seeking DOF post in 2019? ‘It's so hypothetical,’ says Arroyo&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – Speaker Gloria Macapagal Arroyo dispelled rumors she is thinking of joining President Rodrigo Duterte’s Cabinet next year as Department of Finance (DOF) secretary. The former president turned Pampanga 2nd District congresswoman was asked by reporters on Tuesday, November 13, about talks in the banking community that she would become the next DOF chief. “Ay, it's so hypothetical,” said Arroyo, who was smiling as she repeatedly shook her head. Arroyo, an economist who saw the passage on 3rd reading of Duterte’s second batch of tax reforms during her term as Speaker, is a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Arroyo on alleged Finance Secretary appointment: 'It's hypothetical' - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/11/13/gloria-macapagal-arroyo-finance-secretary-rumor.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE2movG-IFjfMNH61VUOq_sqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMJbthQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 08:52:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/11/13/gloria-macapagal-arroyo-finance-secretary-rumor.html" target="_blank"&gt;Arroyo on alleged Finance Secretary appointment: 'It's hypothetical'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, November 13) — House Speaker Gloria Macapagal-Arroyo is again at the center of another appointment rumor. The former President turned House Representative unseated former House Speaker Pantaleon Alvarez in July, something that has been rumored for months prior to the event. Now the House Speaker says rumors about her being appointed as the new Finance Secretary are "hypothetical." "It's hypothetical," Arroyo told the press in an ambush interview Tuesday. Asked if the position was offered to her, she repeated her previous statement. Secretary Carlos Dominguez, ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>Ledesma: Bogus cabal behind Sonny’s ouster plot? - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1772205</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOWrQLN8g9jrErMpMQa8qukqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKeunQM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 13:10:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1772205" target="_blank"&gt;Ledesma: Bogus cabal behind Sonny’s ouster plot?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;IT LOOKS like Coalitions Against Corruption are dime a dozen. I wrote a piece the other day following a headline story of a major daily citing CAC calling for the resignation of Finance Chief Sonny Dominguez for what they claimed was his silence over the huge volume of shipment of shabu in Cavite port that led to the major shakedown in the Bureau of Customs. The banner story did not mention names behind CAC so I proceeded to Google it. There were names of institutions listed but not good enough as a credible source except that towards the end of its information box is Makati Business Club a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Palace shrugs off call for Dominguez resignation - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1771856/Manila/Local-News/Palace-shrugs-off-call-for-Dominguez-resignation?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGGvV2_bPzmehC9r_SRj7KUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKmgnQM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 09:03:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1771856/Manila/Local-News/Palace-shrugs-off-call-for-Dominguez-resignation?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;Palace shrugs off call for Dominguez resignation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MALACAÑANG on Wednesday, October 31, brushed aside an anti-corruption group's call for the resignation of Finance Secretary Carlos Dominguez III, saying there is "no reason or basis" for such appeal. Presidential Spokesperson Salvador Panelo said Domginuez, as one of the administration's "trusted" economic managers, continues to enjoy President Rodrigo Duterte's trust and confidence. "Some quarters have been asking for the resignation of Finance Secretary Carlos Dominguez. The Palace finds no reason or basis for such call," Panelo said in a statement. "Secretary Dominguez continues to enjoy...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Militarization of Customs? I'm a civilian, says Guerrero - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/215648-guerrero-denies-militarization-bureau-customs</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAUgFXKJxAJaE3GIN43zAhkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 05:25:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/215648-guerrero-denies-militarization-bureau-customs" target="_blank"&gt;Militarization of Customs? I'm a civilian, says Guerrero&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – A military takeover of the Bureau of Customs (BOC), as ordered by President Rodrigo Duterte, will not compromise civilian supremacy in the agency, its new chief Rey Leonardo Guerrero assured the public on Wednesday, October 31. In his first press confererence as BOC chief, Guerrero said he was the perfect example that civilians remained in charge of the bureau. "Clearly a civilian – I am the head of the service," Guerrero, a retired military general, said in response to questions about the "military takeover" of the bureau. "The directive of the President to have milit...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Philippines, China launch peso-yuan trading facility - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/business/215587-philippines-china-launch-peso-yuan-trading-facility</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOUAijFvimL_GMxBEMQ7mScqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMP_mmQI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 11:21:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/business/215587-philippines-china-launch-peso-yuan-trading-facility" target="_blank"&gt;Philippines, China launch peso-yuan trading facility&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – Transacting and exchanging Chinese currency to and from the Philippine peso will soon be cheaper and easier, thanks to the establishment of the Philippine Renminbi Trading Community (PRTC) and the peso-renminbi (RMB) spot market. The Bank of China-Manila struck a deal on Tuesday, October 31, with 13 major Philippine banks to create the peso-yuan trading facility, which will facilitate the direct foreign exchange trading of the two currencies. The arrangement enables a direct conversion between the peso and yuan, instead of converting them to dollars first, making trans...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Gov't to rework 2019 budget with likely ₱41-B foregone fuel excise tax revenue - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/business/2018/10/16/2019-budget-fuel-excise-tax.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOs3cAUjGCE4JbXglinYBmQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMOPjmAI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 01:34:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/business/2018/10/16/2019-budget-fuel-excise-tax.html" target="_blank"&gt;Gov't to rework 2019 budget with likely ₱41-B foregone fuel excise tax revenue&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, October 16) — The government will rework the proposed 2019 budget in the wake of possible foregone revenue arising from the suspension of additional excise tax on fuel next year. Economic managers announced this Tuesday after a meeting to revise targets for the year due to headwinds facing the economy. A task force will review and recommend realignments in the 2019 budget. The team will be composed of members of the Department of Budget and Management, the Department of Finance, the National Economic and Development Authority, and the Bangko Sentral ng Pilipin...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>After Dominguez-Piñol 'showdown,' Duterte OKs 'open' rice importation - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/213866-dominguez-pinol-showdown-duterte-approves-open-rice-importation</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH0EtcwQBzqWp3w_i6ZZ6FgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2018 05:14:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/213866-dominguez-pinol-showdown-duterte-approves-open-rice-importation" target="_blank"&gt;After Dominguez-Piñol 'showdown,' Duterte OKs 'open' rice importation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – President Rodrigo Duterte decided to greenlight the lifting of restrictions on rice importation following a "fierce" discussion between at least two secretaries during the Cabinet meeting on Monday, October 8. Duterte "approved unimpeded importation of rice as a measure to reduce inflation," said Presidential Spokesman Harry Roque on Tuesday during a Palace press briefing. "He wants to flood the market with rice so even if prices of crude oil should go up still further, people would still have access to rice," he added. Opening up rice importation means "anyone who can...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>India’s B loan facility available for PH - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1767121</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEELtEb-s3GK_q87-btT06QYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMMuPnAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 14:57:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1767121" target="_blank"&gt;India’s B loan facility available for PH&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A US$1-billion loan facility being offered by India to economies within the Association of Southeast Asian Nations (Asean) is available to the Philippines to help fund its “Build, Build, Build” program and digital connectivity projects. In a recent meeting with Finance Secretary Carlos Dominguez III, Indian Ambassador to the Philippines Jaideep Mazumdar said his country “will be happy to offer” to the Philippines a credit line to this $1-billion loan facility. At the same time, Mazumdar said Indian companies remain bullish on the Philippines’ growth prospects and would want to expand their ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>World Bank lowers Philippine economic outlook, forecasts 6.5% GDP growth - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/business/2018/10/04/world-bank-philippines-economic-update-gdp.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMeTOVqxDtDDtei7VOUerZsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMOPjmAI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2018 09:21:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/business/2018/10/04/world-bank-philippines-economic-update-gdp.html" target="_blank"&gt;World Bank lowers Philippine economic outlook, forecasts 6.5% GDP growth&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, October 4) — The World Bank lowered its projection on Philippine economic growth on the back of weak electronic exports and lower agriculture output, rounding up similar forecasts by other international groups. In its Philippines Economic Update (PEU), the global lender said that it expects the economy to grow by 6.5 percent in 2018. This is lower than its previous forecast of 6.8 percent gross domestic product (GDP) for the year. It noted as growth risks the rising trade tension between the U.S. and China, and rising U.S. interest rates. On the domestic side,...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>PH officials to brief UK investors - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1766000</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOfD6K_QkzPmYPa-1B3kLBEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJeunQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 15:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1766000" target="_blank"&gt;PH officials to brief UK investors&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A DUTERTE Cabinet delegation led by Finance Secretary Carlos Dominguez III is on a three-day mission to London this week to brief British investors on business opportunities in the country’s infrastructure, energy and tourism sectors and explore ways to expand economic cooperation between the Philippines and the United Kingdom. Aside from the Philippine Economic Briefing (PEB) that will showcase investment prospects in the country, the top-level delegation will also take part in a business roundtable in London organized by the Philippine Trade and Investment Center (PTIC) to discuss with le...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Jollibee opens first store in London - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1766228</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEORK1Ah42FrO7lgk7uhiI-wqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKmgnQM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 07:44:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1766228" target="_blank"&gt;Jollibee opens first store in London&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;FILIPINO-owned fast food giant Jollibee Foods Corporation will open its first store in London, England on October 20. Jollibee gave a sneak peek of the store, which is located at Earl's Court, to key Philippine officials who are in London to conduct the Philippine Economic Briefing 2018. Happy to give an exclusive sneak peek of my new home here in Earl’s Court, London for our esteemed Philippine cabinet officials. Looking forward to share the JOY as we open our doors on October 20. #JollibeeLondon #1stJollibeeInUK pic.twitter.com/7CAWhc1tGB — Jollibee (@Jollibee) September 26, 2018 Among th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Dominguez: Goals on inclusive growth ‘on course’ - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1765362/Cebu/Business/Dominguez-Goals-on-inclusive-growth-on-course</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEItd6b2SK-A2Fx55tQbRKmoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJeunQM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 12:45:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1765362/Cebu/Business/Dominguez-Goals-on-inclusive-growth-on-course" target="_blank"&gt;Dominguez: Goals on inclusive growth ‘on course’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;FINANCE Secretary Carlos Dominguez III assured economists and members of the regional financial community that the Philippines remains “on course” towards the government’s medium-term goals of reducing poverty and achieving inclusive growth, driven by stronger investor confidence arising from the rollout of “Build, Build, Build” infrastructure projects and the initial gains from the Comprehensive Tax Reform Program (CTRP). Notwithstanding the elevated inflation and food supply issues in the first semester, Dominguez said the government’s accelerated pace of policy and infrastructure reforms...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Cabinet members to brief financial community - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1764843</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEWbnFVFX0SwMEVOqvKaJt8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJeunQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 14:20:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1764843" target="_blank"&gt;Cabinet members to brief financial community&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE Duterte administration’s economic and “Build, Build, Build” teams led by Finance Secretary Carlos Dominguez III are set to update economists and members of the regional financial community on the Philippines’ economic performance, developments in the fiscal sector and the status of the infrastructure program. The Philippine Economic Briefing (PEB), to be held today at the Bangko Sentral ng Pilipinas (BSP) Complex, will also include updates on New Clark City, which is being developed by the government as the country’s next big metropolis and agro-industrial hub. Dominguez will deliver th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Duterte may issue EO to address inflation - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/211782-duterte-may-issue-executive-order-address-inflation</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE0mQM9jwaTYVC4jpS8SYC8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 01:49:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/211782-duterte-may-issue-executive-order-address-inflation" target="_blank"&gt;Duterte may issue EO to address inflation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – President Rodrigo Duterte agreed to issue an executive order (EO) intended to address soaring inflation, Socioeconomic Planning Secretary Ernesto Pernia told Rappler. The possibility of issuing an EO was discussed during Duterte's private meeting with the economic managers right before the 29th Cabinet meeting on Tuesday, September 11. The EO will help implement the measures proposed by the Cabinet's economic cluster to help lower prices of essential food items like rice, poultry, and sugar. (READ: EXPLAINER: How inflation affects you) "We proposed 9 measures to contai...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Ledesma: Golden era of PH-China ties - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1763797</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBZPqkqvtrlCq9PyTUHb3ZcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKeunQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 12:27:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1763797" target="_blank"&gt;Ledesma: Golden era of PH-China ties&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BURIED and stonewalled in the din that emanates from the never ending clash of ideas on Federalism, senseless razzmatazz over Trillanes and whining over and blaming TRAIN law for the rise of prices of commodities is the successful foray of Finance Sec. Sonny Dominguez in China. At least 10 flagship infrastructure projects are cleared for funding following a series of meetings of the Philippines economic delegation led by Dominguez last week. The formal ceremonies of the approval of multi-billion dollar loans and grants will highlight the visit of China President Xi Jinping this November. "T...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Officials to decide on Bulacan airport project by December - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/09/10/bulacan-international-airport-dotr-grace-poe-sonny-dominguez.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHTpwZMfPRqFDqU1vQhFgOsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMJbthQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 12:22:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/09/10/bulacan-international-airport-dotr-grace-poe-sonny-dominguez.html" target="_blank"&gt;Officials to decide on Bulacan airport project by December&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, September 10) — It may take some time before the proposed Bulacan international airport is built. Officials said no construction will happen this year although they've committed to make a decision by December. Public Services Committee Chair Senator Grace Poe, in a Senate hearing on Monday, asked airport authorities for details on the Bulacan International Airport project. It can accommodate some 100 million passengers a year, and expected to ease congestion problems at the Ninoy Aquino International Airport, which has a capacity of about 65 million passengers...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>PH submits list of 12 big-ticket projects for feasibility studies - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1762544</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEABd6uyhqdESiYBNhYw47bUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMMuPnAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2018 17:16:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1762544" target="_blank"&gt;PH submits list of 12 big-ticket projects for feasibility studies&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE Philippines has submitted to the new aid agency of the People’s Republic of China an indicative list of 12 big-ticket infrastructure projects that will undergo feasibility studies with possible Chinese grant financing, said Finance Secretary Carlos Dominguez III. Two of these are bridges connecting Cebu with its neighboring provinces. In a meeting between a Cabinet-level delegation from Manila and China International Development Cooperation Agency (CIDCA) chairman Wang Xiaotao, an agreement was also reached in which Beijing will provide a $13.4-million grant to fund the feasibility stud...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>AIIB exploring local currency financing for PH projects - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1761918</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFGoWDNi6ouS4lFHoQ-_7soqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJeunQM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2018 14:09:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1761918" target="_blank"&gt;AIIB exploring local currency financing for PH projects&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;FINANCE Secretary Carlos Dominguez III has welcomed a proposal by the Asian Infrastructure Investment Bank (AIIB) to explore the possibility of local currency financing and a variable spread facility in providing loans to help fund the “Build, Build, Build” program of the Duterte administration. According to Dominguez, the AIIB is also eyeing possible co-financing arrangements with other multilateral institutions in implementing big-ticket infrastructure projects under the “Build, Build, Build” initiative. In a meeting at the AIIB Headquarters in Beijing last week, top officials of the bank...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>PH, China to accelerate infra projects - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1760032</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJxNyFeKklYbuUxVerlqpJUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMMuPnAM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 26 Aug 2018 13:11:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1760032" target="_blank"&gt;PH, China to accelerate infra projects&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA and Beijing have affirmed their commitment to speed up the preparation and processes needed to ensure the timely implementation of the Duterte administration’s flagship infrastructure projects with financial support from China. In a meeting here with the People’s Republic of China’s State Councilor and Foreign Affairs Minister Wang Yi Wednesday night (Aug. 22), Finance Secretary Carlos Dominguez said the preparation for the projects to be implemented by the Philippines in cooperation with China “have already been moving quite fast ahead,” particularly the South Long Haul Manila-Bicol...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Remittances to help gov’t boost spending - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1758903</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDwq3BXZDz_kjo-NL8H_rTMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJeunQM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 19 Aug 2018 15:12:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1758903" target="_blank"&gt;Remittances to help gov’t boost spending&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;FINANCE Secretary Carlos Dominguez III has said that record remittances from 54 government-owned and -controlled corporations (GOCCs) will go a long way in helping the Duterte administration hold down deficits and sustain its aggressive spending on infrastructure and human capital development. Dominguez said recently at Malacañang Palace that the “remarkable financial achievement” of these GOCCs, which remitted a combined P32 billion over the January-July period alone, will help offset the subsidies that the government needs to shell out to other GOCCs performing crucial social missions suc...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Proposed reforms in Congress to ‘rev up property market’ - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1759468</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFu2fJ68T9dLdogZuOS9XYAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJeunQM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2018 14:47:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1759468" target="_blank"&gt;Proposed reforms in Congress to ‘rev up property market’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;FINANCE Secretary Carlos Dominguez III said pending legislative proposals to reform the country’s outdated real property valuation system will bring in more investments, further invigorate the property market, and generate additional revenues for local government units (LGUs). Dominguez said they fully support Senate Bill No. 44 filed by Sen. Panfilo Lacson and its counterparts, House Bill No. 2207 introduced by Speaker Gloria Macapagal-Arroyo and H.B. No. 68 by Rep. Joey Salceda (Albay, second district), given that the fundamental valuation reforms being pushed by the government in the rea...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>PH’s strong economy, not incentives, led to rise in FDIs - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1759634</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKrIAsxRrpT6vD1A7iQUqN0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJeunQM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2018 13:47:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1759634" target="_blank"&gt;PH’s strong economy, not incentives, led to rise in FDIs&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE increase in foreign direct investments (FDIs) entering the country in the last 17 months best illustrates that investors are now flocking to the Philippines because of its exciting growth prospects rather than the fiscal incentives it continues to offer to businesses, said Finance Secretary Carlos Dominguez III. Dominguez said Bangko Sentral ng Pilipinas (BSP) data show that FDIs rose to $10 billion in 2017, or double the amount recorded in 2015, and surged further in the first half of 2018 although “approved investments”—or those coursed through investment promotion agencies (IPAs) tha...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>PH, Chinese officials set meeting in Beijing this week - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1759287</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC1W8MeE8H6ld8Xo4HFknCUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJeunQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2018 14:56:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1759287" target="_blank"&gt;PH, Chinese officials set meeting in Beijing this week&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PHILIPPINE and Chinese officials are set to meet in Beijing this week to continue discussions on ways to address issues in the preparation and implementation of the Duterte administration’s “Build, Build, Build” infrastructure projects that China has committed to support through official development assistance (ODA) loans and grants. The Department of Finance (DOF) said that the meetings, set on Aug. 22 to 24, will include updates on the progress of the “first basket” of projects for Chinese loan financing, such as the Chico River Pump Irrigation Project, New Centennial Water Source-Kaliwa ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Ledesma: Attack on Cusi reveals more - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1757725</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPB9vND-iS8ko9cBAQrbsDAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKeunQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2018 03:05:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1757725" target="_blank"&gt;Ledesma: Attack on Cusi reveals more&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THERE’S another variety of wrecking crew that hounds the Duterte government. They’re the more virulent type that had been unleashed by interest groups or individuals who felt there are officials in the government today that cannot be persuaded to follow their bidding. The most recent targets of this sinister black propaganda are Energy Secretary Al Cusi and National Transmission Corporation president Melvin Matibag. Cusi is being accused of bilking P100-billion for power plant projects which were contracted by the Ramos government way back in 1993! The libelous item was so timed when Secret...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Ledesma: Conflict on contentious issues - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1758302</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE6e0TcSMgL-gknEmEH3yvkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKeunQM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 00:47:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1758302" target="_blank"&gt;Ledesma: Conflict on contentious issues&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;I CANNOT understand why there is so much brouhaha over the statements of Cabinet members on some contentious issues in the draft constitution. While there are quarters who said that Cabinet members should have taken their stand on the draft constitution in an executive session with the President, airing their views in public would convey a message that the public should freely participate in the debate. That is what Pres. Rodrigo Duterte precisely wants. Sec. Sonny Dominguez succinctly said his piece. It is better discussed now, he suggested, than leave the discordant issues that may led to...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Palace rejects call to fire economic managers - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1757310</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFtCqJfKZZ-5Ave6SDxHOKwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKmgnQM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2018 06:46:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1757310" target="_blank"&gt;Palace rejects call to fire economic managers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MALACAÑANG on Friday, August 10, rejected a call to fire Finance Secretary Carlos Dominguez III and Socioeconomic Planning Secretary Ernesto Pernia for raising concerns about the proposal to shift to federalism. Presidential Spokesperson Harry Roque Jr., in a statement, defended the two Cabinet officials, saying their misgivings about the proposed federal form of government are merely "part of the continuing discourse." He gave assurance that President Rodrigo Duterte, as an advocate of federalism for a long time, would make sure that his Cabinet would support his plan to establish a federa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Business groups support economic managers over federalism risks - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/business/209433-business-groups-statement-federalism-risks</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFp4daYyuSuTv3T8MACkKiYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMP_mmQI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2018 04:21:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/business/209433-business-groups-statement-federalism-risks" target="_blank"&gt;Business groups support economic managers over federalism risks&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – Seven business groups urged lawmakers to carefully weigh the costs and risks associated with the proposed shift to a federal system of government. The Cebu Business Club (CBC), Employers Confederation of the Philippines (ECOP), Financial Executives Institute of the Philippines (FINEX), Makati Business Club (MBC), Management Association of the Philippines (MAP), Philippine Chamber of Commerce and Industry (PCCI), and Philippine Exporters Confederation (Philexport) came out with a joint statement to express their concerns over how the government would implement and fund ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>DOF: PH fiscal position is strong - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1757078</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFSP3s8S8PvmujnvXDVCXnUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJeunQM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 15:23:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1757078" target="_blank"&gt;DOF: PH fiscal position is strong&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;FINANCE Secretary Carlos Dominguez III has assured senators that the Philippines’ fiscal position remains strong, with revenues expected to be above target, the debt burden continuing its downtrend and the government’s spending program sustainable over the medium term. In a briefing by members of the Development Budget Coordination Committee (DBCC) before the Senate committee on finance, Dominguez said the Duterte administration expects tax revenues to grow by 12.7 percent in 2019 on the back of the projected collection growths by the Bureaus of Internal Revenue (BIR) and of Customs (BOC) o...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Editorial: Push for federalism still on - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1757294/Bacolod/Opinion/Editorial-Push-for-federalism-still-on</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEABLlvxVtknvNiHA4EyMi2cqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMPetnQM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2018 05:50:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1757294/Bacolod/Opinion/Editorial-Push-for-federalism-still-on" target="_blank"&gt;Editorial: Push for federalism still on&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;EVEN if the economic managers of the country have warned the possible risks should the proposed federal system of government will come into fruition, the administration of President Rodrigo Duterte will still continue to push for a change in the charter. Presidential Spokesperson Harry Jr. said the Cabinet members were all supportive of federalism. "There's 100 percent agreement that we are pushing for federalism. Federalism remains a priority of the President and we need to address obviously even the financial aspects of the constitutional change towards federalism," he added. Socioeconomi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Officials discuss free trade agreement - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1752188?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEACBk5Arbqm-tNW5tdTnligqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJeunQM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2018 01:58:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1752188?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;Officials discuss free trade agreement&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SENIOR Philippine and United States officials have discussed ways to deepen bilateral economic cooperation between their two countries, including the possibility of pursuing a free trade agreement (FTA) between these longstanding allies. Discussions led by Finance Secretary Carlos Dominguez III with Jeffrey Gerrish, the US Deputy Trade Representative for Asia, Europe, the Middle East, and Industrial Competitiveness, centered on America’s interest in initiating “informal preparatory meetings” with the Philippines on the “scope, timing and process” leading to an FTA between Manila and Washing...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>RDC 7-endorsed port project gets funding - SunStar Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1748848?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENjEZ9DWHVD9z2zYuP05aHkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMMuPnAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2018 15:47:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1748848?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;RDC 7-endorsed port project gets funding&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE National Economic and Development Authority (NEDA) 7 welcomes the $172-million funding extended by the Export-Import Bank of Korea for the implementation of the New Cebu International Container Port (NCICP) in Consolacion town. “We are pleased with the development, as this would address the congestion issue at the existing port. Once completed, this new facility would support and sustain the level of development in Central Visayas, increase its access to economic opportunities, and reduce traffic congestion in Metro Cebu,” said NEDA 7 Director Efren Carreon. Finance Secretary Carlos Dom...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Dominguez: DOF keen on ‘setting parameters right’ - SunStar Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1747615?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECvYcJmGpSoxRYl1UorgVkkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJeunQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 15:57:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1747615?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;Dominguez: DOF keen on ‘setting parameters right’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;FINANCE Secretary Carlos Dominguez III has said it is the priority of his department to have a selection process that will ensure that the third telecommunications player to be chosen can effectively compete in the telco market. Dominguez said he “find(s) the proposed process fails to set up parameters that will ensure that the third telco has the capability, both financial and technical, to compete in the long term.” The proposed process used “committed level of service” as the main criteria in the selection of the third player. He added, “I’ve expressed my concerns on the proposed process...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>DOF ‘to seriously review’ revenue regulations - SunStar Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1747767?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDD7IJ_gX0Dz_hd9TGuy97gqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJeunQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 15:31:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1747767?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;DOF ‘to seriously review’ revenue regulations&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE Department of Finance (DOF) will review current revenue regulations on the common carriers tax imposed on international air and sea cargo vessels doing business in the Philippines to ensure a level playing field and improve the country’s competitiveness in the global shipping and air cargo sectors. During a recent meeting with Danish officials, Finance Secretary Carlos Dominguez III said the DOF is studying the legislation governing this type of taxation and how it is being currently implemented. “We are seriously reviewing this and again the goal is to make it fair to everyone and to m...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Social mitigation measures in place vs inflation - DOF - SunStar Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1746853?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ6hW676sRCBRBOz_qsqgpwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMMuPnAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 16:58:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1746853?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;Social mitigation measures in place vs inflation - DOF&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE country’s economic managers assured the public on Tuesday that the government is fast-tracking the release of the unconditional cash transfers (UCTs) for the country’s poorest households, along with other social mitigation measures to stay ahead of the temporary elevated inflation rate. In Seoul, Finance Secretary Carlos Dominguez III said that he and the rest of the economic team agree that the best way to address inflation is for Congress to swiftly approve the Rice Tariffication Act, as this would bring down prices of rice by around P7 per kilo and reduce inflation to below four perc...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>DOF: Ex chief backs corporate tax reform - Sun.Star Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1741298?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBc255NYanHWyvQrt1YNzQ4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJeunQM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2018 13:55:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1741298?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;DOF: Ex chief backs corporate tax reform&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Sun.Star Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;FORMER finance secretary Cesar Purisima underscored the need for long-overdue reforms in the corporate tax system to bolster the country’s competitiveness. He expressed full support for the proposal to modernize incentives for businesses and reduce the corporate income tax (CIT) rate to improve the collection efficiency of revenue agencies, the Department of Finance said in a statement.Purisima also congratulated his successor, Finance Secretary Carlos Dominguez III, for the enactment into law of the Tax Reform for Acceleration and Inclusion (TRAIN) Law, the first package of the Duterte adm...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">Sun.Star Philippines</source></item><item><title>Seares: Would BRT kill or feed traffic monster? - Sun.Star Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1591499?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN4JHRRF5mgEMIwhqnwA22YqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJiunQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 02:34:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1591499?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;Seares: Would BRT kill or feed traffic monster?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Sun.Star Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;TRANSPORTATION Secretary Arthur Tugade and President’s Adviser for the Visayas Michael Dino in an April 11 letter to Finance Secretary Carlos Dominguez recommended that the Bus Rapid Transit (BRT) p&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">Sun.Star Philippines</source></item><item><title>DOF receives P11.33B from DOTr agencies - Sun.Star Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/cebu/business/2018/04/16/dof-receives-p1133b-dotr-agencies-598803</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKx2qVhBKHV6325sy_teGawqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJeunQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 14:18:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/cebu/business/2018/04/16/dof-receives-p1133b-dotr-agencies-598803" target="_blank"&gt;DOF receives P11.33B from DOTr agencies&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Sun.Star Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;FINANCE Secretary Carlos Dominguez III received three checks with a total amount of P11.33 billion representing the dividends remitted to the national government for 2017 by three government-owned and controlled corporations (GOCCs) under the supervision of the Department of Transportation (DOTr). The Manila International Airport Authority (MIAA) formally turned over P2.01 billion, the Civil Aviation Authority of the Philippines (CAAP), P6.22 billion, and the Philippine Ports Authority, P3.1 billion in checks on the sidelines of last Friday’s regional press launch of the Philippines’ hostin...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">Sun.Star Philippines</source></item></channel></rss>