<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Sin tax - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIggKIhxDQkFTRHdvSkwyMHZNRE0zYzNCa0VnSmxiaWdBUAE?hl=en-PH&amp;gl=PH&amp;ceid=PH:en</link><language>en-PH</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 12:38:48 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Finance dept prods lawmakers on higher tobacco 'sin tax' - ABS-CBN News</title><link>https://news.abs-cbn.com/business/12/04/18/finance-dept-prods-lawmakers-on-higher-tobacco-sin-tax</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiYWh0dHBzOi8vbmV3cy5hYnMtY2JuLmNvbS9idXNpbmVzcy8xMi8wNC8xOC9maW5hbmNlLWRlcHQtcHJvZHMtbGF3bWFrZXJzLW9uLWhpZ2hlci10b2JhY2NvLXNpbi10YXjSAQA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 03:12:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://news.abs-cbn.com/business/12/04/18/finance-dept-prods-lawmakers-on-higher-tobacco-sin-tax" target="_blank"&gt;Finance dept prods lawmakers on higher tobacco 'sin tax'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABS-CBN News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA -- The Department of Finance said Tuesday it would push for the passage of a bill that will raise excise tax rates on tobacco to help curb smoking, ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://news.abs-cbn.com">ABS-CBN News</source><media:content url="https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/proxy/StlRBf_aTc4UdDCHqHuFDeHWw_1GsuAEeZdVG7QCdK2tRgy8Zm-hepBBmd86xfkd86nNVK9U3CoRnXDkqc2Fsf1u2ZTC4_eQPe7EbWsr0FLlVoKTHVbjwCAB5VT6iutkATUP5M2XA8_A4V-cc2SwF9IlSZpzGz9GqQ-F=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Pakistan: ‘Sin tax’ on the anvil for cigarettes, sugary beverages - INQUIRER.net</title><link>https://newsinfo.inquirer.net/1060620/pakistan-sin-tax-on-the-anvil-for-cigarettes-sugary-beverages</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiY2h0dHBzOi8vbmV3c2luZm8uaW5xdWlyZXIubmV0LzEwNjA2MjAvcGFraXN0YW4tc2luLXRheC1vbi10aGUtYW52aWwtZm9yLWNpZ2FyZXR0ZXMtc3VnYXJ5LWJldmVyYWdlc9IBtQFodHRwczovL25ld3NpbmZvLWlucXVpcmVyLW5ldC5jZG4uYW1wcHJvamVjdC5vcmcvdi9zL25ld3NpbmZvLmlucXVpcmVyLm5ldC8xMDYwNjIwL3Bha2lzdGFuLXNpbi10YXgtb24tdGhlLWFudmlsLWZvci1jaWdhcmV0dGVzLXN1Z2FyeS1iZXZlcmFnZXMvYW1wP2FtcF9qc192PTAuMSN3ZWJ2aWV3PTEmY2FwPXN3aXBl</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 06:30:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://newsinfo.inquirer.net/1060620/pakistan-sin-tax-on-the-anvil-for-cigarettes-sugary-beverages" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistan: ‘Sin tax’ on the anvil for cigarettes, sugary beverages&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;INQUIRER.net&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;After continued lobbying by civil society, Minister for National Health Services (NHS) Aamer Mehmood Kiani announced last Tuesday that soon a 'sin tax' will be ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://newsinfo.inquirer.net">INQUIRER.net</source></item><item><title>Holy smoke! Pakistan Twitter on fire over 'sin tax' on cigarettes - Arab News</title><link>http://www.arabnews.com/node/1416041/lifestyle</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiLmh0dHA6Ly93d3cuYXJhYm5ld3MuY29tL25vZGUvMTQxNjA0MS9saWZlc3R5bGXSAQA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 14:27:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.arabnews.com/node/1416041/lifestyle" target="_blank"&gt;Holy smoke! Pakistan Twitter on fire over 'sin tax' on cigarettes&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Arab News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ISLAMABAD: Electronic cries of rage and amusement are ringing across Pakistan's Twitter community after the government announced on Wednesday its plans ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.arabnews.com">Arab News</source><media:content url="https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/proxy/SZ_L-uKzskilQtmNvd7g9-Vg5dWv-mS1sq7vhYpvCLVcgcgr1sjEeUXiEqyirfaKYiNVIp1jTW9qAdQYMGLf9_qtxUjhTour_s5bwrtK45gWWMbrRdu_d8SjGYcy_IBv8otz_-rpEJ2lzw=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>House committee approves increase in tobacco excise taxes - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/11/27/excise-tax-tobacco-farmers.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPrfjmqcS-yVT789Ctpf10EqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMJbthQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 10:33:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/11/27/excise-tax-tobacco-farmers.html" target="_blank"&gt;House committee approves increase in tobacco excise taxes&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, November 27) — The House Ways and Means Committee approved Tuesday a measure raising excise taxes on tobacco starting next year. The bill, which remains unnumbered, is expected to be sponsored in plenary soon. Under the measure, the tax on each pack of cigarettes will go up from the current ₱32.50 to ₱37.50 in July 2019. Excise tax on cigarette packs would then be raised by ₱2.50 each year starting 2020 until 2022. After that, it will be go up by four percent annually. A nongovernmental policy group also on Tuesday said raising excise taxes on tobacco products...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>Narendra Modi embarks on a great tax gamble - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/a7fa24b6-570b-11e7-9fed-c19e2700005f</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED_YXfHz4XFKLpPn2YIx3lwqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw8tp6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2017 16:44:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/a7fa24b6-570b-11e7-9fed-c19e2700005f" target="_blank"&gt;Narendra Modi embarks on a great tax gamble&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;At a crucial moment during the 16th meeting of ministers convened to thrash out the details of India’s biggest tax overhaul since it became an independent nation, the infuriated finance minister of West Bengal began to read out names of successful Indian film directors. “Adoor Gopalakrishnan, Satyajit Ray, Mrinal Sen: all the Indian film directors who have won international awards have been from regional cinema,” Amit Mitra told his fellow finance ministers. “If we tax cinema tickets at 28 per cent [the top rate under the new tax] we are going to kill off this industry, and then there won’t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>High prices effective to deter smoking as 1.1M Pinoys quit - ABS CBN News</title><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEInkrH7s9nA54KxAFhV11CoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow8IjwCjDw4s8CMNj9mQI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2017 08:02:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABS CBN News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA- Higher cigarette prices are seen as the most effective deterrent to tobacco smoking among adults, the Global Adult Tobacco Survey showed. This as higher excise taxes introduced by the Sin Tax Reform Law of 2012, which raised prices of tobacco and alcohol products, contributed to the decline of Filipino smokers from 17 million in 2009 to 15.9 million in 2015. The 2015 survey also showed that 55.5 percent of smokers attempted to quit smoking in the previous year due to higher cigarette prices of cigarettes. Graphic health warnings have also proven an effective deterrent, with 44.6 per...&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Is Smoking About To Get Even More Expensive? - FHM Philippines</title><link>http://www.fhm.com.ph/news/senate-asks-review-of-two-tier-tobacco-tax-system-a00169-20170206</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELKiETM3REHtdGXcaSz-YuYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowvKfeCjCB1NUBMK7nmQI</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2017 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.fhm.com.ph/news/senate-asks-review-of-two-tier-tobacco-tax-system-a00169-20170206" target="_blank"&gt;Is Smoking About To Get Even More Expensive?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;FHM Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Senate has recently asked its ways and means committee to carefully review the proposed two-tier tobacco tax system before they actually start tackling the proposal in a hearing. This means that for now, there will be no movement for this proposal until the review is completed. But what exactly is this proposal and how does this affect us, particularly the smokers? House Bill No. 4144 or the two-tier tobacco tax system was approved by the Lower House in December last year and then forwarded to the Senate for their own approval. The proposed measure seeks to amend the Sin Tax Reform Law,...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.fhm.com.ph">FHM Philippines</source></item><item><title>Health advocates: Pressure needed to stop 'weak' cigarette tax bill - Rappler</title><link>http://www.rappler.com/nation/156095-health-advocates-pressure-stop-house-bill-4144</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED6-7n0O7ClYchBH0dYTB1MqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2016 06:52:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.rappler.com/nation/156095-health-advocates-pressure-stop-house-bill-4144" target="_blank"&gt;Health advocates: Pressure needed to stop 'weak' cigarette tax bill&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – On the 4th anniversary of the passage of the landmark Sin Tax Reform Law of 2012, health advocates urged the public to pressure their lawmakers to move away from the "weak" bill seeking to impose a two-tier excise tax structure on cigarettes. May-i Fabros of policy advocacy group Action for Economic Reforms (AER) lambasted House Bill (HB) 4144 which was already approved on 3rd and final reading at the House of Representatives just less than two months since it was filed in October. "It was so fast, how they did it, that you'd wonder the audacity of the House leadership...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Sin taxes on alcohol and tobacco have cost the Treasury more than £31 billion, analysis finds - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2016/11/14/sin-taxes-on-alcohol-and-tobacco-have-cost-the-treasury-more-tha/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHyKUVSjSp2ZbkS3itXjdTkqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2016 00:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2016/11/14/sin-taxes-on-alcohol-and-tobacco-have-cost-the-treasury-more-tha/" target="_blank"&gt;Sin taxes on alcohol and tobacco have cost the Treasury more than £31 billion, analysis finds&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sin taxes on alcohol and tobacco have cost the Treasury more than £31 billion, an analysis has disclosed amid calls for a reduction in the Autumn Statement. Around £31.6 billion of tax revenue has been lost because of the illicit market in spirits, beer, wine, cigarettes, rolling tobacco and diesel, according to the analysis of HMRC figures by the Taxpayers’ Alliance. The high taxes on alcohol and tobacco simply fuel a black market in the goods which means that HMRC loses money, the campaign group said. HMRC has clearly been unsuccessful at claiming these duties for some time and... it need...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>10% pollutant tax eyed for cigarette sellers - Sun.Star Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/davao/local-news/2017/07/29/10-pollutant-tax-eyed-cigarette-sellers-555697</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEPhtiNDPpBovnn9XW7fEbsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKeunQM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2017 15:45:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/davao/local-news/2017/07/29/10-pollutant-tax-eyed-cigarette-sellers-555697" target="_blank"&gt;10% pollutant tax eyed for cigarette sellers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Sun.Star Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE Davao City Anti-Smoking Task Force (ASTF) is now planning for another breakthrough in its campaign against cigarette smoking in the country by adding 10 percent pollutant tax to all cigarette sellers in the city. Vice Regulation Unit (VRU) head Voltaire Engracia, in an interview with SunStar Davao, said he has already submitted a request to the city mayor's office regarding the 10 percent pollutant tax on every 2,000 square meters of cigarette boxes of selling establishments in the city. "Cigarette producers are already paying sin tax in the national level. But in cities and provinces, ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">Sun.Star Philippines</source></item><item><title>Fighting tobacco use through local legislation - Rappler</title><link>http://www.rappler.com/move-ph/172808-fighting-tobacco-local-legislation-iloilo-smoking</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDLPbWUNTn9DNQL6-a5pxj0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMM7nmQI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2017 13:14:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.rappler.com/move-ph/172808-fighting-tobacco-local-legislation-iloilo-smoking" target="_blank"&gt;Fighting tobacco use through local legislation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ILOILO, Philippines – Upon landing at the Iloilo International Airport from a seminar-workshop in Manila, urban poor and labor leader Mario Andon heard the flight attendant announce that Iloilo is a no-smoking zone. The flight attendant cited Iloilo Resolution 2015-321, which declares that Iloilo is a smoke-free city, and added that passengers are encouraged to observe the no-smoking policy in public areas. If this announcement were made before he got sick, Andon said he would have ignored it and looked for the nearest smoking area. Things changed for him after he kicked the habit 3 years, ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Smokers 'are good for the economy' think tank finds - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/08/06/smokers-good-economy-think-tank-finds/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED1G3KU6wpkKKPwwmI27Ca8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2017 23:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/08/06/smokers-good-economy-think-tank-finds/" target="_blank"&gt;Smokers 'are good for the economy' think tank finds&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Smoking is worth almost £15 billion to the public purse because of the tax revenue and the savings from smokers' early deaths, according to a think tank's analysis. The free market Institute of Economic Affairs (IEA) calculated the cost of smoking at £4.6 billion, including treating diseases, tidying up dropped cigarette butts and putting out house fires. But tobacco duties brought in £9.5 billion a year and the Government saves £9.8 billion in pension, healthcare and other benefit payments because of the premature deaths of smokers. The think tank accused politicians of "scapegoating" smok...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>DOH chief opposes bill on 2-tier cigarette tax - Rappler</title><link>http://www.rappler.com/nation/158132-ubial-house-bill-4144-senate</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDvpOxVJZVFW0VR2iyCSJWsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 07:34:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.rappler.com/nation/158132-ubial-house-bill-4144-senate" target="_blank"&gt;DOH chief opposes bill on 2-tier cigarette tax&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – Health Secretary Paulyn Ubial made a stand against the House bill seeking to impose a two-tier excise tax structure on cigarettes. "We have a number of health champions in Senate, and we're hoping that it will not push through in the Senate," Ubial said in an interview with Rappler on Tuesday, January 10. House Bill (HB) 4144 was already approved on 3rd and final reading on December 13, 2016, and transmitted to the Senate a day after. It threatens to block the full implementation of Republic Act 10351, or the landmark Sin Tax Reform Law of 2012 passed under the Aquino ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Sin tax law amendment breezes through House panel - ABS CBN News</title><link>http://news.abs-cbn.com/business/12/06/16/sin-tax-law-amendment-breezes-through-house-panel</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDcGLHQ6o7v8qi7EuCNk0qkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow8IjwCjDw4s8CMLb_ngM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2016 09:10:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://news.abs-cbn.com/business/12/06/16/sin-tax-law-amendment-breezes-through-house-panel" target="_blank"&gt;Sin tax law amendment breezes through House panel&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABS CBN News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA - A tax measure that seeks to keep a unitary tax rate for tobacco breezed through the ways and means committee and hit the plenary of the lower House on Tuesday. House Bill 4144 seeks to amend Republic Act 10351, also known as the Sin Tax Reform Act, which introduced higher excise tax rates for alcohol and tobacco products and signaled the move towards a unitary rate system by next year, and indexed the tax rate to inflation by increasing it gradually to 4 percent annually. The bill was authored by ABS party-list Rep. Eugene Michael de Vera and sponsored on the floor by ways and mean...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://news.abs-cbn.com">ABS CBN News</source></item><item><title>India tax increase sends tobacco stocks tumbling - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/d67d0f56-6b79-11e7-bfeb-33fe0c5b7eaa</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPffSMdZQhXOX1azDODKsrkqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:27:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/d67d0f56-6b79-11e7-bfeb-33fe0c5b7eaa" target="_blank"&gt;India tax increase sends tobacco stocks tumbling&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over $7bn was wiped off the value of India’s biggest tobacco companies on Tuesday morning after the government increased taxes on cigarettes under the new goods and services tax. At a meeting on Monday night, ministers decided to raise the tax on cigarettes in a move they said would safeguard public health. The decision triggered a wave of selling on the Mumbai stock exchange on Tuesday with ITC, Asia’s second-biggest listed tobacco company by sales, losing more than 10 per cent of its value in morning trading. The finance ministry said on Monday that the new tax regime, which took effect o...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>P257B needed for first year of universal health care coverage – DOH - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/215965-doh-amount-needed-first-year-universal-health-coverage</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEsn7ea212AQPnY-CZtsdAIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 06:42:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/215965-doh-amount-needed-first-year-universal-health-coverage" target="_blank"&gt;P257B needed for first year of universal health care coverage – DOH&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – The Department of Health (DOH) will need about P257 billion the first year it implements the universal health care (UHC) once the law is passed, the health secretary said on Monday, November 5. Health Secretary Francisco Duque already estimates a funding gap of P164 billion, and points out that higher tobacco taxes is needed to fund the program. “Estimates show that in the first year of implementation, around P257 billion will be needed to introduce the reforms. Taking into account existing budget, the funding gap is estimated to be around P164 billion. Additional rev...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Online gambling, cigarettes and wine hit by 'sin' taxes increase - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2018/oct/29/online-gambling-cigarettes-wine-hit-by-sin-taxes-increase</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKDLIyXPAQ0qQ14HZDY6O_EqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDJ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 19:40:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2018/oct/29/online-gambling-cigarettes-wine-hit-by-sin-taxes-increase" target="_blank"&gt;Online gambling, cigarettes and wine hit by 'sin' taxes increase&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Vices including online gambling, smoking cigarettes and drinking wine or champagne will be hit by increased “sin” taxes, but lovers of beer and spirits escaped with an unexpected duty freeze in Philip Hammond’s budget. The shake-up means: - A bottle of wine goes up by 7p, sparkling wine by 10p. - Average pack of 20 cigarettes to rise above £10. - Online gambling hit by £1bn taxes over five years. The government’s decision earlier this year to cut the maximum stake on fixed-odds betting terminals (FOBTs) from £100 to £2 triggered an overhaul of gambling tax, due to take effect in October. Lo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Health department backs 25% tax increase for alcoholic drinks - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/10/02/doh-backs-sin-tax-increase-alcohol.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGrLKAiygVFq_43ssrbEVNAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMJbthQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 10:25:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/10/02/doh-backs-sin-tax-increase-alcohol.html" target="_blank"&gt;Health department backs 25% tax increase for alcoholic drinks&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, October 2) —Health advocates want to raise excise taxes on alcoholic beverages to 25 percent— to discourage Filipinos from drinking. Lawmakers, through pending House Bills 8286 and 4839, plan to implement a 25 percent ad valorem tax on alcohol products. Once approved, this will be a 5-percent increase from the currently implemented 20 percent. A P30 peso tax, which will be based on the amount of alcohol in the beverage, will also be imposed. Officials from the Department of Health (DOH) and medical practitioners said they will support the proposed measure. In ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>Proposed tobacco tax to benefit health care — Duque - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/08/15/tobacco-tax-benefit-health-care.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMk8r-OCUqiyd9Nn5jNkSDwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMJbthQM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2018 10:42:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/08/15/tobacco-tax-benefit-health-care.html" target="_blank"&gt;Proposed tobacco tax to benefit health care — Duque&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, August 15) — Health Secretary Francisco Duque III said the proposed tobacco excise tax increase will generate more revenue for the government's health care program and at the same time encourage Filipinos to be health conscious. Duque made the statement in a media briefing Wednesday, in relation to the passage of the Universal Health Care (UHC) Bill, a measure certified as urgent by President Rodrigo Duterte. The proposed tax increase will help fund the proposed Universal Health Care system, once it is signed into law. "To make the UHC (Universal Health Care)...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>Cigarette prices to increase more with passage of universal health care bill - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/209627-higher-prices-tobacco-products-universal-health-care-passage</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN9kjsC50HAx4tZ8lP8pdlEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2018 08:10:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/209627-higher-prices-tobacco-products-universal-health-care-passage" target="_blank"&gt;Cigarette prices to increase more with passage of universal health care bill&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – Expect prices of cigarettes to increase more as higher tariffs will be imposed on tobacco products to fund the Universal Health Care (UHC) bill which aims to provide all Filipinos with access to adequate health services. Speaking at press briefing in Malacañang Palace, Department of Health Secretary Francisco Duque III said the price of tobacco products will most likely increase further as these new round of sin taxes will be on top of the hikes due to the first tax reform package or the TRAIN law. Duque said the increased sin taxes will be a major source of funding f...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Alaska's legal pot industry decries taxes, seeks changes - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/eb61caa05ce447d18c6b69c90821cd36</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKcBxT6lzJGzHf6RPN1r66gqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwm4pR</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 20:31:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/eb61caa05ce447d18c6b69c90821cd36" target="_blank"&gt;Alaska's legal pot industry decries taxes, seeks changes&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;JUNEAU, Alaska (AP) — In a push to get Alaska voters to legalize marijuana, supporters suggested a tax on growers of $800 a pound — though they knew it would be unworkable in the long run. The tax aimed to show that the industry was willing to pay its share, said Brandon Emmett, who was part of the successful 2014 legalization campaign. The hope was that once pot become legal, the industry, regulators and lawmakers would work together to revamp the figure, he said. "So far as I can tell, we gambled poorly because that's not happening," he said, adding, "And I think we're running headlong in...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>'Sin tax' looms on tobacco and alcohol in Nigeria as fears grow of a public health crisis - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/06/04/sin-tax-looms-tobacco-alcohol-innigeria-fears-grow-public-health/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEX3G03_7udJxzZqdwpC8rcqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 17:34:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/06/04/sin-tax-looms-tobacco-alcohol-innigeria-fears-grow-public-health/" target="_blank"&gt;'Sin tax' looms on tobacco and alcohol in Nigeria as fears grow of a public health crisis&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nigeria’s government defied private-sector opposition to impose a new “sin tax” on Monday amid fears that growing tobacco and alcohol consumption could threaten a public health crisis. Ignoring a last-minute legal challenge, the country’s finance ministry announced that a rise in excise duties had finally come into force, three months after Muhammadu Buhari, the president, was forced by public opposition to delay the hike. With Nigeria emerging from a painful recession, the new duties will help both to boost revenues and reduce the exchequer’s dependency on the oil sector. But health campai...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Tax sugar, alcohol and tobacco to help the poor, say experts - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2018/apr/04/sin-tax-sugar-alcohol-tobacco-to-help-the-poor</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEBCWkDuJ1-avHBw56tZAIwqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2018 21:00:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/2018/apr/04/sin-tax-sugar-alcohol-tobacco-to-help-the-poor" target="_blank"&gt;Tax sugar, alcohol and tobacco to help the poor, say experts&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;So called “sin taxes” on sugary drinks, alcohol and tobacco not only work, but will help rather than unduly penalise the poor, according to a major new international analysis. Just a day before the UK brings in a levy on sugary drinks, experts are urging every country in the world to use taxes to deter people from the eating, drinking and smoking habits that will damage their health. They warn of the urgent need to check the spread of cancers, diabetes, heart disease, stroke and other conditions caused or exacerbated by our lifestyles which have overtaken infectious diseases as the biggest ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>UK 'sin taxes' are working. Here's the proof - CNN</title><link>http://money.cnn.com/2018/04/05/news/economy/sin-tax-sugar-diesel-plastic-uk/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBa_iM0Cyaim8CwWIRX7eggqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrWrwU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2018 16:43:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://money.cnn.com/2018/04/05/news/economy/sin-tax-sugar-diesel-plastic-uk/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;UK 'sin taxes' are working. Here's the proof&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;First it was plastic. Then diesel cars. Soda is next. The United Kingdom is on a mission to change people's behavior by slapping new taxes on products deemed harmful to health and the environment. The government has, in quick succession, introduced new or higher taxes on plastic bags, diesel cars and sugary soft drinks in an attempt to undermine their popularity. The moves have prompted some criticism. The Institute of Economic Affairs, a free market think tank, ranked the United Kingdom as the second worst country in the European Union for "nanny state oppression," after Finland. There are...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://money.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>DOF expects February inflation to exceed projections - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/business/197472-philippines-inflation-rate-dof-projections-february-2018</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAllwRd__CHzr3jKwZQr99oqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMP_mmQI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Mar 2018 10:11:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/business/197472-philippines-inflation-rate-dof-projections-february-2018" target="_blank"&gt;DOF expects February inflation to exceed projections&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – Higher prices of sin products such as tobacco and alcohol are expected to jack up the inflation rate in February to a new 3-year high of 4.1%, said the Department of Finance (DOF). Ahead of the announcement of the official February 2018 inflation rate, the DOF on Monday, March 5, released an economic bulletin, saying that the inflation rate – or the movement of prices of basic goods and services – likely edged higher to 4.1% in February, from 3.95% last January. It would be much faster than the 3.3% inflation rate recorded in February 2017, and beyond the government's ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Inflation hits 3-year high of 4% in January - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/business/195368-philippines-inflation-january-2018-tax-reform-law</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG8q94vM6GsreIZalpDB59AqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMP_mmQI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2018 06:08:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/business/195368-philippines-inflation-january-2018-tax-reform-law" target="_blank"&gt;Inflation hits 3-year high of 4% in January&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – Inflation hit its highest level in 3 years last January as the effects of the Tax Reform for Acceleration and Inclusion (TRAIN) law kicked in. "Increases in food and non-food prices pushed the country's inflation to 4% in January 2018, hitting the upper band of the government target," the Philippine Statistics Authority (PSA) said on Tuesday, February 6. The level is higher than the 3.3% in December 2017 and the 2.7% in January 2017. In fact, it is the highest in 3 years since inflation quickened to 4.3% in October 2014. The National Economic and Development Authority ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Palace counters economic experts on tax reform's impact on prices - Sun.Star Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/manila/business/2018/02/07/palace-counters-economic-experts-tax-reforms-impact-prices-587750</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEWsqsekv4MJYZzNWlouT3gqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMMuPnAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2018 08:49:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/manila/business/2018/02/07/palace-counters-economic-experts-tax-reforms-impact-prices-587750" target="_blank"&gt;Palace counters economic experts on tax reform's impact on prices&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Sun.Star Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PRESIDENTIAL Spokesperson Harry Roque Jr. on Wednesday, February 7, said it is premature to blame the new tax reform law for the increase in consumer prices. "I think, it's too premature to come up with such conclusion. We only implemented it (tax reform law) last January and we did not immediately slap (excise) taxes (on a number of products)," Roque told Palace reporters in a phone patch interview. He was reacting to the statements of Socioeconomic Planning Secretary Ernesto Pernia and Bangko Sentral ng Pilipinas Governor Nestor Espenilla Jr. that the implementation of the Tax Reform for ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">Sun.Star Philippines</source></item><item><title>Alamon: Accelerating exclusion - Sun.Star Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/cagayan-de-oro/opinion/2018/01/05/alamon-accelerating-exclusion-582456</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIoyUYL-JE4QKWesV42zcIgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMMu4nAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2018 16:17:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/cagayan-de-oro/opinion/2018/01/05/alamon-accelerating-exclusion-582456" target="_blank"&gt;Alamon: Accelerating exclusion&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Sun.Star Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;IN THE first week of 2018, the Duterte Tax Reform Program is rampaging already through consumers’ purses and budgets. If there are still any political stragglers within the Duterte administration who still believe that he embodies progressive economic ideals, then the marauding tax reform law or TRAIN that is now being implemented should leave anyone without any doubt about the obvious neoliberal direction of his administration. The Tax Reform Law for Acceleration and Inclusion by the Duterte administration signed into law by Duterte last December 19, 2017 is a neoliberal technocrat’s wet d...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">Sun.Star Philippines</source></item><item><title>Tax Notes: RA 10963 amends the National Internal Revenue Code of 1997 - Sun.Star Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/cebu/business/2018/01/02/tax-notes-ra-10963-amends-national-internal-revenue-code-1997-582088</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH8qRHnpOqxS5HR4sHk-aIEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJeunQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2018 14:11:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/cebu/business/2018/01/02/tax-notes-ra-10963-amends-national-internal-revenue-code-1997-582088" target="_blank"&gt;Tax Notes: RA 10963 amends the National Internal Revenue Code of 1997&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Sun.Star Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;TO ease the burden of common taxpayers and to provide additional resources for funding social and economic infrastructure that will benefit the poor, President Rodrigo R. Duterte signed into law on Dec. 19 Republic Act (RA) No. 10963. Also known as the “Tax Reform for Acceleration and Inclusion (TRAIN),” the Act amends and repeals certain provisions of the previously amended RA No. 8424, otherwise known as the National Internal Revenue Code of 1997. The TRAIN Law is a consolidation of House Bill No. 5636 and Senate Bill No. 1592 that were both passed by the House of Representatives and the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">Sun.Star Philippines</source></item><item><title>Duterte vetoes five TRAIN line items - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2017/12/28/Duterte-vetoes-five-TRAIN-line-items.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM8VPOMIGIulRwDMasD4EEUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMOPjmAI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2017 20:53:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2017/12/28/Duterte-vetoes-five-TRAIN-line-items.html" target="_blank"&gt;Duterte vetoes five TRAIN line items&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, December 28) — President Rodrigo Duterte has vetoed five line items under the Tax Reform for Acceleration and Inclusion (TRAIN) Act in an effort to "ease the burden of the common taxpayers." On Tuesday, December 19, Duterte signed into law Republic Act No. 10963, or the TRAIN bill, which aims to raise funds for the multi-billion peso infrastructure program key to the government's economic agenda. It takes effect on Jan. 1, 2018. Copies of the vetoes, dated December 19, were released by the Palace Wednesday. The President said Filipinos have been "constrained...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>Health groups to lawmakers: Raise tobacco tax to fund health care program - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2017/12/21/action-for-economic-reforms-tobacco-tax.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC8VLW17u5Xus1bGHKZBSJ4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMJbthQM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2017 05:44:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2017/12/21/action-for-economic-reforms-tobacco-tax.html" target="_blank"&gt;Health groups to lawmakers: Raise tobacco tax to fund health care program&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, December 21) — Health advocates are calling on lawmakers to raise tobacco taxes to help fund universal health care. In a statement released Wednesday, health advocates said the ₱2.50 tobacco tax rate under the recently-signed tax reform law would not be enough to either deter people from smoking or provide funds to patients who would benefit from free healthcare services. RELATED: Duterte signs tax reform bill, 2018 budget into law According to the statement of Action for Economic Reforms, the tobacco tax increase in the Tax Reform for Acceleration and Inclusi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>Duterte vetoes parts of tax reform law - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/business/192032-duterte-vetoes-train-tax-reform</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKdzqKYZ6SaVgnn7fEUuGI8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMP_mmQI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2017 09:08:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/business/192032-duterte-vetoes-train-tax-reform" target="_blank"&gt;Duterte vetoes parts of tax reform law&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines—President Rodrigo Duterte has vetoed some parts of the first package of the Tax Reform for Acceleration and Inclusion (Train) law, Malacañang Palace informed Congress on Friday, December 22. The tax reform measures, which the President signed into law last Tuesday, will take effect on January 1, 2018. The line items from the bill the President vetoed deal with: 1. Reduced income tax rate of employees of Regional Headquarters (RHQB), Regional Operating Headquarters, Offshore Banking Units, and Petroleum Service Contractors and Subcontractors Specifically, the veto was on ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>1st package of tax reform bill now up for Duterte's signature - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/191298-17th-congress-ratifies-tax-reform-train-bill-philippines</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED6fHkWm1vV073BZjAa_XqEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2017 14:43:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/191298-17th-congress-ratifies-tax-reform-train-bill-philippines" target="_blank"&gt;1st package of tax reform bill now up for Duterte's signature&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – The Senate and the House of Representatives on Wednesday, December 13, ratified the bicameral conference committee report on the Tax Reform for Acceleration and Inclusion (TRAIN) bill, seeking to cut income taxes but adding levy on fuel, cars, mining, coal, and tobacco. The bill will now be sent to President Rodrigo Duterte for signing into law. Once signed, the measure is set to be implemented by January 1, 2018. In the House, no questions were asked before ratification, so the process took only one minute. ACT Teachers Representative Antonio Tinio tried to object due...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Measly increase in tobacco tax in TRAIN to increase number of smokers in PH - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2017/12/15/tobacco-tax-increase-smokers-train.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFkK2aO4bB9wG3Nz7josNhsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMJbthQM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2017 08:43:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2017/12/15/tobacco-tax-increase-smokers-train.html" target="_blank"&gt;Measly increase in tobacco tax in TRAIN to increase number of smokers in PH&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, December 15) — A regional anti-smoking alliance on Friday warned of a possible spike in the number of smokers in the country after Congress failed to pass a higher tobacco tax as part of a key tax reform bill. Congress approved on Wednesday Package 1 of the Tax Reform for Acceleration and Inclusion (TRAIN) which lowers income taxes, while raising excise taxes on a number of items. However, despite lobbying from health advocates and lawmakers, the TRAIN bill merely incorporated a meager P2.50 ($ 0.05) excise tax on tobacco. This means a pack of cigarettes which...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>Meat tax ‘inevitable’ to beat climate and health crises, says report - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2017/dec/11/meat-tax-inevitable-to-beat-climate-and-health-crises-says-report</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB4RunKkJ9ty7oozeR6foWIqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2017 06:30:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2017/dec/11/meat-tax-inevitable-to-beat-climate-and-health-crises-says-report" target="_blank"&gt;Meat tax ‘inevitable’ to beat climate and health crises, says report&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Sin taxes” on meat to reduce its huge impact on climate change and human health look inevitable, according to analysts for investors managing more than $4tn of assets. The global livestock industry causes 15% of all global greenhouse gas emissions and meat consumption is rising around the world, but dangerous climate change cannot be avoided unless this is radically curbed. Furthermore, many people already eat far too much meat, seriously damaging their health and incurring huge costs. Livestock also drive other problems, such as water pollution and antibiotic resistance. A new analysis fr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Higher take-home pay but pricier cars, fuel, tobacco by 2018 - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/191079-bicam-version-train-tax-reform-bill-2018</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFqktz_tsuxjJBoQJLPwGqoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2017 13:12:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/191079-bicam-version-train-tax-reform-bill-2018" target="_blank"&gt;Higher take-home pay but pricier cars, fuel, tobacco by 2018&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – Members of the bicameral conference committee on Monday, December 11, finalized the Tax Reform for Acceleration and Inclusion (TRAIN) bill, seeking to cut personal income tax but impose higher levies on fuel, coal, cars, mining, and tobacco, among others. It took the Senate and the House of Representatives at least 3 sessions to reconcile differences between their versions of the bill, considered to be a priority measure of President Rodrigo Duterte. The target revenue is P130 billion. Both chambers of Congress have to ratify the bicam version before it gets sent to Du...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Students urge undecided senators to back proposed tobacco tax hike - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/move-ph/189227-youth-write-senators-increase-tobacco-tax</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOtwZXUpAy96VFz8CZWG6hsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMM7nmQI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 06:11:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/move-ph/189227-youth-write-senators-increase-tobacco-tax" target="_blank"&gt;Students urge undecided senators to back proposed tobacco tax hike&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – Students from different universities and organizations gathered on Wednesday, November 22, in the University of the Philippines (UP) Diliman to launch a campaign that urges legislators to back a proposal to increase tobacco tax. (READ: EXPLAINER: Senate, House versions of the tax reform bill) They wrote letters to undecided senators, hoping to convince them to support the move to raise the levy on so-called “sin” products, especially tobacco. In October 2017, Senator Manny Pacquiao filed Senate Bill No 1599, which seeks to amend Republic Act 10351 or the Sin Tax Reform...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>DOF destroys P142-M worth of cigarettes in Davao - Sun.Star Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/davao/business/2017/11/27/dof-destroys-p142-m-worth-cigarettes-davao-576874</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPm9JQEQ5cgUZl3u285452oqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMMuPnAM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2017 18:45:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/davao/business/2017/11/27/dof-destroys-p142-m-worth-cigarettes-davao-576874" target="_blank"&gt;DOF destroys P142-M worth of cigarettes in Davao&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Sun.Star Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A TOTAL of P 142.440 million worth of Mighty Corporation cigarettes that had been seized from a warehouse in General Santos City due to excise tax liability were destroyed and burned at Holcim Philippines plant in Tibungco, Davao City yesterday, November 26. About 9,496 cases or about 4.748 million packs of Mighty Corporation cigarettes specifically of Mighty Menthol 100’s, Marvels Menthol, Marvels FK, and King Full Flavor that had a total excise tax liability of P1.394 billion, including the penalty, were seized March 6 of this year from Sunshine Cornmill Co., Distribution Inc. a warehouse...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">Sun.Star Philippines</source></item><item><title>Sin tax take reaches P17.7B in September - Sun.Star Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/network/business/2017/10/31/sin-tax-take-reaches-p177b-september-572316</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMvtAX1X5MIhJr3BE-Xg3_UqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMMuPnAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 07:16:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/network/business/2017/10/31/sin-tax-take-reaches-p177b-september-572316" target="_blank"&gt;Sin tax take reaches P17.7B in September&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Sun.Star Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA -- The Bureau of Internal Revenue (BIR) posted P17.7 billion sin tax collection in September 2017, up 12 percent from P16.67 billion a year ago. Department of Finance Undersecretary Antonette Tionko told reporters the bulk of the revenues, amounting to P11.1 billion, was contributed by tobacco products while the balance of P6.6 billion came from alcohol products. Tionko, who is also the head of the Revenue Operations Group, said collections from tobacco products rose by 14 percent year-on-year. Of the total tobacco product taxes, P4.6 billion was collected from JTI-Mighty, up 281 pec...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">Sun.Star Philippines</source></item></channel></rss>