<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Abdul Rasul Sayyaf - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIggKIhxDQkFTRHdvSkwyMHZNREpmTkc1ZkVnSmxiaWdBUAE?hl=en-PH&amp;gl=PH&amp;ceid=PH:en</link><language>en-PH</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 13:54:54 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Malaysia police detain 7 Abu Sayyaf fighters in raids - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/malaysia-police-detain-8-abu-sayyaf-fighters-raids-181116034401267.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIUS1afwq2H5UaX1qHaFQDEqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 06:27:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/malaysia-police-detain-8-abu-sayyaf-fighters-raids-181116034401267.html" target="_blank"&gt;Malaysia police detain 7 Abu Sayyaf fighters in raids&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Malaysian police say they've arrested eight suspects including a number of alleged members of Abu Sayyaf, after reports the group was planning to carry out a series of kidnappings in the waters off eastern Sabah in Malaysian Borneo. The men - one from Malaysia and seven from the Philippines - were picked up in a series of raids over the past two weeks in Malaysia's administrative capital Putrajaya, as well as the Borneo state of Sabah, Chief of Police Mohamad Fuzi Harun said in a statement on Friday. Among those detained was a 30-year-old Filipino who is suspected of being a commander in Ab...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>5 soldiers killed in Sulu while rescuing hostages from Abu Sayyaf - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/216906-5-soldiers-killed-jolo-abu-sayyaf-november-2018</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEANVeG_GHkU1kxzw7nyOxm4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 07:20:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/216906-5-soldiers-killed-jolo-abu-sayyaf-november-2018" target="_blank"&gt;5 soldiers killed in Sulu while rescuing hostages from Abu Sayyaf&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – The Armed Forces of the Philippines (AFP) said on Saturday, November 17, that 5 soldiers were killed and 23 others were injured while troops were trying to rescue hostages from terrorist group Abu Sayyaf. The soldiers were searching for hostages taken by the Abu Sayyaf group when the gunmen attacked them on the island of Jolo, Sulu, on Friday, November 16, regional military spokesman Lieutenant Colonel Gerry Besana told reporters. "The effort is part of our mission to rescue the remaining hostages," Besana said. The Abu Sayyaf is a loose alliance of several hundred arm...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>5 soldiers killed, 23 injured in Patikul ambush - ABS CBN News</title><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBShTWngWccrTX0__miK5TMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow8IjwCjDw4s8CMNj9mQI</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 07:17:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABS CBN News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Militants have killed five Filipino soldiers and wounded 23 others in a major ambush by members of a notorious Islamist kidnap-for-ransom group, the Philippine military said Saturday. The soldiers were searching for hostages taken by the Abu Sayyaf group when the gunmen attacked them in Barangay Liang, Pakitul, Sulu on Friday, regional military spokesman Lieutenant Colonel Gerry Besana told reporters. "The effort is part of our mission to rescue the remaining hostages," Besana said. The Abu Sayyaf is a loose alliance of several hundred armed militants formed in the 1990s with seed money fro...&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>5 soldiers killed in clash vs. Abu Sayyaf - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/regional/2018/11/17/soldiers-killed-abu-sayyaf-sulu-clash.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIyB2Q0OyzDjRN-O70D2x3AqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMPHhmQI</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 06:26:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/regional/2018/11/17/soldiers-killed-abu-sayyaf-sulu-clash.html" target="_blank"&gt;5 soldiers killed in clash vs. Abu Sayyaf&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, November 17) — Five soldiers were killed while 23 others were wounded when they fought members of the Abu Sayyaf group in Patikul, Sulu Friday, the military said Saturday. According to the military's Western Mindanao Command, the firefight lasted for more than an hour at Barangay Liang at around 4 p.m. An initial report said the soldiers encountered around 50 Abu Sayyaf fighters under leader Almuder Yadah. The Abu Sayyaf group is one of the foreign terrorist organizations listed by the United States Department of State. Duterte in July reached out to the bandi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>Officer, 3 soldiers injured in Sulu clash - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1772705</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBSOgjj2G1mj25Ebcdw9WSYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJiunQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 10:42:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1772705" target="_blank"&gt;Officer, 3 soldiers injured in Sulu clash&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOUR soldiers, including an officer, were wounded in a clash as the government offensive continue against the Abu Sayyaf Group (ASG) in Sulu province, a top military official said Tuesday. The firefight took place at 1:40 p.m. Monday at Sitio kan Apo Aluk in Panglayahan village, Patikul, Sulu, according to Lieutenant General Arnel Dela Vega, Western Mindanao Command (Westmincom) commander. Dela Vega said the troops were conducting focused military operation when they clashed with some 50 Abu Sayyaf bandits led by one-armed and senior bandit leader Radullan Sahiron. He did not identify the i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>2 Abu Sayyaf bandits killed in Sulu clash, 2 captured - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1771671</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECR5yU3xA4vuNYgAF86oM44qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJiunQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 08:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1771671" target="_blank"&gt;2 Abu Sayyaf bandits killed in Sulu clash, 2 captured&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MARINE forces have killed two Abu Sayyaf members and captured two wounded bandits following a firefight early Tuesday, October 30, in Sulu. Lieutenant General Arnel Dela Vega, Western Mindanao Command (Westmincom) chief, said the Marines were on combat operations when they encountered around 100 Abu Sayyaf bandits at 5:08 a.m. Tuesday, October 30, in the village of Lihbug Kabaw, Panglima Estino, Sulu. The bandits were led by Radullan Sahiron and sub-leaders Idang Susukan and Almujer Yadah. Dela Vega said two Abu Sayyaf members were killed in the clash, while two others were wounded and capt...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>3 Marines, 1 Abu Sayyaf killed in Sulu clash - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/215225-marines-killed-sulu-clash-abu-sayyaf-october-26-2018</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBgR49y0y6hI2pusUz12qNcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 05:30:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/215225-marines-killed-sulu-clash-abu-sayyaf-october-26-2018" target="_blank"&gt;3 Marines, 1 Abu Sayyaf killed in Sulu clash&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ZAMBOANGA CITY, Philippines – At least 3 marines and an Abu Sayyaf member were killed in an encounter between government troops and the terrorist group in Patikul, Sulu, on Friday, October 26. Troops from the 61st, 62nd, and 64th Marine Companies clashed with Abu Sayyaf members under subleaders Alnijar Ekit and Aldi Alun in Barangay Timpook, Patikul, the military said. Three other soldiers sustained minor injuries and were brought to the KHTB Station Hospital for immediate medical attention. The military said the ongoing firefight also dealt casualties on the Abu Sayyaf side. Troops recover...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>AFP insists 7 slain in a Sulu encounter were Abu Sayyaf men - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/09/18/Abu-Sayyaf-Patikul-Sulu-AFP.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPIuZV9nFVXQkAGYrCLMuSwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMJbthQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 23:57:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/09/18/Abu-Sayyaf-Patikul-Sulu-AFP.html" target="_blank"&gt;AFP insists 7 slain in a Sulu encounter were Abu Sayyaf men&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Updated to include statements from RHRC-ARMM. Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, September 18) — The military stood by its report that seven members of the Abu Sayyaf group were killed in an encounter in Patikul, Sulu on Friday. Families of the slain men, however, condemned the killing of the seven young men in Brgy. Bakong at around 1:30 p.m on September 14. According to human rights group Suara Bangsamoro, the men were harvesting lanzones and mangosteen when they were fired upon by the Armed Forces of the Philippines (AFP). "The AFP should be held accountable for this crime. This is not the f...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>Abu Sayyaf bandits free 3 Indon hostages - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1764642/Zamboanga/Local-News/Abu-Sayyaf-bandits-free-3-Indon-hostages</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJBoi7D3h2SVaud231C-LlwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJiunQM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2018 13:08:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1764642/Zamboanga/Local-News/Abu-Sayyaf-bandits-free-3-Indon-hostages" target="_blank"&gt;Abu Sayyaf bandits free 3 Indon hostages&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE Abu Sayyaf bandits have freed the three Indonesian they kidnapped over a year ago in the waters of Tawi-Tawi, the military reported on Sunday, September 16. Released around 4 p.m., Saturday, September 15, in the village of Buanza, Indanan, Sulu, were Hamdam Bin Salim, 34; Subande Satto, 27; and, Sudarlan Samansung, 41. Lieutenant Colonel Gerry Besana, Western Mindanao Command (Westmincom) information officer, said the three Indonesians were freed due to mounting pressures by the continuous military offensive and efforts exerted by the government officials in Sulu. Besana said the free I...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Were 7 killed in Sulu encounter Abu Sayyaf or not? - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/212088-killed-in-sulu-encounter-abu-sayyaf-or-not</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBe0EBQ6KLWfN0pd1WHlgYkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2018 13:06:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/212088-killed-in-sulu-encounter-abu-sayyaf-or-not" target="_blank"&gt;Were 7 killed in Sulu encounter Abu Sayyaf or not?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – Seven alleged members of the terrorist group Abu Sayyaf were killed in an encounter on Friday, September 14, according to a report of Joint Task Force Sulu headed by Brigadier General Divino Rey Pabayo. The number of dead was based on a body count, according to a press statement from Lieutenant Colonel Gerry Besana, public affairs officer of the Western Mindanao Command. Six others were reported injured, including ASG Senior Leader Hatib Hajan Sawadjaan, who was said to be seriously hit in his stomach and lower extremities. Miliary says they're terrorists: The same rep...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Out of the Shadows, an Afghan Spy Chief Joins Presidential Politics - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/09/01/world/asia/asadullah-khalid-afghanistan-president.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOlePTuUdphcgMTQxUiXxPAqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzwwt4QY</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2018 13:06:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/09/01/world/asia/asadullah-khalid-afghanistan-president.html" target="_blank"&gt;Out of the Shadows, an Afghan Spy Chief Joins Presidential Politics&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Asadullah Khalid, who barely survived a Taliban hit, joins a growing field opposing President Ashraf Ghani. He counts Americans and warlords as benefactors.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>1 Abu Sayyaf member dead, 20 soldiers wounded in Sulu clash - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/regional/2018/08/23/Abu-Sayyaf-Sulu-clash.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBMiwQxIZ7k6316oipn1K7wqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMPHhmQI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2018 10:49:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/regional/2018/08/23/Abu-Sayyaf-Sulu-clash.html" target="_blank"&gt;1 Abu Sayyaf member dead, 20 soldiers wounded in Sulu clash&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, August 23) — An Abu Sayyaf member was killed while 20 soldiers were wounded in a clash in Sulu on Thursday, the military said. Government troops fought at least 40 bandits in Barangay Langhub in Patikul town at around 9:30 a.m., the Western Mindanao Command said. It said a certain Alpata Abdurasa was killed in the 45-minute firefight, while a number of Abu Sayyaf fighters were hurt. On the government side, 18 had shrapnel injuries while two had gunshot wounds, the military said. They were rushed to the Camp Teodulfo Bautista Station Hospital for treatment. The...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>Suspected Abu Sayyaf arrested in Carcar, Cebu - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kbEOiRymHRE</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIinpuDSx3dAUYQO6bX_-h4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMIuVnAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 18:53:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kbEOiRymHRE" target="_blank"&gt;Suspected Abu Sayyaf arrested in Carcar, Cebu&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Suspected Abu Sayyaf arrested in Carcar, Cebu&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.youtube.com">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Abu Sayyaf leader slain, 5 others surrender in Sulu – military - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/regional/2018/08/15/Abu-Sayyaf-leader-killed-5-surrender-Sulu.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENi4pqJTo_fBIubs9DKrsdwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMPHhmQI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2018 07:59:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/regional/2018/08/15/Abu-Sayyaf-leader-killed-5-surrender-Sulu.html" target="_blank"&gt;Abu Sayyaf leader slain, 5 others surrender in Sulu – military&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, August 15) — An Abu Sayyaf subgroup leader was killed while five others surrendered to the military in two separate incidents in Sulu on Wednesday. Reports from the Western Mindanao Command (Wesmincom) said Absulajim Abdulgani, also known as Suraka Ingog, was killed in a joint police and military operation in Patikul town's Kalimayahan Village. Recovered from the body of Abdulgani — an alleged Abu Sayyaf subgroup leader and bomb expert — were a .45-caliber pistol with magazine, ammunition, and ₱2,421 in cash. In a separate incident, another listed Abu Sayyaf s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>Abu Sayyaf behind Basilan van blast - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/208536-abu-sayyaf-behind-basilan-blast-july-31-2018</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM_ua8b9ElgUEohKcIrf6SkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 04:57:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/208536-abu-sayyaf-behind-basilan-blast-july-31-2018" target="_blank"&gt;Abu Sayyaf behind Basilan van blast&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – The Abu Sayyaf group was behind the deadly van explosion in Lamitan City, Basilan, the Armed Forces of the Philippines (AFP) said on Tuesday, July 31. In a Camp Aguinaldo press briefing, AFP Spokesperson Edgard Arevalo said Abu Sayyaf Basilan commander Furuji Indama had a hand in the blast. Indama, Arevalo said, is a "hardline member" of the Abu Sayyaf, refusing to surrender despite intensified community relations efforts of the AFP. In a phone interview with Rappler, Western Mindanao Command chief Lieutenant General Arnel dela Vega said Indama's group may be "trying t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Philippine Bombing Kills 10, Showing Insurgents Remain a Problem - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/07/30/world/asia/philippines-bombing-abu-sayyaf.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFZp-MPj-3B33k6l1G7QupoqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzwwt4QY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 03:56:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/07/30/world/asia/philippines-bombing-abu-sayyaf.html" target="_blank"&gt;Philippine Bombing Kills 10, Showing Insurgents Remain a Problem&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Officials say the blast was carried out by Abu Sayyaf, a militant group that besieged the southern city of Marawi for five months.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>Duterte to Abu Sayyaf: 'Let's talk' - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/208358-duterte-abu-sayyaf-lets-talk</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB2EeFbIk2ZW47uAUzpHUa8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2018 01:24:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/208358-duterte-abu-sayyaf-lets-talk" target="_blank"&gt;Duterte to Abu Sayyaf: 'Let's talk'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – President Rodrigo Duterte said on Friday, July 27, that he wants to dialogue with terrorist group Abu Sayyaf to bring an end to bloodshed in Mindanao. "Mag-usap na lang. Iyong Abu Sayyaf, mag-usap na lang tayo. Ano bang gawain natin? Magpatayan tayong lahat (Let's talk. The Abu Sayyaf, let's just talk. What do we do? Just kill each other)?" Duterte said in a speech in Jolo, Sulu, where the Abu Sayyaf operates from. It was not the first time for the President to express his openness to a dialogue with the Abu Sayyaf. Days before he formally assumed the presidency in 201...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>3 Abu Sayyaf members killed in Sulu clash - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1752445/Manila/Local-News/3-Abu-Sayyaf-members-killed-in-Sulu-clash</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP6j-i1pEK7uHRKnB8LU_OcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKmgnQM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2018 07:22:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1752445/Manila/Local-News/3-Abu-Sayyaf-members-killed-in-Sulu-clash" target="_blank"&gt;3 Abu Sayyaf members killed in Sulu clash&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(UPDATED) - Three suspected members of the Abu Sayyaf Group (ASG) and a soldier were killed in separate clashes between the terrorist group and government troops in Sulu, the military said Thursday, July 12. Brigadier General Divino Rey Pabayo, Joint Task Force Sulu commander, said the three ASG members were killed in a clash at around 4:30 a.m. Thursday in Kuppong village, Indanan town. The soldier was killed in a clash that took place at 1:55 p.m. Wednesday in Sitio Kan Apo Aluk in Panglayahan village, Patikul town. Ten other soldiers were wounded. Pabayo said the clash in Indanan ensued ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Abu Sayyaf demands ransom for release of 2 lady cops - Sun.Star Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1741246/Zamboanga/Local-News/Abu-Sayyaf-demands-ransom-for-release-of-2-lady-cops</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJPDeeE6F-5MLKJ0zW1ePCAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMPionQM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2018 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1741246/Zamboanga/Local-News/Abu-Sayyaf-demands-ransom-for-release-of-2-lady-cops" target="_blank"&gt;Abu Sayyaf demands ransom for release of 2 lady cops&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Sun.Star Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE Police Regional Office (PRO)-Zamboanga Peninsula has secured proof of life of the two policewomen seized by the Abu Sayyaf Group (ASG) in Sulu province.This was disclosed by Chief Superintendent B&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">Sun.Star Philippines</source></item><item><title>Changing lives, one pair of slippers at a time - Sun.Star Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1741254?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIYaTvnkJG-Zu2EmM7d7bYgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMOmhnQM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2018 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1741254?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;Changing lives, one pair of slippers at a time&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Sun.Star Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;IT ALL started last November 8, 2016 when Army Major Arturo Dumalagan and his troops were ambushed by Abu Sayyaf terrorist group in Patikul, Sulu.Since then, Dumalagan and his colleagues have embarked&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">Sun.Star Philippines</source></item><item><title>Abu Sayyaf bandits seize 2 lady cops, 2 others in Sulu - Sun.Star Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1740957?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGIwv_VqfBA4MCxyOxOrGfkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKeunQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1740957?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;Abu Sayyaf bandits seize 2 lady cops, 2 others in Sulu&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Sun.Star Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ABU Sayyaf bandits seized four people, including two policewomen, in Sulu on Sunday, April 29.The victims were identified as Police Officer (PO)3 Benierose Alvarez, PO1 Dinah Gumahad, Jakosalem Blas,&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">Sun.Star Philippines</source></item><item><title>Abu Sayyaf frees 2 Indonesian fishermen - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/regional/2018/01/21/Abu-Sayyaf-frees-2-Indonesian-fishermen.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDdifTrGJ2Jx9dp8I5RouGAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMPHhmQI</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2018 03:19:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/regional/2018/01/21/Abu-Sayyaf-frees-2-Indonesian-fishermen.html" target="_blank"&gt;Abu Sayyaf frees 2 Indonesian fishermen&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, January 21) - The Abu Sayyaf Group (ASG) has released two Indonesian captives, the military said Saturday. Joint Task Force (JTF) Sulu said they received a telephone call from former Governor Sakul Tan Sr. on Friday, who said a concerned citizen brought the two fishermen, La Utu Bin La Raali and La Hadi La Edi, to his house in Barangay Asturias, Jolo, Sulu. The Indonesians underwent medical examination and custodial debriefing at Camp Teodolfo Bautista in Jolo on Saturday, the military said. The two, both captains of two different fishing vessels, were abduct...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>2 Indonesian hostages freed in Philippines - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/194124-two-indonesian-hostages-freed-in-philippines</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMBc4A7CJO9yvKliWb4h2coqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2018 12:23:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/194124-two-indonesian-hostages-freed-in-philippines" target="_blank"&gt;2 Indonesian hostages freed in Philippines&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;JOLO, Philippines – Two Indonesian fishermen have been released by Islamic militants after more than a year in captivity in the southern Philippines, police said Saturday, January 20. There were no official comments on the physical condition of the two who were snatched from their fishing vessel in the waters between the southern Philippines and Malaysia in November 2016, a police statement said. The two were reportedly turned over by a "concerned citizen" late Thursday to a former governor on the southern island of Jolo, a longtime haunt of the Abu Sayyaf extremist group, some of whose mem...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item></channel></rss>