<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Solidarity of Filipino Workers - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqJAgKIh5DQkFTRUFvS0wyMHZNSEEzWXpWeVp4SUNaVzRvQUFQAQ?hl=en-PH&amp;gl=PH&amp;ceid=PH:en</link><language>en-PH</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 14:04:38 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>End contractualization - Sun.Star Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/davao/business/2017/05/02/end-contractualization-539758</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFl1uld3lyWvm_M15Q-KoHYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMMuPnAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2017 15:44:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/davao/business/2017/05/02/end-contractualization-539758" target="_blank"&gt;End contractualization&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Sun.Star Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ON Monday, the country’s working class commemorated the 115th International Labor Day under the Duterte administration with this wish: End labor contractualization scheme practiced by many of our big and small businesses. In rallies nationwide, thousands of Filipino workers reminded President Rodrigo Duterte of his campaign promise to put an end to this labor scheme. But workers are now becoming disenchanted. They told President Duterte in rallies that if he opted to simply follow the footsteps of the past presidents who appeared to have relied much on neo-liberal policies, like contractual...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">Sun.Star Philippines</source></item><item><title>Sanchez: When is the end of endo? - Sun.Star Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/bacolod/opinion/2017/05/03/sanchez-when-end-endo-539799</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH7oiiYBlTwnfkdlZbjZVzcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMPetnQM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2017 02:53:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/bacolod/opinion/2017/05/03/sanchez-when-end-endo-539799" target="_blank"&gt;Sanchez: When is the end of endo?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Sun.Star Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ONE thing about homegrown restaurants such as Aboy’s or Bob’s. Aside from the great Filipino dishes, the employees working there seems family. The waiters and probably the cooks are the same people you met, oh, a decade or even more ago. They recognize me, and I them. The only difference is that many already have silver hair, the same ones that I have in my head. They have been working on the same job for years. Obviously they have job tenure. I don’t know their terms of references with their employment. But one thing for sure, it’s not end-of-contract. The same cannot be said of many big c...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">Sun.Star Philippines</source></item><item><title>Astar drivers hold strike - Sun.Star Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/bacolod/local-news/2017/07/08/astar-drivers-hold-strike-551764</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAleJRfHORMUdWy4hnNieagqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKetnQM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2017 04:24:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/bacolod/local-news/2017/07/08/astar-drivers-hold-strike-551764" target="_blank"&gt;Astar drivers hold strike&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Sun.Star Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THIRTY-ONE members of Bacolod Astar Drivers Union, who are charter members of the Solidarity of Unions in the Philippines for Empowerment and Reform, have been staging a rally against their employer for a week now due to alleged labor malpractice and union-busting. Labor leader Wennie Sancho said the Department of Labor and Employement (Dole) and National Conciliation and Mediation Board (NCMB) should explain why the request for closure of the said transportation company was granted ahead of the request of the drivers for a certification to hold an election. “How can these drivers hold an e...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">Sun.Star Philippines</source></item><item><title>Militant groups give Digong 'zero’ grade - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1753923?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEExjBZOSFxEZMPyxjFTCa0IqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMPetnQM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2018 05:57:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1753923?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;Militant groups give Digong 'zero’ grade&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SOME progressive groups in Negros Occidental gave President Rodrigo “Digong” Duterte a “zero rating" in his two years of office. Members of Bukluran ng Manggagawang Pilipino (BMP), Partido Lakas ng Masa (PLM), Kongreso ng Pagkakaisa ng Maralitang Lungsod (KPML), and Aniban ng Manggagawa sa Agriklutura (AMA) under Sanlakas Negros rated the performance of the president in the aspect of economics, history and geography, civil defense and public safety, public administration and governance, and good manners and right conduct or values education. Based on their score sheet, the groups claimed th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item></channel></rss>