<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Bangsamoro Organic Law - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqJQgKIh9DQkFTRVFvTEwyMHZNREV5ZG5sak1tWVNBbVZ1S0FBUAE?hl=en-PH&amp;gl=PH&amp;ceid=PH:en</link><language>en-PH</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 14:04:40 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Campaign for new Bangsamoro law begins - ABS-CBN News</title><link>https://news.abs-cbn.com/news/multimedia/photo/12/07/18/campaign-for-new-bangsamoro-law-begins</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiXmh0dHBzOi8vbmV3cy5hYnMtY2JuLmNvbS9uZXdzL211bHRpbWVkaWEvcGhvdG8vMTIvMDcvMTgvY2FtcGFpZ24tZm9yLW5ldy1iYW5nc2Ftb3JvLWxhdy1iZWdpbnPSAQA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 11:21:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://news.abs-cbn.com/news/multimedia/photo/12/07/18/campaign-for-new-bangsamoro-law-begins" target="_blank"&gt;Campaign for new Bangsamoro law begins&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABS-CBN News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Filipino Muslims hold a prayer rally at the Golden Mosque in Quiapo Manila on Friday in support to the Bangsamoro Organic Law during the first day of ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://news.abs-cbn.com">ABS-CBN News</source><media:content url="https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/proxy/IVi7jWGMMc8ss5VQiEAB7QM24XdfQDJz7sRcVcr9KMNJVcL1AnKC0Z2DLSOLusXZpfiQ4IYb40Z8FyICtDJgmabF_WNBpOWNAuSxXgMz_lzfcihuexByZD0a3Ch7AGq4rXHNX5vB7APUSGkGTRT69YZIJg=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Bangsamoro law plebiscite to be held on two separate days —Comelec - GMA News</title><link>https://www.gmanetwork.com/news/news/nation/677416/bangsamoro-law-plebiscite-to-be-held-on-two-separate-days-comelec/story/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">52780129182158</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 05:46:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.gmanetwork.com/news/news/nation/677416/bangsamoro-law-plebiscite-to-be-held-on-two-separate-days-comelec/story/" target="_blank"&gt;Bangsamoro law plebiscite to be held on two separate days —Comelec&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;GMA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.abs-cbn.com/news/12/07/18/bangsamoro-plebiscite-set-on-2-separate-days-in-2019" target="_blank"&gt;Bangsamoro plebiscite set on 2 separate days in 2019&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABS-CBN News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://newsinfo.inquirer.net/1061135/comelec-plebiscite-for-bol-set-on-jan-21-feb-6" target="_blank"&gt;Comelec: Plebiscite for BOL set on Jan 21, Feb 6&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;INQUIRER.net&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/stories/CAAqOQgKIjNDQklTSURvSmMzUnZjbmt0TXpZd1NoTUtFUWpPdy1lbWpZQU1FWTZWU2VGNjJ1WTZLQUFQAQ?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;View full coverage on Google News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;</description><source url="https://www.gmanetwork.com">GMA News</source><media:content url="https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/proxy/MwteMSoTpnUycczRBvigHqORRLTTpHWhRTMGWSfp60rA9H_0zAWx8NakEkOBtAzHOwEnhHK3XVRsn350qKuzNyOF6BXW6en0QyhWB8-bS4wmIMbtj0NL7qoiQ908E-7MnHzjW6_xCDmb=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>ARMM youth favor Bangsamoro Organic Law: survey - ABS-CBN News</title><link>https://news.abs-cbn.com/focus/12/06/18/armm-youth-favor-bangsamoro-organic-law-survey</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiVmh0dHBzOi8vbmV3cy5hYnMtY2JuLmNvbS9mb2N1cy8xMi8wNi8xOC9hcm1tLXlvdXRoLWZhdm9yLWJhbmdzYW1vcm8tb3JnYW5pYy1sYXctc3VydmV50gEA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 09:24:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://news.abs-cbn.com/focus/12/06/18/armm-youth-favor-bangsamoro-organic-law-survey" target="_blank"&gt;ARMM youth favor Bangsamoro Organic Law: survey&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABS-CBN News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA - Majority of youth voters in the Autonomous Region in Muslim Mindanao (ARMM) are in favor of the Bangsamoro Organic Law (BOL), a peace ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://news.abs-cbn.com">ABS-CBN News</source><media:content url="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/proxy/LWYDbio1xD06D4ZekVpzPUGrWB9th3tHU84sVkertErIspql7sQjjqLWsFxQiKBSYTCCSVP2FY6bykLq8EWeV9H17ib6NWDy-d6dc7FUINS1WbtQRDNzhUCWKPxJSegSEjJXwRtlvRf9V_jIHEZa-e763oSvEN8uKFMuSw=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Sulu civil society slams Tan petition against BOL - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/216508-sulu-civil-society-slams-governor-tan-petition-against-bangsamoro-organic-law</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHsPCefjXO_RTD8jw6qU_jIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/216508-sulu-civil-society-slams-governor-tan-petition-against-bangsamoro-organic-law" target="_blank"&gt;Sulu civil society slams Tan petition against BOL&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Being a Bangsamoro, a Tausug from Sulu, I would say, I am also free to counter any act of Governor Tan,' says Hadjinur Tingkasan, a Sulu Peace Advocate.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>The Day in Photos: 07 December 2018 - ABS CBN News</title><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMRgyW6n-DUGgER8cy_EoHYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow8IjwCjDw4s8CMNj9mQI</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 05:57:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABS CBN News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bong Revilla acquitted in plunder case Former Senator Ramon "Bong" Revilla Jr. hugs a member of his panel after the Sandiganbayan on Friday cleared him of plunder in connection with the Priority Development Assistance Fund (PDAF) or pork barrel scam case. Public prosecutors had accused the actor-turned-politician of embezzling P224 million in discretionary funds while he was still senator. Mark Demayo, ABS-CBN News Who is the shadow behind Janet Lim Napoles? Pork barrel scam mastermind Janet Lim Napoles, along with Bong Revilla's former chief-of-staff Richard Cambe, is found guilty of plund...&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Plebiscite, campaign period begins countdown to BOL referendum - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1777628/Manila/Local-News/Plebiscite-campaign-period-begins-countdown-to-Bangsamoro-Organic-Law-referendum?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENJF0MyV8dh5kfapp38VibgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKmgnQM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 04:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1777628/Manila/Local-News/Plebiscite-campaign-period-begins-countdown-to-Bangsamoro-Organic-Law-referendum?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;Plebiscite, campaign period begins countdown to BOL referendum&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE countdown for the January 21 plebiscite to ratify the Bangsamoro Organic Law (BOL) officially begins Friday, December 7, as several parts of Mindanao enter both the plebiscite and campaign periods. According to the Commission on Elections (Comelec) Resolution 10432, the plebiscite period will run from December 7 until February 5. During this period, the Comelec prohibits the carrying of firearms or other deadly weapons, as well as the use of security personnel or bodyguards by candidates. Other prohibited acts during this period are: altering the territory of a precinct or establishment...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Most ARMM youth will vote in favor of Bangsamoro Law – survey - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/218388-most-armm-youth-will-vote-in-favor-bangsamoro-organic-law</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHUwvQuvPMUvQjCH8JBS2kkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 02:04:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/218388-most-armm-youth-will-vote-in-favor-bangsamoro-organic-law" target="_blank"&gt;Most ARMM youth will vote in favor of Bangsamoro Law – survey&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – A majority of youth in the Autonomous Region in Muslim Mindanao will vote in favor of the Bangsamoro Organic Law (BOL) in January, according to the results of a survey conducted by peace-building organization International Alert Philippines. The plebiscite for the BOL is set to take place on January 21, 2019. The campaign period for the plebiscite began on Friday, December 7. The survey, conducted from October 29 to November 19, showed that 60.4% of ARMM youth – whether or not they intend to vote in the BOL plebiscite in January – will vote “yes” for BOL ratification...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Comelec to hold two-day Bangsamoro plebiscite in January, February 2019 - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/12/07/comelec-bangsamoro-plebiscite.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELxkWn3Q21Tcd69bE6gVvFYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMJbthQM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 13:44:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/12/07/comelec-bangsamoro-plebiscite.html" target="_blank"&gt;Comelec to hold two-day Bangsamoro plebiscite in January, February 2019&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, December 7) — The plebiscite for the ratification of the Bangsamoro law will be split into two dates, the Commission on Elections (Comelec) announced Friday. The poll body said the initial plebiscite date of January 21, 2019 will still push through. However, another day was added for local government units which petitioned for voluntary inclusion in the region. The second day of the referendum is set on February 6, 2019. comelec bangsamoro In its press release, Comelec said the geographical areas comprising the Autonomous Region of Muslim Mindanao (ARMM)-- Su...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>Plebiscite on Bangsamoro law now set for January, February 2019 - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/218401-bangsamoro-plebiscite-january-february-2019</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIsaovxNh6T048i0-iEvXaUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 04:21:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/218401-bangsamoro-plebiscite-january-february-2019" target="_blank"&gt;Plebiscite on Bangsamoro law now set for January, February 2019&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – The plebiscite to ratify the landmark Bangsamoro Organic Law (BOL) is now set to take place on two dates, the Commission on Elections (Comelec) announced on Friday, December 7. The Comelec originally scheduled the plebiscite to take place on one day, but decided to add another date to allow more time for the full resolution of petitions which local government units (LGUs) submitted to be included in the proposed new region. The first voting day will be on January 21, 2019, in the Autonomous Region in Muslim Mindanao (ARMM), Cotabato City, and Isabela City. The second v...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Comelec splits Bangsamoro plebiscite - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1777660/Manila/Local-News/Comelec-splits-Bangsamoro-plebiscite?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF-JMZL_dvZmnLcioE4XVmUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKmgnQM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 09:43:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1777660/Manila/Local-News/Comelec-splits-Bangsamoro-plebiscite?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;Comelec splits Bangsamoro plebiscite&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NOT one but two days will be designated for the plebiscite for the ratification of the Bangsamoro Organic Law (BOL), according to the Commission on Elections (Comelec). In a statement, Comelec spokesman James Jimenez said the Bangsamoro plebiscite will now be held on January 21 and in February 6. “The plebiscite for the ratification of BOL will be conducted on two separate days to allow time for the full resolution of petitions for voluntary inclusion in the plebiscite,” said Jimenez. As decided by the commission, the plebiscite will push through as originally scheduled, which is on January...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Gov't, MILF kick off campaign for Bangsamoro plebiscite - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/218380-government-milf-plebiscite-campaign-period-kick-off</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELjJ4FqcSZrCfXEAx6B9GWsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 17:40:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/218380-government-milf-plebiscite-campaign-period-kick-off" target="_blank"&gt;Gov't, MILF kick off campaign for Bangsamoro plebiscite&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – Government officials and leaders of the Moro Islamic Liberation Front (MILF) urged the public to unite and take part in the plebiscite to ratify the landmark Bangsmaro Organic Law (BOL) in January 2019. “The BOL is for the welfare not only of the Bangsamoro people but (also of) non-Muslims residing in the Bangsamoro areas…. The BOL is a formula for peace, development, and progress,” MILF peace panel chair Mohagher Iqbal said in a statement Thursday night, December 6. The campaign period for the plebiscite started Friday, December 7, and will end on January 19, 2019. Th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Duterte approves ‘in principle’ recommendation for martial law extension - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/218252-duterte-approves-in-principle-recommendation-ask-for-mindanao-martial-law-extension</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHOlEi2OYp_LDoe5Zpg6EYMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 05:00:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/218252-duterte-approves-in-principle-recommendation-ask-for-mindanao-martial-law-extension" target="_blank"&gt;Duterte approves ‘in principle’ recommendation for martial law extension&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – President Rodrigo Duterte has approved "in principle" the recommendation of the military, police, and the Department of National Defense (DND) to ask for a one-year extension of martial law in Mindanao. "Yes, in principle," said Defense Secretary Delfin Lorenzana on Wednesday, December 5, when asked if the President had approved the recommendations of the security officials. The recommendations were discussed in a small meeting Duterte held with select officials on the sidelines of the Cabinet meeting on Tuesday, December 4. Lorenzana said he "asked for a one-year exte...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Arroyo to support martial law extension - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1777317/Manila/Local-News/Arroyo-to-support-martial-law-extension?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBVJSXj1J6aK8aXwFPsg0UQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKmgnQM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 09:26:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1777317/Manila/Local-News/Arroyo-to-support-martial-law-extension?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;Arroyo to support martial law extension&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;HOUSE Speaker Gloria Macapagal-Arroyo will recommend the approval of the looming proposal to extend martial law in Mindanao. "If it comes to our Chamber, I will recommend that we pass it,” said Arroyo when interviewed by the media on Wednesday, December 5. She did not elaborate. Majority Leader Rolando Andaya Jr. earlier expressed support for a resolution to extend martial law in Mindanao for another year. Philippine National Police Chief Oscar Albayalde and Armed Forces of the Philippines (AFP) Chief-of-Staff Carlito Galvez Jr. have signed a document formally recommending the extension. Ga...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Defense chief OK with martial law extension - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/12/04/mindanao-martial-law-extension-delfin-lorenzana.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMApzsdnQHuEY9TdyndRINIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMJbthQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 06:07:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/12/04/mindanao-martial-law-extension-delfin-lorenzana.html" target="_blank"&gt;Defense chief OK with martial law extension&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, December 4) — Defense Secretary Delfin Lorenzana said he would follow the recommendation of the police and the military to extend martial law for another year. lorenzana martial law extend However, Lorenzana said he would not push for martial law to be expanded nationwide. "In fact the President said on many and many occasions that he is not inclined to proclaim martial law nationwide," Lorenzana said. lorenzana martial law The militant Makabayan bloc in Congress has warned that extending martial law in Mindanao for the third time may embolden the AFP to exp...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>Sultan calls for unity among Muslim leaders ahead of BOL plebiscite - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1776799</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBrsmCgJRgGWxtiw87KyWicqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMIeunQM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 09:32:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1776799" target="_blank"&gt;Sultan calls for unity among Muslim leaders ahead of BOL plebiscite&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MADALUM, Lanao Del Sur -- A Maranao sultan has gathered some 500 traditional leaders from all over the two provinces of Lanao to put up a united front in supporting for the ratification of the Bangsamoro Organic Law (BOL) ahead of the plebiscite on January 21, 2019. Sultan Usman Sarangani Sr., the sultan of Uya-an and reigning paramount sultan of Mindanao, said he has gathered the datus and baes of Lanao del Sur and Lanao del Norte to explain to them that the BOL ratification needs their support. The BOL is a mechanism that will create the Bangsamoro Autonomous Region in Muslim Mindanao (BA...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>AFP, PNP to recommend Mindanao martial law extension - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/218079-afp-pnp-recommend-mindanao-martial-law-extension</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB-Cwk2d7_ZXuNIyC4d7WVcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 02:34:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/218079-afp-pnp-recommend-mindanao-martial-law-extension" target="_blank"&gt;AFP, PNP to recommend Mindanao martial law extension&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – The Armed Forces of the Philippines (AFP) and the Philippine National Police (PNP) will recommend extending martial law in Mindanao. Speaking to reporters on Monday, December 3, military chief General Carlito Galvez Jr said they have yet to submit the formal recommendation, but they will prescribe one more year of martial law for Mindanao. "For now, that's our recommendation that will be submitted to the secretary of national defense and then most probably this conference, this coming [December] 12 with the new chief of staff. We will be presenting the recommendation,"...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>‘Marawi rehab needs own office’ - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1776857/Davao/Local-News/Marawi-rehab-needs-own-office?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPdMDh1OeM5DzfJeXZrq0BwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKeunQM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 12:51:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1776857/Davao/Local-News/Marawi-rehab-needs-own-office?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;‘Marawi rehab needs own office’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A MEMBER of the Bangsamoro Transition Commission (BTC) said there should be a regional office that will solely focus on the rehabilitation of Marawi City. "Ngayon ang ARMM (government), does not know if it will move forward and they do not have enough budget to really supervise the rehabilitation," Datu Mussolini Sinsuat Lidasan, executive director of the Al Qalam Institute, said during the press conference of the MSummit: Moro Youth National Conference Saturday, December 1 at the Ateneo de Davao University. He said while there is a Task Force Bangon Marawi it is "hard for them to get their...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>No word yet on who will replace Dureza as OPAPP chief — Panelo - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/11/29/jesus-dureza-opapp-no-replacement-sal-panelo.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOkCmLrbeSc4xNbjo1B9ct4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMJbthQM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 16:12:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/11/29/jesus-dureza-opapp-no-replacement-sal-panelo.html" target="_blank"&gt;No word yet on who will replace Dureza as OPAPP chief — Panelo&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, November 28) — There is no word on who will take over Jesus Dureza as chief of the Office of the Presidential Adviser on the Peace Process (OPAPP). Presidential Spokesperson Salvador Panelo said Wednesday he has no clue on who will take over at OPAPP, and in what capacity. Outgoing Armed Forces Chief Carlito Galvez recently revealed he intends to join OPAPP after his retirement on December 12. His name is also being floated as the next Presidential Peace Adviser. Defense Chief Delfin Lorenzana said he would strongly recommend Galvez to replace Dureza, whom he ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>DILG set to submit martial law extension recommendation - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1776141</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKsAfwPJraJUitq-ZRwoJqoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKeunQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 12:44:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1776141" target="_blank"&gt;DILG set to submit martial law extension recommendation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;DEFENSE Secretary Delfin Lorenzana said they will submit their recommendation on the extension of Martial Law to the President next week. “Matatapos guro ang buwan nato, first week of December, we are going to present our recommendation to the President. Like Secretary (Eduardo) Año, I’m also inclined to follow the wishes of the people here (in Mindanao),” Lorenzana said in a press conference on Monday here in Davao City. He said based on their consultations, there has been a clamor to extend the Martial Law, which will lapse on December 31. Not only does the local government officials who ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Zambo villages not ‘contiguous’ to Armm areas - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1776404/Zamboanga/Local-News/Zambo-villages-not-contiguous-to-Armm-areas</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEI7pUFYHl_PB9Z1TMDj8fsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJiunQM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 10:22:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1776404/Zamboanga/Local-News/Zambo-villages-not-contiguous-to-Armm-areas" target="_blank"&gt;Zambo villages not ‘contiguous’ to Armm areas&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;CITY Legal Officer Jesus Carbon, Jr. advised any registered voter in Zamboanga City not to file a petition for voluntary inclusion in the January 21, 2019 plebiscite for the Bangsamoro Organic Law (BOL), citing none of this city’s 98 villages is contiguous to any of the areas under the Autonomous Region in Muslim Mindanao (Armm). Carbon cited an en banc decision of the Supreme Court in the case of Tan, et al vs. the Commission on Elections and the Provincial Treasurer of Negros Occidental on July 11, 1986, wherein the meaning of word contiguous was explained as physical contact, touching al...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Military, MILF prepare to secure Bangsamoro vote vs violence - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/217430-philippine-military-milf-security-preparations-bangsamoro-organic-law-plebiscite</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJLSwNqo7EhROTVPoy4eBIMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2018 02:01:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/217430-philippine-military-milf-security-preparations-bangsamoro-organic-law-plebiscite" target="_blank"&gt;Military, MILF prepare to secure Bangsamoro vote vs violence&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – The Moro Islamic Liberation Front (MILF) said the plebiscite on the creation of a new Bangsamoro region on January 21, 2019, will not be marred by the usual violence seen in regular elections in Mindanao. “While we see that there’s a possibility of some violence during the plebiscite, for me, the plebiscite is not like regular elections,” MILF chairman Al Haj Murad Ebrahim said. The military and the MILF discussed security preparations for the plebiscite during Murad’s historic Camp Aguinaldo visit on November 21, two months before the crucial plebiscite. “Napag-usapan...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Youth involvement in Bangsamoro organic law pushed - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1775985</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBlnPdvPbwrUk0xxd7MoR0sqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKeunQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 13:59:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1775985" target="_blank"&gt;Youth involvement in Bangsamoro organic law pushed&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THERE is still a need to intensify the involvement of the Bangasamoro youth in the Bangsamoro Organic Law (BOL) and related issues. Salaam Movement coordinator Fatima Star Lamalan said Monday, November 26, during the SM City’s Kapehan, that the Bangsamoro youth are the future leaders and there is a need to pass on the same vision for peace and unity. “It’s been a month ago na ang issues on inclusions sa Bangsamoro. But we want to start with informing them [Bangsamoro youth] because we cannot really have them fight for these provisions for example kasi they don’t even know the BOL itself,” L...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>MILF chair confident in constitutionality of Bangsamoro law - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/11/19/milf-bangsamoro-law-constitutional.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJdWT5VzrkkNprOYr42TBtsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMJbthQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 08:13:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/11/19/milf-bangsamoro-law-constitutional.html" target="_blank"&gt;MILF chair confident in constitutionality of Bangsamoro law&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, November 19) — Moro Islamic Liberation Front (MILF) Chairman Al Haj Murad Ebrahim said his group remains confident of the constitutionality of the Bangsamoro law amid calls of a local government unit to stop its implementation. Murad on Monday addressed the Sulu government's petition to nullify the measure, and reiterated that it will not stop the peace process in Mindanao. "As far as the petition is concerned… we're very confident that the issue of constitutionality is well-addressed," Murad said during a joint media briefing with the Armed Forces of the Phi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>Non-ratification of Bangsamoro Law may leave 'fertile ground for extremism' - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/216762-non-ratification-bangsamoro-organic-law-may-leave-fertile-ground-extremism</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFPHLEfEyQ6r6KKoZE0w9hMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/216762-non-ratification-bangsamoro-organic-law-may-leave-fertile-ground-extremism" target="_blank"&gt;Non-ratification of Bangsamoro Law may leave 'fertile ground for extremism'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – If efforts to block the Bangsamoro Organic Law (BOL) are successful or if the law is not ratified, violent extremism will flourish in Mindanao, Chief Presidential Adviser Jesus Dureza warned. Dureza expressed this view as he explained the importance of greenlighting the BOL, which is being questioned before the Supreme Court. "If BOL will not pass – I'm not threatening, I'm not making people fearful that you have to support the BOL – but my real sense is that violent extremism may have a fertile ground if we don't push through with the BOL," he said during a Rappler T...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Military rolls out red carpet for Murad before crucial plebiscite - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/217023-milf-al-haj-murad-ebrahim-visit-camp-aguinaldo-november-19-2018</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBRnvXBrfNX8XokOW-QIlF0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 05:07:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/217023-milf-al-haj-murad-ebrahim-visit-camp-aguinaldo-november-19-2018" target="_blank"&gt;Military rolls out red carpet for Murad before crucial plebiscite&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – The Armed Forces of the Philippines (AFP) rolled out the red carpet for Moro Islamic Liberation Front (MILF) chairman Al Haj Murad Ebrahim during his historic visit to Camp Aguinaldo on Monday, November 19. The military band played as Murad stepped off his vehicle onto the red carpet rolled out for him in front of the military headquarters. He was handed a white rose before he was led to meet the AFP hierarchy and shook their hands. Murad is the first MILF chairman to step foot in Camp Aguinaldo following more than 3 decades of Muslim rebellion in Mindanao that histori...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Rappler Talk: Jesus Dureza on preparations for the Bangsamoro plebiscite - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/216749-interview-jesus-dureza-bangsamoro-plebiscite-preparations</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJz6moM4WWUByjdo-ckb7S8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 04:03:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/216749-interview-jesus-dureza-bangsamoro-plebiscite-preparations" target="_blank"&gt;Rappler Talk: Jesus Dureza on preparations for the Bangsamoro plebiscite&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bookmark to watch the interview with Dureza at 3:30 PM MANILA, Philippines – On January 21, 2019, people in the Autonomous Region in Muslim Mindanao will cast their vote on whether or not to ratify the landmark Bangsamoro Organic Law. As early as December 7, the government and supporters of the law will begin campaigning for a "yes vote." This plebiscite period will happen as government contemplates another extension of martial law in Mindanao and as the country gears up for the May 2019 elections. Chief Presidential Adviser Jesus Dureza speaks to Rappler about what the BOL plebiscite mean...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Dureza says martial law extension good for Bangsamoro plebiscite - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/216751-dureza-says-another-mindanao-martial-law-extension-help-bangsamoro-plebiscite</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAm8uW0J3y3urrwGxghJH-gqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/216751-dureza-says-another-mindanao-martial-law-extension-help-bangsamoro-plebiscite" target="_blank"&gt;Dureza says martial law extension good for Bangsamoro plebiscite&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – Chief Peace Adviser Jesus Dureza supports a third extension of martial law, saying it could help ensure a peaceful and successful plebiscite on the Bangsamoro Organic Law in January 2019. "I-extend muna (Extend it first) in order that the climate also be conducive to a peaceful plebiscite and perhaps a peaceful election in May," he said on Wednesday, November 14, during a Rappler Talk interview. "It can help, definitely, in the areas now. You know that some areas in Mindanao are problematic," he added. A regional plebiscite on the BOL is set to take place on January 21...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>MNLF faction reiterates support for Bangsamoro Organic Law - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/215826-mnlf-faction-supports-bangsamoro-organic-law</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOFzzV3zuOcrCH9SkzLbUmEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2018 01:10:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/215826-mnlf-faction-supports-bangsamoro-organic-law" target="_blank"&gt;MNLF faction reiterates support for Bangsamoro Organic Law&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;DAVAO CITY, Philippines – A faction of the Moro National Liberation Front (MNLF) led by fomer Sulu governor Yusop Jikiri renewed its support for the Bangsamoro Organic Law (BOL) amid moves to question the legality of the measure. The Office of the Presidential Adviser on the Peace Process (OPAPP) said in a press statement on Saturday, November 3, that Jikiri relayed his group's support for the BOL in a meeting with Chief Peace Adviser Jesus Dureza earlier this week on Monday, October 29. The meeting was held a day before it was reported that incumbent Sulu Governor Abdusakur Tan II filed a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Bangsamoro advocate retires as Cotabato archbishop - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/216087-cardinal-quevedo-retires-cotabato-archbishop</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAzSCKzhxG8Lp1I0lVCRvyAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 18:14:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/216087-cardinal-quevedo-retires-cotabato-archbishop" target="_blank"&gt;Bangsamoro advocate retires as Cotabato archbishop&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – Cardinal Orlando Quevedo, one of the staunchest advocates of the Mindanao peace process, resigned as archbishop of Cotabato after having reached the age of retirement, the Catholic Church said. Pope Francis accepted Quevedo's resignation and appointed Bishop Angelito Lampon of Jolo as his successor, the Vatican announced on Tuesday evening, November 6. Quevedo has long pushed for what is now known as the Bangsamoro Organic Law (BOL), which aims to create a more powerful Muslim region in the southern Philippine island group of Mindanao. The BOL is up for plebiscite on J...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Governor Tan of Sulu runs to Supreme Court to block Bangsamoro law - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/215554-sulu-abdusakur-tan-ii-supreme-court-petition-block-bangsamoro-organic-law</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFFEbOMXf5T1yMLB-M0Yfa8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 06:00:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/215554-sulu-abdusakur-tan-ii-supreme-court-petition-block-bangsamoro-organic-law" target="_blank"&gt;Governor Tan of Sulu runs to Supreme Court to block Bangsamoro law&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – Governor Abdusakur Tan II of Sulu filed the first Supreme Court (SC) petition to block the landmark Bangsamoro Organic Law (BOL), citing questions on constitutionality. Tan filed a petition for certiorari and prohibition with a request for temporary restraining order (TRO) before the SC. Lawmakers who crafted the BOL expected this petition, and welcomed the move as it would settle questions on legality and allow them to move forward without constraints. “I truly believe though that the Organic Law that we passed can stand the test of constitutionality after careful scr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>BOL holds hydro's privatization - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1770780</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECWuj7g3P6097VfSUxgX_6gqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKeunQM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 12:58:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1770780" target="_blank"&gt;BOL holds hydro's privatization&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;AN OFFICIAL of the Mindanao Development Authority (Minda) said the Power Sector Assets and Liabilities Management (Psalm) has put on hold the privatization of the 982.8 megawatts (MW) Agus-Pulangi Hydroelectric Power Plants (HEPP) due to certain provisions in the Bangsamoro Organic Law. "It may not be privatizing the Agus and Pulangi in the immediate term. Therefore, it is sort of an indefinite plan at the moment," Assistant secretary Romeo M. Montenegro, Minda deputy executive director, said yesterday during a press conference at the Habi at Kape, Abreeza Mall. He said Psalm is yet to dete...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Where do 2019 senatorial bets stand on key national issues? - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/newsbreak/iq/214974-where-senatorial-bets-stand-key-issues-philippines</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKqwpiZ_QZyvoNT-RlYpCq4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJ_jmQI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 19:28:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/newsbreak/iq/214974-where-senatorial-bets-stand-key-issues-philippines" target="_blank"&gt;Where do 2019 senatorial bets stand on key national issues?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – A number of those running for senator in the 2019 midterm elections have been in government or the public eye for long, and so they have surely made known their positions on key national issues. Rappler takes a look at where they stand on the issues that have so far made headlines in 2018 based on either statements they have made or votes they have cast on bills and resolutions as lawmakers. Some of the issues here have been on the nation's plate for some time. Recent events and developments, however, have brought them back into the spotlight. Among the top issues, di...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Neighboring LGUs of Bangsamoro region may ask to be part of plebiscite - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/214925-bangsamoro-neighboring-lgus-may-ask-to-be-part-plebiscite</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIsfpAMHDzAJ7Uvar_rt6NsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 13:05:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/214925-bangsamoro-neighboring-lgus-may-ask-to-be-part-plebiscite" target="_blank"&gt;Neighboring LGUs of Bangsamoro region may ask to be part of plebiscite&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – Local government units (LGU) that are neighbors of the proposed Bangsamoro Autonomous Region (BAR) may ask to be included in the January 2019 plebiscite to be part of the region's territory. In a statement on Monday, October 22, the Commission on Elections (Comelec) said contiguous LGUs may apply for voluntary inclusion in the plebiscite on January 21, 2019, to ratify the Bangsamoro Organic Law. In accordance with Republic Act 11054, Comelec's rules state that a petitioning LGU must submit 9 copies of a local council or sanggunian resolution bearing its official seal a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Autonomy to speed up CAR’s development - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1769530</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENK4tHUAgaicN-8JUOgDNQ8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMLignQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 13:45:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1769530" target="_blank"&gt;Autonomy to speed up CAR’s development&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BAGUIO City Mayor Mauricio Domogan emphasized the realization of the Cordillera Administrative Region’s (CAR) quest for autonomy will result to faster development of the rural areas around the region that will spread out the desired economic growth and prevent people from flocking to urban centers. The local chief executive pointed out the establishment of the proposed Autonomous Region in the Cordillera (ARC) will guarantee more funds for development, faster development of other potential growth areas and the crafting of policies suitable to the prevailing situation in the region. “We have...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Islamic scholars calls for unity ahead of Bangsamoro plebiscite - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/214236-national-ulama-conference-philippines-unity-bangsamoro-organic-law</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKbXlf6lex2IhrT6iaRnkrIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2018 09:31:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/214236-national-ulama-conference-philippines-unity-bangsamoro-organic-law" target="_blank"&gt;Islamic scholars calls for unity ahead of Bangsamoro plebiscite&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;DAVAO CITY, Philippines – The National Ulama Conference of the Philippines (NUCP) urged for unity and preparation so that the "hearts and minds of the electorate" would be won towards the ratification of the Bangsamoro Organic Law (BOL). In a statement issued October 7 and released to reporters on Saturday, October 13, the NUCP said the BOL is "a milestone towards the realization of self-determination for the Bangsamoro." (DOCUMENT: Bangsamoro Organic Law) The 13-man group made up of ulama or Islamic scholars regarded the BOL as a means of achieving peace and development for the people of M...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Draft federal charter respects CAR customs, traditions - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1769205/Baguio/Local-News/Draft-federal-charter-respects-CAR-customs-traditions?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHBfsWuXfQF-5zySl8gpHPQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMLignQM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2018 14:06:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1769205/Baguio/Local-News/Draft-federal-charter-respects-CAR-customs-traditions?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;Draft federal charter respects CAR customs, traditions&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PASAY CITY – Former Senate President Aquilino Pimentel reiterated that the culture and traditions of the different regions must always be respected under the proposed federal form of government. Pimentel, during the Luzon leg of the seminar-workshops for journalists on Understanding Federalism in the Philippine Context, stressed this is part of the proposal submitted by the Consultative Committee (ConCom). “Once Cordillera will form part of the federated region, the assurance that their customary practices is explicitly indicated in the federal constitution provided they do not violate the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Martial law helped lessen violence in ARMM – report - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/213348-martial-law-helped-lessen-violence-armm-conflict-alert-2018</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKu_Q5fkM-p86Fs4IQq2RhQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 10:15:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/213348-martial-law-helped-lessen-violence-armm-conflict-alert-2018" target="_blank"&gt;Martial law helped lessen violence in ARMM – report&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – President Rodrigo Duterte’s martial law in Mindanao helped lessen violence in the Autonomous Region in Muslim Mindanao (ARMM) by discouraging armed groups from bringing out their weapons. This was one of the findings of the 2018 Conflict Alert report, launched on Tuesday, October 2. “It disabled the ability of armed groups to take out their weapons….The biggest effect we saw of martial law is control of the weapons,” said Francisco Lara Jr, Senior Peace and Conflict Adviser in Asia for International Alert Philippines. Lara was among those who presented the report to m...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Lidasan: Gun culture and the peace process - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1764985</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEZ7DWh7s8RW-ws910A6NBgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKeunQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 12:25:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1764985" target="_blank"&gt;Lidasan: Gun culture and the peace process&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;IN MY recent engagements with our partners in the communities in the Autonomous Region in Muslim Mindanao (Armm), I spent much time in trying to convince my relatives to support the Bangsamoro Organic Law. I presented the pertinent points of the law to my young cousins who are public officials. One of my cousins asked me, what will happen to our security and safety of our family and land? I was not able to categorically answer the question. As I reflect on the conversations I had with my relatives, I remembered what my elder brother, Datu Mohammad, told me regarding gun culture of the Musli...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Plebiscite on Bangsamoro Organic Law set for January 2019 - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/211191-plebiscite-bangsamoro-organic-law-january-21-2019</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFoqSjDaB28DJ1wTeHCjzaUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2018 02:33:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/211191-plebiscite-bangsamoro-organic-law-january-21-2019" target="_blank"&gt;Plebiscite on Bangsamoro Organic Law set for January 2019&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines (UPDATED) – The plebiscite on the landmark Bangsamoro Organic Law is set to take place on January 21, 2019, the Commission on Elections (Comelec) announced on Wednesday morning, September 5. "The Commission on Elections en banc, pursuant to the authority granted by Republic Act 11054, has set the date for the Bangsamoro Organic Law plebiscite on 21 January 2019," said Comelec Spokesperson James Jimenez. "The plebiscite period shall run from 7 December 2018 to 5 February 2019, while the campaign period begins on 7 December 2018 and ends on 19 January 2019," Jimenez added....&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Special voter registrations set for Bangsamoro plebiscite - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/211614-bangsamoro-plebiscite-special-voter-registration-schedule-september-2018</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPNQfc6o0_0WMsxhl3kbtB4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 04:44:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/211614-bangsamoro-plebiscite-special-voter-registration-schedule-september-2018" target="_blank"&gt;Special voter registrations set for Bangsamoro plebiscite&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – The Commission on Elections (Comelec) will conduct satellite voter registrations in Mindanao from Tuesday to Thursday, September 11 to 13, to prepare for the upcoming plebiscite on the landmark Bangsamoro Organic Law (BOL). The special satellite registrations will be held "in 16 venues in the provinces of Lanao del Sur, Maguindanao, Basilan, Sulu, Tawi-Tawi, Lanao del Norte, and North Cotabato; in Cotabato City, Maguindanao; and in Isabela City, Basilan," said the Comelec on Monday, September 10. The registration will be conducted by 9 special registration teams (SRTs)...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Bangsamoro new region to remove 'bad leaders' - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1762483</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENOygZ7ao1HmDgFwtmo6UbkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMIeunQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2018 13:31:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1762483" target="_blank"&gt;Bangsamoro new region to remove 'bad leaders'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MARAWI CITY -- The Bangsamoro Organic Law (BOL) aims to replace the "incompetent" leaders in the Autonomous Region in Muslim Mindanao (Armm) through the creation of the new Bangsamoro Autonomous Region in Muslim Mindanao (Barmm), an assemblyman said. Lawyer Abol Alam Padate, assemblyman of the second district of Lanao del Sur, said in a forum on the BOL for the Barmm held at Mindanao State University-Marawi, said the replacement of the former unitary government of Armm to parliamentary is a means to "replace people" currently leading the Bangsamoro region. "If the same people (former leader...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>MILF leader: Better understanding of Bangsamoro Organic Law needed - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/08/26/milf-mohagher-iqbal-bangsamoro-organic-law.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBJhbyaTkjbxEfVPTto1CAEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMJbthQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 08:58:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/08/26/milf-mohagher-iqbal-bangsamoro-organic-law.html" target="_blank"&gt;MILF leader: Better understanding of Bangsamoro Organic Law needed&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manlila (CNN Philippines, August 26) — A lot of people in Muslim Mindanao are still clueless about the new Bangsamoro law, a leader from the Moro Islamic Liberation Front (MILF) said Sunday. "Generally, the people really do not understand fully the content of the Bangsamoro Organic Law (BOL) and, as I said a while ago, how these provisions would really redound to the benefit of the people," MILF Chief Peace Negotiator Mohagher Iqbal said. He added, "The BOL is equated to peace. Peace, development." This ahead of the plebiscite, which will happen either in December or in January next y...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>House panel approves P6.7-B Office of the President budget for 2019 - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/210651-house-panel-approves-office-of-the-president-2019-budget</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF7dx_7LKmNCsXq0nyQiXWEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2018 05:49:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/210651-house-panel-approves-office-of-the-president-2019-budget" target="_blank"&gt;House panel approves P6.7-B Office of the President budget for 2019&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – As in previous years, the House appropriations committee approved within minutes the 2019 proposed budget of the Office of the President. After 9 minutes and with no questions asked, Albay 1st District Representative Edcel Lagman, a member of the opposition and among President Rodrigo Duterte's critics in the House, moved for the termination of the hearing "consistent with the enduring tradition in this committee." He, however, said questions on the OP budget could still be asked during the plenary. Speaker Gloria Macapagal Arroyo was present at the budget hearing. Exe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Arroyo supports possible martial law extension in Mindanao - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/210731-arroyo-statement-possible-mindanao-martial-law-extension-after-sultan-kudarat-explosion</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELbgVuTc-_HBfxKfPbk1PbUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2018 05:41:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/210731-arroyo-statement-possible-mindanao-martial-law-extension-after-sultan-kudarat-explosion" target="_blank"&gt;Arroyo supports possible martial law extension in Mindanao&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – Speaker Gloria Macapagal Arroyo supports the proposal to extend the declaration of martial law in Mindanao after a deadly bombing in Sultan Kudarat. "I support martial law in Mindanao. I'll support what the President does because I've been president and I believe that he does not need a peanut gallery to tell him what to do," said Arroyo in a chance interview in Floridablanca, Pampanga, on Thursday, August 30. The former president turned Pampanga 2nd District representative was asked to react to Executive Secretary Salvador Medialdea floating the option to extend marti...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Sunio: BOL is for the non-Moro, too - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1759460</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJuoyEP8MOXyFHsQAk4yQ4AqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMIeunQM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2018 14:47:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1759460" target="_blank"&gt;Sunio: BOL is for the non-Moro, too&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SOME non-Muslims in Armm feared of what will happen to them if the Bangsamoro Organic Law is passed – will the new Islamic state persecute us, or perhaps chase us away from their new established government? It turns out that the better protection and benefits of settlers and non-Muslims like us was ensured in the proposal for the new parliamentary government. When the then, Bangsamoro Basic Law, was still being discussed, the security and welfare of the Lumad and Christian settlers was probed. There was fear among us that the proposals might antagonize the likes of us. First, it was assured...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Not enough funds for Bangsamoro block grant in proposed 2019 budget - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/209090-not-enough-funds-bangsamoro-block-grant-2019-budget</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBD8WD6O7-1dp6nRRdxKRYoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 04:43:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/209090-not-enough-funds-bangsamoro-block-grant-2019-budget" target="_blank"&gt;Not enough funds for Bangsamoro block grant in proposed 2019 budget&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – The Department of Budget and Management (DBM) on Wednesday, August 8, admitted there are not enough funds for the Bangsamoro block grant in the proposed 2019 budget. Upon the questioning of Senate Minority Leader Franklin Drilon, the DBM said the financial implications of the recently signed Bangsamoro Organic Law (BOL) have yet to be included in the proposed allocation for next year. Drilon pointed out that the law provides for an annual block grant, or a 5% share in the national internal revenue. This shall be automatically appropriated to the Bangsamoro region witho...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Bangsamoro law to be 'vaccine' vs terrorism - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/208966-bangsamoro-organic-law-vaccine-vs-terrorism</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDDq7cvWupXTXGxO28eXnXgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2018 10:38:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/208966-bangsamoro-organic-law-vaccine-vs-terrorism" target="_blank"&gt;Bangsamoro law to be 'vaccine' vs terrorism&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – President Rodrigo Duterte formally handed the Bangsamoro Organic Law (BOL) to Moro Islamic Liberation Front (MILF) chairman Al Haj Murad Ebrahim on Monday, August 6, marking a milestone in the group's efforts to bring peace to Mindanao. The landmark law was presented by Duterte to Murad during a ceremony in Malacañang, in the presence of Congress leaders and Cabinet members. The BOL is a significant step to stopping the spread of terrorism and extremist beliefs in Mindanao, a region that has been besieged with conflict, said Deputy Presidential Peace Process Adviser Na...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Duterte signs ID law, presents Bangsamoro law - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1756568/Manila/Local-News/Duterte-to-sign-Philippine-ID-System-Act</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDF71zt8s96rsksumB_fkSwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKmgnQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2018 07:05:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1756568/Manila/Local-News/Duterte-to-sign-Philippine-ID-System-Act" target="_blank"&gt;Duterte signs ID law, presents Bangsamoro law&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(UPDATED) - President Rodrigo Duterte signed the Philippine Identification System (PhilSys) Act and presented the new Bangsamoro law to Moro leaders in separate ceremonies on Monday afternoon, August 6. The Philippine Identification System (PhilSys) Act mandates the issuance of a single official identification card for all citizens and foreign residents that would serve as a de facto national identification number. The new law is expected to improve efficiency and transparency in public services as well as promote ease of doing business, Presidential Spokesperson Harry Roque Jr. said in a s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Ceremonial signing of Bangsamoro law set tomorrow - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/08/05/bangsamoro-organic-law-ceremonial-signing.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMgjkBbj_CYzj0Tf1Osd8OYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMJbthQM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Aug 2018 11:47:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/08/05/bangsamoro-organic-law-ceremonial-signing.html" target="_blank"&gt;Ceremonial signing of Bangsamoro law set tomorrow&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, August 5) — A ceremony for the signing of the Bangsamoro Organic Law (BOL) will be held tomorrow, August 6, at the Malacañang Palace. President Rodrigo Duterte, the first Philippine President who hails from the South, is set to lead the ceremonial signing. Members of the Moro Islamic Liberation Front (MILF) and the Bangsamoro Transition Commission are also expected to attend the historic event. The BOL, now officially called the Organic Law for the Bangsamoro Autonomous Region in Muslim Mindanao (OLBARMM), is the result of decades-long peace negotiations betwe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>Bangsamoro police to still under PNP - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1756246?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIZI4euDMizbK_UDkOPwm2sqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKeunQM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1756246?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;Bangsamoro police to still under PNP&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;UNDER the newly-signed Bangsamoro Organic Law (BOL), an official clarified that once it will be ratified, the defense force of the new Bangsamoro region will still be under the national government. Lawyer Jose Lorena Jr., Bangsamoro Transition Commission commissioner, during his session on Understanding the Bangsamoro Basic Law at a media forum yesterday at Linmarr Apartelle, said that there would be no separate policing for the new Bangsamoro. The police will still be under the Philippine National Police (PNP) and the soldiers will be from the Armed Forces of the Philippines. “The defense ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Comelec pegs Bangsamoro plebiscite for January 2019 - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/08/07/comelec-bangsamoro-plebiscite-january-2019.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBHCb1wv_9mJbdKWNnBI4i8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMJbthQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 05:17:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/08/07/comelec-bangsamoro-plebiscite-january-2019.html" target="_blank"&gt;Comelec pegs Bangsamoro plebiscite for January 2019&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, August 7) — The plebiscite determining the scope of the new Bangsamoro Autonomous Region in Muslim Mindanao could be held by January next year, the Commission on Elections (Comelec) said. "The December [or] January timeline would be more realistic at this point," Comelec spokesman James Jimenez told CNN Philippines. Comelec Commissioner Sheriff Abas pegged the same schedule on Monday. On the same day, the House Committee on Appropriations allotted a ₱854 million budget for polls in January 2019. The plebiscite will determine whether Cotabato City in Maguindana...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>Bangsamoro law ceremonial signing set for August 6 - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/208490-bangsamoro-organic-law-ceremonial-signing-august-6-2018</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMjF9jSt2LszhMxyNCuvcPAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 09:33:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/208490-bangsamoro-organic-law-ceremonial-signing-august-6-2018" target="_blank"&gt;Bangsamoro law ceremonial signing set for August 6&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – President Rodrigo Duterte wants to mark the passage of the historic Bangsamoro Organic Law with a ceremonial signing ceremony in early August. A ceremony for the BOL will be held on Monday, August 6, inside Malacañang, said Special Assistant to the President Bong Go on Monday, July 30. The signed BOL, Republic Act Number 11054, was released by Malacañang last Friday, July 27. But Duterte had said that though he had signed the BOL, he wanted to hold a ceremony to celebrate its passage. He said members of the Moro Islamic Liberation Front (MILF) and of the Bangsamoro Tra...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Palace: Duterte open to possible amendments for Bangsamoro law - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/07/30/Duterte-open-to-possible-amendments-for-Bangsamoro-law.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEDk4UCZ9BKYWJ7-uQ2liwUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMJbthQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 08:46:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/07/30/Duterte-open-to-possible-amendments-for-Bangsamoro-law.html" target="_blank"&gt;Palace: Duterte open to possible amendments for Bangsamoro law&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, July 30) — President Rodrigo Duterte is willing to talk about possible amendments for the Bangsamoro Organic Law, spokesperson Harry Roque said Monday during his press briefing. Roque said Duterte expressed openness in reviewing specific provisions, but reiterated that the enactment of the measure that will establish a new Bangsamoro Autonomous Region in Mindanao was not rushed. "It wasn't really rushed. It's been there, it's pending," Roque said of the Bangsamoro law. "Although you know, nothing is perfect. The BOL being signed into law is a result of a compr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>MILF starts consultations on Bangsamoro Organic Law - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/07/29/milf-consultations-bangsamoro-organic-law.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBSDXDAFVBkHE4qybJ5o9R0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMJbthQM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jul 2018 13:33:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/07/29/milf-consultations-bangsamoro-organic-law.html" target="_blank"&gt;MILF starts consultations on Bangsamoro Organic Law&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, July 29) — The Moro Islamic Liberation Front (MILF) has called on its supporters to meet about the Bangsamoro Organic Law (BOL). The rebel group had a consultative assembly on the BOL in its main base at Camp Darapanan, Sultan Kudarat on Sunday. The MILF hopes to seek the support of the people for a favorable referendum of the proposed Bangsamoro Government for the plebiscite that could be held either late December or early January next year. MILF Peace Panel Chair Mohagher Iqbal said 85 percent of the BOL is compliant to the original draft of the bill, which ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>Carvajal: Miracle of sorts - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1755726?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELleEEGlMYUWM8_cXG69eUsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJeunQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 16:06:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1755726?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;Carvajal: Miracle of sorts&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;I REFUSE to fret, with traditional political patrons and their wards, over a Gloria Arroyo House speakership. I’d much rather rejoice with those who appreciate the Bangsamoro Organic Law (BOL). Its passage is nothing short of a miracle and is of more positive consequence to our national life. It is a miracle of sorts that our traditional vested-interest-politician-legislators actually came up with an organic law that is acceptable to the Bangsamoro people. Yet, as it happened, the Moro Islamic Liberation Front (MILF), the leading group in the fight for Muslim autonomy, was jubilant over it....&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Bunye: The long road to peace and development - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1755393?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELs06l-zUns6bTd3flZF13EqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKmgnQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 03:38:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1755393?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;Bunye: The long road to peace and development&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;FINALLY, President Rodrigo Duterte signed into law last Thursday, July 26, the Bangsamoro Organic Law (BOL), which seeks to end the decades-old conflict in Mindanao through the establishment of a new framework for the island's governance and development. The original measure was first proposed in the 16th Congress, during the time of former President Benigno Aquino III, but got derailed by the Mamasapano Massacre in 2015. Following the bloody encounter, the public rejected the proposed law forcing Congress to momentarily shelve it. But thanks to the persistence of the current administration...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Duterte open to amendments to Bangsamoro law - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1755419?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM3gwyx-DF-JTAg7cbkxsIQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKmgnQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 08:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1755419?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;Duterte open to amendments to Bangsamoro law&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PRESIDENT Rodrigo Duterte has expressed willingness to review and propose amendments to the contentious provisions in the recently-signed Bangsamoro Organic Law (BOL) to make it acceptable to all Filipinos, Malacañang said on Monday, July 30. "You know, nothing is perfect. And of course, the BOL signed into law is a result of compromise. So all that the President was saying was, if you have specific complaints, we're open to discuss[ing] these complaints with a view of possibly amending further the law," Presidential Spokesperson Harry Roque Jr. told Palace reporters. "But I think the gener...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Duterte signs Bangsamoro Organic Law - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/207952-duterte-signs-bangsamoro-organic-law</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG_sqGoK5dHUUPzVmzrXwFsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 11:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/207952-duterte-signs-bangsamoro-organic-law" target="_blank"&gt;Duterte signs Bangsamoro Organic Law&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – President Rodrigo Duterte signed the landmark Bangsamoro Organic Law (BOL) on Thursday, July 26. "This is to announce that the President has just signed the BOL into law," said Presidential Spokesperson Harry Roque in a message to reporters on Thursday. The signing came 8 days after the bicameral conference committee (bicam) finalized the bill following days of heated discussions. Duterte had certified the bill as urgent, paving the way for the speedy passage of the measure in Congress. The Senate was the first to ratify the bicam report on the measure, ahead of Dutert...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Historic Autonomy Deal for Philippine Muslims Takes Aim at 50 Years of Strife - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/autonomy-philippine-muslims/4502200.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEsVfPEd_g4vdpwoBUnUekwqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2018 05:46:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/autonomy-philippine-muslims/4502200.html" target="_blank"&gt;Historic Autonomy Deal for Philippine Muslims Takes Aim at 50 Years of Strife&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A landmark local autonomy law passed this week in the Philippine capital, Manila, gives restive Muslim Filipinos a new sense of hope for resolving a half-century-old conflict over self-rule that has killed 120,000 people and attracted the terrorist group Islamic State. The Bangsamoro Organic Law received full congressional approval and the president’s signature in the Philippines this week. It follows up a peace deal signed with the most established separatist group, the Moro Islamic Liberation Front. The law will give state funding and local control of natural resources to a largely Muslim...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Lidasan: Thoughts and actions for the Bangsamoro - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1754506?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKQeeBPEa2qwas17UY7tkWIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKeunQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 15:10:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1754506?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;Lidasan: Thoughts and actions for the Bangsamoro&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MAHATMA Gandhi once said, “A man is but the product of his thoughts; What he thinks, he becomes”. I believe these words are powerful in addressing the problems of violent extremism in Mindanao. In our fight against violent extremism, we need to learn how the violent extremists think and act to advance their political agenda. The current Bangsamoro peace process tells us that the drivers for insurgency are almost always the same as the drivers of violent extremism. These drivers include feelings of being oppressed, a sense of victimhood, and the government not doing enough for their welfare....&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Duterte signs Bangsamoro law - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1754771?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFG1CkLTUnOROUPhm3oNTpsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKmgnQM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 10:55:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1754771?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;Duterte signs Bangsamoro law&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PRESIDENT Rodrigo Duterte has signed into law the Bangsamoro Organic Law, which seeks to create a new Bangsamoro region to replace the Autonomous Region in Muslim Mindanao (ARMM). "Signed na ang BBL," Duterte said Thursday, July 26, in a speech delivered in Ipil, Zamboanga Sibugay. (The BBL - Bangsamoro Basic Law - has been signed into law.) The bill was first known as BBL and later renamed to Bangsamoro Organic Law. But the President said he still needed to consult Nur Misuari, Moro National Liberation Front (MNLF) founder, to make sure the law is implemented by the end of the year. Presid...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Duterte Signs Law Giving More Autonomy to Muslims in Southern Philippines - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/07/26/world/asia/philippines-rodrigo-duterte-marawi.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGX5pR5lf625I092J6Rd9S0qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzwwt4QY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 15:23:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/07/26/world/asia/philippines-rodrigo-duterte-marawi.html" target="_blank"&gt;Duterte Signs Law Giving More Autonomy to Muslims in Southern Philippines&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The long-delayed legislation is expected to bring some measure of peace to a region that had been choked by four decades of separatist violence.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>Congress ratifies Bangsamoro Organic Law, up for Duterte signing - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/07/24/congress-bangsamoro-organic-law-ratified-president-rodrigo-duterte.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDeVcYslp9htYYg1x8NsVJMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMJbthQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 12:57:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/07/24/congress-bangsamoro-organic-law-ratified-president-rodrigo-duterte.html" target="_blank"&gt;Congress ratifies Bangsamoro Organic Law, up for Duterte signing&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, July 24) — Congress on Tuesday ratified the Bangsamoro Organic Law, which creates the Bangsamoro Autonomous Region in Muslim Mindanao. With both Houses of Congress having ratified the Organic Law for the Bangsamoro Autonomous Region in Muslim Mindanao (OLBARMM), President Rodrigo Duterte can already sign it into law. This comes after the House of Representatives failed to ratify the bill before the SONA due to the political power-play that led to the change in leadership. The Senate had ratified the proposed law earlier. Presidential Spokesperson Harry Roque ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>Duterte to Abu Sayyaf: 'Let's talk' - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/208358-duterte-abu-sayyaf-lets-talk</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB2EeFbIk2ZW47uAUzpHUa8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2018 01:24:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/208358-duterte-abu-sayyaf-lets-talk" target="_blank"&gt;Duterte to Abu Sayyaf: 'Let's talk'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – President Rodrigo Duterte said on Friday, July 27, that he wants to dialogue with terrorist group Abu Sayyaf to bring an end to bloodshed in Mindanao. "Mag-usap na lang. Iyong Abu Sayyaf, mag-usap na lang tayo. Ano bang gawain natin? Magpatayan tayong lahat (Let's talk. The Abu Sayyaf, let's just talk. What do we do? Just kill each other)?" Duterte said in a speech in Jolo, Sulu, where the Abu Sayyaf operates from. It was not the first time for the President to express his openness to a dialogue with the Abu Sayyaf. Days before he formally assumed the presidency in 201...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Duterte to sign Bangsamoro Organic Law within 48 hours - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/07/23/duterte-sona-2018-bangsamoro-organic-law-senate-house-of-representatives.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECgcHoOUgxDdRrQKWIXLiu4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMJbthQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2018 11:12:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/07/23/duterte-sona-2018-bangsamoro-organic-law-senate-house-of-representatives.html" target="_blank"&gt;Duterte to sign Bangsamoro Organic Law within 48 hours&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, July 23) — President Rodrigo Duterte committed to signing the Bangsamoro Organic Law within two days during his third State of the Nation Address on Monday. "When the approved version was transmitted and received by my office, the law has been passed and I intend to… Give me 48 hours to sign it and ratify the law," Duterte said. Duterte also said in jest that he still needs to read the final version approved by the congressional bicameral conference committee as there might be unfavorable provisions added. The President's pronouncement was met with applause fr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>Lawmakers OK common bill on Bangsamoro organic law - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/07/18/Bangsamoro-Basic-Law-Rodrigo-Duterte-Bangsamoro-Oragnic-Law-BBL.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK_dX6BERpR2-1nRnSD5chcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMJbthQM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jul 2018 03:26:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/07/18/Bangsamoro-Basic-Law-Rodrigo-Duterte-Bangsamoro-Oragnic-Law-BBL.html" target="_blank"&gt;Lawmakers OK common bill on Bangsamoro organic law&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, July 18) — Lawmakers tasked to iron out provisions of the proposed Bangsamoro Basic Law have approved a common version Wednesday ahead of its possible enactment on July 23 when President Rodrigo Duterte delivers his the State of the Nation Address. The bill is called Organic Law for the Bangsamoro Autonomous Region in Muslim Mindanao (OLBARMM). The 28-member bicameral conference committee approved it on the sixth day of its marathon deliberations that began on July 9. The committee reconciled Senate Bill 1717 and House Bill 6475. "We approve the bicameral conf...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>After one-day delay, House ratifies Bangsamoro law - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/208082-house-representatives-ratification-bangsamoro-organic-law</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOGz7B7lDeeEBd_PEwPf1DgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 08:25:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/208082-house-representatives-ratification-bangsamoro-organic-law" target="_blank"&gt;After one-day delay, House ratifies Bangsamoro law&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – The House of Representatives finally ratified the bicameral conference committee (bicam) report on the Bangsamoro Organic Law (BOL). Speaker Gloria Macapagal Arroyo made good on her promise for the lower chamber to ratify the BOL during the session on Tuesday, July 24. This was a process that should have happened on Monday, July 23, but got delayed after the ouster of Davao del Norte 1st District Representative Pantaleon Alvarez as House Speaker, and Arroyo's subsequent election. Critics have slammed the takeover in the House, as the power play among lawmakers delayed ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item></channel></rss>