<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Child custody - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIggKIhxDQkFTRHdvSkwyMHZNRGgyZUcxaUVnSmxiaWdBUAE?hl=en-PH&amp;gl=PH&amp;ceid=PH:en</link><language>en-PH</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 11:03:50 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Brad Pitt, Angelina Jolie reach child custody agreement - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/entertainment/news/218055-brad-pitt-angelina-jolie-child-custody-agreement</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB0TDUq6d6QCx1iM3klPD34qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMI7omQI</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 13:04:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/entertainment/news/218055-brad-pitt-angelina-jolie-child-custody-agreement" target="_blank"&gt;Brad Pitt, Angelina Jolie reach child custody agreement&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jolie's lawyer Samantha Bley DeJean says a custody arrangement has been agreed upon, which was signed by both parties.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Angelina Jolie, Brad Pitt reach child custody agreement - lawyer - ABS-CBN News</title><link>https://news.abs-cbn.com/entertainment/12/01/18/angelina-jolie-brad-pitt-reach-child-custody-agreement-lawyer</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMibWh0dHBzOi8vbmV3cy5hYnMtY2JuLmNvbS9lbnRlcnRhaW5tZW50LzEyLzAxLzE4L2FuZ2VsaW5hLWpvbGllLWJyYWQtcGl0dC1yZWFjaC1jaGlsZC1jdXN0b2R5LWFncmVlbWVudC1sYXd5ZXLSAQA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 22:57:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://news.abs-cbn.com/entertainment/12/01/18/angelina-jolie-brad-pitt-reach-child-custody-agreement-lawyer" target="_blank"&gt;Angelina Jolie, Brad Pitt reach child custody agreement - lawyer&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABS-CBN News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;LOS ANGELES - Divorcing Hollywood power couple Angelina Jolie and Brad Pitt have reached a final agreement over the custody of their 6 children, Jolie's ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://news.abs-cbn.com">ABS-CBN News</source></item><item><title>Family separations at border down, but dozens still affected - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/dcb05d02726e4d4c9b6de2a31944ba81</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKqocS-K-A1PjIBkQTbgLeAqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwv7tQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 18:01:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/dcb05d02726e4d4c9b6de2a31944ba81" target="_blank"&gt;Family separations at border down, but dozens still affected&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Trump administration separated 81 migrant children from their families at the U.S.-Mexico border since the June executive order that stopped the general practice amid a crackdown on illegal crossings, according to government data obtained by The Associated Press. Despite the order and a federal judge's later ruling, immigration officials are allowed to separate a child from a parent in certain cases — serious criminal charges against a parent, concerns over the health and welfare of a child or medical concerns. Those caveats were in place before the zero-tolerance poli...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Lumad kids 'rescued' in Talaingod back with parents – DSWD - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/218160-lumad-kids-rescued-talaingod-davao-del-norte-back-with-parents</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJcn61blWxkz6NLCYsXGiPYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 06:39:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/218160-lumad-kids-rescued-talaingod-davao-del-norte-back-with-parents" target="_blank"&gt;Lumad kids 'rescued' in Talaingod back with parents – DSWD&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – The Department of Social Welfare and Development (DSWD) said on Friday, December 7, that 12 of the 14 minors found traveling with the group of former Bayan Muna representative Satur Ocampo in Talaingod, Davao del Norte, have returned to their families. The DSWD returned the children to their parents on Wednesday, December 5, after Davao Regional Trial Court Branch 8 Presiding Judge Glenn Aquino ordered it. Aquino said in his decision that the DSWD had “no authority or lawful basis to retain the children in its custody, let alone, to deprive the petitioners, who are the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>For N.Y.’s Foster Children, Running Away Can Lead to Handcuffs - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/12/06/nyregion/foster-children-arrest-warrants-nyc.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGmZoHpOzkpFwe4O-VDZVlUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzwwloIY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 01:05:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/12/06/nyregion/foster-children-arrest-warrants-nyc.html" target="_blank"&gt;For N.Y.’s Foster Children, Running Away Can Lead to Handcuffs&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;[What you need to know to start the day: Get New York Today in your inbox.] Nevayah still remembers the feel of the handcuffs. They were foreign to her; she had never been in trouble. A latecomer to New York City’s foster care system, Nevayah had been signed over to the Administration for Children’s Services when she was 16. Rather than enter a group home, she told her caseworker she would prefer to live with her mother in Ohio. Eager to start school, she bought a bus ticket, made it to Cleveland and phoned the agency to let them know that she was safe. Per protocol, A.C.S. said, they would...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>81 children separated from families at US-Mexico border since June, government data shows - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-07/trump-government-separates-81-migrant-children-from-families/10592152</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC3RAuy2W1sUFOeHyWJE0LUqFwgEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDD7kIkG</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 13:08:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-07/trump-government-separates-81-migrant-children-from-families/10592152" target="_blank"&gt;81 children separated from families at US-Mexico border since June, government data shows&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Trump administration has separated 81 migrant children from their families at the United States-Mexico border since an executive order sought to end the practice in June, according to government data. Key points: - Since June 21, 76 adults were separated from the children, according to the data - It showed 51 of those adults were criminally prosecuted - At its height, more than 2,400 children were separated from their guardians Despite the order and a federal judge's later ruling, immigration officials are allowed to separate a child from a parent in certain cases — serious criminal cha...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Nocppo welcomes raps vs 3 Sagay cops - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1777476</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHQPlYYmeHhjf5rrlT1u4PoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMPetnQM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 08:11:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1777476" target="_blank"&gt;Nocppo welcomes raps vs 3 Sagay cops&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE Negros Occidental Police Provincial Office (Nocppo) is ready to answer the charges filed by the minor-witness on the “Sagay 9” incident, through his mother, against the three cops assigned in Sagay for allegedly coercing him to testify on the incident. Senior Superintendent Rodolfo Castil Jr., director of Nocppo, said on Wednesday, November 5, that they’ve been expecting the camp of the minor, through the assistance of the National Union of Peoples’ Lawyers (NUPL), to press charges against the policemen. “Expected naman na din yun. Karapatan din naman nila yun” (It was expected. It’s al...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Getting Past the Barriers: When a Mother Is in Prison - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/12/06/well/family/getting-past-the-barriers-when-a-mother-is-in-prison.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKRexTD8A6_u2_nwcMKB0xoqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzwwxqlf</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 10:00:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/12/06/well/family/getting-past-the-barriers-when-a-mother-is-in-prison.html" target="_blank"&gt;Getting Past the Barriers: When a Mother Is in Prison&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;When Courtney Saunders was sentenced to two and a half years in prison for drug possession, everything in her life seemed to be falling apart. But perhaps the most agonizing aspect was that she would be separated from her daughters, then 4 and 2. “Visits in jail took place behind plexiglass windows, no physical contact,” said Ms. Saunders. “I worried this would traumatize my daughters if they saw me like that. If we were given the chance to have a more child-friendly visit, that would have meant so much to the mothers there — it would have helped us hold onto some hope,” she said. After ser...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>Raps filed vs Sagay minor-survivor’s pa, cops - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1777290</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDjlOtM5RZSoyUxHTala4i8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMPetnQM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 05:25:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1777290" target="_blank"&gt;Raps filed vs Sagay minor-survivor’s pa, cops&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE father of the minor who witnessed the bloody massacre in Sagay City, Negros Occidental, and three policemen from Sagay City Police Station are facing charges before the Department of Justice (DOJ) on Tuesday, December 4, for allegedly forcing the minor to testify on the “Sagay 9” incident which happened on October 20. Lawyer Katherine Panguban of the National Union of Peoples’ Lawyers (NUPL), in a phone interview with SunStar Bacolod on Tuesday, said the mother of the minor filed a complaint for violation of Republic Act 9262 or the Anti-Violence Against Women and Children Act against V...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Deported Parents Make Last-Ditch Effort To Reunite With Separated Kids In U.S. - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/deported-immigrant-parents-children_us_5bf5990ce4b0771fb6b54847</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENlZVz9gTiTMm3SNM9dkz7wqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMOGXAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 01:38:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/deported-immigrant-parents-children_us_5bf5990ce4b0771fb6b54847" target="_blank"&gt;Deported Parents Make Last-Ditch Effort To Reunite With Separated Kids In U.S.&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A number of the roughly 400 parents who were separated from their kids under the Trump administration’s zero tolerance policy and deported back to Central America want the U.S. government’s permission to cross the border once again. On Monday, the American Civil Liberties Union sent the Department of Justice the first batch of declarations from 12 parents who claim they were denied a fair chance at applying for asylum. Advocates say that in many instances, returning to the U.S. is the only way deported parents and their children, who have now been separated for up to six months, can see eac...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Brad Pitt and Angelina Jolie reach custody agreement over their children - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/12/01/brad-pitt-angelina-jolie-reach-custody-agreement-children/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA8gV6N07nwdNitIUsKWZH8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 03:16:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/12/01/brad-pitt-angelina-jolie-reach-custody-agreement-children/" target="_blank"&gt;Brad Pitt and Angelina Jolie reach custody agreement over their children&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Divorcing Hollywood power couple Angelina Jolie and Brad Pitt have reached a final agreement over the custody of their six children, Jolie's lawyer said on Friday, after more than two years of often bitter negotiations. "A custody arrangement was agreed to weeks ago, and has been signed by both parties and the judge," Jolie's lawyer Samantha Bley DeJean said in a statement to Reuters. "The agreement, which is based on the recommendations of the child custody evaluator, eliminates the need for a trial. The filing and details of the agreement are confidential to protect the best interests of ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Child prisons are beyond reform - it's time to stop jailing young people - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2018/dec/03/child-prisons-beyond-reform-stop-jailing-young-people</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIaYihZ9SXu6PuXxN5xtbkwqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 09:08:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/2018/dec/03/child-prisons-beyond-reform-stop-jailing-young-people" target="_blank"&gt;Child prisons are beyond reform - it's time to stop jailing young people&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jake Hardy was 17 years old when he hanged himself in prison in 2012. Minutes before, CCTV cameras captured other children crowded around his cell goading him to kill himself, while prison officers watched. Like so many imprisoned children, Jake had special educational needs and mental health difficulties. Jake’s mother, Liz, spoke at the recent launch of a new campaign – run by Article 39, the Centre for Crime and Justice Studies, the Howard League for Penal Reform, Inquest and the National Association for Youth Justice – pressing for the closure of England’s child prisons. Most of the 861...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Fate of New Mexico man who killed 5 as a teen revisited - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/5f02cb136b8b4e74a6f3a65e27b2c933</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJM__3HX8peyLvtFMCRJivwqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvKadAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 17:10:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/5f02cb136b8b4e74a6f3a65e27b2c933" target="_blank"&gt;Fate of New Mexico man who killed 5 as a teen revisited&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ALBUQUERQUE, N.M. (AP) — A New Mexico man who killed five family members as a teen is set to return to court Monday for a weeklong hearing to determine whether he has been rehabilitated while in state custody. It is the second such hearing for 21-year-old Nehemiah Griego, who three years ago pleaded guilty to second-degree murder and child abuse resulting in death in the shootings of his parents and three siblings at the family's home south of Albuquerque. The details of the 2013 shootings stunned New Mexico's largest city, in part because of the number of fatalities, the chilling details o...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Judge in family separation case turns attention to database flaws - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/30/politics/separated-families-case-hearing/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEwwCIdqeTcfjpes1Ib_IuQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMJrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 00:27:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/30/politics/separated-families-case-hearing/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Judge in family separation case turns attention to database flaws&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The federal judge in California who ordered the US government to reunite separated immigrant families is now turning his attention toward what he calls a "root cause" of the problem he's spent months trying to help solve. When US District Judge Dana Sabraw first ordered reunifications of thousands of parents and children in June, he slammed the government for not having an effective system for tracking children after officials had separated them from their parents. "The unfortunate reality is that under the present system migrant children are not accounted for with the same efficiency and a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Who pays for the stepchildren in a blended family? - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/who-pays-for-the-stepchildren-in-a-blended-family-2018-11-02</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL9LoDHb9l7x8AZ6opAzUEsqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwiJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 02:35:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/who-pays-for-the-stepchildren-in-a-blended-family-2018-11-02" target="_blank"&gt;Who pays for the stepchildren in a blended family?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;LOVE &amp;AMP; MONEY By Alessandra Malito Parents face myriad financial conundrums when they’re part of a blended family Navigating two families doesn’t usually come with a simple resolution and a laugh track. Courtesy Everett Collection Love &amp; Money is a new MarketWatch series looking at how money issues impact our relationships with significant others, friends and family. Bobbi Rebell and her husband are both in their second marriages — and that creates a myriad of emotional and financial complications. When they married more than 10 years ago, her husband had a 6-year-old and 9-year-old with...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Taiwanese reject legalizing same-sex unions in referendum - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/a34cf44ef92949d8b31d84090f64c6ad</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHdyOSmPuYbyHMXDBgYs_JcqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2018 15:57:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/a34cf44ef92949d8b31d84090f64c6ad" target="_blank"&gt;Taiwanese reject legalizing same-sex unions in referendum&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;TAIPEI, Taiwan (AP) — Voters in Taiwan passed a referendum asking that marriage be restricted to one man and one woman, a setback to LGBT couples hoping their island will be the first place in Asia to let same-sex couples share child custody and insurance benefits. The vote on Saturday, organized by Christian groups that make up about 5 percent of Taiwan's population and advocates of the traditional Chinese family structure, goes against a May 2017 Constitutional Court ruling. Justices told legislators then to make same-sex marriage legal within two years, a first for Asia, where religion a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>A girl at mom’s, a boy at dad’s: ‘Transgender’ Texas child caught in custody battle - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/usa/445172-transgender-child-mom-court/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGq_4bFz2ngL3e8lASQ6ngMqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww7oMo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 18:15:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/usa/445172-transgender-child-mom-court/" target="_blank"&gt;A girl at mom’s, a boy at dad’s: ‘Transgender’ Texas child caught in custody battle&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In Texas, a six-year-old boy is being torn apart by the transgender debate. James’ mother thinks he’s a girl, but he acts like a normal boy at his father’s house. Now she’s accusing him of child abuse. Welcome to 2018. Divorce is tough on children, but especially so for six-year-old James Younger. When he’s with his father, Jeff Younger, James is a normal boy. He dresses like a boy, hangs out with other boys, and refers to himself as a boy. When he’s with his mother, Anne Georgulas, James lives as a girl called Luna. Since he expressed an interest in wearing girls’ clothes, Georgulas a pedi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Her rapist was offered the chance to see her child, victim claims - CNN</title><link>https://edition.cnn.com/2018/11/28/uk/rotherham-child-rape-scli-gbr-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOvF2z9kpW51N6nYDOxAyvgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 16:20:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://edition.cnn.com/2018/11/28/uk/rotherham-child-rape-scli-gbr-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Her rapist was offered the chance to see her child, victim claims&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A child sex abuse victim is alleging her jailed rapist was offered the chance to see her son, who was born as a result of the attack. Sammy Woodhouse, who has waived her legal right to anonymity in a bid to help other victims, released a video on Tuesday calling for the British government to change the law after a local council in the English city of Rotherham offered her rapist the option to apply "parental rights" over her son, she alleges. Woodhouse was attacked when she was a teen. "This story is actually about myself, about my son, and about the man that raped me," she said in the vide...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://edition.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Concerns raised about 'traumatized' immigrant children still in custody - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/29/politics/separated-families-reunification-update/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ1k1UpzRuPU_v80ZFupqYQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 02:43:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/29/politics/separated-families-reunification-update/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Concerns raised about 'traumatized' immigrant children still in custody&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Advocates for immigrant families that were separated by the US government said Thursday they're concerned about a group of children who've remained in custody for months even though their parents had designated sponsors to take them in. In a filing in a California federal court Thursday evening, attorneys from the American Civil Liberties Union said there are up to 59 children in this situation. In these cases, parents who'd been deported without their kids told officials they didn't want their children to be repatriated and designated sponsors to care for them in the United States. "We are...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>A former judge spent time in prison for attacking his wife years ago. Now he's a suspect in her death - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/21/us/ohio-judge-ex-wife-killed/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH8aOWL2OzhcX62KoICh2FEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMIrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 00:34:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/21/us/ohio-judge-ex-wife-killed/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;A former judge spent time in prison for attacking his wife years ago. Now he's a suspect in her death&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lance Mason wrote a letter of apology to his ex-wife, Aisha Fraser, in April 2016 from an Ohio prison. He was serving time for domestic violence and felonious assault for hitting Fraser and smashing her face into a car dashboard while their two daughters were in the back seat. Mason, a former trial court judge, offered contrition for the "harm and pain" he caused their family. He pointed out all he had done to try to make amends, including counseling, prayer and accepting the court's punishment "without complaint." "You entrusted me with your safety and the safety of our daughters. I violat...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Record numbers of migrant children are in US custody, hoping they won't be forgotten - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/30/politics/record-numbers-migrant-children-us-custody/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENsztOrfcObdfTSZff2ZOs8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 11:00:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/30/politics/record-numbers-migrant-children-us-custody/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Record numbers of migrant children are in US custody, hoping they won't be forgotten&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Juan has been detained in an unaccompanied child shelter for nearly a year, long enough to see the emotional impact prolonged confinement has on children. "They get depressed. They cut their skin," he told CNN by phone from inside a Texas detention center. Juan is not his real name. His attorney asked CNN to change his name for his safety. The 16-year-old says he fled his native El Salvador after being threatened by gangs. During this past year, four sponsors have tried taking him out of detention; but all of them have been rejected by the government, he says. A sponsor is a parent, family ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Record 14,000 unaccompanied immigrant children in US custody, HHS confirms - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/23/politics/hhs-record-14000-immigrant-children-us-custody/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL6jUWeOcj7w1AIrDvIlL5UqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2018 16:00:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/23/politics/hhs-record-14000-immigrant-children-us-custody/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Record 14,000 unaccompanied immigrant children in US custody, HHS confirms&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A record number of unaccompanied immigrant children, about 14,000, are currently in US custody, a Health and Human Services spokesman said Friday. The spokesman, Mark Weber, said the additional requirements put in place by the Trump administration to "reduce risk and increase safety" for immigrant children contributed to the high number. "We are taking all possible steps to protect children in an environment with many bad actors," Weber said. "We are balancing speed with safety and will err on the side of safety." The San Francisco Chronicle and Houston Chronicle earlier reported the figure...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Some families split up at border still detained months later - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/41fd6fa7635b4fd19baea7aebc1d251f</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJOZFcJQMophhHVkAXQedroqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvKadAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 22:29:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/41fd6fa7635b4fd19baea7aebc1d251f" target="_blank"&gt;Some families split up at border still detained months later&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PHOENIX (AP) — Half a dozen families who were separated at the U.S.-Mexico border are still detained in Texas months after reuniting with their children. Immigrant advocates say the government has violated a longstanding legal agreement that bars it from detaining children past 20 days in unlicensed facilities like the South Texas Family Residential Center. The detention center in Dilley, Texas, had been holding about 40 families for four months following the court-ordered reunifications. About 30 of the families were just released last week. "We are still suffering because they don't want ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>A Guatemalan Mother Could Lose Her Daughter, Because She’s an American - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/23/us/migrant-family-separation-citizen-domestic-abuse.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHzRuNuPe8GIxE4_1Sguz_oqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzwwt4QY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 20:28:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/23/us/migrant-family-separation-citizen-domestic-abuse.html" target="_blank"&gt;A Guatemalan Mother Could Lose Her Daughter, Because She’s an American&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Correction: November 23, 2018 This article has been revised to reflect the following correction: An earlier version of this article misstated the age of Vilma Carrillo. She is 38, not 28. Vilma Carrillo was one of a group of migrant women flown to Texas in July from a detention center in Georgia to be reunited with their children, who had been separated from them as part of the Trump administration’s clampdown at the border. Over the next several days, she watched as immigration officials paged one mother after another and took them to meet their children. “I was never called,” Ms. Carrillo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>The Price Tag of Migrant Family Separation: $80 Million and Rising - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/20/us/family-separation-migrant-children.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM5_nPrnfHBWBvGLAVR8QfQqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzwwt4QY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 01:12:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/20/us/family-separation-migrant-children.html" target="_blank"&gt;The Price Tag of Migrant Family Separation: $80 Million and Rising&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The federal government has spent $80 million to care for and reunite migrant children who were separated from their parents by immigration authorities, a figure that continues to grow months after the policy ended because more than 140 children are still in custody. The first official price tag on family separations — which ended abruptly in June in the face of widespread public opposition — comes to about $30,000 per child. That data, along with new details on the children who remain mired in the policy’s lingering effects, were handed over last week by the Health and Human Services Depart...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>Child at centre of Ohio family massacre is safe, family of suspected killers set to face trial - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-15/ohio-mass-killing-child-is-safe-in-custody-family-says/10500542</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENTnTU790JHb5w_bAd64N-UqFwgEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDD7kIkG</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 05:06:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-15/ohio-mass-killing-child-is-safe-in-custody-family-says/10500542" target="_blank"&gt;Child at centre of Ohio family massacre is safe, family of suspected killers set to face trial&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A child at the centre of a custody dispute that may have set off a gruesome Ohio massacre is safe in state custody, her great-grandfather said. Key points: - One Ohio family is facing trial for executing another over custody of a child, who is safe - The investigation is one of the most complicated and extensive in Ohio history - One alleged murderer was also charged with unlawful sexual conduct with a minor Leonard Manley, whose daughter and grandchildren were among the eight people killed in 2016, told The Cincinnati Enquirer the four-year-old girl was in state custody. One of the suspect...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Child at center of Ohio mass killing is safe, family says - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/bc49da22e85e43eda9136d9114589c24</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDjkeTijLHKMwCdLeB8rDIMqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwu4lR</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 22:04:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/bc49da22e85e43eda9136d9114589c24" target="_blank"&gt;Child at center of Ohio mass killing is safe, family says&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;COLUMBUS, Ohio (AP) — A child at the center of a custody dispute that may have set off a gruesome Ohio massacre is safe in state custody, her great-grandfather said Wednesday, before one of the four suspects in the killings appeared in court. Leonard Manley, whose daughter and grandchildren were among the eight people killed in 2016, told The Cincinnati Enquirer the 4-year-old girl is in state custody. One of the suspects, Edward "Jake" Wagner, was the long-time former boyfriend of 19-year-old Hanna Rhoden, one of the victims, and shared custody of their daughter at the time of the massacre...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Record high of 14,000 immigrant children in US custody as potential carers ‘deterred by fears of retribution’ - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/us-politics/record-high-immigrant-children-us-government-custody-ice-background-checks-a8638771.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHgki9Oxz1wHPUIaMR_I6G8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 13:59:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/us-politics/record-high-immigrant-children-us-government-custody-ice-background-checks-a8638771.html" target="_blank"&gt;Record high of 14,000 immigrant children in US custody as potential carers ‘deterred by fears of retribution’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A record number of children from overseas are in US government custody as Donald Trump's administration continues to enforce hardline immigration policies. More than 14,000 unaccompanied migrant children were being held in detention facilities this week, the Department of Health and Human Services (HHS) said. The figure tops a record set two months ago. The rise, first reported by the San Francisco Chronicle, is thought to be largely due to increased background checks on adults who come forward to take children into care. Read more - Inside the tent city housing migrant children in the Texa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>County braces for long, pricey court case in family massacre - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/6ed052bd1f9845438360db0e90be6c2f</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEhCotts6JMI_RCV2096k88qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwu4lR</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 21:37:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/6ed052bd1f9845438360db0e90be6c2f" target="_blank"&gt;County braces for long, pricey court case in family massacre&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;CINCINNATI (AP) — Two women who are the mothers of two suspects in the massacre of a family, and the grandmothers of the other two, pleaded not guilty Thursday to misleading investigators of the crime, which went without any arrests for more than two years. Authorities, meanwhile, braced for a long, complex and expensive court case that has already taken a financial toll on the small, rural Ohio county where eight members of the Rhoden family — seven adults and a teenage boy — were found shot in the head in April 2016. Fredericka Wagner, 76, and Rita Newcomb, 65, face felony charges of obst...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Rhoden Family Massacre: Custody Battle Led to Murder of Entire Ohio Family, Cops Say - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/rhoden-family-massacre-rival-clan-arrested-in-murder-of-entire-ohio-family</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPjYpksRJQoWA7uEy_8PxlcqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMPGMAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 19:56:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/rhoden-family-massacre-rival-clan-arrested-in-murder-of-entire-ohio-family" target="_blank"&gt;Rhoden Family Massacre: Custody Battle Led to Murder of Entire Ohio Family, Cops Say&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;via Ohio AG Mike DeWine/Twitter Ohio police have finally nabbed four people in the shocking 2016 murders of a family that was running a massive marijuana operation when they died. The state’s attorney general, Mike DeWine, announced the busts on Tuesday, in connection to a crime that appears to stem from a custody battle between two families. “This is just the most bizarre story I’ve ever seen in being involved in law enforcement,” DeWine said at a press conference on Tuesday, adding that the defendants had an “obsession” with custody and controlling children connected to the victims. In Ap...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Authorities: Custody dispute played role in family's slaying - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/f2ce7334381f486099f5026cb09e7742</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAEzIRoDFJQZf4a36PQ9zdYqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwu4lR</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 03:31:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/f2ce7334381f486099f5026cb09e7742" target="_blank"&gt;Authorities: Custody dispute played role in family's slaying&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WAVERLY, Ohio (AP) — Authorities arrested a family of four Tuesday in the gruesome 2016 slayings of eight people from another family in rural Ohio, a crime that prosecutors suggested stemmed from a custody dispute. The announcement marked the culmination of a massive investigative effort that began after seven adults and a teenage boy were found shot in the head at four separate homes in April 2016. The killings terrified local residents and spawned rumors that it was a drug hit. Ohio Attorney General Mike DeWine said a grand jury indicted the four on aggravated murder charges and they coul...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Divorce and child custody: Men cry foul - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/05/us/divorce-child-custody-tips-lisa-ling-this-is-life/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP8-xkxS7kZLQFBbFMb_CpkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMIrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 19:13:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/05/us/divorce-child-custody-tips-lisa-ling-this-is-life/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Divorce and child custody: Men cry foul&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Watch "This Is Life with Lisa Ling" Sunday at 10 p.m. ET. Mothers often complain about getting the short end of the stick in divorce cases involving child custody, but so do many fathers. For parents who are trying to juggle shared custody, child support payments and their careers — finding the right life-balance can seem impossible. Sometimes disagreements escalate into messy legal battles that require judges, attorneys and therapists to step in and help. In her CNN Original Series, "This is Life," Lisa Ling spoke with fathers who feel the system has let them down. One is a divorced father...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Judge in family separations case: 'We're approaching the end of reunification' - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/09/politics/separated-families-hearing/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELiFg1ToG_Ew4B1qcqGW9XEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 23:48:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/09/politics/separated-families-hearing/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Judge in family separations case: 'We're approaching the end of reunification'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The reunification process for undocumented immigrant families the US government separated at the southern border is nearly finished, a federal judge said Friday. "It's heading clearly in the right direction and I think we're approaching the end of reunification, and by all accounts, it's moving very successfully," US District Judge Dana Sabraw said in a telephone status hearing more than four months after he had ordered the government to reunite most of the families. The painstaking process -- spurred by an American Civil Liberties Union class action lawsuit over family separations -- has s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Angelina Jolie and Brad Pitt going to trial in custody case - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/06/entertainment/brad-pitt-angelina-jolie/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAriHCc7AfvZ3wPdi24PBowqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMNHPpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 15:33:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/06/entertainment/brad-pitt-angelina-jolie/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Angelina Jolie and Brad Pitt going to trial in custody case&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This is Life with Lisa Ling" explores divorced fathers and child custody issues Sunday at 10 p.m. ET. Angelina Jolie and Brad Pitt are taking their fight for custody of their children to court. A trial is set to begin on December 4, according to court documents obtained by CNN. Jolie and Pitt separated in September 2016 after two years of marriage and filed for divorce shortly after. The pair have six children together, ranging from ages 10 to 17. How did Brad Pitt and Angelina Jolie end up here? The former couple's quest to find a mutually agreeable custody arrangement has been long and, ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Mother who allegedly went on the run with kids charged with child stealing - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-05/mother-charged-with-child-stealing-afp-investigating-syndicate/10463810</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO92l0wYaShWI9m1XaNlbg8qFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 19:53:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-05/mother-charged-with-child-stealing-afp-investigating-syndicate/10463810" target="_blank"&gt;Mother who allegedly went on the run with kids charged with child stealing&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Kristian Silva A Townsville mother who allegedly went on the run with her young daughters is the latest to be charged by Australian Federal Police (AFP) officers investigating a syndicate that has allegedly smuggled women and children around the country. Seven people with connections to the alleged group have now been charged, with police claiming the network helped mothers commit child abductions in breach of court-ordered custody arrangements. Three women charged late last week had "active roles" in the abduction of three children, the AFP said. "Police will allege these people provide...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Judges speak out about Family Court funding - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-10-31/judges-go-public-family-court-shouldnt-be-making-do/10450514</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOSGKoNNxuJgcua1v-a3MoUqFwgEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDD6kIkG</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 03:50:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-10-31/judges-go-public-family-court-shouldnt-be-making-do/10450514" target="_blank"&gt;Judges speak out about Family Court funding&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some of Australia's most senior current and former judges are going public, calling out a severe lack of government funding for the Family Court system. They say this means families, particularly children, are suffering because they are subject to court delays and costs. They are calling for change and believe the court should become the last resort for resolving family and property disputes. Bringing it out from behind closed doors Divorce and custody battles can take years to resolve in court. Brooke (not her real name) told AM the law and the court system suffered from "paralysis" when i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Paedophile taken to hospital after being sentenced over 'vile, shocking' crimes - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-10-25/paedophile-andrew-philips-taken-to-hospital-after-sentencing/10428030</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENsB1AR2s5WxFdFywzQgkHAqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 05:15:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-10-25/paedophile-andrew-philips-taken-to-hospital-after-sentencing/10428030" target="_blank"&gt;Paedophile taken to hospital after being sentenced over 'vile, shocking' crimes&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By court reporter Rebecca Opie A paedophile has been wheeled out of the court room and taken to hospital after being sentenced to 14 years in prison over seven child sex offences. Andrew Thomas Philips, 53, pleaded guilty in the Adelaide District Court to committing seven child sex offences over the past three years, including gross indecency and maintaining an unlawful sexual relationship with a child. The offending was against three boys in separate incidents. During the sentencing, Judge Geraldine Davison had to stop several times as Philips coughed, heaved and was removed from the dock ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Report: Chaos and confusion after 'zero tolerance' policy on immigration - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/24/politics/government-accountability-office-family-separations-report/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGelWzBtDn2PiIKeTS_61RMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 12:19:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/24/politics/government-accountability-office-family-separations-report/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Report: Chaos and confusion after 'zero tolerance' policy on immigration&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A report from the US Government Accountability Office released Wednesday describes chaos and confusion among federal agencies this past summer over efforts to reunify undocumented children separated from their parents at the US-Mexico border. According to the report, officials at the department of Homeland Security and Health and Human Services "did not plan for the potential increase in the number of children separated from their parent or legal guardian as a result of the Attorney General's (Jeff Sessions) April 2018 'zero tolerance' memo." A similar report from the DHS Inspector General ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Report: Agencies blindsided by Trump immigration order - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/70a8db79cf4441739650480f2181de14</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIbPKcMEhZZpz3Cbw1IK4wwqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwu4lR</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 14:38:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/70a8db79cf4441739650480f2181de14" target="_blank"&gt;Report: Agencies blindsided by Trump immigration order&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Federal immigration and health officials were blindsided by President Donald Trump's "zero tolerance" policy on migrants crossing the southwest border, triggering a cascade of problems as agencies struggled with the fallout from family separations, congressional investigators said in a critical report issued Wednesday. The investigation by the nonpartisan Government Accountability Office dissects the consequences of launching a major policy change without consulting with the agencies that have to carry it out. The report makes no recommendations as it reconstructs a turbul...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Hundreds of migrant children held in U.S. tent city for months: filings - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-immigration-tentcity/hundreds-of-migrant-children-held-in-us-tent-city-for-months-filings-idUSKCN1MX02F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEALq-zZZZbTNylBmeWI3I9EqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 11:41:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-immigration-tentcity/hundreds-of-migrant-children-held-in-us-tent-city-for-months-filings-idUSKCN1MX02F" target="_blank"&gt;Hundreds of migrant children held in U.S. tent city for months: filings&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.S. authorities have held some immigrant children who entered the country illegally and without a parent in a temporary "tent city" in Texas for months, violating a 20-year-old court order on how long minors can be detained, according to court filings by civil rights lawyers and immigration advocates. More than 500 children have been housed in tents near Tornillo, Texas since August, and 46 have been held there since June, according to a Friday court filing in Los Angeles federal court by civil rights organizations and advocacy groups representing migrant children. The filing opposes a gov...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Foreign parents fight in vain for custody in Japan - ABS CBN News</title><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKVSjiHoKVucGDgrHDE5TJUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow8IjwCjDw4s8CMLf4ngM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 01:31:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABS CBN News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This handout self-portrait photograph taken on August 26, 2018 shows French Emmanuel de Fournas posing next to his child's doll at the playground of Benjasiri park in Bangkok, where he used to take his child to play. Emmanuel de Fournas, Agence France-Presse TOKYO - Emmanuel, Stephane, Henrik and James come from very different backgrounds, but they share the same painful experience of battling Japan's legal system -- in vain -- for access to their children after divorce. Once married to Japanese women, they say they were prevented from contact with their children when their relationships di...&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>More than 200 children from separated immigrant families remain in US custody - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/15/politics/separated-families-reunification-update-undocumented-immigrant/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF4eXuN6oF9NgRTVqu4gG-YqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 02:17:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/15/politics/separated-families-reunification-update-undocumented-immigrant/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;More than 200 children from separated immigrant families remain in US custody&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;More than 200 children from separated undocumented immigrant families remain in US custody, officials said in a court filing Monday night. Most of the 245 children in custody have parents who were removed from the United States -- 175 children, according to the latest government tally. Of those, only 18 children are currently in the pipeline to reunite with their parents in their countries of origin, according to court documents. Deported parents of 125 kids in custody have said they don't want their children to be returned to the countries of origin. And there are 32 children in government...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Former general says UK-US military cooperation under threat - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/1eb95a9a345548778a0e84116ef637fe</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN7ZtslBhzhO214v5PVNnHQqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 09:44:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/1eb95a9a345548778a0e84116ef637fe" target="_blank"&gt;Former general says UK-US military cooperation under threat&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;LONDON (AP) — The former commander of American forces in Iraq and Afghanistan warned Friday that the United States' military cooperation with the U.K. could be threatened by the growing use of human rights laws to target British soldiers. Writing in the Times of London, retired Gen. David Petraeus says the European Court of Human Rights is increasingly extending domestic human rights legislation to the battlefield. This has led to British soldiers being charged with human rights abuses — sometimes decades after the events in question. "The current 'fog of law' may undermine the operational ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Prosecutors: Father helped daughter in murder-suicide plot - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/62e6e6dc82864ade926237672b308db8</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELJQZsecM58JSP5pAd5PR9QqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvKadAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 19:55:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/62e6e6dc82864ade926237672b308db8" target="_blank"&gt;Prosecutors: Father helped daughter in murder-suicide plot&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KANSAS CITY, Mo. (AP) — A former Missouri jail guard persuaded her terminally ill father to fatally shoot her estranged husband to resolve a custody dispute and then kill himself so it appeared to be a murder-suicide, authorities allege. Elizabeth Kilgore, 35, of Quincy, pleaded not guilty last week to first-degree murder in the death of Lance Kilgore. No attorney is listed for her in online court records. She is jailed without bond. A Missouri State Highway Patrol sergeant wrote in charging documents that 77-year-old Charles Sander killed his son-in-law and himself in September. The shooti...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>‘Most cruel of cruelties’: father and son separated under Trump policy to be reunited - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/oct/15/judge-orders-reunification-father-and-son-separated-under-trump-policy</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENU1W9A8JS91rFfQMrU9uF4qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCtvxU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 21:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/oct/15/judge-orders-reunification-father-and-son-separated-under-trump-policy" target="_blank"&gt;‘Most cruel of cruelties’: father and son separated under Trump policy to be reunited&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A federal judge has ordered the immediate reunification of an asylum-seeking father and his two-year old son, who have been separated for nearly six months under Donald Trump’s family separation policy. Related: US government accused of 'devastating damage' to families separated at border “It’s the most cruel of all cruelties to separate a child from his father when there is no basis,” said New York southern district judge Alvin Hellerstein at a hearing on Monday afternoon. The father, known as Mr C, was released from detention last week after crossing the border around 30 April. His son, w...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Border Patrol Agents Arrest 16,658 Family Members in September Alone - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/border-patrol-agents-arrest-16658-family-members-in-september-alone</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFSJTmM-BDkGVUQxc21Ha0kqFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMLXUiQY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 19:11:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/border-patrol-agents-arrest-16658-family-members-in-september-alone" target="_blank"&gt;Border Patrol Agents Arrest 16,658 Family Members in September Alone&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mario Tama/Getty, Border Patrol agents reportedly arrested 16,658 family members along the U.S. border in September, the highest one-month total on record, The Washington Post reports. Groups of over 100 children and adults from Central America have been crossing the border to turn themselves in, citing “a fear of return.” The newspaper notes that families are typically assigned a court date and then released from custody. Figures from the Department of Homeland Security also reportedly show that 107,212 family members were taken into custody and 396,579 arrests were made along the border i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Report: White House Seeks New Approach on Family Separations at Border - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/report-white-house-seeks-new-approach-on-family-separations-at-border/4612071.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIDsSKmO-65pcnwa_HZoMhMqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2018 12:14:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/report-white-house-seeks-new-approach-on-family-separations-at-border/4612071.html" target="_blank"&gt;Report: White House Seeks New Approach on Family Separations at Border&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A report in The Washington Post says the Trump administration is "actively considering plans that could again separate parents and children at the U.S.-Mexico border," but would add options to previous approaches. Citing anonymous sources, the report says the plans are under consideration because of the "soaring numbers of families" trying to enter the U.S. from Mexico. One plan, the sources say, would allow the government to confine asylum-seeking families for up to 20 days and then give them two choices. One choice would have parents remaining in government detention with their children a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>ICE Is Sending Separated Children Home With No One To Pick Them Up - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/ice-separated-children-central-america_us_5bc0b8bae4b0bd9ed559a75c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECBkPzWj5VyUS6GD3P3-anUqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 17:46:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/ice-separated-children-central-america_us_5bc0b8bae4b0bd9ed559a75c" target="_blank"&gt;ICE Is Sending Separated Children Home With No One To Pick Them Up&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;On Tuesday, U.S. Immigration and Customs Enforcement sent a 4-year-old separated child from the U.S. to Guatemala City without telling her family she was coming home. When Karla, a pseudonym HuffPost is using to protect the child’s identity, arrived in Guatemala, no one came to pick her up at a reunification center near the airport. Instead of reuniting with her deported father, whom she hadn’t seen since they crossed the U.S. border together six months ago, the child spent yet another night in a government-run shelter, according to Kids In Need of Defense, an organization helping the U.S. ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>ICE ending practice of coordinating release plans for undocumented families in Arizona - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/10/politics/ice-post-release-plan/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOYvfONPmFk2LGZiab_eUcwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMJrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 03:00:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/10/politics/ice-post-release-plan/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;ICE ending practice of coordinating release plans for undocumented families in Arizona&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Immigration and Customs Enforcement has ended its practice of coordinating plans for undocumented immigrant families, including asylum-seekers, in Arizona that are released from custody but still awaiting a court hearing on their request. Department of Homeland Security Secretary Kirstjen Nielsen, who oversees ICE, told senators Wednesday that the "vast" increase in families crossing the border has put strain on the department's resources. She acknowledged the change in Arizona, saying that when DHS can't keep families in a facility "long enough to have that conversation" the department tri...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>ICE put a 4-year-old on a plane to Guatemala. Her dad found out 30 minutes before she landed - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/11/us/ice-separated-families/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOcCSFdC6OBNGdTZxb_jbl8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMIrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 13:09:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/11/us/ice-separated-families/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;ICE put a 4-year-old on a plane to Guatemala. Her dad found out 30 minutes before she landed&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Six months after US officials separated them at the border, ICE put a 4-year-old girl on a plane to Guatemala this week so she could be reunited with her father. But there was one major problem, according to advocates who worked on the case: The man didn't learn his daughter was coming until 30 minutes before her flight was set to land in Guatemala City. He lives eight hours away -- too far to get there in time. After half a year apart from her father, the girl would have to spend another night in a shelter alone. The case sparked fury and frustration this week from advocates working to hel...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>UN urges Venezuela to probe opposition politician's death - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/d1ef4f6c6a2c4aaf9d990b1002a8f5d8</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG8OnGZBgmgRy-n2CJu8RIsqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2018 15:10:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/d1ef4f6c6a2c4aaf9d990b1002a8f5d8" target="_blank"&gt;UN urges Venezuela to probe opposition politician's death&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;CARACAS, Venezuela (AP) — The United Nations on Tuesday urged Venezuelan officials to perform an independent and transparent investigation into the death of an opposition councilman jailed by Venezuela's intelligence police on allegations that he plotted to kill President Nicolas Maduro. Venezuelan officials said that Fernando Alban killed himself by leaping from the 10th floor of the state police agency's headquarters. But opposition leaders denied the official version. Ravina Shamdasani with the Office of United Nations High Commissioner for Human Rights in Geneva said the UN's Human Righ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Mitt Romney: Family separations at border a 'dark chapter in American history' - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/09/politics/mitt-romney-family-separations/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIEfEKUDz9jGvcigsusR22MqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMJrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 02:44:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/09/politics/mitt-romney-family-separations/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Mitt Romney: Family separations at border a 'dark chapter in American history'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the Utah Senate debate Tuesday night, GOP candidate Mitt Romney called family separations at the border "a dark chapter in American history," and said that "this is inexcusable, and can't go on." "This was a heartbreak," Romney said at the debate, in response to a question about immigrant family separation. "This was a dark chapter in American history, to see children separated from their parents." "This is inexcusable, and can't go on," the Senate candidate said. Romney faces off in November against Democratic opponent Jenny Wilson, a member of the Salt Lake County Commission. In May, t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Malubog shooting survivor in sanctuary - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1767978</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECXQP-h2LRAygw693TUfVqsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJeunQM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2018 16:08:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1767978" target="_blank"&gt;Malubog shooting survivor in sanctuary&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ONE of the survivors of the shooting incident in Barangay Malubog, a mountain barangay of Cebu City, was discharged from the Cebu City Medical Center (CCMC) yesterday. Sharmaine Poran was released from the hospital around 7:30 p.m., and was brought to a sanctuary where she will stay until a case is filed against those responsible for the incident. Poran is under the custody of the Commission on Human Rights (CHR) 7 after her family requested the commission to secure her. Aside from Poran, CHR 7 chief investigator Leo Villarino said they will also take custody of habal-habal driver Antonio R...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>There’s love, you’ll say, but is there any real point in getting married these days? - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/oct/06/theres-love-youll-say-but-is-there-any-point-in-getting-married-these-days</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC13g7y_byHmqGlBm6gvHKEqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTC9vBU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2018 16:00:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/oct/06/theres-love-youll-say-but-is-there-any-point-in-getting-married-these-days" target="_blank"&gt;There’s love, you’ll say, but is there any real point in getting married these days?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Imagine the biggest financial contract you’ll enter into. What comes to mind? Your mortgage? Student debt? Think again. For many of us, the heftiest, not to mention the most open-ended, financial commitment we will make is marriage. The marriage contract isn’t quite “what’s mine is yours”, but almost. Once you’ve married someone, you have legal financial obligations to them even after it’s over and even if there are no children involved. Yet the vast majority of us don’t take even cursory legal advice before saying “I do”. Forgive me if that sounds cynical. But I’m in my mid-30s and having ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Justin Bieber, Hailey Baldwin And Premarital Agreements - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/legalentertainment/2018/10/04/justin-bieber-hailey-baldwin-and-pre-marital-agreements/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELHnlsiXTgQMPz81LB3QB0kqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2018 17:37:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/legalentertainment/2018/10/04/justin-bieber-hailey-baldwin-and-pre-marital-agreements/" target="_blank"&gt;Justin Bieber, Hailey Baldwin And Premarital Agreements&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photo by: KGC-182/STAR MAX/IPx 2018 Justin Bieber and Hailey Baldwin out and about in London. The trades are writing about Justin Bieber and Hailey Baldwin’s supposed decision to marry without a Pre-Martial Agreement. I will discuss, in the most general terms, the circumstances where Pre-Marital Agreements should be considered before parties enter into a marriage contract. It is common for parties to enter into Pre-Marital Agreements to deal with present and future property rights and rights to spousal support. Often, I am consulted and asked if a Pre-Marital Agreement is necessary. And, if...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Sheriff: Veteran Ambushed Officers Coming to Question Adult Son - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/sheriff-veteran-ambushed-officers-coming-to-question-adult-son/4602296.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKstgLD6WpJYvG3z98bV2AAqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2018 01:32:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/sheriff-veteran-ambushed-officers-coming-to-question-adult-son/4602296.html" target="_blank"&gt;Sheriff: Veteran Ambushed Officers Coming to Question Adult Son&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The decorated 74-year-old Vietnam War veteran accused of shooting seven South Carolina law enforcement officers had set an ambush for investigators coming to question his adult son about a child sexual assault, the sheriff investigating the case said Friday. Frederick Hopkins was charged with murder and six counts of attempted murder Friday, Richland County Sheriff Leon Lott said. Hopkins had been in the hospital since he was taken into custody after the Wednesday afternoon shooting, but was to be taken to jail Friday, Lott said. Florence County investigators called Hopkins’ home and arrang...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Mom of slain Filipina in Sweden seeks custody of grandchildren - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/213519-mother-of-mailyn-conde-sinambong-seeks-custody-grandchildren</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJUN4UWb6fE6ZQkZ2WNTRF8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2018 09:18:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/213519-mother-of-mailyn-conde-sinambong-seeks-custody-grandchildren" target="_blank"&gt;Mom of slain Filipina in Sweden seeks custody of grandchildren&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – The mother of the Filipina slain recently in Sweden, 28-year-old Mailyn Conde Sinambong, is now seeking custody of her grandchildren, said the Philippine Department of Foreign Affairs (DFA). Sinambong died on September 23 after she was allegedly beaten to death by her husband, 50-year-old Swedish actor-director Steve Abou Bakr Aalam. The suspect is now in the custody of authorities and is facing a murder case. Sinambong's mother, Maria Monato, is based in Cebu. Philippine Consul General to Oslo Maria Elena Algabre said that the Philippine embassy will "hire a lawyer to...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Under Trump, juveniles are 'offenders' and aren't 'healthy and educated' - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/oct/04/trump-administration-juvenile-justice-websites</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFsY-Ev2t5NsgnaBAykKrXcqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCtvxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2018 09:00:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/oct/04/trump-administration-juvenile-justice-websites" target="_blank"&gt;Under Trump, juveniles are 'offenders' and aren't 'healthy and educated'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Trump administration has surreptitiously altered federal government websites dealing with juvenile justice to remove the ambition that American children should be “healthy and educated”. The change was among a raft of revisions quietly imposed on public information websites by a little-known agency of the justice department known as the Office of Juvenile Justice and Delinquency Prevention (OJJDP). It advises states and local communities on how to treat minors in trouble with the law. Under the agency’s old vision statement, the office expressed a desire for America to be “a nation wher...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>An Infant Is Dead, Her Twin Is Injured, and Their Mother Is in Police Custody - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/10/04/nyregion/queens-baby-dead.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFE12VarrDXsimk7h2WArzcqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzwwt4QY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2018 22:58:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/10/04/nyregion/queens-baby-dead.html" target="_blank"&gt;An Infant Is Dead, Her Twin Is Injured, and Their Mother Is in Police Custody&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A 30-year-old woman, who had an order of protection against her estranged husband, was in police custody after her toddler daughter was found dead.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>California divorce courts go to dogs as pets gain status - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/7e14e2d2506d4d8e8488f40e8d747440</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDqHnDRvP9siCtBuUcxPbq8qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvKadAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2018 01:05:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/7e14e2d2506d4d8e8488f40e8d747440" target="_blank"&gt;California divorce courts go to dogs as pets gain status&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — California courts could be going to the dogs — and maybe cats, too — under a new law granting judges authority to settle disagreements over who keeps the family pet in divorce cases the same way they handle child-custody disputes. Until now, Fido and Kitty have been considered family property, a status giving them little more standing in a divorce than a family's big-screen TV. Under a bill signed Thursday by Gov. Jerry Brown, pets will still be considered community property but a judge deciding who gets to keep them will have the discretion of weighing such factors as wh...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>New Trump Rules Keep Immigrant Kids Locked Up Longer. This Pregnant Mom Is Terrified. - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/trump-immigrant-children-locked-up_us_5bb3d26be4b028e1fe38a8e8</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFV5l-8WByChRpcYR8h338MqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMOGXAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 22:59:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/trump-immigrant-children-locked-up_us_5bb3d26be4b028e1fe38a8e8" target="_blank"&gt;New Trump Rules Keep Immigrant Kids Locked Up Longer. This Pregnant Mom Is Terrified.&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thousands of undocumented children ― even ones with parents or other adults eager to take them in ― are languishing in U.S. government custody for increasingly long periods thanks to new background check and fingerprint screening requirements implemented by the Trump administration. Despite a decline in border crossings over the past few years, the Trump administration is holding more undocumented children (a record 12,800, five times more than last year) for longer periods (an average of 59 days, up from the 35-day average in the final year of the Obama administration). The Trump administr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Rights Group Says Egypt 'Forcibly Disappeared' Lawyer - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/rights-group-says-egypt-forcibly-disappeared-lawyer/4597750.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGrLcDuOztrkLajiG2KlS2QqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw6pwi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 12:45:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/rights-group-says-egypt-forcibly-disappeared-lawyer/4597750.html" target="_blank"&gt;Rights Group Says Egypt 'Forcibly Disappeared' Lawyer&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;An international rights group on Wednesday urged Egypt to reveal the whereabouts of a well-known human rights lawyer who went missing after being detained. An Egyptian court ordered the release of Ezzat Ghoneim and another lawyer, Azzoz Mahgoub, on Sept. 4, pending investigations, but the two have not been seen or heard from since Sept. 13. Egyptian police have “forcibly disappeared” Ghoneim, who has been held since March on charges of plotting against the government, Human Rights Watch said in a statement. The New York-based watchdog quoted Ghoneim’s wife, Rasha, as saying that she last sa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>'I wouldn't wish it even on my worst enemy': Reunited immigrant moms write letters from detention - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/09/30/politics/separated-mothers-reunited-letters/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAsALp5bpNsa2TlcD91ioOsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMJrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2018 09:14:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/09/30/politics/separated-mothers-reunited-letters/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;'I wouldn't wish it even on my worst enemy': Reunited immigrant moms write letters from detention&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The women say they were treated like dogs and told that their children would be given up for adoption. They lied awake at night, wondering if their kids were safe. But even after being reunited with their children, they say their nightmare has not ended. Their anguish is conveyed in a collection of letters written from one of the few immigrant family detention centers in the country, where some moms and children who were separated at the border this summer are now being held together while they await their fate. The mothers' writings reflect a mix of despair, bewilderment and hope as they r...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Migrant Children Describe Tent City As 'Punishment,' Experts Say - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/migrant-children-say-being-in-texas-tent-city-is-punishment_us_5bb2a902e4b00fe9f4f9ab0f</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKqt8XjLvhKUnITsZxH33-kqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 04:27:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/migrant-children-say-being-in-texas-tent-city-is-punishment_us_5bb2a902e4b00fe9f4f9ab0f" target="_blank"&gt;Migrant Children Describe Tent City As 'Punishment,' Experts Say&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over the past two weeks, hundreds of migrant children have been sent to a tent city in Tornillo, Texas, according to The New York Times, in what experts are calling a humanitarian crisis of the U.S. government’s own making. Although the Office of Refugee Resettlement (ORR) claims the tent camp is a necessary response to filled shelters, experts say that overcrowding is a result of the Trump administration’s recent decision to more thoroughly scrutinize potential sponsors of immigrant children. And that has caused children to languish in conditions that harm their physical and mental health....&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Trump Administration Quietly Moves 1,600 Migrant Children To Texas Tent City: Report - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/tornillo-tent-city-migrant-children_us_5bb1fcc6e4b0c7575966ff2e</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJA2AdvhrPugd0jNR5f8-GAqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 12:11:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/tornillo-tent-city-migrant-children_us_5bb1fcc6e4b0c7575966ff2e" target="_blank"&gt;Trump Administration Quietly Moves 1,600 Migrant Children To Texas Tent City: Report&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;More than 1,600 migrant children in U.S. custody have quietly been relocated in recent weeks from private foster homes and shelters to a barren tent city in the Texas desert, The New York Times reported on Sunday. Most of the children were moved “under the cover of darkness” and with almost no prior warning, according to the paper. They were roused from sleep in the middle of the night so they would be “less likely to try to run away” and loaded onto buses bound for the sprawling tent city in Tornillo, a border town in El Paso County. Hundreds of migrant kids are being shipped each week to ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Migrant Children Moved Under Cover of Darkness to a Texas Tent City - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/09/30/us/migrant-children-tent-city-texas.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMJd1KqtAyYf-gIBdttzbnsqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzwwqIQY</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2018 09:00:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/09/30/us/migrant-children-tent-city-texas.html" target="_blank"&gt;Migrant Children Moved Under Cover of Darkness to a Texas Tent City&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The federal government has been moving hundreds of children a week under cover of darkness to a tent city on the Mexican border in West Texas.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>Lack of prep plagued Trump's child separation border policy: watchdog - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-immigration-separations/lack-of-prep-plagued-trumps-child-separation-border-policy-watchdog-idUSKCN1MC2B6</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEb6HXrF6YWUbnq9Evs8PK0qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMMT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 18:36:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-immigration-separations/lack-of-prep-plagued-trumps-child-separation-border-policy-watchdog-idUSKCN1MC2B6" target="_blank"&gt;Lack of prep plagued Trump's child separation border policy: watchdog&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Trump administration's "zero tolerance" immigration crackdown at the U.S.-Mexico border earlier this year was plagued by a lack of preparation, resource shortfalls and communication failures, according to a government audit released on Tuesday. The review, conducted by the Department of Homeland Security's Inspector General, is the first official audit of President Donald Trump's policy of separating migrant families at the U.S.-Mexico border, criminally prosecuting parents and sending their children to shelters and foster homes across the country. Trump administration officials have sa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>How To Handle Money With Your Ex After Divorce - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/handle-money-with-an-ex-after-divorce_us_5ba8fa93e4b0181540df2a97</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI-W_UCzRJPggIEgGgOGZQ8qFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 18:11:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/handle-money-with-an-ex-after-divorce_us_5ba8fa93e4b0181540df2a97" target="_blank"&gt;How To Handle Money With Your Ex After Divorce&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Disagreements about money can put stress on a marriage — something I learned the hard way. As my ex and I went through our divorce, though, we managed to solve our problems and come up with an amicable solution that left us both satisfied, focusing on the wellbeing of our son and giving us both a solid new start. However, even with custody and child support figured out, as well as issues like who’d pay for my son’s travel to visit his dad and whose health insurance plan our son would be covered by, we were surprised to discover that new money issues came up. We hadn’t planned for everything...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Do Migrant Teenagers Have Abortion Rights? Two Volatile Issues Collide in Court - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/09/29/us/politics/court-abortion-immigrants.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHt8ldxruoGYuHDN-vS5ZfAqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzwwt4QY</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2018 13:20:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/09/29/us/politics/court-abortion-immigrants.html" target="_blank"&gt;Do Migrant Teenagers Have Abortion Rights? Two Volatile Issues Collide in Court&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Trump administration says it has broad authority to block abortions for young undocumented immigrants in federal custody, because they can return to their home countries at any time.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>Jason Miller, Former Trump Aide Leaves CNN After Ex Claims He Gave Woman ‘Abortion Pill’ - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/jason-miller-leaves-cnn-child-custody_us_5ba6e8f4e4b0375f8f9da26d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIxE2zLjXH4j0D46-bFjUTIqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2018 05:17:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/jason-miller-leaves-cnn-child-custody_us_5ba6e8f4e4b0375f8f9da26d" target="_blank"&gt;Jason Miller, Former Trump Aide Leaves CNN After Ex Claims He Gave Woman ‘Abortion Pill’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jason Miller, a former senior adviser to Donald Trump’s presidential campaign, is leaving his post as a political commentator for CNN after reports surfaced that a woman is claiming he dosed her with an abortion pill without her consent. The woman’s accusation was included in a new court filing linked to a child custody battle between Miller and his former lover A.J. Delgado, who also worked on Trump’s campaign, according to a Splinter News report published Friday. Miller, who denied the accusation, announced his departure from CNN in a statement he shared on Twitter. “I have decided to ste...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item></channel></rss>