<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Emmanuel Piñol - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqKAgKIiJDQkFTRXdvTkwyY3ZNVEZpZW5sdU1YUTRNUklDWlc0b0FBUAE?hl=en-PH&amp;gl=PH&amp;ceid=PH:en</link><language>en-PH</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 13:30:49 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Philippines, Papua New Guinea ink deal on agriculture cooperation - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/216916-philippine-papua-new-guinea-deal-agriculture-cooperation</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPA82xlilj4IavLX0FXIqW0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/216916-philippine-papua-new-guinea-deal-agriculture-cooperation" target="_blank"&gt;Philippines, Papua New Guinea ink deal on agriculture cooperation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Philippine Agriculture Secretary Emmanuel Piñol says Filipino farmers will be sent to Papua New Guinea to plant rice.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Duterte asks PCA execs to file courtesy resignation - ABS CBN News</title><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAIKxyn9ernTF3h5gYzmx0AqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow8IjwCjDw4s8CMNj9mQI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 02:09:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABS CBN News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA - President Rodrigo Duterte is asking the board members of the Philippine Coconut Authority (PCA) to file their courtesy resignations, Agriculture Secretary Emmanuel Piñol said Wednesday. Piñol said it was him who suggested to the President to seek the courtesy resignation of the officials. Piñol said the courtesy resignation was sought in preparation for the expected reorganization of the PCA under the proposed Coco Levy Act. “It was I who suggested to give [the filing of courtesy resignation] to give PRRD a free hand in selecting new officials,” Piñol said. “They will work until su...&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>To tame inflation, agriculture must improve – economic managers - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/business/218251-economic-managers-say-agriculture-must-improve-to-tame-inflation</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGGGzBpblg9HOYWz-PIrY-8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMP_mmQI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 04:59:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/business/218251-economic-managers-say-agriculture-must-improve-to-tame-inflation" target="_blank"&gt;To tame inflation, agriculture must improve – economic managers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – The government's economic team welcomed the slowdown of the inflation rate in November, but renewed calls for the Department of Agriculture (DA) to improve the state of farming and fisheries in the country. In a joint statement, the National Economic and Development Authority, the Department of Budget and Management, and the Department of Finance said inflation eased to 6% in November due to the improvement in the supply of key agricultural goods such as rice, fish, meat, and vegetables. They also said that President Rodrigo Duterte's Administrative Order No. 13, whic...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Pangilinan to NFA: Budget deliberations to be deferred until 'malpractices' are addressed - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/11/27/pangilinan-nfa-budget.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM3DNHQJbktUcmmb8x_K4yoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMJbthQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 02:10:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/11/27/pangilinan-nfa-budget.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pangilinan to NFA: Budget deliberations to be deferred until 'malpractices' are addressed&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, November 27) — Senator Kiko Pangilinan said he will put deliberations on the National Food Authority's (NFA) 2019 budget on hold until the alleged corruption that led to the spikes in prices of goods is addressed. Pangilinan requested Agriculture Secretary Manny Piñol to submit a detailed report on the council's "malpractices" by Friday. Until then, the speedy deliberations on their budget would have to wait. The NFA proposed a ₱7 billion budget for next year. "Let us inform Secretary [Manny] Piñol that we will raise this in plenary. We can speed up the [budge...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>Benguet, Mt. Province mayors to visit Israel - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1775373</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMPyp_Zcwx9a8TkI8yL8LbEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMLignQM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 14:03:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1775373" target="_blank"&gt;Benguet, Mt. Province mayors to visit Israel&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;LOCAL chief executives of Benguet and Mt. Province were invited by Agriculture Secretary Emmanuel Piñol for field visit to Israel to observe and study their agricultural technologies. Andrew Villacorta, assistant secretary designate for agribusiness and field operations, asked Department of the Interior and Local Government Secretary Eduardo Año in a letter for travel authority for 14 local chief executives of Benguet and Mt. Province. Some chief executives of both provinces signified their intention to join the visit slated for November 25 to December 1. Mayor Romeo Salda of La Trinidad, B...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>13th organic farmers festival underscores greening Negros - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1776216</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA90IgQFzjUI2dHirJtXeewqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMPetnQM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 05:04:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1776216" target="_blank"&gt;13th organic farmers festival underscores greening Negros&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE 13th Negros Island Organic Farmers Festival (Nioff), underscores the push for a green island to further promote the organic agriculture industry in Negros Occidental. The Nioff kicks off on Wednesday, November 28. Provincial Agriculturist Japhet Masculino said on Tuesday, November 27, that as the province continues its bid to “green” the island, there is a need to further maximize its potential in further developing the local organic agriculture industry. Masculino said that Negros Occidental alone hosts at least 17,000 organic practitioners with about 16,000 hectares devoted to organic...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>NFA strictly monitors rice SRP compliance in NegOcc - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1773967</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPU4bWOzdec1FvqPBGsu1DIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMPetnQM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 05:03:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1773967" target="_blank"&gt;NFA strictly monitors rice SRP compliance in NegOcc&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE National Food Authority (NFA) in Negros Occidental is strictly monitoring the compliance on the just-implemented suggested retail prices (SRPs) for rice among retailers in the province, its top official said. Frisco Canoy, provincial manager of NFA-Negros Occidental, on Tuesday, November 13, told SunStar Bacolod that the SRPs for milled rice actually took effect on November 11. This is 15 days after the implementing guidelines were published in a newspaper of general circulation on October 26. On Friday, November 9, NFA-Negros Occidental already met and briefed some local retailers on t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>NFA-Negros Occidental: SRPs for rice 'flexible' - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1774108</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIk-LKj_08sRRp8ZFqPRIpoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMPetnQM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 03:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1774108" target="_blank"&gt;NFA-Negros Occidental: SRPs for rice 'flexible'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE National Food Authority (NFA) in Negros Occidental said the just-implemented suggested retail prices (SRPs) for rice are "flexible" thus, adjustments can be made depending on prevailing factors. Frisco Canoy, provincial manager of NFA-Negros Occidental, said that a monthly basis evaluation might be conducted given that SRPs are not fixed. Canoy said the Department of Agriculture (DA) through Secretary Emmanuel Piñol, who is also the chairman of the NFA Council, may eventually issue new SRPs for rice. "It is flexible, thus, it may change depending on the prevailing situation in the marke...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Tell it to SunStar: Faulty party-list setup - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1773921/Cebu/Opinion/Tell-it-to-SunStar-Faulty-party-list-setup?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIrjbtqOOlFch7_KyDGezWIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMMu4nAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 16:19:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1773921/Cebu/Opinion/Tell-it-to-SunStar-Faulty-party-list-setup?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;Tell it to SunStar: Faulty party-list setup&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THERE are party-list groups whose nominees are government officials, including those believed to be supportive of the President despite their controversial removal from public office. The first nominee of Pambansang Nagkakaisa sa Paggawa at Agrikultura is Socrates Piñol, Provincial Board member of North Cotabato and brother of Agriculture Secretary Emmanuel Piñol. The first and third nominees of Gawing Una Tagumpay ng Ordinaryong Mamamayan are worth noting. The first nominee, Rex Anthony Villegas, is a former Board member of Nayong Filipino who was fired due to a complaint by another Board ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Agricultural damage from Typhoon Rosita hits P1.85 billion - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/business/215896-typhoon-rosita-agricultural-damage-november-3-2018</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDX-hBfTqIgrB7-8OCjmad4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMP_mmQI</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 06:25:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/business/215896-typhoon-rosita-agricultural-damage-november-3-2018" target="_blank"&gt;Agricultural damage from Typhoon Rosita hits P1.85 billion&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – Typhoon Rosita (Yutu) resulted in at least P1.85 billion in agricultural damage, said the Department of Agriculture's Disaster Risk Reduction and Management Operations Center (DA-DRRMOC) on Saturday, November 3. Agricultural goods lost to the typhoon was estimated at 98,870 metric tons and covered 93,209 hectares in Northern Luzon. A total of P1.41 billion worth of rice was damaged, mostly coming from Isabela and Cagayan. Meanwhile, a total of P48.57 million worth of corn was affected, with Isabela and Nueva Vizcaya taking most of the hit. A total of 19,213 farmers and...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>NFA: No SRPs for rice in province yet - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1772484/Bacolod/Business/NFA-No-SRPs-for-rice-in-province-yet?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFu1JokTnYBiqkRZxdRwhFgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMPetnQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 03:20:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1772484/Bacolod/Business/NFA-No-SRPs-for-rice-in-province-yet?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;NFA: No SRPs for rice in province yet&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE National Food Authority (NFA) in Negros Occidental has yet to receive the memorandum from the Department of Agriculture (DA) before it can start implementing the suggested retail prices (SRPs) for rice in the province, its top official said Sunday, November 4. Frisco Canoy, provincial manager of NFA-Negros Occidental, said that there is no communication yet from the agency as to the effectivity of rice SRPs in the province, which was earlier announced by Agriculture Secretary Emmanuel Piñol to start Monday, November 5. “Aside from the effectivity, the memorandum will also contain the ne...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Prescribed labeling, SRP for rice launched - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1771808</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENpJAyKug19QMmuuTHrDlB4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMIeunQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 14:33:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1771808" target="_blank"&gt;Prescribed labeling, SRP for rice launched&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;DEPARTMENT of Trade and Industry (DTI) Secretary Ramon Lopez, Department of Agriculture (DA) Secretary Emmanuel Piñol, and the National Food Authority (NFA) Deputy Administrator Tomas Escarez joined forces in launching the prescribed labeling and suggested retail price (SRP) for milled rice on 27 October 2018 at Commonwealth Market in Quezon City. There are four classification of milled rice – regular milled, well milled, premium grade, and special rice – which will be sold following the mandated SRPs except for special rice that covers organic, Cordillera heirloom, and other indigenous var...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Rice, sugar SRPs to take effect in NegOcc soon - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1771235</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHF1E0jUWLin46gLLTbbflAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMPetnQM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Oct 2018 08:04:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1771235" target="_blank"&gt;Rice, sugar SRPs to take effect in NegOcc soon&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PRICES of rice in the local markets are seen to further drop as suggested retail prices (SRPs) for the commodity will take effect in Negros Occidental starting November 5 this year. This was announced by Agriculture Secretary Emmanuel Piñol, also the chairman of the National Food Authority (NFA) Council, who was in the province on Friday, October 26, to visit the wake of the victims of "Sagay 9" massacre in Sagay City. Piñol, in an interview at RU Foundry in Bacolod City, said they are finalizing the guidelines for the implementation of SRPs for rice in Bacolod City and Negros Occidental. H...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Piñol amenable to transfer NFA office - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1771227</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEj57YL4XaN1Fgz-idoNXaYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMPetnQM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Oct 2018 06:32:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1771227" target="_blank"&gt;Piñol amenable to transfer NFA office&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;AGRICULTURE Secretary Emmanuel Piñol is amenable to the offer of the provincial government of Negros Occidental to move the National Food Authority (NFA) office in Barangay Tabunan, Bago City. The site is beside the Rice Processing Complex. "I visited the area along with Provincial Agriculturist Japhet Masculino and our NFA manager Frisco Canoy. I found the place very good. In fact, I am personally looking at establishing a silo (series of silos). If the NFA Council would approve it, and I think they would, the provincial government has agreed to construct a building for the NFA in the area...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>DA may supplement rice stocks in NegOcc through ‘Bigasan ng Bayan’ - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1771456</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPzLeYqcKxVDqqCAPZIhWCMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMPetnQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 03:10:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1771456" target="_blank"&gt;DA may supplement rice stocks in NegOcc through ‘Bigasan ng Bayan’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;AGRICULTURE Secretary Emmanuel Piñol said they can supplement the existing limited buffer stocks of government rice in Negros Occidental through the establishment of “Bigasan ng Bayan” in the province. Piñol, who was in Bacolod City last week, said while the arrival of 100,000 bags of imported rice for the province is still pending, the agency may source out stocks from the nearby province of Iloilo and sell it here at P38 or P39 per kilogram. “There is a volume in Iloilo coming from those sold by some traders. We can have it shipped here in Negros Occidental,” he said, adding that “it is u...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>DA chief meets kin of ‘Sagay 9’ victims; extends aid, livelihood - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1771237</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFJYnnPjlhwVDTXZD1btuMUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMPetnQM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Oct 2018 08:12:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1771237" target="_blank"&gt;DA chief meets kin of ‘Sagay 9’ victims; extends aid, livelihood&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;AS HE visited the wake of the “Sagay 9” victims in Sagay City gymnasium yesterday, Agriculture Secretary Emmanuel Piñol told the bereaved families that they would like to see to it that whoever is behind of the heinous crime will be brought to justice. Piñol, in an interview at the RU Foundry in Bacolod City after his visit along with Governor Alfredo Marañon Jr. and Sagay City Mayor Alfredo Marañon III, said the government would like to see an impartial investigation on the brutal killings. On the evening of October 20, nine members of the National Federation of Sugar Workers (NSFW) were k...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Labor sector bucks rice importation - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1770080</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMU3_Mc1HTR7myptMVad-O4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMPetnQM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 07:07:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1770080" target="_blank"&gt;Labor sector bucks rice importation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE labor sector in Negros Occidental is opposing the move of the government to import more rice to lower down prices in the country. Wennie Sancho, secretary-general of the General Alliance of Workers Association (Gawa), said rice importation will kill the rice farmers if prices would be too low and that many would prefer not to plant rice anymore. Instead of rice importation, Sancho said that government should give subsidy to rice farmers like what the governments of Vietnam and China are doing to sustain the production of our staple food and for the farmers to survive. The National Food ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>No such thing as 'unimpeded' rice importation, Piñol says - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/10/15/pinol-no-unimpeded-rice-importation.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJjLFpV01STwCBnYTWCYaSEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMJbthQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 07:58:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/10/15/pinol-no-unimpeded-rice-importation.html" target="_blank"&gt;No such thing as 'unimpeded' rice importation, Piñol says&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, October 15) — Agriculture Secretary Manny Piñol on Monday countered previous claims that the country will undertake "unimpeded" rice importation, saying that doing so would be an injustice to local farmers. He made the pronouncement in a media briefing, where he also announced that the National Food Council approved on Monday the importation of an additional 750,000 metric tons of rice. It was not immediately clear if that is on top of an earlier announced importation of 750,000 metric tons of the staple. Piñol said that while President Rodrigo Duterte's direc...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>Agriculture department to impose SRP on rice - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1768386</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIAbFbXCx3j3tSkvL_qcV8UqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKeunQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2018 12:16:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1768386" target="_blank"&gt;Agriculture department to impose SRP on rice&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE Department of Agriculture (DA) is set to impose the suggested retail price (SRP) on rice by the end of this month, an agriculture official said. Emmanuel Piñol, DA secretary, said in this way rice traders and retailers can be regulated from monopolizing the price on rice affecting Filipino households. “In fact last Wednesday (October 3, 2018), I met with rice traders, millers, and farmers under the PCAF (Philippine Council for Agriculture and Fisheries) in Manila, and we all agreed by the end of this month, we will set SRPs already,” Piñol said during a media forum at the National Food ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>After Dominguez-Piñol 'showdown,' Duterte OKs 'open' rice importation - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/213866-dominguez-pinol-showdown-duterte-approves-open-rice-importation</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH0EtcwQBzqWp3w_i6ZZ6FgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2018 05:14:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/213866-dominguez-pinol-showdown-duterte-approves-open-rice-importation" target="_blank"&gt;After Dominguez-Piñol 'showdown,' Duterte OKs 'open' rice importation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – President Rodrigo Duterte decided to greenlight the lifting of restrictions on rice importation following a "fierce" discussion between at least two secretaries during the Cabinet meeting on Monday, October 8. Duterte "approved unimpeded importation of rice as a measure to reduce inflation," said Presidential Spokesman Harry Roque on Tuesday during a Palace press briefing. "He wants to flood the market with rice so even if prices of crude oil should go up still further, people would still have access to rice," he added. Opening up rice importation means "anyone who can...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>FAST FACTS: Rice prices in the Philippines - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/newsbreak/fast-facts/211310-things-to-know-rice-prices-philippines</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIe3vJMt_D09p_XfVnTuBqoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJ_jmQI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 07:44:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/newsbreak/fast-facts/211310-things-to-know-rice-prices-philippines" target="_blank"&gt;FAST FACTS: Rice prices in the Philippines&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – How much a kilo of rice costs has a major impact on how Filipino families eat, or if they will eat at all. In November 2017, a kilo of rice cost P42.17. This has increased since, rising to P49.37, even to as much as P55 to P66 in some provinces as of the 4th week of September. Despite the price increases, the President and his spokesperson have denied there is a rice shortage in the country. But should we get worried? Take a quick look at the numbers and controversies revolving around our staple food. Rice crises, past and present Rice available in the market has two t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>DA, LGU to work closely for food security - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1767795</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKRtMjHZpL6TrWQcTMk_T4gqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKeunQM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 13:45:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1767795" target="_blank"&gt;DA, LGU to work closely for food security&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE participation of the local government units (LGUs) is a big help in addressing the issue on food security, Agriculture secretary Emmanuel Piñol said. Piñol underscored that the close coordination of the LGUs will help assess for DA in knowing the needs of the cities which agriculture is a huge sector in their economic activity. “As I were saying this event is very simple, it actually hinges on the belief that if only, the DA and the LGUs would come to a firm and strong partnership, we could provide enough food supply in this country,” Piñol said in a media forum on Friday, October 05, a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Piñol counters Diokno, says DA is 'doing well' - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/10/03/agriculture-department-counters-diokno-ompong-challenge.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDey8MZ9SyBRWu9VC7ecDiMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMJbthQM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 09:02:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/10/03/agriculture-department-counters-diokno-ompong-challenge.html" target="_blank"&gt;Piñol counters Diokno, says DA is 'doing well'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, October 3) — Agriculture Chief Manny Piñol maintained that the Department of Agriculture (DA) is "doing well" amid recent criticisms saying the country's performance in agriculture is falling behind. "If you talk of performance in the agriculture sector I don't have to debate with anybody. Let numbers speak for themselves," he told the press Wednesday. Piñol explained that Philippine agricultural growth skyrocketed to over six percent in the first year of President Rodrigo Duterte's term, bouncing back from a performance of -1.4 percent during the previous ad...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>Bukidnon eyed as PH vegetable basket - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1766665</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOwTu9aEtwiJ7aUuvWtzr1gqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMIeunQM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 14:14:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1766665" target="_blank"&gt;Bukidnon eyed as PH vegetable basket&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ASIDE from being the fruit basket of Mindanao, Bukidnon is poised to be the vegetable center in the country and is eyeing to supply regularly to Manila. The Department of Agriculture (DA) in Northern Mindanao said they will spend over P300 million to empower farmers in Bukidnon and be able to link them directly to buyers in Manila. DA-Northern Mindanao director Carlene Collado said Impasug-ong, Talakag, Sumilao, and Lantapan or the Imtasula complex will be the primary municipalities where high-value vegetable production will be prioritized. Collado said they have allocated P270 million for ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Department of Agriculture to invest P300 million in Bukidnon for vegetable production - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/business/212997-department-agriculture-to-invest-in-bukidnon-vegetable-production</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN8WT8bk_SytOYK4tNR1FvQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMP_mmQI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2018 14:02:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/business/212997-department-agriculture-to-invest-in-bukidnon-vegetable-production" target="_blank"&gt;Department of Agriculture to invest P300 million in Bukidnon for vegetable production&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;CAGAYAN DE ORO CITY, Philippines – The Department of Agriculture (DA) in Region 10 is investing P300 million into a 5-year vegetable production development program in the Impasug-ong-Talakag-Sumilao-Lantapan (IMTASULA) towns in Bukidnon. The investment aims to bring food supplies to the National Capital Region and stabilize food prices. The towns sit on the foot of the Mount Kitanglad and Mount Kalatungan mountain ranges, providing a pocket climate ideal for production of high value crops. On September 14, Agriculture Secretary Manny Piñol visited Barangay Miarayon, Talakag, to source veget...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>After Piñol slams rice imports, PH to import 1 million MT of rice in 2019 - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/business/212746-philippines-to-import-rice-2019</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECwmQOB4wAao-TqajHs3wCQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMP_mmQI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 12:55:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/business/212746-philippines-to-import-rice-2019" target="_blank"&gt;After Piñol slams rice imports, PH to import 1 million MT of rice in 2019&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – The National Food Authority (NFA) Council approved the standby importation of one million metric tons (MT) of rice for 2019, Agriculture Secretary Emmanuel Piñol announced on Monday, September 24. Piñol, who now serves as the NFA Council head, also announced the entry of an additional 750,000 MT of rice imports for this year. The move aims to tame the soaring prices of commercial rice in the market. (READ: Taming rice prices: What lawmakers, experts say) It is also a stern warning for rice hoarders, according to Piñol. "You better release your stocks in the market now...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Agricultural damage by Typhoon Ompong highest since Yolanda - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/business/212731-typhoon-ompong-agricultural-damage-highest-since-yolanda</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDQRecP-GhQCrcN5y2LI5J8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMP_mmQI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 09:18:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/business/212731-typhoon-ompong-agricultural-damage-highest-since-yolanda" target="_blank"&gt;Agricultural damage by Typhoon Ompong highest since Yolanda&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – The damage to agriculture caused by Typhoon Ompong (Mangkhut) climbed to P26.7 billion, said Agriculture Secretary Emmanuel Piñol on Monday, September 24. "This is the highest damage to agriculture since [Super Typhoon] Yolanda (Haiyan), which was at P35 billion," Piñol said. Rice production was the hardest hit, with damage amounting to P14.5 billion. Damage to corn and high value crops were at P8.2 billion and P3.4 billion, respectively. (READ: After tragic landslide, mayor says Itogon to transition to farming) {source} if("undefined"==typeof window.datawrapper)window...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Piñol is new NFA Council chairman, HUDCC moved to OP - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/212354-manny-pinol-nfa-council-chairman-hudcc-office-president</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHCPwePNqHOz6ThnP84IzgIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 10:58:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/212354-manny-pinol-nfa-council-chairman-hudcc-office-president" target="_blank"&gt;Piñol is new NFA Council chairman, HUDCC moved to OP&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – Through an executive order (EO), President Rodrigo Duterte made Agriculture Secretary Emmanuel Piñol the new National Food Authority Council (NFAC) chairman and transferred the Housing and Urban Development Coordinating Council (HUDCC) to the Office of the President. EO No. 62, signed on Monday, September 17, changed the NFAC composition, replacing its former head, Cabinet Secretary Leoncio Evasco Jr, with Piñol. Duterte had removed Evasco from the council, the government's policy-making body on rice and food security, last April, for supposedly engaging in a "turf war...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>DA: Agricultural damages from Ompong could reach up to ₱12 billion - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/09/17/agriculture-manny-pinol-damage-ompong-12-billion.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC6apEm4w1NqD8mTZFIX04oqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMJbthQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 10:11:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/09/17/agriculture-manny-pinol-damage-ompong-12-billion.html" target="_blank"&gt;DA: Agricultural damages from Ompong could reach up to ₱12 billion&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, September 17) — The Department of Agriculture (DA) is expecting up to ₱12 billion in agricultural damages from Typhoon Ompong, Secretary Manny Piñol said on Monday. "We're looking at about ₱11 to 12 billion in agriculture damage," Piñol told CNN Philippines' The Source, saying rice and corn took the hardest hit. The typhoon, which has the international name Mangkhut, killed about 60 people, leaving dozens buried in a Benguet landslide, and affected about half a million people, officials said. "Now the rice sector could recover, because we have coordinated with...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>Philippine paddy rice losses from typhoon exceed forecasts - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-asia-storm-philippines-rice/philippine-paddy-rice-losses-from-typhoon-exceed-forecasts-idUSKCN1LX03W</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMSWReJVefFuxk6FuSwCOswqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 05:41:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-asia-storm-philippines-rice/philippine-paddy-rice-losses-from-typhoon-exceed-forecasts-idUSKCN1LX03W" target="_blank"&gt;Philippine paddy rice losses from typhoon exceed forecasts&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Philippines lost a total of 250,730 tonnes of paddy rice due to the strong typhoon that hit its northern provinces over the weekend, according to initial official estimates, exceeding a worst-case forecast by 60 percent. The Philippines, one of the world's biggest rice importers, had been under pressure to boost its stocks of the grain even before Typhoon Mangkhut struck, with soaring retail prices helping to push inflation to its highest in nearly a decade. The Department of Agriculture initially estimated crop damage at about 9.6 billion pesos ($177 million), but said that may increas...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Agricultural losses from Typhoon Ompong hit P14 billion - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/business/212272-typhoon-ompong-agricultural-damage-september-18-2018</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGkFmk-SQXNY-5Q4rt7IyZEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMP_mmQI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 11:28:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/business/212272-typhoon-ompong-agricultural-damage-september-18-2018" target="_blank"&gt;Agricultural losses from Typhoon Ompong hit P14 billion&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – Damage to agriculture from Typhoon Ompong (Mangkhut) ballooned to an estimated P14.3 billion on Tuesday, September 18, according to the National Disaster Risk Reduction and Management Council (NDRRMC). The initial cost of damage is nearly double what Agriculture Secretary Emmanuel Piñol estimated would be "worst-case scenario" losses of about P7.9 billion. Office of Civil Defense Spokesperson Edgar Posadas earlier said the NDRRMC pegged the cost of damage to agriculture at about P2.8 billion as of Monday, September 17. But this was only for the Cordillera Administrativ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Duterte signs EO reverting NFA back to Agriculture Dept. - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/09/19/duterte-nfa-eo-62-department-of-agriculture.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPt010HDXTtL0VFiGHfdwXEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMJbthQM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 12:24:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/09/19/duterte-nfa-eo-62-department-of-agriculture.html" target="_blank"&gt;Duterte signs EO reverting NFA back to Agriculture Dept.&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, September 19) — The National Food Authority (NFA) is now back under the supervision of the Department of Agriculture (DA) . This, after President Rodrigo Duterte signed Executive Order No. 62 on September 17 stating the DA would have jurisdiction over the NFA, as well as the Philippine Coconut Authority (PCA) and the Fertilizer and Pesticide Authority (FPA). EO 62 amends EO 165 (series 2014), which put the three officers under the Office of the President. "The transfer of the NFA, PCA, and FPA to the DA...will ensure efficiency and coordination in the perform...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>Vegetable prices skyrocket after ‘Ompong’ - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1764942</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA4Z0RxTxCJiwPzx9KUoEu8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMLignQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 11:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1764942" target="_blank"&gt;Vegetable prices skyrocket after ‘Ompong’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WITH several road cuts along Halsema Highway, delivery of goods are hampered resulting to high prices of vegetables. Benguet Provincial Agriculturist Lolita Bentres and Benguet Farmers Marketing Cooperative general manager Augusta Balanoy said the very high price of vegetables is due to the impassable roads but assured there is an ample supply of highland vegetables. Balanoy said the supply of vegetables have increased because of the opening of Madaymen-Atok-Tublay road. Prices of vegetables at the La Trinidad Vegetable Trading Post, as of September 18, indicates P200 to P270 for carrots, P...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Typhoon Ompong leaves at least P2.8 billion in agricultural damage - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/business/212199-typhoon-ompong-agricultural-damage-september-17-2018</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF8BCkagJHyBA4aA4VzDgjMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMP_mmQI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 11:44:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/business/212199-typhoon-ompong-agricultural-damage-september-17-2018" target="_blank"&gt;Typhoon Ompong leaves at least P2.8 billion in agricultural damage&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – Office of Civil Defense Spokesperson Edgar Posadas said the damage to agriculture from Typhoon Ompong (Mangkhut) has reached an estimated P2.8 billion in the Cordillera Administrative Region (CAR) as of Monday, September 17. But the cost is likely to increase, he said, as the National Disaster Risk Reduction and Management Council (NDRRMC) has yet to fully assess the damage to crops. "Mababago pa 'yan (That will still change) because those are just estimates. We have procedures on a more structured assessment later on as we are focused right now on response," he said i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Expensive sili in markets? Plant your own, says Piñol - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/business/211585-pinol-suggestion-high-sili-red-chili-pepper-prices-markets</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMKCKfTcZGa81tOqFZMe_9cqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMP_mmQI</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 16:15:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/business/211585-pinol-suggestion-high-sili-red-chili-pepper-prices-markets" target="_blank"&gt;Expensive sili in markets? Plant your own, says Piñol&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – Social media was on fire after reports that the price of sili or red chili pepper reportedly soared to as much as P1,000 per kilo in markets. Agriculture Secretary Emmanuel Piñol offered a practical solution: learn how to plant sili in flower pots. "In these times, when the price of almost every commodity has gone up in the market because of the increase in fuel prices and electricity rates, it would be wise to be innovative," Piñol said in a Facebook post on Friday, September 7. He also shared that sili was only at around P50 per kilo in his hometown Kidapawan in Nort...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Duterte wants ancient barter trade to tame inflation - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/business/211738-duterte-barter-trade-sabah-tame-inflation-rice-prices</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDxhyIMm5_dJ6nqlbCcPCDsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMP_mmQI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 09:00:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/business/211738-duterte-barter-trade-sabah-tame-inflation-rice-prices" target="_blank"&gt;Duterte wants ancient barter trade to tame inflation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – President Rodrigo Duterte admitted that prices of goods, particularly rice, remain high. His solution? Reviving an ancient form of economic activity: barter trade. In a one-on-one chat with Chief Presidential Legal Counsel Salvador Panelo aired live on Tuesday, September 11, Duterte said he is willing to open up barter trade again with Sabah. "There are many options. Maybe I'll set up thebartertradeagain, depende kung papayag ang finance people (depends if the finance people agree)," the President said. Barter trade is one of the most ancient economic activities, where...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Luczon: A Song of rice and fire – 2 - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1762729</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN7WSczCzrtygq3ggRVOSD0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMIeunQM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2018 02:09:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1762729" target="_blank"&gt;Luczon: A Song of rice and fire – 2&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;IN 2015, the problem was about how El Niño affected rice production. It resulted into the dismay of farmers that prompted the Kidapawan onslaught. This year, it's a mixture of economic policy, taxation, and equal distribution. It has yet to be confirmed though, but so far there were no major reports recently that rice farmers are having difficulties in planting and harvesting rice, except for the continuing land rights issues. So when the prices spiked to an impossible figures, and not to mention some rice reserves were infested with weevils, this can seriously have an implication to everyo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>PH to import 250,000 metric tons of rice by November - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/09/05/nfa-nfac-additional-rice-import-november.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIRguLcsHDfAly8iElY4m8YqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMJbthQM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2018 14:13:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/09/05/nfa-nfac-additional-rice-import-november.html" target="_blank"&gt;PH to import 250,000 metric tons of rice by November&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, September 5) — An additional 250,000 metric tons of rice will be imported to the country. The National Food Authority Council (NFAC) said, in a statement Wednesday, it instructed the NFA to hold open tender immediately for the importation of the additional rice stocks to arrive in November. The imported rice would beef up current NFA's stock of the staple grain. The council added the importation could increase the NFA's active participation in the market by as much as 20 percent. This is the third time the country has imported rice. An initial 250,000 metric t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>Badiangan to host 13th Farmer’s Congress - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1762778</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE1bwC3s6zUmMwGThZNpRFkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMOidnQM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2018 10:23:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1762778" target="_blank"&gt;Badiangan to host 13th Farmer’s Congress&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE Municipality of Badiangan that is known for its booming organic farming and high-value crops will host the 13th Iloilo Provincial Farmer’s Congress on Friday, September 7. The congress, organized by the Iloilo Provincial P4MP Federation of Farmer’s Associations, will be anchored on the theme – “Para sa Panguma nga Mainuswagon, Agribusiness Adoptaron” (Adopt Agribusiness for Progressive Farming). Elias Sandig Jr., assistant provincial agriculturist, explained that the congress will focus on agribusiness as key to developing marginalized farmers. To optimize their potentials as producers,...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Piñol: Report rice hoarders, get P250,000 - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/business/211026-report-rice-hoarders-cash-reward</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJGRZnJwsiikMpvspJPN3vgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMP_mmQI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2018 05:41:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/business/211026-report-rice-hoarders-cash-reward" target="_blank"&gt;Piñol: Report rice hoarders, get P250,000&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – Citizens who have vital information on rice hoarders can get as much as P250,000 if they report incidents to the Department of Agriculture (DA). Agriculture Secretary Emmanuel Piñol said on Monday, September 3, that the agency has a "report a hoarder" campaign that rewards individuals up to P250,000. According to Piñol, the reward money will be "provided by the private millers and traders who said that the activities of the hoarders affect their business." The government will not shell out funds. Piñol has not mentioned, however, whether there is indeed cash already av...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Villar bucks importation of galunggong, legalization of rice smuggling - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1762133</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBcfiwkfeB04tsbiAd4y_M8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMPetnQM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2018 09:18:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1762133" target="_blank"&gt;Villar bucks importation of galunggong, legalization of rice smuggling&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SENATOR Cynthia Villar is against the importation of galunggong and the proposed legalization of smuggling rice in Mindanao. Villar, who was the speaker in the 27th Visayas Area Business Conference and Expo at L' Fisher Hotel in Bacolod City yesterday, said the importation of fish is allowed under the law for processing but not for the wet market. "Instead of doing the importation, we should encourage our fisher folk and help our aquaculture to produce more," Villar pointed out. “What they are doing maybe, is they import for processing purposes but they divert it to the wet market if it has...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>NFA spends bulk of 2018 budget to pay off loans, not buy rice - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/09/03/nfa-2018-budget-pay-off-loans-rice-shortage.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHELrpumORXPpGl_d17vsQUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMJbthQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2018 00:39:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/09/03/nfa-2018-budget-pay-off-loans-rice-shortage.html" target="_blank"&gt;NFA spends bulk of 2018 budget to pay off loans, not buy rice&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, September 3) — Most of the ₱7 billion budget set for the National Food Authority (NFA) in 2018 was used to pay loans instead of buying rice supply from local farmers. This came out during the NFA budget hearing at the House of Representatives Monday, where lawmakers grilled agency officials on the status of rice in the country. The NFA revealed that more than ₱6 billion was spent to repay loans — more than 90 percent of the NFA's budget allocation. Congress gave the NFA the funds to ensure there is enough buffer stocks of the staple grain to last at least 30 d...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>Duterte warns rice traders against "artificial scheme" - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/09/02/duterte-rice-traders-artificial-scheme.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFKQ0IfLS1NPs2eJuL_PGOgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMJbthQM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2018 11:25:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/09/02/duterte-rice-traders-artificial-scheme.html" target="_blank"&gt;Duterte warns rice traders against "artificial scheme"&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, September 2) — President Rodrigo Duterte warned traders who would take advantage of the country's rice situation. "Do not force me to resort to emergency measures," he told the media after delivering a speech before he left for historic visits to Israel and Jordan. If there was an artificial scheme going around, Duterte said he would not hesitate to exercise the powers of the President and ask the military and police to raid warehouses, adding that these would be subject to just compensation. The President said he would not let Filipinos go hungry. "I can do t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>'Serve me bukbok rice, I will eat it,' says Piñol - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/business/210584-emmanuel-pinol-will-eat-weevil-bukbok-rice</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEItjNb-2I1HDLgcmluI8FZAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMP_mmQI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2018 09:03:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/business/210584-emmanuel-pinol-will-eat-weevil-bukbok-rice" target="_blank"&gt;'Serve me bukbok rice, I will eat it,' says Piñol&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – Agriculture Secretary Emmanuel Piñol dismissed fears that bukbok- or weevil-infested rice is not safe for consumption. In an interview with ANC on Tuesday, August 28, the agriculture chief said rice with weevils "don't even have to be fumigated for the public to eat," and can just be washed with water. "Serve me bukbok rice, I will eat it," he said. The statement comes after reports that National Food Authority (NFA) imports from Thailand arrived with many weevils and needs fumigation. But Piñol said if it is only around 10 "lonely bukbok crawling over a sack of rice,"...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Bzzzzz: A Digong-Tomas meeting set? May defuse Cebu City's anti-police rally - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1760480</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOEOFa1yEGedDq-FybyD0PkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJeunQM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2018 10:13:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1760480" target="_blank"&gt;Bzzzzz: A Digong-Tomas meeting set? May defuse Cebu City's anti-police rally&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scrolling down, check out how hubris in the president and the mayor might abort the meeting, derail it or produce nothing substantial; why the city mayor is fighting the police single-handedly (probably because the other mayors can deal with their police without fighting them); and Tomas doesn't seem to like a collective dealing of the crisis by Metro Cebu mayors BUT first, about that famous quote of Agriculture Secretary Emmanuel Piñol, "Serve me 'bukbok' rice, I will eat it." He may be right. But the rice infested with "hanip" (termite) or "bukbok" (weevil) has to be thoroughly cleaned an...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Another rice shipment arrives in Zamboanga - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1760485</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDbbxqmXSLCWOb51zHXmfGsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJiunQM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2018 11:41:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1760485" target="_blank"&gt;Another rice shipment arrives in Zamboanga&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;AT LEAST 80,000 bags of were unloaded and delivered to the National Food Authority (NFA) warehouse in San Roque, Zamboanga City, over the weekend ensuring sufficient rice supply in the next few months. The rice stocks, imported from Thailand, arrived at the Zamboanga port onboard M/V New Sailing I last August 24 coinciding with the visit of Agriculture Secretary Emmanuel Piñol to this city. NFA Assistant Regional Director Ruben Manatad said the vessel was loaded with a total of 9,000 MT or 180,000 bags of NFA rice for distribution to the different areas in the region. Some 110,000 bags were...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Makabayan lawmakers seek House probe into bukbok rice importation - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/210646-makabayan-lawmakers-seek-house-probe-weevil-bukbok-rice-importation</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJNK5gXZZi80ub_64FnZdMcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2018 05:25:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/210646-makabayan-lawmakers-seek-house-probe-weevil-bukbok-rice-importation" target="_blank"&gt;Makabayan lawmakers seek House probe into bukbok rice importation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – Seven lawmakers forming the progressive Makabayan bloc are seeking a congressional probe into the importation of thousands of bags of rice infested with rice weevils or bukbok from Thailand. The Makabayan bloc filed House Resolution (HR) No. 2107 on Wednesday, August 29, a day after Agriculture Secretary Emmanuel Piñol dismissed fears that the bukbok or weevil-infested rice is not safe for consumption. He even offered to eat it. In HR 2107, the lawmakers said that 130,000 bags of bukbok rice imported by the National Food Authority (NFA) arrived at the Subic Bay Freepor...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>[ANALYSIS] Filipinos don’t deserve fumigated nor weevil-infested rice - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/thought-leaders/210621-filipinos-do-not-deserve-fumigated-weevil-bukbok-infested-rice</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOtD2iYY8od3JINDQiMFFykqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJDgmQI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2018 01:30:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/thought-leaders/210621-filipinos-do-not-deserve-fumigated-weevil-bukbok-infested-rice" target="_blank"&gt;[ANALYSIS] Filipinos don’t deserve fumigated nor weevil-infested rice&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rice policy has always been a source of frustration among economists. But this time around, things seem to be crazier than usual. By all accounts, the country seems to be on the cusp of a rice crisis. Figure 1 shows that commercial rice prices have skyrocketed in recent months. Rice prices similarly surged back in 2014, but we’ve now exceeded those levels. Figure 1. Aside from hurting the poor most of all, higher rice prices are also felt more acutely in some regions than in others. Officials in Zamboanga City, where rice prices already reached P70 per kilo, have already declared a state of...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Piñol wants special rice imports for Zambasulta area - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/business/210484-special-rice-imports-zamboanga-basilan-sulu-tawi-tawi</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFa3I6HVQBBj4laognYodKAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMP_mmQI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 04:57:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/business/210484-special-rice-imports-zamboanga-basilan-sulu-tawi-tawi" target="_blank"&gt;Piñol wants special rice imports for Zambasulta area&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – Agriculture Secretary Emmanuel Piñol proposed additional rice imports for the Zamboanga-Basilan-Sulu-Tawi-Tawi (Zambasulta) area due to sky-high prices. Zamboanga City and Basilan earlier declared a state of calamity due to rice woes. Rice prices in these two areas reached as high as P70 per kilo. Piñol also said a kilo of rice in some areas in Tawi-Tawi reached as high as P100 after Eid'l Fitr. In a Facebook post, the agriculture chief said he submitted a memorandum to President Rodrigo Duterte to allow the special importation of 132,000 metric tons of rice from the p...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Agriculture chief: Zamboanga rice crisis is over - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/regional/2018/08/25/Zamboanga-rice-crisis-Agriculture-Secretary-Manny-Pi%C3%B1ol.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECRLTADNWl9fd9vnwvcmpVgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMPHhmQI</guid><pubDate>Sat, 25 Aug 2018 06:31:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/regional/2018/08/25/Zamboanga-rice-crisis-Agriculture-Secretary-Manny-Pi%C3%B1ol.html" target="_blank"&gt;Agriculture chief: Zamboanga rice crisis is over&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zamboanga City (CNN Philippines, August 25) — Agriculture Chief Manny Piñol declared on Friday that the Zamboanga rice supply crisis is now over, with the entry of buffer stocks. In a Facebook post Friday, Piñol met with Zamboanga City Mayor Maria Isabel Climaco, Zamboanga Sibugay Governor Wilter Palma and representatives from the island provinces of Basilan, Sulu and Tawi-Tawi. "Local officials today heaved a sigh of relief as it was officially declared that the crisis is over with the arrival of fresh stocks from the National Food Authority (NFA) and the neighboring provinces where harves...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>Piñol wants to legalize smuggled rice in Zamboanga-Basilan area - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/business/210619-pinol-wants-smuggled-rice-legalized-zamboanga-basilan-sulu-tawi-tawi</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENQbvuFh7O_R4F0RQ2ZcIhcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMP_mmQI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2018 16:29:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/business/210619-pinol-wants-smuggled-rice-legalized-zamboanga-basilan-sulu-tawi-tawi" target="_blank"&gt;Piñol wants to legalize smuggled rice in Zamboanga-Basilan area&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – After saying it was smuggled rice that caused sky-high prices in Zamboanga-Basilan-Sulu-Tawi-Tawi (Zambasulta), Agriculture Secretary Emmanuel Piñol is considering to legalize their entry. Piñol earlier floated the idea in a Facebook post, and only expounded on it on Tuesday, August 28. “So my proposal is to establish a rice trading center, where you bring in rice, wherever that came from, and pay a little tariff,” Piñol said. “This is a peculiar problem because Zambasulta relied on smuggled rice,” he added. Smuggled rice supply was suddenly cut off after President Rod...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Poor agricultural growth? Increase our budget – Piñol - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/business/209556-agriculture-budget-poor-growth-emmanuel-pinol</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELqn1A4l2hPNbFBdLwwplJ4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMP_mmQI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2018 09:59:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/business/209556-agriculture-budget-poor-growth-emmanuel-pinol" target="_blank"&gt;Poor agricultural growth? Increase our budget – Piñol&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – After economic managers pointed out the poor agricultural output as one of the major forces that dragged down the country's growth, Agriculture Secretary Emmanuel Piñol defended his agency and asserted that his sector would "not be made a whipping boy." "You cannot squeeze milk from a thin and hungry cow!" Piñol said in a Facebook post on Monday, August 13. The country's gross domestic product (GDP) grew by only 6% in the 2nd quarter of 2018, missing market and government estimates. Socioeconomic Planning Secretary Ernesto Pernia said they are "gravely concerned about ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Leave farm lands alone, LGUs told - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1756698?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAvV3EoydN0Zr-Zclo77RJYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJeunQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2018 15:59:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1756698?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;Leave farm lands alone, LGUs told&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;DEPARTMENT of Agriculture (DA) Secretary Manuel Piñol has said that local government units (LGUs) must refrain from converting prime agricultural lands to residential lots to maintain food production. Piñol said he is happy that President Rodrigo Duterte has certified as urgent the passage of the National Land Use Act by Congress. “As DA secretary, I am concerned about the conversion of prime agricultural lands into residential, commercial and agricultural lands because it will affect food production,” Piñol said. He said some business owners bought agricultural lands and left these idle fo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>[OPINION] Is it downhill for Duterte? - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/thought-leaders/208677-is-it-downhill-rodrigo-duterte</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIL-Pp-Qy7TBR3nzj6hOXboqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJDgmQI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2018 04:38:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/thought-leaders/208677-is-it-downhill-rodrigo-duterte" target="_blank"&gt;[OPINION] Is it downhill for Duterte?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Recent approval rating surveys are contradictory. SWS says Duterte’s numbers are going down, Pulse Asia says they remain high. We cannot, of course, predict where Duterte’s approval ratings will go. We might as well read tea leaves at the bottom of a cup. In general, I don’t think approval rating surveys are as important as people think. But I find one recent survey intriguing. An SWS survey at the end of June says that “…64% of Filipinos think Duterte's ‘cursing’ the chief and members of the United Nations Human Rights Council is vulgar (bastos).” Respondents were also asked about what th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>DA’s challenge: Financial literacy - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1755078?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEKLALzosGtrNvby24WkOG0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJeunQM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2018 16:03:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1755078?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;DA’s challenge: Financial literacy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE Department of Agriculture (DA) is facing a bigger challenge—to make farmers and fisherfolk financially literate. In his talk during the Philippine Association of Agriculturists Summit held in Cebu last Wednesday, Agriculture Secretary Emmanuel Piñol disclosed that the agency has crafted a financial literacy program to help farmers and fishermen across the country make a better living. Lectures on basic accounting and financial literacy will kick off in Bohol next month. Piñol said they want farmers and fisherfolk to learn simple accounting so they could get more from what they produce. ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Domoguen: A PLEA story: Responding to our farmers’ need for affordable credit - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1751931?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPOWfxVbZoE7yNI6tq6VHGIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMLignQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2018 12:42:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1751931?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;Domoguen: A PLEA story: Responding to our farmers’ need for affordable credit&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PUGO. La Union – In times of need, a farmer or even an honest and ordinary Filipino residing in the countryside, for that matter, will be happy to make a loan or undertake a credit agreement with an individual or institution. You can validate that with the farmers themselves or with community development officers working directly with them. The consistency of that claim was again drilled into my mind during discussions I had with our agricultural technicians from the provinces. They said that farmers will always avail themselves of credit for their production inputs and other livelihood and...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Domoguen: Light moments with the Gods - SunStar Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1750746?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDnb_bbb9J-8VtDwQpKitJ0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMLignQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 11:14:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1750746?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;Domoguen: Light moments with the Gods&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SINCE I joined the government service several decades ago today, I have never really appreciated a light moment with a cabinet official who visited the places and realms of my influence. Even if during their visits, they talk and joke about mundane things like any human being does, they can’t reach and touch the heart. They maintained their distinctive flair for royalty and being society’s top honchos. The events of their visits have always compelled everybody to be serious with almost all resources trained and commandeered at any moment to serve them. At most, the atmosphere can be suffoca...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Technology for accurate crop projection vital for NegOcc agriculture sector - SunStar Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1749633?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBeHCcp5tZ6m7LF0yVlFcuoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMPetnQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2018 05:10:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1749633?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;Technology for accurate crop projection vital for NegOcc agriculture sector&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;HAVING the largest sugarcane plantation in the country, the move of the Department of Agriculture (DA) to employ technology for accurate production projection is seen to impact positively Negros Occidental. Provincial Agriculturist Japhet Masculino said yesterday, June 24, that sometimes there are big discrepancies between the projected and actual production using the "pamata" scheme, or based on just looking at the standing crops and area. Masculino said the local agriculture sector needs more appropriate technology for projection of harvest as well as the determination of actual productio...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Agriculture department imposes suggested prices for rice, other goods - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/business/205698-suggested-retail-prices-agricultural-products-metro-manila-june-2018</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGzhJ-vNnAD43DLiQjUEwYgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMP_mmQI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2018 04:39:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/business/205698-suggested-retail-prices-agricultural-products-metro-manila-june-2018" target="_blank"&gt;Agriculture department imposes suggested prices for rice, other goods&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – To avoid further abnormal movement of prices in local markets, the Department of Agriculture (DA) imposed a suggested retail price (SRP) scheme for 8 agricultural products on Monday, June 25. Agriculture Secretary Emmanuel Piñol said the department order covers only Metro Manila markets. The SRP scheme will be rolled out to other regions in the coming days. Piñol also clarified that the order does not cover supermarkets and malls. Under the order, the SRP of regular milled rice was pegged at P39/kilo. Prices of regular milled rice had soared due to depleted National Fo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Domoguen: Growing free range chicken, a lovely farming hobby at our backyards - SunStar Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1749687?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED51R_EN9HAPwpe53A0UjgAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMLignQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2018 12:13:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1749687?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;Domoguen: Growing free range chicken, a lovely farming hobby at our backyards&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;IT WAS during the third staging of his “Byaheng Bukid” visit to the Cordillera, in 2016, when Agriculture Secretary Emmanuel F. Piñol first discussed the need to promote backyard livestock production, particularly the growing of ducks and free-range chicken (FRC) for meat and eggs that a local farm family needs. In his visit to Amlao, Tabuk, Kalinga, a barangay that the good Secretary visited to monitor the progress of an on-going multi-million farm-to-market road (FMR), Secretary Piñol was particularly concerned that even farmers and their families in the countryside today would rather buy...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>SRP eyed for agricultural products - SunStar Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1748484?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELuCQilxz-qTy0w5sinqamUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKeunQM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jun 2018 13:25:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1748484?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;SRP eyed for agricultural products&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE Department of Agriculture (DA) eyes to implement suggested retail prices (SRP) for selected farm products as an anti-profiteering measures. Agriculture Secretary Emmanuel “Manny” Piñol reportedly announced that SRPs will be implemented for basic vegetables, including pechay and eggplant, and of fishes such as galunggong, tilapia, and bangus. There will also be SRP for regular-milled rice between P38 to P39 and well-milled rice between P40 and P42 per kilo. Implementation of SRP for agricultural products will be covered by the anti-profiteering law, according to Piñol. A price increase o...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Fisherfolk seen to benefit from SRP for farm products - SunStar Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1748639?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC09XK_CQ_fzXUMadwAL-CIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKeunQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2018 12:48:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1748639?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;Fisherfolk seen to benefit from SRP for farm products&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SUGGESTED retail prices (SRP) for certain types of fishes in the market as ordered to be implemented by Agriculture Secretary Emmanuel “Manny” Piñol will be beneficial both to the fisherfolks and the conumers in Davao Region, said Bureau of Fisheries and Aquatic Resources (BFAR) Davao Region official. In previous reports, Piñol said he is eyeing to implement SRP for agricultural products such as well-milled and regular-milled rice, eggplant, and pechay. As for the fishes, the project will initially have galunggong, tilapia, and bangus to follow the SRP. “It’s good just like other commoditie...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>DA holds trade expo at Robinsons Starmills - SunStar Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1749102?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM4s5nodtq8R8vjZNPe-ba4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJmtnQM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 11:21:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1749102?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;DA holds trade expo at Robinsons Starmills&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;CITY OF SAN FERNANDO -- The Department of Agriculture (DA) in partnership with Department of Trade and Industry (DTI), Philippine Chamber of Commerce and Industry (PCCI) and other private sector industry groups launched the 2nd Agribusiness Support for Promotion and Investment in Regional Expositions (Aspire) at Robinsons Starmills here. The event, which will run from June 20 to 22, aims to promote the regional priority commodities and agri-fishery based products, and to showcase strong linkages with farmers and fisher folk. The components of the programs are: production support, enterprise...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Sanchez: Learning from Sugarlandia - SunStar Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1748176?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENkwx5G1Ie4pKb8Njt-j5uwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMPetnQM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 06:54:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1748176?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;Sanchez: Learning from Sugarlandia&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;HOW about that? Negros Occidental, the so-called Sugarlandia, has something to show the rest of the country in rice production. Sugar is no longer the province’s Achilles Heel where a sneeze causes Negros Occidental to catch a cold. Once touted as the sugar capital of the country, the Department of Agriculture (DA) conferred on Bago City as one of 2017 Rice Achievers for its dedicated efforts to the rice industry. Bago remains to be the rice granary of the province as it was able to produce 4.20 tons per hectare of rice higher than the 4.01 metric tons per hectare in 2017, the minimum requi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Bad weather stalls NFA rice distribution - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/business/204748-bad-weather-nfa-rice-distribution</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP-0kvX26B44hzu04IQfbpwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMP_mmQI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 08:44:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/business/204748-bad-weather-nfa-rice-distribution" target="_blank"&gt;Bad weather stalls NFA rice distribution&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – While rice imports from Thailand and Vietnam have arrived in the country, bad weather has kept the National Food Authority (NFA) from distributing its fresh stocks to the local market. "As soon as the weather becomes a little better, the stocks will be immediately brought to NFA warehouses and immediate dispersal will follow," NFA administrator Jason Aquino said. NFA spokesperson Rex Estoperez said in a GMA News interview that rice imports have been stuck in the ports for 9 days. In a Facebook post, Agriculture Secretary Emmanuel Piñol said Aquino had informed him that...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Piñol open to debate over abolishing 4Ps program - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/203564-emmanuel-pinol-open-debate-4ps-program-conditional-cash-transfer</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECT7aYjw2u4gA-dLkDrxe48qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2018 13:45:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/203564-emmanuel-pinol-open-debate-4ps-program-conditional-cash-transfer" target="_blank"&gt;Piñol open to debate over abolishing 4Ps program&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines— Agriculture Secretary Emmanuel Piñol said he is open to a debate over his proposal to scrap the government’s P70 billion Pantawid Pamilyang Pilipino Program (4Ps) and have the funds diverted to livelihood programs. In a Facebook post, the agriculture chief said that he received an invitation from a law school dean to argue his point against Akbayan party-list representative Tom Villarin. Piñol said that the funds should be allocated to productivity in small scale economic activities. He also stressed that the program was used for political purposes “especially during th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>OPA: Bago’s award shows NegOcc rice production program on the right track - Sun.Star Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1746367?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPe7NVxYFBgyG5ff3zBL3N0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMPetnQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 02:48:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1746367?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;OPA: Bago’s award shows NegOcc rice production program on the right track&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Sun.Star Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE recognition given by the Department of Agriculture (DA) to Bago City as one of the recipients of the 2017 Rice Achievers Award in the country shows that Negros Occidental's rice production program is on the right track. Provincial Agriculturist Japhet Masculino lauded the city for making it as a winner of the said national agriculture award. “We hope that other local government units in the province also attain what Bago City has achieved so that, together, we can attain our goal of being a rice self-sufficient province,” Masculino said on Saturday, June 2.. Bago City was among the seve...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">Sun.Star Philippines</source></item><item><title>Duterte begins official Seoul visit - Sun.Star Philippines</title><link>http://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1746244?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDlAQ40-SZ8w-6kAfHY55iIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKmgnQM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2018 09:28:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1746244?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;Duterte begins official Seoul visit&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Sun.Star Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PRESIDENT Rodrigo Duterte on Sunday, June 3, kicked off his three-day official visit to the Repubic of Korea by meeting with the Filipino community. Ambassador Raul Hernandez, who welcomed the President and his delegation, said the Filipino community is "very excited to meet the President. “You know, the Filipino community here in South Korea is solidly behind the President and in his campaign against corruption, against drugs, and against criminality,” Hernandez said. The President took a commercial flight and arrived at the Incheon International Airport at 4:57 am (Seoul time) Sunday. He ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.sunstar.com.ph">Sun.Star Philippines</source></item></channel></rss>