<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Department of Justice - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIggKIhxDQkFTRHdvSkwyMHZNR0p3T1hCM0VnSmxiaWdBUAE?hl=en-PH&amp;gl=PH&amp;ceid=PH:en</link><language>en-PH</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 12:52:18 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>It’s a stalemate for DOJ, Trillanes at Makati court - INQUIRER.net</title><link>https://newsinfo.inquirer.net/1056853/its-a-stalemate-for-doj-trillanes-at-makati-court</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiV2h0dHBzOi8vbmV3c2luZm8uaW5xdWlyZXIubmV0LzEwNTY4NTMvaXRzLWEtc3RhbGVtYXRlLWZvci1kb2otdHJpbGxhbmVzLWF0LW1ha2F0aS1jb3VydNIBqQFodHRwczovL25ld3NpbmZvLWlucXVpcmVyLW5ldC5jZG4uYW1wcHJvamVjdC5vcmcvdi9zL25ld3NpbmZvLmlucXVpcmVyLm5ldC8xMDU2ODUzL2l0cy1hLXN0YWxlbWF0ZS1mb3ItZG9qLXRyaWxsYW5lcy1hdC1tYWthdGktY291cnQvYW1wP2FtcF9qc192PTAuMSN3ZWJ2aWV3PTEmY2FwPXN3aXBl</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2018 08:00:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://newsinfo.inquirer.net/1056853/its-a-stalemate-for-doj-trillanes-at-makati-court" target="_blank"&gt;It’s a stalemate for DOJ, Trillanes at Makati court&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;INQUIRER.net&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Department of Justice (DOJ) and the camp of Sen. Antonio Trillanes IV have reached a stalemate after a Makati court denied their appeals on.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://newsinfo.inquirer.net">INQUIRER.net</source></item><item><title>DOJ asks Davao court to keep Trillanes from leaving PH - Rappler</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kUBHOXhSC9A</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENKzp7JjsWQ-1lPVcva9iboqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMMCTnwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 19:50:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kUBHOXhSC9A" target="_blank"&gt;DOJ asks Davao court to keep Trillanes from leaving PH&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Department of Justice (DOJ) has asked a Davao court to issue a Hold Departure Order (HDO) against opposition Senator Antonio Trillanes IV, Justice Secretary Menardo Guevarra said on Thursday, December 6. Story: https://www.rappler.com/nation/218328-doj-resorts-to-davao-court-hold-departure-order-vs-trillanes&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.youtube.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Trillanes on arrest warrant: ‘Baliktad ang hustisya sa gobyerno ni Duterte’ - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/218461-trillanes-statement-arrest-warrant-libel-case-justice-duterte-government</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP_TQY7cneHVOZYUaQAbCeoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 12:03:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/218461-trillanes-statement-arrest-warrant-libel-case-justice-duterte-government" target="_blank"&gt;Trillanes on arrest warrant: ‘Baliktad ang hustisya sa gobyerno ni Duterte’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – Opposition Senator Antonio Trillanes IV on Friday, December 7, slammed what he called “topsy-turvy" justice under the Duterte administration, after a Davao City court issued a warrant for his arrest stemming from a libel complaint filed by presidential son Paolo Duterte in his hometown. On the day Judge Melinda Alconcel Dayanghirang of the Davao City Regional Trial Court Branch 54 ordered his arrest, the anti-graft court Sandiganbayan acquitted former senator Bong Revilla of plunder in relation to the pork barrel scam. “Baliktad ang hustisya sa gobyerno ni Duterte. Ang...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>[OPINION] A new weapon against press freedom in the Philippines - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/thought-leaders/218315-court-cases-new-weapon-against-press-freedom-philippines</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEILQIw6kD48VvabqpQ0BMwsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJDgmQI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 02:04:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/thought-leaders/218315-court-cases-new-weapon-against-press-freedom-philippines" target="_blank"&gt;[OPINION] A new weapon against press freedom in the Philippines&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(This piece first appeared in The Globe and Mail.) As a former journalist, I often find myself straining to explain press freedom in the Philippines. Many people I meet seem to have a rather straightforward view: Either the press is free or it is not. I wish it were that simple, I tell them. The Philippines, officially, does not have prior restraint regulations that prevent journalists from publishing. Pretty much anything goes, which is why the Philippine press has been classified as free, rambunctious even. Filipino journalists struggled quite a lot, particularly during the Ferdinand Marc...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Drop 'politically motivated' criminal charges vs Rappler, Maria Ressa - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/217952-human-rights-watch-statement-rappler-tax-cases</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGcHnNO7iAz0r2FhQDtzFB0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 01:35:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/217952-human-rights-watch-statement-rappler-tax-cases" target="_blank"&gt;Drop 'politically motivated' criminal charges vs Rappler, Maria Ressa&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philipppines – Human Rights Watch (HRW) on Saturday, December 1, called on the Duterte administration to drop the “politically motivated” charges against Rappler Holdings Corporation and its president Maria Ressa. The New York-based human rights group made the call days after the Philippines' Department of Justice (DOJ) filed 4 tax cases before the Court of Tax Appeals, and a fifth case before the Pasig Regional Trial Court against Rappler Holdings and Ressa. "The Philippine government is targeting Rappler and Maria Ressa for their dogged reporting on Duterte’s murderous ‘drug war.'...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Maria Ressa, Rappler Holdings charged in court for alleged tax evasion - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/217776-doj-charges-maria-ressa-rappler-holdings-tax-cases-november-2018</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECfLRYMdsu-RvMy4HMocj-UqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 08:10:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/217776-doj-charges-maria-ressa-rappler-holdings-tax-cases-november-2018" target="_blank"&gt;Maria Ressa, Rappler Holdings charged in court for alleged tax evasion&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – Rappler Holdings Corporation and its president Maria Ressa have been charged with tax evasion before the Court of Tax Appeals (CTA), the court's record's division confirmed. On the basis of a Bureau of Internal Revenue (BIR) complaint, the Department of Justice (DOJ) filed on November 26 and 28 three counts of failure to file returns, and one count of tax evasion against Rappler and Ressa. The department moved ahead with the filing of the cases despite respondents’ motion for reconsideration filed last week with the DOJ. Through their lawyers, Rappler and Ressa said th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>De Lima seeks to stop drug convicts from testifying against her - ABS CBN News</title><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOU85Tcf1d1AlsayMai2PggqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow8IjwCjDw4s8CMNj9mQI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 07:04:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABS CBN News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The detained senator also calls DOJ’s reasoning “palusot” Senator Leila de Lima. File MANILA- Detained Senator Leila de Lima has again sought to stop 13 drug convicts from testifying against her over her alleged involvement in illegal drugs. The senator, in a petition for certiorari and prohibition filed at the Court of Appeals last Nov. 19, questioned Muntinlupa Regional Trial Court Branch 206 Judge Lorna Navarro Domingo's decision denying her plea to disqualify 13 drug convicts as state witnesses. Detained Sen. Leila de Lima questions before the Court of Appeals Muntinlupa RTC Br 206 Judg...&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>DOJ files yet another tax case vs Maria Ressa, Rappler Holdings in Pasig court - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/217838-separate-tax-case-filed-vs-rappler-maria-ressa-pasig-regional-trial-court</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIDHUJHc3qkhhO5xx9zuPW8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 09:09:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/217838-separate-tax-case-filed-vs-rappler-maria-ressa-pasig-regional-trial-court" target="_blank"&gt;DOJ files yet another tax case vs Maria Ressa, Rappler Holdings in Pasig court&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – A separate tax case was filed before the Pasig Regional Trial Court (RTC) against Rappler Holdings Corporation and Maria Ressa, adding to the list of charges also pending at the Court of Tax Appeals. The Department of Justice (DOJ) filed 4 tax cases before the CTA on November 26 and 28, but Rappler’s lawyers discovered on Thursday, November 29, that a 5th case was separately filed before the Pasig RTC. The charges were filed at the Pasig court on November 14. This happened a day before the DOJ decided to serve a copy of the indictment on Rappler's counsels. The separat...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>DOJ mulls creating task force to look into 'lawless or terrorist' acts - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/11/24/Department-of-Justice-task-force-lawless-acts.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGsjHXQ6Kxj0tuiE1rMuorMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMJbthQM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2018 07:41:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/11/24/Department-of-Justice-task-force-lawless-acts.html" target="_blank"&gt;DOJ mulls creating task force to look into 'lawless or terrorist' acts&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, November 24) — The Department of Justice (DOJ) said it is considering to create a special task force to investigate "lawless or terrorist acts." Justice Secretary Menardo Guevarra said this two days after Malacañang ordered the deployment of more soldiers and policemen to the Bicol Region, Samar, Negros Oriental and Occidental. "The DOJ is called upon to expeditiously investigate and prosecute those who may be apprehended for commission of lawless or terrorist acts," he said. Guevarra said the decision to create a task force or special investigating team will ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>Despite NBI graft complaint, Duterte still trusts Lapeña – Panelo - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/216571-duterte-still-trusts-lapena-despite-nbi-graft-complaint</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOPleluvknPzHTjVgxXlOBwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 04:50:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/216571-duterte-still-trusts-lapena-despite-nbi-graft-complaint" target="_blank"&gt;Despite NBI graft complaint, Duterte still trusts Lapeña – Panelo&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – President Rodrigo Duterte continues to trust former Customs chief Isidro Lapeña even after the National Bureau of Investigation (NBI) filed a graft complaint against him, Malacañang said on Tuesday, November 13. Chief Presidential Counsel and Presidential Spokesman Salvador Panelo said since there is no final verdict yet on Lapeña's guilt or innocence, he has a "right to be presumed innocent." "Until and unless proven otherwise, he still enjoys the trust and confidence of the appointing authority who happens to be the President," Panelo said in a statement on Tuesday. ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Raps vs Lapeña 'part of Duterte's anti-corruption crackdown' - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1773786/Manila/Local-News/Raps-vs-Isidro-Lape-ntildea-part-of-Dutertes-anti-corruption-crackdown?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE80khz6CZPzb2P8I6C8hIYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKmgnQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 05:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1773786/Manila/Local-News/Raps-vs-Isidro-Lape-ntildea-part-of-Dutertes-anti-corruption-crackdown?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;Raps vs Lapeña 'part of Duterte's anti-corruption crackdown'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;FORMER Customs Commissioner Isidro Lapeña is not exempt from any liabilities even if he is an ally of President Rodrigo Duterte's administration, Malacañang said on Tuesday, November 13. The National Bureau of Investigation (NBI) has lodged criminal and administrative complaints against Lapeña over alleged irregularities in the release of 105 containers of ceramic tiles worth P69 million. Presidential Spokesperson Salvador Panelo said the NBI was merely following Duterte's order to rid the government of corruption when it recommended the filing of charges against Lapeña. "Good governance is...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>DOJ indicts Rappler Holdings for tax evasion - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/216337-doj-indicts-rappler-holdings-tax-evasion-november-9-2018</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL1mxoEg_wQKZVbNd7HCuIYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 09:41:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/216337-doj-indicts-rappler-holdings-tax-evasion-november-9-2018" target="_blank"&gt;DOJ indicts Rappler Holdings for tax evasion&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines (UPDATED) – The Department of Justice (DOJ) indicted Rappler Holdings Corporation (RHC) for tax evasion and failure to file tax returns, the department said in a statement on Friday, November 9. The DOJ's statement did not indicate the subject amount of tax evasion, but it said that when Rappler issued its Philippine Depositary Receipts (PDRs), "it gained close to P162.5 million from the transaction, which it failed to declare in its tax return." "The National Prosecution Service (NPS) has found probable cause to indict Rappler Holdings Corporation (RHC), its President M...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Rappler chief Maria Ressa says tax evasion charges won't silence news site's journalists - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/12/asia/maria-ressa-intv-philippines-rappler-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBk-b8ciK1gZ0XBX8PZBXuMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 17:50:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/12/asia/maria-ressa-intv-philippines-rappler-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Rappler chief Maria Ressa says tax evasion charges won't silence news site's journalists&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Maria Ressa, the CEO of the Philippine news website Rappler, said Monday that her reporters would not be silenced in the face of tax evasion charges, telling CNN that "journalists are more important today than ever." Ressa vowed to fight the charges from the Philippines Department of Justice for tax evasion, which many see as a thinly veiled attempt by President Rodrigo Duterte to muzzle the investigative news site. "In many ways the government's attacks against Rappler have made it very clear to us exactly who we are, what our identity is, and for our young reporters who are on the ground,...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Tax case vs Rappler 'desperate attempt to silence critical voice' – HRW - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/216386-human-rights-watch-statement-rappler-tax-evasion-indictment</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECHyR1mfQ_hLAcCgU6QoXRMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 05:40:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/216386-human-rights-watch-statement-rappler-tax-evasion-indictment" target="_blank"&gt;Tax case vs Rappler 'desperate attempt to silence critical voice' – HRW&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – International group Human Rights Watch (HRW) on Saturday, November 10, decried the Philippine justice department's indictment of Rappler for tax evasion. In a statement on Saturday, HRW Asia Director Brad Adams called the indictment a "clear desperate attempt by the administration of President Rodrigo Duterte to shut down one of the critical voices in Philippine journalism." The Department of Justice (DOJ) announced on Friday, November 9, that its prosecutors found probable cause to charge Rappler of tax evasion and failure to file tax returns over its Philippine Depos...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>DOJ indicts Davidson Bangayan over rice cartel - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/216314-doj-indicts-davidson-bangayan-rice-trade-monopoly</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFDXz3xrdb3_b7GDk3nn3lIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 06:02:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/216314-doj-indicts-davidson-bangayan-rice-trade-monopoly" target="_blank"&gt;DOJ indicts Davidson Bangayan over rice cartel&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – The Department of Justice (DOJ) indicted alleged rice smuggler Davidson Bangayan, also known as David Tan, for rice trade monopoly. Bangayan was ordered charged for violation of Paragraph 3, Article 186 of the Revised Penal Code (RPC) which penalizes trade monopoly with imprisonment of 6 months to 6 years plus fines. Paragraph 3, Article 186 of RPC punishes: “Any person who, being a manufacturer, producer, or processor of any merchandise or object of commerce or an importer of any merchandise or object of commerce from any foreign country, either as principal or agent,...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>De Lima runs to Ombudsman: DOJ use of convicts as witnesses 'illegal' - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/216035-de-lima-ombudsman-complaint-vs-doj-using-convicts-as-witnesses-illegal</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPiyOT20haEXirKI7NrADbsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 06:16:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/216035-de-lima-ombudsman-complaint-vs-doj-using-convicts-as-witnesses-illegal" target="_blank"&gt;De Lima runs to Ombudsman: DOJ use of convicts as witnesses 'illegal'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – Detained Senator Leila de Lima ran to the Office of the Ombudsman to file a complaint against former justice secretary Vitaliano Aguirre II and his successor, Secretary Menardo Guevarra, for using convicts as state witnesses in the drug case against her. De Lima filed the complaint before the Ombudsman on October 29, accusing Aguirre and Guevarra of violation of both the Witness Protection Program (WPP) and the anti-graft law. The Muntinlupa Regional Trial Court (RTC) Branch 206, handling one of the 3 counts of conspiracy to commit illegal drug trade against De Lima, h...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Maquiling wins 2 titles - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1772626</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP09IubXkTOz6e1Vmfg23OwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJeunQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 15:32:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1772626" target="_blank"&gt;Maquiling wins 2 titles&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PAUL JOHN MAQUILING won the Open/Advance category of the First Isog Warrior Challenge held at Camp Ceperino Genovia last Oct. 6 and 7. The event was organized by the Regional Mobile Force Battalion 7 and featured an obstacle challenge. Maquiling beat Jimboy Frampatanta and Wilbert Laurecio, who settled for second and third, respectively. In the women’s division, Josephine Rodriguez won the title over Katy Salvacion and Daisy Batac. In the women’s open division, Rodriguez beat Salvacion and Batac, while John Cliff Debulosan won the beginners category over Arcel Bohol and Jamiel Gamboa. Lance...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Cabaero: Military approach - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1772276</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJxZsr3W8b2_rUlrB7IYg4YqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJeunQM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2018 10:55:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1772276" target="_blank"&gt;Cabaero: Military approach&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THERE cannot be a single approach to a complex problem. The decision last week of President Rodrigo Duterte to place the Bureau of Customs (BOC) under military control appears to be that single approach: definitive and strong, but untested. It also raised questions on how a military approach could defeat a web of corruption when three former police and military top officials who were named BOC head failed in their separate attempts. Former Marine captain Nicanor Faeldon was BOC chief from May 2016 until August 2017 when he tendered his resignation. His appointment raised hopes he could fina...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Justice Department appeals Makati RTC decision not to arrest Trillanes - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/10/26/justice-department-menardo-guevara-appeal-motion-reconsideration-makati-rtc-soriano-antonio-trillanes-arrest.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL-dHgcrWgbS-4MRgYy_oZMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMJbthQM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 11:40:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/10/26/justice-department-menardo-guevara-appeal-motion-reconsideration-makati-rtc-soriano-antonio-trillanes-arrest.html" target="_blank"&gt;Justice Department appeals Makati RTC decision not to arrest Trillanes&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, October 26) — The Department of Justice (DOJ) said Friday it has filed a motion for partial reconsideration of a Makati Regional Trial Court's decision against arresting opposition Senator Antonio Trillanes. Justice Secretary Menardo Guevarra confirmed in a text message to CNN Philippines that the motion was filed late Thursday and it would be heard on October 30. Anjo Alimario tweet: DOJ files motion for partial reconsideration Makati RTC Branch 148, helmed by Judge Andres Soriano, rejected the DOJ's petition to arrest Trillanes, a vocal critic of President ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>Calida defers to DOJ on handling of Trillanes case - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/215062-solgen-calida-defers-to-doj-handling-trillanes-case</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJyHIr3YXim_dkV135cBxbYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 07:26:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/215062-solgen-calida-defers-to-doj-handling-trillanes-case" target="_blank"&gt;Calida defers to DOJ on handling of Trillanes case&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – Solicitor General Jose Calida abandoned his plan to go straight to the Court of Appeals (CA) to seek a reversal of the Makati City Regional Trial Court (RTC) Branch 148's decision not to issue an arrest warrant for Senator Antonio Trillanes IV. According to Malacañang, Calida will defer to the Department of Justice (DOJ) strategy to first file a motion for partial reconsideration with the Makati court. "He (Calida) will defer to the DOJ secretary move to file an MR before the RTC," Presidential Spokesperson and Chief Presidential Legal Counsel Salvador Panelo told Rapp...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Duterte keeping hands off Trillanes case - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1770720/Manila/Duterte-keeping-hands-off-Trillanes-case?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHYsD4Io1nY4k53dGgITWo0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKmgnQM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 08:34:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1770720/Manila/Duterte-keeping-hands-off-Trillanes-case?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;Duterte keeping hands off Trillanes case&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PRESIDENT Rodrigo Duterte will not intervene in the next moves of the Department of Justice (DOJ) and the Office of Solicitor General (OSG), after a Makati court junked the government's petition for Senator Antonio Trillanes IV's arrest, Malacañang said Wednesday, October 24. Presidential Spokesperson Salvador Panelo said the President has no plans of giving orders to the DOJ and the OSG. Panelo said Duterte's mere directive was to "do what is best." "Everyone will have to ask advice either from me or directly to the President. But mostly, hindi na kailangan mag-paalam kay Presidente kasi a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Justice Chief: DOJ, not SolGen, to decide next move on Trillanes case - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/10/23/Trillanes-arrest-amnesty-SolGen-Calida-DOJ-appeal.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHteV9U1v9bILpg06IVaj5AqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMJbthQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 10:11:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/10/23/Trillanes-arrest-amnesty-SolGen-Calida-DOJ-appeal.html" target="_blank"&gt;Justice Chief: DOJ, not SolGen, to decide next move on Trillanes case&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, October 23) — Justice Secretary Menardo Guevarra said it is up to his department to decide on the government's next move after a Makati court junked their plea to have Senator Antonio Trillanes IV arrested. "It is the DOJ who will decide what legal step to take," Guevarra said in a text message to reporters on Tuesday. His message contradicted the statement of Presidential Spokesperson Sal Panelo that Solicitor General Jose Calida is preparing to take the fight to the Court of Appeals, where he will seek the reversal of Makati judge Andres Soriano's decision i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>No new arrest warrant vs Trillanes - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1770370</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC7VhnY2C0eUuUUR-N2E4PYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKmgnQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 08:26:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1770370" target="_blank"&gt;No new arrest warrant vs Trillanes&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(UPDATED) - A Makati court has denied the government's petition for an arrest warrant and hold departure order against opposition Senator Antonio Trillanes IV in connection with a dismissed case of coup d' etat, but upheld the legality of President Rodrigo Duterte's proclamation that voided the amnesty granted to the senator. Acting Prosecutor General Richard Anthony Fadullon confirmed the court's denial of the DOJ petition. Judge Andres Bartolome Soriano of Makati RTC Branch 148 released his resolution on the Department of Justice's petition shortly before 4 p.m. Monday, October 22, more t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Boracay reopens without a casino - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1771065</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECepvby4XEnvEvn0FQ4oTh8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMOidnQM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 05:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1771065" target="_blank"&gt;Boracay reopens without a casino&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;AUTHORITIES assured that Boracay will operate without a casino after its reopening Friday, October 26. The Department of Justice (DOJ), though, recommended the issuance of an executive order (EO) for the "no casino" policy in Boracay to be implemented strictly. The island was reopened to tourists on Friday after a six-month rehabilitation. About 157 accommodation establishments were allowed to accept visitors. Local Government Officer-in-Charge Eduardo Año said in a press briefing that the Philippine Amusement and Gaming Corporation (Pagcor) has ordered the cancellation of permits of establ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Makati judge contradicts Duterte, says Trillanes filed for amnesty - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/214908-makati-judge-andres-soriano-contradicts-duterte-trillanes-filed-amnesty-application</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIQE6LVUEJuW2Mu6vWZHUn8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 09:21:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/214908-makati-judge-andres-soriano-contradicts-duterte-trillanes-filed-amnesty-application" target="_blank"&gt;Makati judge contradicts Duterte, says Trillanes filed for amnesty&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines– In a much-awaited decision, the presiding judge of Makati Regional Trial Court (RTC) Branch 148 on Monday, October 22, contradicted President Rodrigo Duterte, and in doing so keeps the Chief Executive’s fiercest enemy, Senator Antonio Trillanes IV, out of jail. In his 33-page decision, Makati Judge Andres Soriano junked the justice department's request to have Trillanes arrested for charges of coup d’etat that the court had dismissed 7 years ago. Soriano also struck down the factual basis of Duterte’s Proclamation No. 572, saying that “the Court finds and so holds that ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Palace respects ruling on Trillanes coup d' etat case - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1770516/Manila/Local-News/Palace-respects-ruling-on-Trillanes-coup-d-etat-case?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP4xfR7JaC_-4ZfFvlboyy8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKmgnQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 02:05:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1770516/Manila/Local-News/Palace-respects-ruling-on-Trillanes-coup-d-etat-case?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;Palace respects ruling on Trillanes coup d' etat case&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MALACAÑANG said it respects the refusal of a Makati court to issue a warrant for the arrest of opposition Senator Antonio Trillanes IV in connection with his dismissed coup d’ etat case. Presidential Spokesperson Salvador Panelo said the executive branch would not "unfairly appeal" to public's "pity," stressing that it would address Trillanes's case in the proper forum. "While the Office of the President has yet to receive a copy of the ruling issued by the Regional Trial Court of Makati and conduct a thorough study thereof, we respect its denial on the motion submitted by the Department of...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Judge says dismissal of Trillanes case 'final, executory' - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1770380/Manila/Local-News/Judge-says-dismissal-of-Trillanes-coup-d-etat-case-final-executory?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEO4e2dKlszk77UG30aVmCAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKmgnQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 11:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1770380/Manila/Local-News/Judge-says-dismissal-of-Trillanes-coup-d-etat-case-final-executory?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;Judge says dismissal of Trillanes case 'final, executory'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SENATOR Antonio Trillanes IV needs not worry about the coup d' etat case against him as a Makati court ruled on Monday, October 22, that the dismissal of the case has become "final and executory" and could no longer be changed. Judge Andres Soriano of the Makati Regional Trial Court Branch 148, in his decision issued on October 22, junked the urgent motion of the Department of Justice for the issuance of an arrest warrant and hold departure order against the senator. Soriano, who tried and then dismissed the coup d' etat case against Trillanes, invoked a “well-established” doctrine that a f...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>SolGen to appeal Makati court ruling on Trillanes - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1770550/Manila/Local-News/SolGen-to-appeal-Makati-court-ruling-on-Trillanes?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP3zx3fJ64qsllhEgTLQ_hMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKmgnQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 06:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1770550/Manila/Local-News/SolGen-to-appeal-Makati-court-ruling-on-Trillanes?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;SolGen to appeal Makati court ruling on Trillanes&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SOLICITOR General Jose Calida will "very soon" challenge before the Court of Appeals (CA) the refusal of Makati Regional Trial Court (RTC) Branch 148 to issue an arrest warrant against opposition Senator Antonio Trillanes IV, Malacañang said on Tuesday, October 23. Instead of filing a motion for reconsideration before the Makati court, Calida would submit a petition before the appellate court, questioning the decision, Presidential Spokesperson Salvador Panelo said. "I've talked with the SolGen and he said he will not file a motion for reconsideration but will go immediately to appeal the r...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Duterte names Faeldon BuCor chief - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/10/12/Duterte-names-Faeldon-BuCor-chief.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIqGE820B6Epvll8F36Dn8wqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMJbthQM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 04:55:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/10/12/Duterte-names-Faeldon-BuCor-chief.html" target="_blank"&gt;Duterte names Faeldon BuCor chief&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, October 12) — Nicanor Faeldon may soon head the Bureau of Corrections (BuCor). President Rodrigo Duterte "has chosen" Faeldon as BuCor Director General, Justice Secretary Menardo Guevarra said Friday. The BuCor, an agency under the Department of Justice (DOJ), is charged with the custody and rehabilitation of offenders. "The DOJ has interposed no objections to the proposed appointment of Mr. Faeldon, and is now seeking the favorable endorsement of the Civil Service Commission (CSC) as part of the requirements under the Bureau of Corrections Act of 2013," Gueva...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>Nicanor Faeldon to take over Bureau of Corrections - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/214137-nicanor-faeldon-bureau-of-corrections</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENQXyyOs3-Rdgdk_eiuhPLoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 04:52:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/214137-nicanor-faeldon-bureau-of-corrections" target="_blank"&gt;Nicanor Faeldon to take over Bureau of Corrections&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – President Rodrigo Duterte wants his first Bureau of Customs chief Nicanor Faeldon to lead another agency – the Bureau of Corrections (BuCor). Justice Secretary Menardo Guevarra said Faeldon is Duterte's choice to succeed former police chief Ronald dela Rosa in that position after the latter filed his candidacy for senator on Friday, October 12. "He's the choice of Malacañang," Guevarra told Rappler in a message. Faeldon has no formal appointment papers yet. Guevarra said the Civil Service Commission (CSC) must first endorse Faeldon. "We need a favorable endorsement fro...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Pasay prosecutor summons Trillanes for 2nd inciting to sedition complaint - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/214460-pasay-prosecutor-summons-trillanes-inciting-to-sedition</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKQlIx9MEpbjVF3gbYOOl4cqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 10:07:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/214460-pasay-prosecutor-summons-trillanes-inciting-to-sedition" target="_blank"&gt;Pasay prosecutor summons Trillanes for 2nd inciting to sedition complaint&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – Senator Antonio Trillanes IV has been summoned to the Pasay City Prosecutor’s Office for a hearing on the newest complaint filed against him by lawyers allied with President Rodrigo Duterte. Lawyer Manny Luna, who has since been appointed commissioner of the Presidential Anti-Corruption Commission (PACC), told reporters on Tuesday, October 16, that city prosecutors issued a subpoena for Trillanes to appear before them on Thursday, October 18, at 1:30 pm. This is over a complaint for inciting to sedition filed against Trillanes by Luna’s group, after the embattled senat...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>DOJ denies allegations of pressure on judge handling Trillanes' coup case - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/10/14/guevarra-alejano-trillanes-soriano-makati-rtc-148-coup-doj.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDMLKykey1jDG3AzR31as5wqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMJbthQM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2018 07:49:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/10/14/guevarra-alejano-trillanes-soriano-makati-rtc-148-coup-doj.html" target="_blank"&gt;DOJ denies allegations of pressure on judge handling Trillanes' coup case&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, October 14) — The Department of Justice (DOJ) is denying allegations a Makati Regional Trial Court (RTC) judge was being told to rule against Senator Antonio Trillanes' coup d'etat case. Justice Secretary Menardo Guevarra said Sunday they took "very strong exception" to a statement by Magdalo Partylist Rep. Gary Alejano Saturday who said they received information that Makati RTC Branch 148 Judge Andres Soriano was receiving pressure to give a negative decision against the embattled lawmaker. "The DOJ does not interact with the judge except through the pleading...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>2nd Makati court's decision on Trillanes' case out anytime - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/214131-makati-rtc-branch-148-decision-trillanes-case-out-anytime-october-12-2018</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJrEixTz7Oay5gEy9kuppNYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 04:12:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/214131-makati-rtc-branch-148-decision-trillanes-case-out-anytime-october-12-2018" target="_blank"&gt;2nd Makati court's decision on Trillanes' case out anytime&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – Anytime soon, the Makati Regional Trial Court Branch 148 will be resolving the Department of Justice (DOJ) request to issue an arrest warrant against Senator Antonio Trillanes IV over his previously dismissed coup d'etat charges. In an order dated October 11, Branch 148 Presiding Judge Andres Soriano said that the court has admitted most of the documentary evidence filed by Trillanes, and will therefore be issuing a decision soon. "[T]he factual issues as specified in the order dated September 28, 2018, and the issue on the 'legality' of Proclamation No. 572, series of...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Trillanes given until October 9 to submit evidence - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1767732</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFB2gqFBIVwd7JxgH5pr5QsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKmgnQM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 11:42:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1767732" target="_blank"&gt;Trillanes given until October 9 to submit evidence&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE Makati Regional Trial Court (RTC) Branch 148 gave the camp of Senator Antonio Trillanes IV more time to submit evidence in connection with the Department of Justice’s (DOJ) motion seeking the issuance of a warrant of arrest and a hold departure order against the embattled senator. Judge Andres Bartolome of Makati RTC Branch 148 gave Trillanes until Tuesday, October 9 within which to file his formal offer of exhibits (evidence). The DOJ will be given one day after the receipt of the said offer to file its comment before the case will be submitted for resolution. During the hearing on Fri...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>No budget to build new prisons, only additional beds for prisoners - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/213424-bucor-budget-2019-increased-bed-capacity</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA6cCyuVxMRjTlCkdZqum-4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 08:31:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/213424-bucor-budget-2019-increased-bed-capacity" target="_blank"&gt;No budget to build new prisons, only additional beds for prisoners&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – The Bureau of Corrections (BuCor) failed to get an additional P5 billion budget to build 6 regional penal facilities, and will have to settle for now for an increased bed capacity in its existing prisons. BuCor Chief General Ronald “Bato” Dela Rosa tried on Wednesday, October 3, to secure an “insertion” of P5 billion for their dreamed 6 prison facilities. “But nung lumabas sa GAA your honor, good for one lang, gusto naming makumpleto ng anim, ito ang bulk ng insertion na gusto namin,” Dela Rosa told Senate Finance Committee Chairman Senator Loren Legarda on Wednesday d...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Guevarra: Up to Duterte if he wants to review other amnesties - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/213655-guevarra-up-to-duterte-review-other-amnesties</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKr_yyYAU1eiE8v6Ee353p8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2018 05:03:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/213655-guevarra-up-to-duterte-review-other-amnesties" target="_blank"&gt;Guevarra: Up to Duterte if he wants to review other amnesties&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – It would be up to President Rodrigo Duterte if the amnesty grants to over 250 people involved in past uprisings with opposition Senator Antonio Trillanes IV would also undergo review, Justice Secretary Menardo Guevarra said on Saturday, October 6. “It is up to the President what he wants to do with the grant of amnesty to other individuals,” Guevarra said. The justice secretary was asked about the fate of 250 other individuals who were granted amnesty in connection with their participation in the 2003 Oakwood mutiny and the 2007 Manila Peninsula siege, after the Depar...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>DOJ's latest proof vs Trillanes: No minutes of all amnesty deliberations - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/213569-doj-latest-proof-vs-trillanes-no-minutes-amnesty-deliberations</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELv1Q96XzTFo4tKhug2hm-EqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 02:50:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/213569-doj-latest-proof-vs-trillanes-no-minutes-amnesty-deliberations" target="_blank"&gt;DOJ's latest proof vs Trillanes: No minutes of all amnesty deliberations&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines - The Department of National Defense (DND) said on Friday, October 5, that there are no records of minutes of deliberations for the more than 250 amnesty applications under former president Benigno Aquino III's Proclamation No. 75. The Department of Justice (DOJ) initially told the Makati Regional Trial Court (RTC) Branch 150 that DND has no minutes for the deliberations of Senator Antonio Trillanes IV’s application amnesty. But a cross examination of DND chief counsel Norman Daanoy showed that there are no minutes for everyone who applied under Aquino’s amnesty grant. T...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>DOCUMENTS: Calida security firm 'corners' at least 16 gov't contracts - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/213339-documents-calida-security-agency-government-contracts-since-2016</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG84ynm5QjGvc9CHS2h_UhQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 08:32:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/213339-documents-calida-security-agency-government-contracts-since-2016" target="_blank"&gt;DOCUMENTS: Calida security firm 'corners' at least 16 gov't contracts&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – It was business as usual for opposition Senator Antonio Trillanes IV as he delivered a privilege speech hitting Solicitor General Jose Calida, who instigated the review of his amnesty records. Trillanes in a privilege speech on Tuesday, October 2, bared a rundown of at least 16 government contracts "cornered" by Vigilant Investigative and Security Agency Incorporated, owned by Calida and his family, since becoming solicitor general in 2016. The contracts have a total amount of P358.3 million. Rappler separately obtained copies of the contracts. This amount is higher th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Palparan transferred to New Bilibid Prison - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/10/03/jovito-palparan-transfer-new-bilibid-prison.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMUwm5jhDdoTQP36951xAkwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMJbthQM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 15:28:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/10/03/jovito-palparan-transfer-new-bilibid-prison.html" target="_blank"&gt;Palparan transferred to New Bilibid Prison&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, October 3) — Retired Major General Jovito Palparan Jr. has been turned over to the New Bilibid Prison (NBP). This was confirmed by Justice Secretary Menardo Guevarra Wednesday who said the transfer happened at 7:45 p.m. Army spokesperson Lt. Col. Louie Villanueva also confirmed Palparan's transfer, saying, "Naturn-over na, naturn-over na namin sa (New) Bilibid Prisons...What's important is we already did our job of turning them over to (New) Bilibid... We transported them there." [Translation: We've turned them over to the New Bilibid Prisons...What's importan...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>Trillanes to Guevarra: Learn to say 'no' - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/10/03/Trillanes-Guevarra-Duterte-amnesty-row.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKoHC6s60BuhLb_oqenjd2YqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMJbthQM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 09:52:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/10/03/Trillanes-Guevarra-Duterte-amnesty-row.html" target="_blank"&gt;Trillanes to Guevarra: Learn to say 'no'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, October 3) — Senator Antonio Trillanes IV on Wednesday met face-to-face with the head of the government agency that had asked the court to have him arrested. The embattled senator was calm as he confronted Justice Secretary Menardo Guevarra during a Senate hearing on the proposed budget of the Department of Justice (DOJ) for next year. "Your department is very powerful. You can be, for the matter, the instrument for dispensing justice. Sadly, in the wrong hands, it can be used also as an instrument of injustice," Trillanes told Guevarra who was seated across h...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>Legarda pushes new law to raise salary of immigration workers - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/213432-bureau-of-immigration-2019-budget-augmented-salaries</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGsNbzxfxtxfNtQGRLei_lcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 09:17:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/213432-bureau-of-immigration-2019-budget-augmented-salaries" target="_blank"&gt;Legarda pushes new law to raise salary of immigration workers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – Senator Loren Legarda on Wednesday, October 3, arranged for a special meeting to expedite the passage of a bill that seeks to address the problem of low pay in the Bureau of Immigration (BI). Legarda said she will push for a meeting with Senator Richard Gordon, chair of the Senate justice committee, to hold hearings on the passage of Senate Bill No 1556 which she authored. The measure, filed last year, remained at the committee level. “Let’s urge Senator Gordon – just one hearing. It’s a recurring problem. Until it’s enacted we’ll always have this problem,” Legarda sai...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Palparan to be moved to Bilibid soon – DOJ - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/213341-jovito-palparan-move-bilibid</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN_6blE3hIT0vBXm_H2SyhEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 08:59:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/213341-jovito-palparan-move-bilibid" target="_blank"&gt;Palparan to be moved to Bilibid soon – DOJ&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – Convicted kidnapper Jovito Palparan will be moved to the New Bilibid Prison (NBP) soon, the Department of Justice said on Tuesday, October 2. Justice Secretary Menardo Guevarra said on Tuesday that the Malolos Regional Trial Court (RTC) denied the motion of the retired army major general to stop his transfer from a military camp in Fort Bonifacio to Bilibid. Palparan argued before Malolos RTC Branch 15 that he should be allowed to remain in Fort Bonifacio as he had a pending case before another branch. Branch 15 Judge Alexander Tamayo denied Palparan’s appeal, citing S...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Albayalde orders recall of Trillanes' police detail over amnesty issue - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/213536-pnp-chief-albayalde-orders-trillanes-police-detail-recall</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAj-ZBoYwD3jF8pOS3zVOoUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2018 11:59:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/213536-pnp-chief-albayalde-orders-trillanes-police-detail-recall" target="_blank"&gt;Albayalde orders recall of Trillanes' police detail over amnesty issue&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – Following President Rodrigo Duterte’s order to revoke Senator Antonio Trillanes IV’s amnesty, Philippine National Police chief Oscar Albayalde also ordered the recall of the opposition senator’s police detail. A source from the PNP confirmed this to Rappler on Thursday, October 4. The source said Albayalde ordered it on September 4, the same day Duterte’s Proclamation 572 was published in the Manila Times. "Instruction ni CPNP (It was the instruction of the chief of the PNP)," said a source from the PNP Police Security and Protection Group in a text message to Rappler....&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Palparan's transfer to Bilibid seen this week - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/10/02/Jovito-Palparan-transfer-Bilibid-kidnappping-Sherlyn-Cadapan-Karen-Empe%C3%B1o.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEACGv0VM8f9dm0yjd9nqppQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMJbthQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 10:16:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/10/02/Jovito-Palparan-transfer-Bilibid-kidnappping-Sherlyn-Cadapan-Karen-Empe%C3%B1o.html" target="_blank"&gt;Palparan's transfer to Bilibid seen this week&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, October 2) — Retired Major General Jovito Palparan, Jr. will finally be transferred to the New Bilibid Prison (NBP) on Thursday, more than two weeks after he was found guilty of kidnapping two students. The Department of Justice (DOJ) said Tuesday the decision came after the Malolos, Bulacan Regional Trial Court Branch 15 denied Palparan's motion to hold the implementation of his transfer to the national penitentiary in Muntinlupa. The DOJ said the Malolos court in its decision cited the Supreme Court's circular, "which directs all trial court judges to cause ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>Ledesma: The tale of EJK (Part 2 of 2) - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1767496</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM-2ACN2yb6UWPSjYnH4AWcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKeunQM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 16:52:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1767496" target="_blank"&gt;Ledesma: The tale of EJK (Part 2 of 2)&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;IN ANOTHER celebrated case several members of a kidnap-for-ransom syndicate who victimised a businesswoman from Quezon City were all killed in an exchange of gunfire with police operatives led by then Davao City Police Chief Ronald “Bato” dela Rosa. In an on-the-spot interview with Bato, he told the media: “The order of the Mayor (Duterte) was shoot-to-kill if they will fight it out with the law”. Years had elapsed CHR Chair De Lima became Secretary of Justice and was replaced by Etta Rosales. De Lima had spent over four months digging for what she claimed were common graves of EJK victims ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>SC junks Peter Lim's bid to stop drug case - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1766232</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEANmbWGyqKoRptP4P3COAKEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKmgnQM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 10:07:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1766232" target="_blank"&gt;SC junks Peter Lim's bid to stop drug case&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE Supreme Court (SC) has junked the petition filed by accused drug lord Peter Lim that challenged the Department of Justice’s (DOJ) order to reinvestigate the drug charges against him, Justice Secretary Menardo Guevarra said on Wednesday, September 26. In a text message, Guevarra said the Supreme Court has found no abuse of discretion on the part of the DOJ when it decided to reinvestigate the charges against Lim. The SC Third Division said in its decision, dated July 23 and released to the media on September 26, that it junked Lim’s petition "for failure to show any grave abuse of discre...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Guevarra: Logical to start amnesty review with 'most vocal' Trillanes - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/212867-doj-guevarra-logical-start-amnesty-review-trillanes</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJHvcGreM0AkVJ4QN83jXFYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 04:49:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/212867-doj-guevarra-logical-start-amnesty-review-trillanes" target="_blank"&gt;Guevarra: Logical to start amnesty review with 'most vocal' Trillanes&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – Justice Secretary Menardo Guevarra said on Wednesday, September 26, that other amnesty grants will be reviewed or reopened following the case of the “most vocal” opposition Senator Antonio Trillanes IV. The amnesties given to Trillanes’ fellow mutineers at the Magdalo group, in particular, are also being reviewed, said Guevarra. “We cannot take away that risk that they're found to be deficient or non-compliant with the requirements for amnesty. Then any other person who might have not complied may suffer the same situation as Senator Trillanes,” he said. Guevarra added...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>2nd Makati court defers decision on Trillanes arrest - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/212930-makati-rtc-branch-148-no-decision-trillanes-arrest-september-28-2018</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENLVP7K0ge0zi9byLi85spEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 05:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/212930-makati-rtc-branch-148-no-decision-trillanes-arrest-september-28-2018" target="_blank"&gt;2nd Makati court defers decision on Trillanes arrest&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines (UPDATED) – The Makati Regional Trial Court (RTC) Branch 148 on Friday, September 28, deferred its decision on the Department of Justice (DOJ) request to issue an arrest warrant against Senator Antonio Trillanes IV over his previously dismissed coup d’etat charges. Makati RTC branch 148 Judge Andres Soriano set another hearing on October 5, Trillanes' lawyer Rey Robles confirmed. “The resolution of the Very Urgent Ex-parte Omnibus Motion for the issuance ofHold Departure Order (HDO) and Alias Warrant of Arrest against Antonio Trillanes IV is DEFERRED,” the court said. T...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Lawyers press military to transfer Palparan to Bilibid - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/212736-national-union-peoples-lawyers-press-military-transfer-palparan-new-bilibid-prison</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFLkG8PZ3ic9biZjiaMnTacqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 09:39:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/212736-national-union-peoples-lawyers-press-military-transfer-palparan-new-bilibid-prison" target="_blank"&gt;Lawyers press military to transfer Palparan to Bilibid&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – Why is retired army major general Jovito Palparan still inside a military camp in Fort Bonifacio? The National Union of Peoples’ Lawyers (NUPL), which represented the families of University of the Philippines (UP) student activists Sherlyn Cadapan and Karen Empeño, said on Monday, September 24, that the military is acting in contempt of a court order to transfer Palparan to the New Bilibid Prison. Malolos, Bulacan Regional Trial Court Branch 15 had issued a commitment order to transfer Palparan to Bilibid on the same day (September 17) that the guilty verdict was hande...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Supreme Court allows drug charges vs Peter Lim to continue - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/212892-supreme-court-decision-allows-drug-charges-vs-peter-lim-to-continue</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENTMW7DdJLbPN2fgfGFla-4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 08:59:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/212892-supreme-court-decision-allows-drug-charges-vs-peter-lim-to-continue" target="_blank"&gt;Supreme Court allows drug charges vs Peter Lim to continue&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – The Supreme Court denied fugitive Peter Lim’s request to nullify the Department of Justice (DOJ) reinvestigation against him, and in effect, allowed the drug charges to continue against him at the Makati Regional Trial Court (RTC). “The Court resolves to dismiss the petition for failure to show any grave abuse of discretion in rendering the challenged order and resolution, which, on the contrary, appear to be in accord with the facts and the applicable law and jurisprudence,” said a notice from the Supreme Court received by parties on September 24, but dated July 23. L...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>ANALYSIS: Philippine courts dribble, stall on Trillanes amnesty issue - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/newsbreak/iq/213063-courts-philippines-dribble-stall-trillanes-amnesty</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGV9hRW0bhqQBIWwwyz_CWYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJ_jmQI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 10:49:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/newsbreak/iq/213063-courts-philippines-dribble-stall-trillanes-amnesty" target="_blank"&gt;ANALYSIS: Philippine courts dribble, stall on Trillanes amnesty issue&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – It started with a loud, clear message on September 4, when Malacañang published the presidential proclamation that voided the amnesty granted to President Rodrigo Duterte’s fierce enemy Senator Antonio Trillanes IV. Arrest Trillanes and send him back to jail, said the order. That day, Justice Secretary Menardo Guevarra, who was also the country’s officer-in-charge at the time, confirmed the government’s order to apprehend Trillanes even without a warrant of arrest. But the military and the police pushed back, with the Philippine courts dribbling and stalling. So the mo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>From posh hotels to the Senate: The 3 times Senator Trillanes was arrested - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/newsbreak/iq/212816-antonio-trillanes-iv-arrests</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN3C0jz5SJC7h1lNX_b_lhcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJ_jmQI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2018 10:06:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/newsbreak/iq/212816-antonio-trillanes-iv-arrests" target="_blank"&gt;From posh hotels to the Senate: The 3 times Senator Trillanes was arrested&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippine – Senator Antonio Trillanes IV was arrested on Wednesday, September 25, for the charge of rebellion, a case that he was already given amnesty under the Aquino administration. He became the 2nd opposition senator arrested under President Rodrigo Duterte. The controversy was sparked by issuance of Proclamation No. 572 which revoked the amnesty granted in connection to the 2003 Oakwood mutiny and the 2007 Manila Peninsula siege. (TIMELINE: Trillanes, from mutiny to amnesty) But this is not the first arrest of Trillanes. The latest development raises his arrest counter to 3 –...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Groups on Trillanes arrest: Part of crackdown on gov't critics - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/212885-groups-condemn-trillanes-arrest-crackdown-duterte-critics</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH6D3TAkBYX6YGZGaSHuS0sqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 07:34:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/212885-groups-condemn-trillanes-arrest-crackdown-duterte-critics" target="_blank"&gt;Groups on Trillanes arrest: Part of crackdown on gov't critics&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – Groups condemned the arrest of Senator Antonio Trillanes IV, calling it a blatant political attack of President Rodrigo Duterte against the political opposition. Human Rights Watch (HRW) on Tuesday, September 25, said that the arrest is just part of persecution of people deemed critics of the government. “It’s the latest in the relentless campaign to silence those who dared to challenge the president’s murderous drug war,” Carlos Conde of HRW’s Asia Division said. “Trillanes's arrest today sends a chilling effect among other critics of the Duterte administration,” Con...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Taguba, 8 others indicted for breaking Tariff Code in shabu case - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/212648-doj-indicts-mark-taguba-violation-tariff-code-shabu-shipment-customs</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFOH9SLKVck3pxIPfOicMjwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2018 11:48:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/212648-doj-indicts-mark-taguba-violation-tariff-code-shabu-shipment-customs" target="_blank"&gt;Taguba, 8 others indicted for breaking Tariff Code in shabu case&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – The Department of Justice (DOJ) indicted customs broker Mark Taguba and 8 others for allegedly breaking the Tariff Code in relation to the P6.4-billion shabu shipment smuggled into the Philippines in 2017. The 9 individuals allegedly violated Section 1400 of the Customs Modernization and Tariff Act (CMTA), which prohibits the "misdeclaration, misclassification, and undervaluation" of imported goods. In its resolution, the DOJ said the actions of the respondents showed there was "conspiracy" in bringing the shipment into the Philippines from China in May 2017 despite th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>PNP vows legal support to Espenido amid homicide raps - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1765238</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENBRJrfLBuVCwiot2B3fKRMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKmgnQM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2018 07:51:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1765238" target="_blank"&gt;PNP vows legal support to Espenido amid homicide raps&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE Philippine National Police (PNP) vowed to give support to Ozamiz City Police Director Jovie Espenido and two other police officers who are facing homicide charges over the killing of six drug and robbery suspects in June 2017. “Definitely, we will support our people in their legal struggle lalo na ang kanilang legal struggle ay as a result of the performance of duty,” said PNP spokesperson Chief Superintendent Benigno Durana Jr. “Meron po tayong legal service sa PNP and, of course, having a legal counsel they should have familiarity and confidence who will represent in court. So depende...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Sister Fox appeals denial of missionary visa extension - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/212184-patricia-fox-appeals-denial-missionary-visa-extension-bureau-immigration</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH_VcOzEifbO5xEVWMaQtb8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 09:56:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/212184-patricia-fox-appeals-denial-missionary-visa-extension-bureau-immigration" target="_blank"&gt;Sister Fox appeals denial of missionary visa extension&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – Australian nun Sister Patricia Fox on Monday, September 17, appealed the Bureau of Immigration (BI) order refusing to extend her missionary visa in the Philippines. Fox appeared at the BI at around 2 pm on Monday along with her lawyer, Jobert Pahilga, to file a 6-page appeal against the BI order released to the media on Sunday, September 16. Fox is the 72-year-old Australian missionary nun whom the BI ordered deported for allegedly engaging in political activities. It was President Rodrigo Duterte himself who had Fox investigated, prompting the BI to expel her from the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>DOJ to court: 'Simply ignore' case dismissal, get Trillanes out of his 'hole' - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/211902-doj-told-makati-rtc-148-ignore-trillanes-case-dismissal</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECeDAyqeAQ33ZS20NAxaRR0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 05:09:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/211902-doj-told-makati-rtc-148-ignore-trillanes-case-dismissal" target="_blank"&gt;DOJ to court: 'Simply ignore' case dismissal, get Trillanes out of his 'hole'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – The Department of Justice (DOJ) has told the Makati Regional Trial Court (RTC) Branch 148 that it “may simply ignore” the dismissal of the cases of Senator Antonio Trillanes IV in 2011, and order his arrest to get him out of his "hole." Thursday, September 13, is Trillanes’ 10th day holed up inside his Senate office as he tried to fend off a warrantless arrest that remained his top fears, despite a pronouncement from President Rodrigo Duterte himself that he will not be arrested without a warrant. (READ: EXPLAINER: What the Supreme Court TRO denial means for Trillanes)...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>No warrant again, Trillanes can rest easy this weekend - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/211961-no-arrest-warrant-trillanes-makati-rtc-branch-150-september-14-2018</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED7IPCgGqH_DWkcr8gOy4qoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 02:19:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/211961-no-arrest-warrant-trillanes-makati-rtc-branch-150-september-14-2018" target="_blank"&gt;No warrant again, Trillanes can rest easy this weekend&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines (UPDATED) – Still no warrant of arrest for Senator Antonio Trillanes IV. The Makati Regional Trial Court (RTC) Branch 150 allowed for more time to file pleadings, deferring the decision on the issuance of an arrest warrant after a hearing on Friday, September 14. Branch 150 Judge Elmo Alameda ordered the Department of Justice (DOJ) to submit within 5 days a reply to the opposition of Trillanes. Afterwards, Trillanes is also given 5 days to file a rejoinder to the DOJ’s reply. So as far as court-issued warrants are concerened, Trillanes can rest easy this weekend and even...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Court defers arrest warrant vs Trillanes - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1764115</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENdMZcNQ5Asnnir91slOFjsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKmgnQM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 06:31:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1764115" target="_blank"&gt;Court defers arrest warrant vs Trillanes&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE Makati Regional Trial Court (RTC) Branch 148 has deferred the resolution on the motion filed by the Department of Justice that seeks the issuance of an alias warrant of arrest and a hold departure order against Senator Antonio Trillanes IV. The court gave Trillanes 10 days to submit a supplemental comment and a rejoinder to the pleading filed against him by the DOJ, in compliance with Proclamation 572. The Makati RTC Branch 150 also earlier deferred the issuance of a warrant of arrest against the senator, a former Navy officer involved in two uprisings against former President Gloria Ma...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>New case? De Lima is summoned by NBI for a drug investigation - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/211660-nbi-subpoena-de-lima-drug-investigation-september-2018</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIgQwXllIdbO28Dxf08TcpwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 11:46:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/211660-nbi-subpoena-de-lima-drug-investigation-september-2018" target="_blank"&gt;New case? De Lima is summoned by NBI for a drug investigation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines (UPDATED) – Senator Leila de Lima has been served a subpoena by the National Bureau of Investigation (NBI) for a drug-related probe connected to “the extrajudicial confession” of alleged Visayas drug lord Kerwin Espinosa. According to the subpoena received on September 7, NBI agents will go inside Camp Crame on Friday, September 14, to ask De Lima to giver “her evidence..in a certain investigation conducted by this bureau.” “There being no copy of the purported extrajudicial confession attached to the one-page Subpoena, I have no idea what allegations or accusations are ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>TIMELINE: Trillanes, from mutiny to amnesty - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/newsbreak/iq/211894-timeline-antonio-trillanes-iv-mutiny-to-amnesty</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEECk7wYcJuqg9jWlCIsUb2kqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJ_jmQI</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2018 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/newsbreak/iq/211894-timeline-antonio-trillanes-iv-mutiny-to-amnesty" target="_blank"&gt;TIMELINE: Trillanes, from mutiny to amnesty&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – Coup d'etat and rebellion charges against Senator Antonio Trillanes IV were once again in the spotlight, after President Rodrigo Duterte signed on August 31 a proclamation revoking the amnesty granted to the opposition senator in 2011. Here's a rundown of what happened to Trillanes, from the mutiny that started it all, leading up to the voiding of his amnesty. 2003 Rumors have been circulating about junior military officers planning to take action against reported corruption in the armed forces. Among their grievances are the lack of housing and incentives for soldiers...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>DOJ hands off on other Trillanes cases for now - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/211655-doj-hands-off-trillanes-cases-for-now</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG6d-wWZIa822-U7xm8YhEkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 10:32:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/211655-doj-hands-off-trillanes-cases-for-now" target="_blank"&gt;DOJ hands off on other Trillanes cases for now&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – The Department of Justice (DOJ) is actively seeking the arrest of Senator Antonio Trillanes IV on charges connected to the failed coup attempts led by the former soldier in 2003 and 2007, but Justice Secretary Guevarra said those are the only two cases against Trillanes that they will handle for now. “There is no such order for state prosecutors to take over other pending criminal cases against Senator Trillanes,” Guevarra said in a text message on Monday, September 10. The other cases and complaints against Trillanes are being handled by city prosecutors of Pasay City...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>IBP hits DOJ for 'mischief' in Trillanes case - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/211601-ibp-statement-doj-trillanes-amnesty-arrest-case</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ0rGdAwbqv_rVY6k066Hm0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 03:08:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/211601-ibp-statement-doj-trillanes-amnesty-arrest-case" target="_blank"&gt;IBP hits DOJ for 'mischief' in Trillanes case&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – The Integrated Bar of the Philippines (IBP) called out the Department of Justice (DOJ) for what it called "potential mischief" in trying to get two courts in Makati City to order the arrest of opposition Senator Antonio Trillanes IV. The DOJ filed two motions for an arrest warrant within 4 days of each other before Branches 148 and 150 of the Makati City Regional Trial Court (RTC). "An apparent act of forum shopping, IBP decries the potential mischief where we subject the judiciary to an anomalous situation where one court upholds the validity of the amnesty while the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>2nd Makati court defers Trillanes arrest order, travel ban - CNN Philippines</title><link>http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/09/14/Trillanes-arrest-amnesty-Makati-RTC-Branch-150.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKu2-oW39Uf8DOXW_F52BqgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqJnyCjCDutUBMJbthQM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 08:03:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/09/14/Trillanes-arrest-amnesty-Makati-RTC-Branch-150.html" target="_blank"&gt;2nd Makati court defers Trillanes arrest order, travel ban&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Manila (CNN Philippines, September 14) — No civilian court will issue an arrest warrant and travel ban order against Senator Antonio Trillanes IV for now. Makati Regional Trial Court Branch 150 Judge Elmo Alameda on Friday asked the Department of Justice reply within five days on Trillanes' comments. It also asked Trillanes to file a rejoinder on the agency's petition for an arrest warrant and hold departure order against the senator after five days. During the hearing, Trillanes' chief legal counsel Rey Robles presented evidence proving there is no basis for President Rodrigo Duterte...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cnnphilippines.com">CNN Philippines</source></item><item><title>Supreme Court denies Trillanes request for TRO - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/211694-sc-action-trillanes-denied-tro-duterte-order-amnesty-revocation</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPZpUvB-P7eNEFbHJr1NaaYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/211694-sc-action-trillanes-denied-tro-duterte-order-amnesty-revocation" target="_blank"&gt;Supreme Court denies Trillanes request for TRO&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines (4th UPDATE) – The Supreme Court (SC) en banc on Tuesday, September 11, denied the request of Senator Antonio Trillanes IV for a temporary restraining order (TRO). The en banc also asked the Office of the Solicitor General (OSG) to comment in 10 days on Trillanes' main petition for further deliberations. With this, the attention now shifts again to the two Makati courts which will hear this week the DOJ’s motions for a warrant of arrest against Trillanes in previously dismissed cases of coup d’etat and rebellion. "It is appropriate that the Makati Regional Trial Courts (...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Still no warrant, as judge tells DOJ to give Trillanes due process - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/211626-no-arrest-warrant-trillanes-from-makati-rtc-branch-150-september-10-2018</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP_e5k-acozhJ_E6P6Y7ZuEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 06:32:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/211626-no-arrest-warrant-trillanes-from-makati-rtc-branch-150-september-10-2018" target="_blank"&gt;Still no warrant, as judge tells DOJ to give Trillanes due process&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – Give the opposition senator his due process. This is what Makati Regional Trial Court (RTC) Branch 150 Judge Elmo Alameda said in his order issued Monday, September 10, setting for hearing the Department of Justice or DOJ’s urgent motion to issue an arrest warrant against Senator Antonio Trillanes IV. This follows President Rodrigo Duterte's Proclamation No. 572 that voided the amnesty of Trillanes, and which prompted the DOJ to try and reopen charges at the lower courts related to Trillanes et al's failed coup attempts. Alameda said he “is not persuaded with the argum...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Agabin, Hilbay join Trillanes legal team - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/211886-agabin-hilbay-join-trillanes-legal-team</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPJ8ZHS3em5qqn7SoRJQVXsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 01:10:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/211886-agabin-hilbay-join-trillanes-legal-team" target="_blank"&gt;Agabin, Hilbay join Trillanes legal team&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – Senator Antonio Trillanes IV has tapped legal experts to join his team of counsels as they prepare for battle both in the lower courts and the Supreme Court. Trillanes announced on Thursday, September 13, that his lead counsel Rey Robles will be joined by 3 law professors considered experts in their fields. Former University of the Philippines (UP) Law Dean Pacifico Agabin and former solicitor General Florin Hilbay will join the team. Both taught or are teaching Constitutional Law. Agabin also chairs the Constitutional Law Department of the Philippine Judicial Academy ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Duterte did not consult Lorenzana on Trillanes' amnesty - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/211619-duterte-did-not-consult-lorenzana-trillanes-amnesty</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELveKBWerQ6E3BLIQltzDW8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 05:02:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/211619-duterte-did-not-consult-lorenzana-trillanes-amnesty" target="_blank"&gt;Duterte did not consult Lorenzana on Trillanes' amnesty&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines (UPDATED) – Defense Secretary Delfin Lorenzana was not consulted by President Rodrigo Duterte before the latter signed Proclamation No. 572, which voided the amnesty of mutineer-turned-senator Antonio Trillanes IV. Lorenzana disclosed this to reporters in Camp Aguinaldo on Monday, September 10. "Did the President consult you before he signed Proclamation 572?" a reporter asked. "No, I was not," Lorenzana, who has administrative supervision over the armed forces, replied even before the question ended. (READ: Analysis: Don't mess with the miltary) Duterte's proclamation o...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Trillanes will not leave Senate anytime soon: 'I won't fall into Duterte trap' - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/211617-trillanes-will-not-leave-senate-office-anytime-soon</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELGQ8OW0E85dypcJZoX6AJUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 04:58:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/211617-trillanes-will-not-leave-senate-office-anytime-soon" target="_blank"&gt;Trillanes will not leave Senate anytime soon: 'I won't fall into Duterte trap'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – Opposition senator Antonio Trillanes IV would continue staying in his Senate office despite the statements of President Rodrigo Duterte and the Armed Forces of the Philippines ruling out a warrantless arrest for him. For Trillanes, it was just Duterte's trap to lure him into going out of the chamber to arrest him. Citing supposed sources on the ground, Trillanes said the military still has a standing order to arrest him. “Ang problema sa statement n'ya may deniability kaya vinalidate natin doon sa ground, sa operating units, at meron pa rin eh (The problem with his sta...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Lorenzana assures Trillanes: 'No warrant, no arrest' - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/nation/211773-lorenzana-trillanes-assurance-no-warrant-no-arrest</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAVvjBdQZnuflGMnQApi-uwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJuOnAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 15:15:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/nation/211773-lorenzana-trillanes-assurance-no-warrant-no-arrest" target="_blank"&gt;Lorenzana assures Trillanes: 'No warrant, no arrest'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA, Philippines – Defense Secretary Delfin Lorenzana ruled out any possibility of a warrantless arrest against Senator Antonio Trillanes IV after the Supreme Court (SC) denied the senator's request for an order halting the President's proclamation that voided his amnesty. "No warrant, no arrest," Lorenzana told Rappler when asked what for the military's action following the decision of the SC. Why this matters: If the chief of the Department of National Defense (DND) is to be believed, Trillanes may consider leaving the Senate. The former mutineer-turned-senator previously said he would...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item></channel></rss>