<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Test - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIggKIhxDQkFTRHdvSkwyMHZNREZuWkRGakVnSmxiaWdBUAE?hl=en-PH&amp;gl=PH&amp;ceid=PH:en</link><language>en-PH</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 14:17:04 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Headteacher leaves primary school after tests investigation - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/education/2018/dec/04/headteacher-leaves-primary-school-after-tests-investigation</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMKfwuWJiXfSFOUCzCAbMw4qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 15:34:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/education/2018/dec/04/headteacher-leaves-primary-school-after-tests-investigation" target="_blank"&gt;Headteacher leaves primary school after tests investigation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The headteacher and two other staff members have left a London primary school after an internal investigation found that Sats papers had been systematically ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>A test of critical thinking: Why don’t all AP students take AP tests? - Washington Post</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/local/education/a-test-of-critical-thinking-why-dont-all-ap-students-take-ap-tests/2018/12/06/01c3283c-f998-11e8-8d64-4e79db33382f_story.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMirAFodHRwczovL3d3dy53YXNoaW5ndG9ucG9zdC5jb20vbG9jYWwvZWR1Y2F0aW9uL2EtdGVzdC1vZi1jcml0aWNhbC10aGlua2luZy13aHktZG9udC1hbGwtYXAtc3R1ZGVudHMtdGFrZS1hcC10ZXN0cy8yMDE4LzEyLzA2LzAxYzMyODNjLWY5OTgtMTFlOC04ZDY0LTRlNzlkYjMzMzgyZl9zdG9yeS5odG1s0gGDAmh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LXdhc2hpbmd0b25wb3N0LWNvbS5jZG4uYW1wcHJvamVjdC5vcmcvdi9zL3d3dy53YXNoaW5ndG9ucG9zdC5jb20vYW1waHRtbC9sb2NhbC9lZHVjYXRpb24vYS10ZXN0LW9mLWNyaXRpY2FsLXRoaW5raW5nLXdoeS1kb250LWFsbC1hcC1zdHVkZW50cy10YWtlLWFwLXRlc3RzLzIwMTgvMTIvMDYvMDFjMzI4M2MtZjk5OC0xMWU4LThkNjQtNGU3OWRiMzMzODJmX3N0b3J5Lmh0bWw_YW1wX2pzX3Y9MC4xI3dlYnZpZXc9MSZjYXA9c3dpcGU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 12:01:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/local/education/a-test-of-critical-thinking-why-dont-all-ap-students-take-ap-tests/2018/12/06/01c3283c-f998-11e8-8d64-4e79db33382f_story.html" target="_blank"&gt;A test of critical thinking: Why don’t all AP students take AP tests?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Washington Post&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Houston's system shows why this daring idea is a money-saver in the long run.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.washingtonpost.com">Washington Post</source></item><item><title>Students taking STAAR tests this week can get free guacamole - KXAN.com</title><link>https://www.kxan.com/news/local/austin/students-taking-staar-tests-this-week-can-get-free-guacamole/1636243038</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMibmh0dHBzOi8vd3d3Lmt4YW4uY29tL25ld3MvbG9jYWwvYXVzdGluL3N0dWRlbnRzLXRha2luZy1zdGFhci10ZXN0cy10aGlzLXdlZWstY2FuLWdldC1mcmVlLWd1YWNhbW9sZS8xNjM2MjQzMDM40gG3AWh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LWt4YW4tY29tLmNkbi5hbXBwcm9qZWN0Lm9yZy92L3Mvd3d3Lmt4YW4uY29tL2FtcC9uZXdzL2xvY2FsL2F1c3Rpbi9zdHVkZW50cy10YWtpbmctc3RhYXItdGVzdHMtdGhpcy13ZWVrLWNhbi1nZXQtZnJlZS1ndWFjYW1vbGUvMTYzNjI0MzAzOD9hbXBfanNfdj0wLjEjd2Vidmlldz0xJmNhcD1zd2lwZQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 14:56:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.kxan.com/news/local/austin/students-taking-staar-tests-this-week-can-get-free-guacamole/1636243038" target="_blank"&gt;Students taking STAAR tests this week can get free guacamole&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;KXAN.com&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;AUSTIN (KXAN) — Some students in Texas are taking standardized tests before they head off to Christmas break, and Chipotle wants to give them an early ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.kxan.com">KXAN.com</source></item><item><title>79,000 pass September 2018 board exams for teachers - ABS CBN News</title><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKk23VnmTXEjqq4kJs58HTkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow8IjwCjDw4s8CMNj9mQI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 06:41:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABS CBN News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA- A total of 79, 212 passed the licensure examination for teachers given last September, the Professional Regulation Commission (PRC) announced Friday. The PRC said 18,409 elementary teachers out of 90,750 examinees and 60,803 secondary teachers out of 126,582 examinees passed the exams. Of the elementary teachers who passed, 17,200 are first timers and 1,209 are repeaters. For the secondary teachers, 52,453 passers are first timers and 8,350 are repeaters. Rhea Joy Yebes Genson from the University of Southeastern Philippines- Davao City topped the licensure exams for elementary teach...&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Americans Don't Agree On What They Want From Schools. That's OK. - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/mikemcshane/2018/12/07/americans-dont-agree-on-what-they-want-from-schools-thats-ok/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJHGVkVbH9wjUoUYTu4UdXoqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMKGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 14:44:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/mikemcshane/2018/12/07/americans-dont-agree-on-what-they-want-from-schools-thats-ok/" target="_blank"&gt;Americans Don't Agree On What They Want From Schools. That's OK.&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;What do we want out of our schools? It turns out, opinions differ. That is the takeaway from EdChoice’s annual Schooling in America Survey. The survey asked respondents where they would send their children if they had a totally free choice. Thirty-six percent said traditional public school, 13% said charter, 40% said private, and 10% said homeschool (two percent didn’t know). Now, the headline of this graph is usually the comparison between stated preferences and the actual enrollment of students across the country (82% of children attend traditional public schools, 5% attend charter school...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Getting In: Admissions Advice from Architecture Programs Around the World - ArchDaily</title><link>https://www.archdaily.com/907252/getting-in-admissions-advice-from-architecture-programs-around-the-world</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECHh0UHrZdMgFWe6XZcmscIqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowkLQGMJBaMK-8Ag</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.archdaily.com/907252/getting-in-admissions-advice-from-architecture-programs-around-the-world" target="_blank"&gt;Getting In: Admissions Advice from Architecture Programs Around the World&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ArchDaily&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MIT. Image As a follow up to A Glimpse Into the Weird World of Architecture Students' First Assignments I wanted to explore what architecture schools from around the world are looking for in creating their institution’s community of young architects. Approximately 3,550 students enroll annually in the United States into an accredited Bachelor of Architecture (BArch) program according to the National Architectural Accrediting Board (NAAB) and about 70% of that enrollment eventually graduate with a degree in architecture. There are 51 Accredited BArch programs in the United States compared to...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.archdaily.com">ArchDaily</source></item><item><title>How Academic Standards Can Hold Students Back - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/nataliewexler/2018/12/05/how-academic-standards-can-hold-students-back/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKBwTrerAdfuZjBcGrspsmcqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMKGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 14:36:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/nataliewexler/2018/12/05/how-academic-standards-can-hold-students-back/" target="_blank"&gt;How Academic Standards Can Hold Students Back&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Education experts have long argued for rigorous state standards on the theory they’ll lead to better curriculum—and higher student achievement. But in most of the U.S., literacy standards have only perpetuated confusion about what good curriculum looks like. And students have suffered as a result. Here’s how things were supposed to work, according to the standards-based reform movement that began about thirty years ago: First, states would adopt broad and ambitious descriptions of what students “should know and be able to do” at each grade level. Then education publishers would create detai...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Revealed: bias faced by minorities in UK driving tests - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2018/dec/03/black-women-far-less-likely-than-white-men-to-pass-driving-tests</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOTWVftzcQV_XQmB7g_D1W0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 10:54:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2018/dec/03/black-women-far-less-likely-than-white-men-to-pass-driving-tests" target="_blank"&gt;Revealed: bias faced by minorities in UK driving tests&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Women and people of colour are significantly less likely than white men to pass UK practical driving tests, according to data analysed by the Guardian. Related: An instructor on driving test bias: 'he was fine with white students...' Figures released by the Driver and Vehicle Standards Agency (DVSA) after a freedom of information request show black women had the lowest pass rates (32%) and white men the highest (56%). The figures, covering 2008-17, also show all women had a pass rate of 43% and all men 50%. Women’s groups and racial equality charities said the figures, revealed as part of t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>6 Interview Tips to Ensure You Land The Best New Hire - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/karagoldin/2018/12/05/6-interview-tips-to-ensure-you-land-the-best-new-hire/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKgUYyTMjP6K9eYwxIibLxsqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMKGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 18:25:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/karagoldin/2018/12/05/6-interview-tips-to-ensure-you-land-the-best-new-hire/" target="_blank"&gt;6 Interview Tips to Ensure You Land The Best New Hire&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Getty The hiring process is continually changing and evolving. LinkedIn and other social networks offer fresh options for finding candidates. There’s always a new tool or technique for ranking resumés and testing an applicant’s ability up front. And it’s increasingly easier to do background research on a candidate as part of the initial screening process. Yet, no matter what the process, the result is always the same. You identify a small number of people that you want to meet for a face-to-face interview. Despite all you could uncover about someone in an hour of browsing online, that in-pe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>‘An education arms race’: inside the ultra-competitive world of private tutoring - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/education/2018/dec/05/an-education-arms-race-inside-the-ultra-competitive-world-of-private-tutoring</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEW7H6RbT8UXw9me8ryK76oqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 06:00:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/education/2018/dec/05/an-education-arms-race-inside-the-ultra-competitive-world-of-private-tutoring" target="_blank"&gt;‘An education arms race’: inside the ultra-competitive world of private tutoring&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;As dusk falls in the Girlington district of Bradford, a trickle of cars begin to arrive in front of a small parade of shops. Parents who have just collected their children at the end of the school day are dropping them off at the Explore Learning tuition centre for extra maths and English coaching. The children sit at a cluster of computer terminals, where they log in to begin their evening studies. The atmosphere is relaxed and lighthearted. The children stay for an hour to work through their lessons, helped where necessary by a member of staff, with 15 minutes’ playtime at the end. Locate...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>The U.S. Army is cracking down on potential recruits who can’t pass the fitness test - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90276144/the-u-s-army-is-cracking-down-on-potential-recruits-who-cant-pass-the-fitness-test</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKHwAQIzWZcPfSz4Y1ZgiqMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOGbAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 09:21:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90276144/the-u-s-army-is-cracking-down-on-potential-recruits-who-cant-pass-the-fitness-test" target="_blank"&gt;The U.S. Army is cracking down on potential recruits who can’t pass the fitness test&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The U.S. Army wants you–to get fit. The military recently announced a new microsite aimed to help potential recruits master the latest reiteration of the Army Combat Fitness Test (ACFT). There, they can access training information, video tutorials, and proper safety technique tips for the rigorous physical test meant to weed out less-combat-ready candidates. Those interested in enlisting must be able to perform a three-repetition maximum deadlift, a 250-meter sprint-drag-carry, a two-mile run, and two minutes of hand-release push-ups, among other feats. One feat dubbed the “leg tuck” involv...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcompany.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>Seven Steps To Recruit (And Retain) An All-Star Team - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbescoachescouncil/2018/12/05/seven-steps-to-recruit-and-retain-an-all-star-team/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIXT5j8b-muapiSvgV8IkmMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMKGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 12:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbescoachescouncil/2018/12/05/seven-steps-to-recruit-and-retain-an-all-star-team/" target="_blank"&gt;Seven Steps To Recruit (And Retain) An All-Star Team&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Getty Building an all-star team is one of the biggest challenges business leaders face. Nothing affects your company’s growth and culture more than the people you hire and retain. Competitors can imitate your products, services or processes, but they can never exactly duplicate your team, how you manage it and how you take care of your people. Some businesses get hiring right, while most others get it wrong. In fact, a McKinsey &amp; Company study found that “82% of companies don’t believe they recruit highly talented people” and that only 7% think they can retain those executives. As an entrep...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Now, AI Makes Online Courses Even Smarter - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/joemckendrick/2018/12/04/now-ai-makes-online-courses-even-smarter/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPI7riX5rZdS8Pl0cZj83vkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 21:41:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/joemckendrick/2018/12/04/now-ai-makes-online-courses-even-smarter/" target="_blank"&gt;Now, AI Makes Online Courses Even Smarter&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The educational system is broken. For decades, if not centuries, learning was limited by geography and having the means to continue with higher education. Online learning and massive open online courses (MOOCs) promised to address the inequities in education while extending its reach across all geographies. However, the online model simply paved over the older methods with technology, and perhaps even making things worse — pushing course material to students, with no effective way to track how much they’re learning, or even if they’re paying attention. Now, artificial intelligence (AI) may ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Candidates in up to 40% of A-level and GCSE exams may be awarded incorrect grades, study finds - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/11/30/candidates-40-a-level-gcse-exams-may-awarded-incorrect-grades/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN76Y0es1B4DOZz8mz8aQ2MqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/11/30/candidates-40-a-level-gcse-exams-may-awarded-incorrect-grades/" target="_blank"&gt;Candidates in up to 40% of A-level and GCSE exams may be awarded incorrect grades, study finds&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Candidates in up to 40% of GCSE and A-level exams are being awarded incorrect grades, a study by the regulator has revealed. In the first analysis of its kind, Ofqual has calculated the probability of a pupil getting the correct grade in “subjective” subjects like English or History as between 52% and 58%. That means more than four in ten could be incorrectly graded. For Maths and Chemistry where examiners can be more definitive about answers, the chance of a correct grade rises to more than 90%. Overall across the 13 popular subjects analysed by Ofqual, statisticians estimated that meant ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>The Neediest Cases Fund: After Years Spent Working for a Diploma, He’s Eager for a New Role - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/12/02/neediest-cases/high-school-diploma-acting.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECTCjML66KSpUkRbB9i3NSoqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzwwloIY</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 23:04:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/12/02/neediest-cases/high-school-diploma-acting.html" target="_blank"&gt;The Neediest Cases Fund: After Years Spent Working for a Diploma, He’s Eager for a New Role&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By the time he entered 11th grade, Hosea Matthews was ready to quit high school. Only one thing held his interest: an acting workshop intended to use the craft to improve the students’ social and emotional skills. “I was always telling him how talented he was,” said one of the workshop’s teaching artists, Erica Bradshaw, “and that he should use his super power of charisma and charm for good.” But the workshop at William Cullen Bryant High School in Long Island City did not last. “They canceled it,” said Mr. Matthews, now 27. “That was my last straw. I dropped out of high school because of t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>China nationalism unleashes boom in Confucian schooling - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/a5bd3212-d75a-11e8-a854-33d6f82e62f8</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPIdev-WuIbPWcfBlzg5SyUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 05:06:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/a5bd3212-d75a-11e8-a854-33d6f82e62f8" target="_blank"&gt;China nationalism unleashes boom in Confucian schooling&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;On a misty morning in the city of Chengdu, pre-schoolers at the Wan Hui School dutifully copy Chinese characters as a teacher identifies the origins of each symbol. “We aim to cultivate global students with Chinese qualities,” said Lan Jihong, the principal and co-founder of the school and part of a vanguard of educators behind guoxue, or Chinese “national studies”, which emphasise classical Confucian teachings. “Our responsibility is to lay a secure foundation of Chinese culture especially when students are young, in pre-school.” Although the Chinese Communist party has imposed stricter ed...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>This company uses AI to test unlikely engineers for their potential - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90269298/this-company-uses-ai-to-test-unlikely-engineers-for-their-potential</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENCK9JQpdOkTFYuBmmg-61sqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOGbAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 08:00:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90269298/this-company-uses-ai-to-test-unlikely-engineers-for-their-potential" target="_blank"&gt;This company uses AI to test unlikely engineers for their potential&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Money troubles had forced him to put his electrical engineering degree on hold at Morgan State University before a failing grade at the Community College of Baltimore County put another halt in his education plans. Reed had no choice but to move back into his parent’s home. Needless to say, he needed to make some moves. It was around this time that he came across a vague Craigslist advertisement that read: “Get paid to become a software developer” with mention that 20-weeks of training would be provided at no cost to the jobseeker and a guaranteed job would be waiting upon completion. Reed ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcompany.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>Bots Strike Back At College Cheating - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/dereknewton/2018/11/30/bots-strike-back-at-college-cheating/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENSfmqmKNLMZ2C2CyLAacWgqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMKGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 19:44:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/dereknewton/2018/11/30/bots-strike-back-at-college-cheating/" target="_blank"&gt;Bots Strike Back At College Cheating&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Google Jump, an array of 16 GoPro Inc. Hero4 cameras, is displayed during the Google I/O Annual Developers Conference in San Francisco, California, U.S., on Thursday, May 28, 2015. Photographer: David Paul Morris/Bloomberg It’s been campus legend for generations that some fraternities, sororities and other social organizations kept file cabinets of work done by previous members. So, if you’re in Professor Smith’s Colonial American History class, for example, you could just go pull out past tests, essays and other assignments that, more likely than not, Professor Smith had not updated since ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>'Eat Bulaga' scholar dedicates Civil Engineer board exam success to late pa - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1776542/Manila/Feature/Eat-Bulaga-scholar-dedicates-Civil-Engineer-board-exam-success-to-late-pa?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFVF1oBHn0Bp3L8313RIg2EqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKmgnQM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 04:14:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1776542/Manila/Feature/Eat-Bulaga-scholar-dedicates-Civil-Engineer-board-exam-success-to-late-pa?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;'Eat Bulaga' scholar dedicates Civil Engineer board exam success to late pa&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;"EAT Bulaga" scholar Jaydee Lucero, who topped the November 2018 Civil Engineering licensure examination, dedicated his well-earned success to his late father. Lucero, who graduated magna cum laude from the University of the Philippines-Diliman, got the highest passing rate of 97.20 percent among all the 13,887 examinees who took the board exams this year. Here's the complete list of passers: The 22-year-old said he did study for six straight months but never expected to come out on top. “It was a grueling six months for me. My focus was just to review as much as I can. During the exam day ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>States Tackling Civic Illiteracy in America - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/tomlindsay/2018/11/30/states-tackling-civic-illiteracy-in-america/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOh51HDqwXxPH0zzVNmFFC0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMKGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 16:22:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/tomlindsay/2018/11/30/states-tackling-civic-illiteracy-in-america/" target="_blank"&gt;States Tackling Civic Illiteracy in America&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;American government is divided into three branches. Can you name them? If so, you’re in the minority. National polling finds that only 26 percent of Americans can name all three branches of the government. This is down from 38 percent in 2011. Worse, 33 percent of Americans surveyed were unable to name even one branch of government. The reality and importance of our civic literacy crisis is no longer subject to partisan debate. In 1983, the Reagan Administration published A Nation at Risk, which detailed the decline of American public education. The report was criticized for being “conserva...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Are Civics Lessons a Constitutional Right? This Student Is Suing for Them - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/28/us/civics-rhode-island-schools.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC6ltcZ_Kg9VSQG0TmRMqDUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzwwqIQY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 16:44:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/28/us/civics-rhode-island-schools.html" target="_blank"&gt;Are Civics Lessons a Constitutional Right? This Student Is Suing for Them&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aleita Cook, 17, has never taken a class in government, civics or economics. In the two social studies classes she took in her four years at a technical high school in Providence, R.I. — one in American history, the other in world history — she learned mostly about wars, she said. Left unanswered were many practical questions she had about modern citizenship, from how to vote to “what the point of taxes are.” As for politics, she said, “What is a Democrat, a Republican, an independent? Those things I had to figure out myself.” Now she and other Rhode Island public school students and parent...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>Test, Test, Test: The Secret To Viral Growth - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbestechcouncil/2018/11/28/test-test-test-the-secret-to-viral-growth/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECBQBz-07QhF9qfpGkvMfq8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbestechcouncil/2018/11/28/test-test-test-the-secret-to-viral-growth/" target="_blank"&gt;Test, Test, Test: The Secret To Viral Growth&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Getty The first viral video happened before Facebook or YouTube. Simply titled “badday.mpg,” it was a brief clip of a man swinging a keyboard at a computer monitor. It made the rounds all the way back in 1997, eventually passing through so many email inboxes that it ended up on TV, all before “going viral” was even a concept. But perhaps the most interesting part of the story is that while the viral sharing was organic, the video wasn’t. Far from a chance recording, it was actually promotional footage intended to showcase DVR technology for security cameras. In short, even the world’s first...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Number of primary schools investigated for cheating during exams rises to almost 600 - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/education/education-news/primary-schools-cheating-sats-exams-pupils-teachers-education-a8656026.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEILTNVgGAIn15LwuO2e9E_oqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 14:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/education/education-news/primary-schools-cheating-sats-exams-pupils-teachers-education-a8656026.html" target="_blank"&gt;Number of primary schools investigated for cheating during exams rises to almost 600&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The number of primary schools investigated for cheating during statutory exams has risen – and experts say increasing pressure on teachers to get good results has played a part. A report from the Standards and Testing Agency shows that 599 schools were investigated for maladministration during the Sats exams in 2017, compared with 524 in 2016 – a rise of 14 per cent. There has also been a rise in the number of cases that resulted in exam results being amended or annulled as a result of maladministration. - Read more London academy school praised by ministers cheated in Sats exams In Key Sta...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Louisiana School Made Headlines for Sending Black Kids to Elite Colleges. Here’s the Reality. - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/30/us/tm-landry-college-prep-black-students.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHEa6nA0kDDcHNWa-q4pg4sqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzwwqIQY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 16:00:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/30/us/tm-landry-college-prep-black-students.html" target="_blank"&gt;Louisiana School Made Headlines for Sending Black Kids to Elite Colleges. Here’s the Reality.&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BREAUX BRIDGE, La. — Bryson Sassau’s application would inspire any college admissions officer. A founder of T.M. Landry College Preparatory School described him as a “bright, energetic, compassionate and genuinely well-rounded” student whose alcoholic father had beaten him and his mother and had denied them money for food and shelter. His transcript “speaks for itself,” the founder, Tracey Landry, wrote, but Mr. Sassau should also be lauded for founding a community service program, the Dry House, to help the children of abusive and alcoholic parents. He took four years of honors English, th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>Lawsuits Won't Solve Our Civics Crisis - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/nataliewexler/2018/11/30/lawsuits-wont-solve-our-civics-crisis/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBbRb_3dFgkIvlD7rTqYH5wqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMKGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 20:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/nataliewexler/2018/11/30/lawsuits-wont-solve-our-civics-crisis/" target="_blank"&gt;Lawsuits Won't Solve Our Civics Crisis&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A lawsuit claiming there’s a constitutional right to civics instruction has gotten a lot of publicity, but it’s unlikely to succeed. And it’s premised on a vast oversimplification of what schools need to do to produce responsible, productive citizens. Earlier this week, a group of students and parents in Rhode Island filed a federal lawsuit claiming the state is violating their constitutional rights by failing to provide a quality education, singling out the failure to require schools to teach civics. Riding the crest of a wave of concern about civics education—triggered by the 2016 electio...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>For The Education Policy Bookshelf - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/petergreene/2018/11/30/for-the-education-policy-bookshelf/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBUZaPUkWKsxMdjWYzPHcRcqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMKGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 00:07:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/petergreene/2018/11/30/for-the-education-policy-bookshelf/" target="_blank"&gt;For The Education Policy Bookshelf&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A great way to decorate for Christmas. Perhaps you are interested in reading up on education policy and the great education reform debates that have been running for the past couple of decades, or perhaps you need to buy a present for someone who is so inclined. Here are some recommendations for you. A Parent’s Guide To Public Education In The 21st Century by Russ Walsh This is a great introductory book for someone who is just saying, “So what is all this fuss about with education?” Walsh lays out the major sides for the major issues of the past decade, from Common Core to School Choice, wh...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Unconditional university offers higher than previously thought, UCAS report reveals - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/11/29/unconditionaluniversity-offers-higher-previously-thought-ucas/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPKdR19_P3FmsQm-eqKI9ZIqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 00:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/11/29/unconditionaluniversity-offers-higher-previously-thought-ucas/" target="_blank"&gt;Unconditional university offers higher than previously thought, UCAS report reveals&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unconditional university offers are much higher than previously thought because universities are upgrading places, new UCAS data has revealed. A report released today shows that 116,945 unconditional offers were handed out to students starting university in 2018, up from the 67,915 unconditional offers originally reported in July this year. The substantial rise, described as “disturbing” by an education minister, is down to a new type of offer being made by universities known as ‘conditional unconditional’ offers, which UCAS has investigated for the first time this year. Starting in 2013, t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Lessons From Cool Schools Volume 2: How Do You Measure Success? - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/mikemcshane/2018/11/28/lessons-from-cool-schools-volume-2-how-do-you-measure-success/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEos8QirE9jxCexxkbIzD8kqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMKGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 13:45:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/mikemcshane/2018/11/28/lessons-from-cool-schools-volume-2-how-do-you-measure-success/" target="_blank"&gt;Lessons From Cool Schools Volume 2: How Do You Measure Success?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(This post is the second is a series teasing out lessons from the first season of my Cool Schools podcast. See the first installment, on talent, here. Check out all 14 episodes of Cool Schools here.) Cool Schools set out to do something different. As a result, they are often fit poorly in traditional models of school accountability and struggle to fully capture what they are trying to do with traditional measures of academic performance. But just because a school is trying to do something different shouldn’t be carte blanche for it to evade responsibility. While standardized tests or existi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>How to become a racing driver – getting a National B (ARDS) race licence - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/cars/advice/become-racing-driver-getting-national-b-ards-race-licence/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAaSzcHx_hXgXE2eNA2eXJAqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDX0bcF</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 17:39:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/cars/advice/become-racing-driver-getting-national-b-ards-race-licence/" target="_blank"&gt;How to become a racing driver – getting a National B (ARDS) race licence&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's about time I got a racing licence. Some of my friends race, I come from a motorsports family, and I spend most of my life around cars, either on the road or in the auction room. But like thousands of other racing fans, I've never really considered actually taking part. I've always just assumed my position in the grandstand or the beer tent, and watched as others assembled on the grid. An invitation to take part in a racing series changed that, though. I began to research the complex, difficult and expensive process of becoming a licenced racing driver, only to discover that it was none...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Nearly one in five pupils get extra time in exams, watchdog finds - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/education/2018/11/22/nearly-one-five-pupils-get-extra-time-exams-watchdog-finds/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB3pXhyF9-yg840i9mInuNoqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCA8LkF</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 18:48:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/education/2018/11/22/nearly-one-five-pupils-get-extra-time-exams-watchdog-finds/" target="_blank"&gt;Nearly one in five pupils get extra time in exams, watchdog finds&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nearly one in five pupils get extra time in exams, the watchdog has found, amid concern that the axing of modules is fuelling the rise. In the most recent series of GCSE and A-level exams, 18.4 per cent of all students were awarded 25 per cent extra time. Requests for extra time have soared in recent years and Ofqual, the exams watchdog, said that it is concerned by the rise. Andrew Harland, Director, International Exam Officers’ Association, said that the axing of module and retakes has increased the stakes of exams. “Students who are less capable can’t retake and retake,” he said. “Now yo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Blockchain: A Revolution For STEM Education - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbestechcouncil/2018/11/30/blockchain-a-revolution-for-stem-education/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP0S4AdN8cl1YKkZ2o4oDaAqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 12:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbestechcouncil/2018/11/30/blockchain-a-revolution-for-stem-education/" target="_blank"&gt;Blockchain: A Revolution For STEM Education&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Getty These days, it seems like everyone is talking about blockchain technology. News about bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies is hard to resist, especially when their value shoots up and everyone wants to know how the blockchain can make them rich. But the real value of blockchain isn’t necessarily just the alternative currency component. It also lies in how this technology could transform and streamline transactions and recordkeeping in all sorts of fields — specifically education. Blockchain For Beginners If you’re not familiar with how blockchain technology works, it’s helpful to compar...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Why Graduation Rates Are Rising But Student Achievement Is Not - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/nataliewexler/2018/11/29/why-graduation-rates-are-rising-but-student-achievement-is-not/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC67IDHgaV8qfttQBfTckyYqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMKGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 17:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/nataliewexler/2018/11/29/why-graduation-rates-are-rising-but-student-achievement-is-not/" target="_blank"&gt;Why Graduation Rates Are Rising But Student Achievement Is Not&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nation’s high school graduation rate has reached an all-time high, but new data suggest much of that “progress” has been achieved by funneling underprepared students into watered-down online courses. Politicians and education officials have long been under pressure to get more students graduating from high school. But since 2010, the pressure has increased. That year, the federal government—in an effort to lower the number of dropouts—required states to track the percentage of students who graduated within four years. If schools failed to make “adequate yearly progress” in raising the f...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Are Australian universities using international students as 'cash cows'? - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-25/poor-english-no-jobs-little-support-international-students/10513590</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFk8V_FJpjYZtdfX8cs7gaIqFwgEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDD7kIkG</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2018 02:00:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-25/poor-english-no-jobs-little-support-international-students/10513590" target="_blank"&gt;Are Australian universities using international students as 'cash cows'?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Recently at an elite Australian university, a senior humanities lecturer opened her office door to a young international student who was accompanied by another woman and seemed nervous. The student had emailed the lecturer in advance about changing to another degree — but right away there was a problem. Key points: - English standards kept low to bring in more students, claim academics - Some students are unable to learn or communicate effectively - Universities rely on international fees for billions in revenue "She couldn't speak any English and she didn't understand anything that I said,...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>[OPINION | Deep Dive] What's the big deal about the bar exams? - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/thought-leaders/217231-opinion-deep-dive-bar-exams</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELajTCcB76UULGvUOI53DmgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJDgmQI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 10:31:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/thought-leaders/217231-opinion-deep-dive-bar-exams" target="_blank"&gt;[OPINION | Deep Dive] What's the big deal about the bar exams?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This Sunday, November 25, the 2018 bar examinations will conclude, officially signaling the start of the waiting period for the 8 bar examiners to check and grade all the notebooks – a process that will, on the average, take the next 4 to 5 months to complete. The bar examinations are notoriously difficult and the preparations for taking them – 5 months of review with life being placed in suspended animation – highly stressful. Yet, the number of bar exam hopefuls has increased every year (except in 2016). This year’s 8,701 admitted candidates is the highest since 2013: - 2017 – 7,227 candi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>Speech pathologists soon required to take board exam - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1775862/Manila/Local-News/Speech-pathologists-soon-required-to-take-board-exam?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG-7X-shhcOnrb8_paXQChEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMKmgnQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 07:56:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1775862/Manila/Local-News/Speech-pathologists-soon-required-to-take-board-exam?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;Speech pathologists soon required to take board exam&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SPEECH language pathologists in the country may soon have to take a licensure examination and comply with other measures aimed at professionalizing the sector after the House of Representatives, voting 170-0, approved on third and final reading the bill seeking to regulate the profession. House Bill 8529, or the “Speech Language Pathology Act”, seeks to “promote the development of a corps of competent, world class and globally competitive speech language pathologists” through the establishment of mechanisms, safeguards, and procedures for the development of the profession in the country." I...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>More than one in three students offered place on degree regardless of exam grades - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/education/education-news/university-unconditional-offers-ucas-a-level-student-degree-uk-a8656426.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBj_b9cVFbIY5hlGHkzPZfcqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 00:08:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/education/education-news/university-unconditional-offers-ucas-a-level-student-degree-uk-a8656426.html" target="_blank"&gt;More than one in three students offered place on degree regardless of exam grades&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;More than one in three students who applied to university were offered a place on a degree course regardless of their final exam grades, figures from Ucas show. A total of 87,540 university applicants, who were yet to complete their qualifications at school or college, received an offer that could be considered unconditional, the new analysis suggests. Just 1 per cent of 18-year-old applicants from England, Northern Ireland and Wales received an unconditional offer in 2013 – but 34 per cent of these applicants received an offer in 2018. - Read more Unconditional offers may mean A-level stud...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>5 Easy Ways to Massively Improve Your Interviewing Process - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/williamvanderbloemen/2018/11/29/5-easy-ways-to-massively-improve-your-interviewing-process/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBqLfLpVlJ3YvrxpPzsuKPgqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMKGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/williamvanderbloemen/2018/11/29/5-easy-ways-to-massively-improve-your-interviewing-process/" target="_blank"&gt;5 Easy Ways to Massively Improve Your Interviewing Process&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photo by Tim Gouw, courtesy of pexels.com Sometimes, the expert isn’t the smartest person in the room, but rather the person with the most repetitions. That certainly seems true when it comes to interviewing. The longer I interview candidates, the more I’m a believer that repetitions create expertise. Malcolm Gladwell has famously said that 10,000 hours of training is magic. Now that we have done over 10,000 face to face interviews, I know there’s a lot more to learn, but I also have learned a whole lot more than I knew ten years ago. Here at Vanderbloemen, we not only get to interview cand...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Embracing shaving cream and slimy balls: The schools welcoming play into the classroom - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-25/primary-schools-reap-the-benefits-of-play-based-learning/10517964</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELCY07-DuCf-Ia4WI2CqBgkqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2018 22:29:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-25/primary-schools-reap-the-benefits-of-play-based-learning/10517964" target="_blank"&gt;Embracing shaving cream and slimy balls: The schools welcoming play into the classroom&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Rebecca Carmody Schools have been given the green light to put worksheets to one side, minimise desk time and make learning fun again for young students. The WA Education Department wants schools to fully embrace play-based learning for kindergarten and pre-primary students aged between three and six, listing it as a key priority for 2019. The move follows a backlash from some early childhood educators and parents, who were concerned overly-structured learning was being imposed on students before they were ready, causing them to disengage. They blamed NAPLAN testing and the publication o...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Honey testing not reliable enough to prove adulteration - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/rural/2018-11-22/accc-finds-honey-testing-methods-not-reliable/10516724</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIUs-z8NomWqGPUz73iEeLwqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDD9QQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 19:12:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/rural/2018-11-22/accc-finds-honey-testing-methods-not-reliable/10516724" target="_blank"&gt;Honey testing not reliable enough to prove adulteration&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The honey industry is looking at different ways of testing and analysing imports after concerns were raised about the integrity of some honey imported into Australia. A recent study by a team of scientists at Macquarie University using a process known as Nuclear Magnetic Resonance (NMR) found one in five samples of honey in Australia showed adulteration. As a result the Australian Competition and Consumer Commission (ACCC) launched an investigation following reports several honey products labelled as 'pure' or '100 per cent honey', including Capilano's Allowrie honey, were adulterated with ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Could You Get An MD Online? - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/shivgaglani/2018/11/28/could-you-get-an-md-online/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA1ff39XvpamsU1PreODwo8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 13:50:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/shivgaglani/2018/11/28/could-you-get-an-md-online/" target="_blank"&gt;Could You Get An MD Online?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The short answer: Not yet, but it’s trending that way. Less than a decade ago couples would often hesitate before admitting that they “met online.” Since then, the rise of apps like Tinder and Bumble have reduced the stigma around online dating. A parallel acceptance has been occurring in education with the massive growth of online courses and whole degree programs. Companies such as Udacity, Lynda.com (bought by LinkedIn), and 2U (NASDAQ: TWOU) have thrived because they offer a combination of convenience, quality, and cost savings that enable students to upskill while, for example, continu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Libre: On becoming a lawyer again - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1775542/Cebu/Opinion/Libre-On-becoming-a-lawyer-again?rss=1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK8cAEvJsr1Ogq8OfM6wCwcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMMu4nAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 15:10:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1775542/Cebu/Opinion/Libre-On-becoming-a-lawyer-again?rss=1" target="_blank"&gt;Libre: On becoming a lawyer again&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;IT was not in my plan. When I migrated to New Zealand in 2005, I knew that I would no longer make use of my licenses as a Certified Public Accountant and a lawyer though I am a lifetime member of both the Philippine Institute of Certified Public Accountants and the Integrated Bar of the Philippines. Both licenses are not recognized in New Zealand. After a stint in the High Court of New Zealand, I availed of a student loan so I could become a lawyer. Good that the New Zealand Law Society acknowledged both my legal education as well as experience as a lawyer in the Philippines, that all I nee...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>Education secretary slams rise in unconditional university offers - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/dda17d90-f321-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDWZA-0T6G_soEom1daN6EAqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 00:02:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/dda17d90-f321-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d" target="_blank"&gt;Education secretary slams rise in unconditional university offers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The education secretary Damian Hinds has asked the universities regulator to use the “full range of powers” at its disposal against universities that hand out unconditional offers of places after what he called a “disturbing” rise in the practice. Mr Hinds said he had “made clear” to the Office for Students, which regulates higher education in England, that it should consider action after new figures released by UCAS, the universities admission service, on Thursday. They revealed that 34.4 per cent of offers made to 18-year-olds to start studying in the 2018-19 academic year in England, Wal...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Major Tim Peake reveals what ground control wants in an astronaut - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/science/2018/nov/24/major-tim-peak-reveals-what-ground-control-wants-in-an-astronaut</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPEYUks6DjFKF057V-3-9NwqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2018 07:00:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/science/2018/nov/24/major-tim-peak-reveals-what-ground-control-wants-in-an-astronaut" target="_blank"&gt;Major Tim Peake reveals what ground control wants in an astronaut&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The astronaut selection process at the European Space Agency is unforgiving from the start. On day one, candidates assemble in Hamburg for six rounds of tests that run back to back, with 10-minute breaks in between. All are designed to expose weaknesses in people’s “hard skills”: their mental arithmetic, visual perception, working memory, pattern recognition, concentration, and more. Most are abilities that cannot be taught. “On the first day of testing you are so exposed. There is no hiding place,” says Tim Peake, an army major and former helicopter test-pilot who became Britain’s first ES...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Cheating scandal erupts as South Korean students face their toughest test - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/14/asia/korea-csat-test-cheating-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFaxj19J4gp46NC43pIAp84qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 05:28:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/14/asia/korea-csat-test-cheating-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Cheating scandal erupts as South Korean students face their toughest test&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;All flights in South Korea will be grounded Thursday, with no takeoffs or landings permitted for an hour. Around the country, parents will be praying and packing lunch, and everyone will be avoiding words like "fail" or "fall" to avoid causing bad luck for the hundreds of thousands students taking the College Scholastic Ability Test (CSAT), South Korea's university entrance exam. The temporary no-fly order was issued by the Ministry of Interior to avoid distracting airplane noise and give test takers a fair shot, but in the run-up to this year's exam, attention has focused on the opposite o...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>What To Do About Standardized Tests - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/nataliewexler/2018/11/15/what-to-do-about-standardized-tests/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKs2hvg-QFA-aoWKURNHqOoqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMKGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 17:50:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/nataliewexler/2018/11/15/what-to-do-about-standardized-tests/" target="_blank"&gt;What To Do About Standardized Tests&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Critics of standardized testing say scores merely reflect family income and other factors beyond schools’ control—while also narrowing the curriculum and warping instruction. Still, the tests have value, and there’s much more that schools could do to address the inequities they reveal. “Standardized tests are best at measuring family income,” education-reform opponent Diane Ravitch has opined. “Well-off students usually score in the top half of results; students from poor homes usually score in the bottom.” Similarly, an education policy analyst told the Washington Post earlier this year th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Stress is taking a disturbing toll on year 12. Should we do away with exams? - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/nov/19/stress-is-taking-a-disturbing-toll-on-year-12-should-we-do-away-with-exams</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMMPbRm-cdkI4t8sy-MZlGIqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTC9vBU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 21:00:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/nov/19/stress-is-taking-a-disturbing-toll-on-year-12-should-we-do-away-with-exams" target="_blank"&gt;Stress is taking a disturbing toll on year 12. Should we do away with exams?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the end of 2017 I was appointed to the role of head of year 12. It came as a bit of a surprise as, in a teaching career spanning over 40 years, I had never been appointed head of anything. What attracted me to this position was that it gave me an opportunity to play an active role in shepherding year 12 through their higher school certificate (HSC) year. I didn’t quite know how I was going to do it but having taught year 12 for many years, I did know that for some inexplicable reason the pressure on students in their final years has multiplied exponentially. Let alone the pressure on tea...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>To Close The Gender Gap, Start With Internships - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/joankuhl/2018/11/20/to-close-the-gender-gap-start-with-internships/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBMk-OlncBb1p4MNb8HDRIEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMKGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 15:10:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/joankuhl/2018/11/20/to-close-the-gender-gap-start-with-internships/" target="_blank"&gt;To Close The Gender Gap, Start With Internships&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;High learning agility, critical thinking skills and a strong work ethic are attributes I often hear cited by recruiters looking to hire their next intern class. But let’s ensure diversity and gender representation goals are a priority if you want to truly reflect today’s workforce. Did you know employers are most interested in hiring entry-level employees who have had an average of three internships? They’re onto something. Since most intern candidates are looking for a job offer at its conclusion, an internship program targeting ambitious and diverse students can be an effective way to: -...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Building skills for life: student builds tiny house - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-25/tiny-house-project-gets-student-through-year-12/10492660</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEHgAvaw9IMYLiTS429hXAkqFwgEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDoiokG</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2018 19:45:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-25/tiny-house-project-gets-student-through-year-12/10492660" target="_blank"&gt;Building skills for life: student builds tiny house&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Liz Farquhar She didn't spend her final year at high school cramming for a gruelling series of exams, or aiming for an impressive university entrance ranking. Instead the 18-year-old, from Newcastle in New South Wales, spent her last year of school doing a combination of self-directed learning, completing open university courses, and working on a major project. Ms Saul decided she would build her own tiny house and install it on the back of a ute. "As a kid I've always loved travelling and I did it a lot with my family," she said. "To be able to have my own space, take it wherever I want...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Unlocking The Soft Skills Within Your Workforce (And Why It Matters) - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbescoachescouncil/2018/11/21/unlocking-the-soft-skills-within-your-workforce-and-why-it-matters/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFpyoRxR7Ugfb4jM4aAVidgqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMKGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbescoachescouncil/2018/11/21/unlocking-the-soft-skills-within-your-workforce-and-why-it-matters/" target="_blank"&gt;Unlocking The Soft Skills Within Your Workforce (And Why It Matters)&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Getty Existing pedagogic traditions continue to miss the mark in preparing young professionals as best they can for the workforce. Sweeping changes in industries due to automation and artificial intelligence (AI) beckon even more disjunctions between traditional education methods and the skills required for the shift from an industrial economy to a knowledge economy. Forget about coding, as Linkedin CEO Jeff Weiner put it. It’s with harnessing their soft skills that young professionals and the corporate world will be able to position themselves competitively in the changing world. A Focus O...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Free education is disappearing before our eyes - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/nov/28/free-education-schools-money-parents-children</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHdoRj3r1jCGk2Zck8Apw-sqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 06:00:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/nov/28/free-education-schools-money-parents-children" target="_blank"&gt;Free education is disappearing before our eyes&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Second world war references are hard to avoid in the context of Brexit, so here’s one that actually has something constructive to offer. When Britain was facing the horror of Stalingrad, the second battle of El Alamein and the challenge of the Normandy landings, it was also undertaking wholesale reform of the education system. The mass evacuation of children from British cities to rural areas laid bare the abysmal lack of education many had received. The government response was the 1944 Education Act, which established what we now call state-maintained comprehensive schools and free, compul...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>After rapid growth, Zuckerberg-backed school program faces scrutiny over effectiveness, data privacy - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90269809/after-rapid-growth-zuckerberg-backed-school-program-faces-scrutiny-over-effectiveness-and-data-privacy</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPi8KqD8etfq96_8aWCxC0QqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOGbAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 14:00:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90269809/after-rapid-growth-zuckerberg-backed-school-program-faces-scrutiny-over-effectiveness-and-data-privacy" target="_blank"&gt;After rapid growth, Zuckerberg-backed school program faces scrutiny over effectiveness, data privacy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Earlier this month, nearly 100 students from Brooklyn’s Secondary School for Journalism walked out of school to protest the use of Summit Learning, a personalized education system backed by Facebook CEO Mark Zuckerberg’s philanthropic organization. The students complained that the program, designed in part to deliver individualized lessons to students at their own pace, kept them busy at computers rather than working with teachers and classmates. It also failed to prepare them for standardized tests and violated their privacy by collecting data on their grades, disciplinary records, and dem...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcompany.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>Capitalised words should not be used by university staff setting assignments because it can worry students, memo reveals - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/11/19/capitalised-words-should-not-used-university-staff-setting-assignments/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEASEYchDIP40id9lxN3YWtwqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 21:33:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/11/19/capitalised-words-should-not-used-university-staff-setting-assignments/" target="_blank"&gt;Capitalised words should not be used by university staff setting assignments because it can worry students, memo reveals&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Capitalised words should not be used when setting assignments because it can worry students, university lecturers have been told. Academics at Leeds Trinity were sent advised to "write in a helpful, warm tone, avoiding officious language and negative instructions". According to a staff memo aimed at "enhancing student understanding, engagement and achievement", capitalising a word could emphasise "the difficulty or high-stakes nature of the task". The memo says: "Despite our best attempts to explain assessment tasks, any lack of clarity can generate anxiety and even discourage students from...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Students say they don't know what 'trivial' means in exam question fiasco - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/16/students-say-they-dont-know-what-trivial-means-in-exam-question-fiasco</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIRZCIwdg-MaUh3woL8a0PEqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 04:13:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/16/students-say-they-dont-know-what-trivial-means-in-exam-question-fiasco" target="_blank"&gt;Students say they don't know what 'trivial' means in exam question fiasco&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;New Zealand high school students have demanded examiners ignore that they don’t know what the word “trivial” means, after it appeared in a final-year exam and left many confused. Some students who took the year 13 history exam claimed the “unfamiliar word” was too hard, and the exam should now be marked according to each student’s different understanding and interpretation of “trivial”. The exam asked for students to write an essay on whether they agreed with a quote from Julius Caesar which reads: “Events of importance are the result of trivial causes”. Related: 'Impossible' New Zealand ma...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Can Standardized Tests Be Rescued? - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/petergreene/2018/11/20/can-standardized-tests-be-rescued/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENOlilEcLgEEi9YL-uGG9xoqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMKGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 15:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/petergreene/2018/11/20/can-standardized-tests-be-rescued/" target="_blank"&gt;Can Standardized Tests Be Rescued?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not relaxing for anyone. Last week, here on the Forbes site, Natalie Wexler considered how to rehabilitate the Big Standardized Test. Wexler is an education writer perhaps best known for co-creating The Writing Revolution, which contains some valuable elements. But her dreams of rehabilitating standardized testing fall short. She opens with a standard “critics say” section to give space to two large criticisms of the modern testing regimen. She quotes Diane Ravitch saying that “standardized tests are best at measuring family income,” and Wexler tips her hand by sticking Ravitch with the ver...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Foreign MBA students face tougher US jobs market - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/44eb5838-ecb8-11e8-8180-9cf212677a57</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHP7tdBTjLnbH_WbVq1nYCUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 05:00:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/44eb5838-ecb8-11e8-8180-9cf212677a57" target="_blank"&gt;Foreign MBA students face tougher US jobs market&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Foreign MBA students are being shut out of a buoyant US jobs market for people with their qualifications because of the red tape required to hire them, business school careers advisers have warned. Hiring of MBA graduates has risen at several leading US business schools this year, according to recently published employment reports. But while those with American citizenship are enjoying the rewards of an increase in companies seeking MBA graduates, hiring levels among non-US students have fallen at several institutions. At the University of Virginia’s Darden School of Business, the proportio...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>University leaves third of English male students worse off - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/d262ace8-f17c-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJGBMr1U_bsc6533ncO6gPAqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 00:02:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/d262ace8-f17c-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d" target="_blank"&gt;University leaves third of English male students worse off&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A third of English male university students attend institutions likely to leave them worse off at age 29 than peers that never attended higher education, research commissioned by the government has found. Universities minister Sam Gyimah said the results of the research, by the Institute for Fiscal Studies, underlined the need to have a “relentless focus on quality” and to act against courses that failed to offer good value. Only 67 per cent of men attended universities that on average left men earning more at age 29 than similar peers who skipped higher education altogether, the research s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Six Lessons To Land The Job That Pays Off Your College Education - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/mattsymonds/2018/11/27/six-lessons-to-land-the-job-that-pays-off-your-college-education/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJrpv9IuPrSVJs9EiAaXphkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMKGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 08:12:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/mattsymonds/2018/11/27/six-lessons-to-land-the-job-that-pays-off-your-college-education/" target="_blank"&gt;Six Lessons To Land The Job That Pays Off Your College Education&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A mobile phone’s screen shows a news item headlined ‘students drowning in debt’ illustrated by a miserable looking young girl. The photo and website design are by the photographer. The web address is fabricated. College education is expensive – horribly expensive. Students and parents in other countries, particularly the UK, might moan about the price of the university experience, but in comparison to their peers in the US, what they are being asked to pay looks like small change. Tuition fees at Oxford or Imperial, for example, are just under $12,000 a year – almost a quarter of what a Har...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>6 Innovative Procedures To Implement In Your Recruitment Process - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/williamcraig/2018/11/26/6-innovative-procedures-to-implement-in-your-recruitment-process/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHsjZbT1XsvkWYgS_trM6m0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMKGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 16:42:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/williamcraig/2018/11/26/6-innovative-procedures-to-implement-in-your-recruitment-process/" target="_blank"&gt;6 Innovative Procedures To Implement In Your Recruitment Process&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Recruitment feels like it’s gotten a bit stale lately. Whether it’s the predictable interview formula or the lack of a personal, cultural engagement by the company, there’s lots about modern recruitment that can change with new technologies and a new outlook. Here are six ideas. Be Open and Accessible When It Comes to Communication Being transparent about your hiring process isn’t a new idea, but in the age of constant contact, it comes with new caveats attached. There were any number of opportunities in your on-boarding process to ask applicants which communication method they’re most comf...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>‘It stops the scary stuff’: pupils thrive with mindfulness lessons - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2018/nov/25/schools-deprived-areas-embrace-mindfulness</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFPskZ-lT9RUuNZAU_3GfvAqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2018 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2018/nov/25/schools-deprived-areas-embrace-mindfulness" target="_blank"&gt;‘It stops the scary stuff’: pupils thrive with mindfulness lessons&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;English Martyrs Catholic primary school in Litherland is a stone’s throw from one of Merseyside’s most notorious areas for gangs and gun crime, and most children at the school have been affected by the violence. It is an unlikely place, perhaps, to find a thriving mindfulness teaching programme. But English Martyrs is one of a growing number of schools in deprived parts of Britain that are embracing meditation techniques to help vulnerable children cope. “We see a lot of pressure put on children’s shoulders due to family circumstances, parents losing their jobs, financial stress, anxiety ab...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>My son's school journey is at an end. Here's what we've both learnt - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-17/school-leavers-parenting-teenagers-parents-school-graduation/10499732</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFHgcQPOjZroQcnZs7m1gyIqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDtiw4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 18:00:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-17/school-leavers-parenting-teenagers-parents-school-graduation/10499732" target="_blank"&gt;My son's school journey is at an end. Here's what we've both learnt&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Vanessa Wiltshire School's over for my son Matt and his mates in the Year 12 Class of 2018. And just like that, our role as parents of schoolchildren is over, too. c) sadness to the point of tears, after revisiting photos of both our children from their first day of school. A moment ago, we were parents of 5-year-olds with gap-toothed smiles and floppy hats with uniforms way too big for them. Now we have two older teenagers, the second of whom is now graduating. His school hat has survived a year with a hole it; there's wear and tear around the collar of his uniform where the fabric's fa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>3 Cebu grads in top 10 of Civil Engineering board exam - SunStar Philippines</title><link>https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1774298</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIXoSL4rPDF4TtURdGFslPgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4YjwCjDD5s8CMJeunQM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 01:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sunstar.com.ph/article/1774298" target="_blank"&gt;3 Cebu grads in top 10 of Civil Engineering board exam&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SunStar Philippines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THREE graduates of two schools in Cebu are among the top 10 performers in the Civil Engineering (CE) Licensure Exam given by the Professional Regulatory Commission (PRC) earlier this month. University of San Carlos (USC) graduates Kevin Miscala Melendres placed sixth and John Ivan Manticajon Gapod placed ninth with a score of 94.65 percent and 94.30 percent, respectively. University of Cebu (UC) graduate Jared Bihag Jumalon placed 10th with a rating of 94.25 percent. Jaydee Niere Lucero of the University of the Philippines-Diliman topped the exam with a rating of 97.20 percent. Out of 13,88...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sunstar.com.ph">SunStar Philippines</source></item><item><title>[OPINION] Punishing the pregnant woman - Rappler</title><link>https://www.rappler.com/thought-leaders/217031-opinion-punishing-the-pregnant-woman</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF3iIEK-Iang-jCLGrEqaC0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowkInwCjCi5s8CMJDgmQI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 03:20:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rappler.com/thought-leaders/217031-opinion-punishing-the-pregnant-woman" target="_blank"&gt;[OPINION] Punishing the pregnant woman&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rappler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The mandatory testing for pregnancy by the Pines City Colleges (PCC) of all their dentistry, nursing, and pharmacy students is a classic illustration of the proverb that says, “the road to hell is paved with good intentions.” Women’s and privacy rights advocates began criticizing the policy when a letter calling for the mandatory tests dated October 25, 2018, and signed by PCC vice president for administration Maria Regina Prats and school physician Dr. Aurelia Navarro, began circulating in social media. In a Facebook post, the PCC claims that the intention is to protect mother and fetus. T...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rappler.com">Rappler</source></item><item><title>How Do You Get Students to Think Like Criminals? - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/14/opinion/cybersecurity-education-skills.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBtmgRV-r3G31JuXvrOU3QYqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzwwqIQY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 17:09:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/14/opinion/cybersecurity-education-skills.html" target="_blank"&gt;How Do You Get Students to Think Like Criminals?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Between September 2017 and August 2018, employers in the United States posted 313,735 job openings for cybersecurity professionals. Filling those jobs would mean increasing the country’s current cybersecurity work force of 715,000 people by more than 40 percent, according to data presented at the National Initiative for Cybersecurity Education Conference this month. With the number of unfilled cybersecurity jobs worldwide projected to multiply into the millions in the next three years, it’s no surprise that governments, companies and schools are racing to pour more resources into cybersecur...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>Here's An Interview Question To Test If Candidates Are Problem Solvers Or Problem Bringers - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/markmurphy/2018/11/16/heres-an-interview-question-to-test-if-candidates-are-problem-solvers-or-problem-bringers/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHevBGa5tjULaoT7hxtLBNcqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMKGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 14:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/markmurphy/2018/11/16/heres-an-interview-question-to-test-if-candidates-are-problem-solvers-or-problem-bringers/" target="_blank"&gt;Here's An Interview Question To Test If Candidates Are Problem Solvers Or Problem Bringers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Problem bringers bring problems because it’s how they’re attitudinally wired to behave. Getting these low performers to change isn’t easy, and while coaching instead of managing when employees bring you problems is the best approach to take, wouldn’t it be easier to avoid hiring problem bringers in the first place? Identifying low performers during the interview process requires asking questions that probe for the truth about attitude and that don’t tip off even the savviest of job seekers as to the desired answers. One interview question that separates problem bringers from problem solvers...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>College Admission, Helplessness, And Choice - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/brennanbarnard/2018/11/14/college-admission-helplessness-and-choice/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFPHDQJTBm63KgaUmwrcFXwqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMKGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 13:33:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/brennanbarnard/2018/11/14/college-admission-helplessness-and-choice/" target="_blank"&gt;College Admission, Helplessness, And Choice&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you shock a rat or dog enough times (please do not do this) without the animal having control over its circumstances, it is likely to give up hope, believing it has no other choice but to receive a shock. This is what psychologist Martin Seligman, and his colleagues at The University of Pennsylvania, discovered in the 1960’s and 70’s with their experiments on learned helplessness. While I do not support any kind of cruelty to animals—or humans—it is a phenomenon not dissimilar to what we often observe in college admission. Coming of age in today’s world is not easy. Teenage years have a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Indonesian police deny allegations of 'virginity testing' females — but they must be 'good looking' - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-14/indonesian-policewomen-must-be-good-looking/10491422</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG8YyMnMhXtrUBZiATBCfagqFwgEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDD7kIkG</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 19:33:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-14/indonesian-policewomen-must-be-good-looking/10491422" target="_blank"&gt;Indonesian police deny allegations of 'virginity testing' females — but they must be 'good looking'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indonesia's police force has hit back at allegations that female recruits must undergo virginity tests, but confirmed that the women do have to be "not only pretty, but good looking". Key points: - HRW claim female police recruits undergo invasive virginity tests - A senior police officer says many females are "average" but they all have "individual skills" - There are currently some 30,000 female police officers out of a total 461,000 officers Last month, the ABC cited a Human Rights Watch report that found Indonesian women looking to become police officers in the country continue to under...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>The Secret To Increasing Revenue For Low-Traffic Sites - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/theyec/2018/11/16/the-secret-to-increasing-revenue-for-low-traffic-sites/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDCROlj1i60QAL27QFZaCb4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMKGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 13:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/theyec/2018/11/16/the-secret-to-increasing-revenue-for-low-traffic-sites/" target="_blank"&gt;The Secret To Increasing Revenue For Low-Traffic Sites&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Getty It’s very hard to increase revenue for low-traffic sites. For many business owners, this is the reality behind why they’re failing. We see so many blogs and articles about research methods to understand your audience, but these methods almost always need a large enough pool of site visitors to be trusted and to have statistical significance. Here, I’ll be talking about how to increase revenue for sites without the benefit of a substantial level of traffic and how to learn about the visitors you do have to attract more. The first step is to ask these two very important questions: Quest...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Meet Lia: At-Home Pregnancy Steps Into The 21st Century - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/karlulrich/2018/11/14/meetlia/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKvWYCDkehDyEmv0_BIrkKsqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMKGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 16:23:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/karlulrich/2018/11/14/meetlia/" target="_blank"&gt;Meet Lia: At-Home Pregnancy Steps Into The 21st Century&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;lia chart On my radio show, Launch Pad, airing on Sirius XM Channel 132, Business Radio Powered by the Wharton School, I talk with entrepreneurs about their startups. Once a month I choose an Elevator Pitch of the Month. This month my selection is Lia Diagnostics, co-founded by Bethany Edwards and Anna Simpson. Listen to our in-depth, half-hour conversation here. As a professor who teaches entrepreneurship, I’m often asked if it can truly be taught. Unsurprisingly, my answer is yes. To back up that assertion, I’d like to share the story of a terrific company that came about because of a sch...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Common Core Testing And The Fracturing Of Literature - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/petergreene/2018/11/09/common-core-testing-and-the-fracturing-of-literature/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC5-UPsHZCv4MgtIMTcZOTwqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMKGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 16:57:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/petergreene/2018/11/09/common-core-testing-and-the-fracturing-of-literature/" target="_blank"&gt;Common Core Testing And The Fracturing Of Literature&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;We won’t need all the magic; just tear out one page. (Getty Royalty Free) The Common Core Standards do not require reading complete long works of literature. Even by the time we arrive at the 11th and 12th grade set of standards for reading literature, the standards only refer to “stories, dramas, and poems.” There are, throughout the standards, references to Shakespeare and “foundational works” or literature. But the standards do not suggest that students should, at some point in their academic career, read an entire book. Appendix A provides highly technical explanations of how to conside...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>30 Under 30 Education 2019: The Masterminds Shaping the Future of Learning, Access And Opportunity - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/cartercoudriet/2018/11/13/30-under-30-education-2019-the-masterminds-shaping-the-future-of-learning-access-and-careers/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENhMwjUPcsFIkiT9eX0uhmcqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMKGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 11:48:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/cartercoudriet/2018/11/13/30-under-30-education-2019-the-masterminds-shaping-the-future-of-learning-access-and-careers/" target="_blank"&gt;30 Under 30 Education 2019: The Masterminds Shaping the Future of Learning, Access And Opportunity&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rebecca Kantar founded Imbellus to take on the college admissions test. She’s raised over $20 million in VC funding to create a more valuable assessment of students’ abilities. College debt has hit $1.5 trillion nationwide. Schools are struggling to integrate 21st century-skills into the classroom. A third of high school grads don’t enroll in further education, and a third of ACT test-takers reach zero of its college readiness benchmarks. The education industry needs a shake-up, and the leaders best-equipped to become its shakers may just be its most recent grads and users. The Forbes 30 Un...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item></channel></rss>